<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 I can hear the Black Bull jukey calling....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tony_Robinson ..or the Agincourt salute...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insight into how challenging touring is for a lot of artists/bands https://t.co/xjDKoVOsOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Of The Rat https://t.co/RAsKh9KRsC Classic Purps..boogie on down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 He switched his twitter aff. Give him a poke on FaceBook The Windsor on Leith walk have drink to honour the FB singer..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took my American colleague and her husband on epic Edinburgh Pub crawl last night- ended up The Scotsman Lounge. The whole pub was drunk dancing by the end of the night. Feeling it a bit "tender" today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @haveigotnews: Shops to be banned from selling energy drinks to children, despite concerns among Brexiteers it will affect their perform…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea I think the lower half of the Royal Mile should pedestrianised. It can get almost grid locked in summer. 
https://t.co/S5vu0xsvWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew there was reason that @Kezzang69 went to work there.... https://t.co/vl6LgIHMMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner Its sending attack coordinates for The Predator ship to land.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @flyingmonkphoto: 'Alternative' and 'New Wave' charts. Sounds, July/August 1977.
#BuzzcocksScrapbook https://t.co/7XnHWtqMDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymannion77 Or.."Still Too Bloody Quiet"....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pilotbeeruk: Sorry to hear you didn't enjoy these beers @thesun - we've left the details of some beers you might prefer on our voicemai…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carlychaikin: Just got the butterflies.. I’ve been waiting as long as all of you to find out where this is all going. Best roller coast…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianjaffa: Festivals, cultural groups &amp; artists will get a £100,000 share of a £2.4m pot for Leith projects during work to finish the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Oliver__Bond: The FA have backed ‘safe standing’ areas in stadiums. Huge news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good read. Been saying this for years. https://t.co/aIlaYxagPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Sagan's Contact is 99p on Kindle today..just saying. Saw the film but have never read the book- so I bought it. #kindledeals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattLindsayHT Murrayfield will work fine..you seem to be saying that only the  toxic twins can not play outside their west coast bubble? So if both of them get through to a Euro final what then??  This  shows how backward looking some people are in the certain parts of the media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 You keep your Super Soft Rock Classics private though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arlenparsa: so just as an experiment I put the president's ~supremely~ awkward oval office moment to the @VeepHBO closing credits theme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Images From Netflix's Shirley Jackson Adaptation THE HAUNTING OF HILL HOUSE https://t.co/hArotpSObs  The Robert Wise version still creeps me out every time I watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airdrieonians Vs Raith Rovers https://t.co/B8lm867x5c 
The most Fife As F- commentary ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: New ‘Game of Thrones’ Teaser Shows Cackling, Power-Mad George R.R. Martin Burning Completed ‘Winds Of Winter’ Manuscript http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymannion77 Have you seen Impulse yet? It's a TV series but it has the "superhuman powers' but there is a difficult underlying story of a young woman dealing with terrible aftermath of an assault. Great writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pieandbov: Delete your league. https://t.co/AT6mgynPUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 @RenZelen Stand down laddie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen Peeps are awfy precious are they no. His comments will not stop super movies with dudes in spandex being made..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damocrat @Bernie_Torme "We want to go up this smelly creek"
"We dont have a paddle"
"We are still going up this smelly creek"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spfl @RaithRovers That wiz a "Yahoorsunneebs" of a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJaninaRamirez https://t.co/XaxURnCiUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial bakery fights back against 'Cornish pasty fascists' https://t.co/M9HY9iRrq6  it's all kicking aff in Cornwall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says Scottish football is boring...

https://t.co/vTxE4mMApX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @historyinmoment: Amazing vertical view of Manhattan, New York, in 1944. By Andreas Feininger https://t.co/zus79RRueY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @usasoccerguy: Kyle Lavatory's makes a double insertion in his first ever EPL Scotland game for the Glasgow Raiders after his roster ref…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#headphonemoment #HeadphonesOn https://t.co/NSfiFvynUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 https://t.co/olRqWafz4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pieandbov: Absolutely brilliant tempo to this game at Fir Park. 

Scottish football is fucking amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Bands_FC: Here you go @StenhousemuirFC ; ) One of our favourite bands ever https://t.co/3qOAHReQc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap. We really are going up that creek without a steering wheel aren't we https://t.co/WZ5K4vbWIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Branson1873: @gash1965 @FawltySybil @SkamanD14 @BrookeED0217 @FleegleJason @FatOldAnarchist @sineadmcfc @nikidoog @brunstead @JBGBs @de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJaninaRamirez @edbookfest Have great time in City. Head doon The Black Bull (on Leith St) for some rawk choons :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Femi_Sorry @Jacob_Rees_Mogg This man wants to drag UK back to some Georgian age of Empire that even the Victorians baulked at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 You have gone full Paul again..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 This is you in the Bull isn't it... https://t.co/rsPcG7435Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a rare picture of @Kezzang69 in the Kinch. https://t.co/dt1yzZXGyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to get the air drums out @Kezzang69 @chris_sheph 

https://t.co/8bK12oCXcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalinkaDirndl ha..no chance 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw a guy walking his cat on a leash around the street we live..Cat did not look happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Bands_FC: Bands F.C. 
Pink Floyd https://t.co/P2YJGufVFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jo_Caulfield: Live in Leith? Please support @saveleithwalk PLS RT thanks https://t.co/BIGoQ8VgCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lady who normal cuts my barber was shut so I had to venture to somewhere else. The guy who I did go to proceeded to try and turn my hair into some sort "modern style". I applaud his attempts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Filthy Tongues  - Jacob's Ladder https://t.co/Oh5S6jikbo Saturday grooves..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Bands_FC: Retweet to win! One lucky retweeter will get one of each of our brilliant new button badges. Winner 10pm Friday #BandsFC 
Wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Bands_FC: Bands F.C. 
Marillion https://t.co/iXMUDk1Xxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pilotbeeruk Hope he was using Mother's Pride bread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerPressured Mother's Pride bread makes the best toast..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmanavis Yep, pretty much schoolyard humour, that should stay in schoolyard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smicht no soap dodging for you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Livingston manager Gary Holt last night "We all have to be fighting from the same Hymn Sheet" 
@Kezzang69 I think the Livv'y players need to come on to the pitch with this

https://t.co/5JUkSASDTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesleyRiot @HeveStarveyYALL @eliistender10 @Maisie_Williams will just leave this here

https://t.co/wpxLq7xPLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 @chris_sheph another goes to the Great Gig In The Sky...#LynyrdSkynyrd https://t.co/Kp2Sf8aWYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QVdO8oerqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezzang69 and his friends walking into the local pub this evening. https://t.co/ol6FiGJiPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymannion77 I am bit unsure of this "untold" tagline they are using-Bruce's story is very well known and there are plenty of historical texts-Still you cannie beat a good medieval bloody battle- especially when its a scots army handing an English army its arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliistender10 @Maisie_Williams The way English peeps say Banana--Bananrrrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Blokes In The Pub... Talk NO DEAL Brexit https://t.co/Rk6uUVcJfS Interesting discussion- worth a listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bernie_Torme: Good on Steven Tyler! https://t.co/K99hd94h8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @without_pity: There literally a border, with security, around this "beer without borders". https://t.co/JTepG2eMgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Channel4: When you hear The End of the F***ing World series 2 has been commissioned. #TEOTFW https://t.co/NdP2G9TYyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved that show. https://t.co/lJdIiGXLVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fergusboden: Great crowd gathered outside the City Chambers as @saveleithwalk hand in their massive 10,000 signature strong petition to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lindasomervill: Evicting businesses and boarding up shops is economic vandalism. @adamrmcvey
@cllrcammyday 
@susan4leithwalk
@BenMacphe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its time @Kezzang69 and I went to a Raith game..mon lad pick a game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymannion77 Aww man we really need movie of this..say in the style of Frank Capra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipping heck..This is happening in the USA... https://t.co/OdjIZMtRea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ha I would have put 9% @StephenKing and 0.5 no one knows https://t.co/ciBb1tNDGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curve - Clipped https://t.co/ow9E7jnKt7 Fuzzed Up Guitars all they way up loud...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner Ha..the tag line "Untold" story- I seem to remember my history class told me a lot of the story unless they left things out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outlaw King | Official Trailer [HD] | Netflix https://t.co/7NWvX5cavi Chris Pine's Scottish accent does not sound that bad. I hope they have the scene where Bruce takes a knight's head off during the Battle of Bannockburn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pilotbeeruk: Here's something mad. We're finalists in the Favourite Beer / Craft Brewer category at tomorrow's Scottish Bar &amp; Pub award…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NeuReekie: Leith doesnt need more "visitors". It needs more social housing &amp; less toxic corporate developments by @EdinburghUni  #SaveL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brian_bilston: Here’s a poem entitled ‘Thirty Rules for Midlife Rebellion’. https://t.co/wzxUzO7TJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There you go @Kezzang69 noo is yer chance... https://t.co/lj5Lz4s0vR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardcore Scottish dinner. https://t.co/UvpkvDxZO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrRPMurphy: The Coven Returns. What a thrilling night with the legend Stevie Nicks on the set of AHS. https://t.co/wsI1FlfN1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakeNorthcott Ha same thing happens to us Scots when go abroad. I just normally say "Oh aye I ken Jock. He's a bit of nippy so and so tho..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rivera: @Shawna https://t.co/1Wcs3pKGCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jjmitchell: These horrible screens are back in Princes Street. If banning access to the Gardens (and even benches) is needed for concer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to wake up @Kezzang69 from his Sunday afternoon nap. @chris_sheph 

https://t.co/XI3wBTQFUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw man had some mad nights in there-One night there was some very strangely dressed people in there. Turned it was some of the cast of a show that happening across in the Kings having "between scenes" drink ha! https://t.co/IWlRONPZIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CHIMPSINSOCKS: I already loved Stewart Lee. This makes me love him more. Excellent piece. https://t.co/5gUr33fb0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all weird

https://t.co/HeNyILEhED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Fripp does some serious shredding on this track from Eno

https://t.co/qCcUCGDjOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try that again. Here are some nice aerial shots of my hame toon. I can see the many places where @Kezzang69 as kids we used to hang out...and oh the pubs we tried to sneak into and get served. 
https://t.co/UdElo1qxXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest regret I never got to see them play live..humf. https://t.co/DJjelGFa4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @andymannion77 I have been that man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Led Zep-Friends https://t.co/tiEo9pBiQb More Sunday tunes. I am putting off learning how to use Visual Studio...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not sure that the Turkeys will vote for an early Christmas.. https://t.co/YKSty6LB5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Mason - Stars Around My Heart (Official Video) https://t.co/GZnQoyDQj9 Sunday Choon!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>