<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Analyst: IT Security Analyst – Berkshire – Permanent – SOC, Threat, vulnerability, SIEM, risk, malware Outsource UKs cyber team have an exciting opportunity for an IT Security Analyst to join an organisation that are currently insourcing… https://t.co/sKOc98PIad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Developer ( Dynamics): I have an immediate requirement for a Dynamics CRM Developer to join my client on an initial 6 month contract (Outside of IR35) . You will be working on a major Dynamics 365 project for a leading organisation based in… https://t.co/NEwKWpVeI5 https://t.co/mTipJar3V4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The election overseer for critical Palm Beach County says there is no way the recount for 3 races will be finished by Thursday's deadline: The election overseer for a critical county in Florida confirmed to CNN on Sunday what observers in both parties… https://t.co/aXmntXQhBN https://t.co/VoI9MzVkpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C++ / C# / UML: Software Engineer – C++ / C# / UML – Various Levels Commutable from Uxbridge / Slough / Watford / High Wycombe / Staines / Twickenham A market leading Global manufacturer is seeking to recruit a Software Engineer to… https://t.co/wA0S8fmqZU https://t.co/RmSKLPX8ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Recruiter OXY Location Houston, Texas Salary Competitive Posted 12 Oct 2018 Closes 10 Nov 2018 Ref ******** Sector Oil and Gas Category Information Technology Contract Type Permanent Hours Full Time You need to sign in or create an… https://t.co/8X2vFOdz6d https://t.co/ZUaRYcFKky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonizing immigrants is a losing cause for House GOP: Republicans across the country spent a lot of time and money trying to make the midterm elections about immigration. https://t.co/nPvHAlzEkl https://t.co/GHpLoDVkWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality &amp; Support: Position: Software Quality &amp; Support Location: Hull Salary: £18-30k Ref: (Apply online only) Our client based in Hull are a collective of companies, expertise, and talent assembled specifically to help brands own every… https://t.co/kaQRldMSDI https://t.co/gIxxx4Ys5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy's letter to Cowboys owner goes viral: 7-year-old Rylan Wood wrote a letter to Dallas Cowboys team owner Jerry Jones. His main point: "We suck." https://t.co/Hb5ZZiXyst https://t.co/2Rakc8bVHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect – Legal, Risk and Compliance: To assist in the execution of the vision, strategic direction, and initiative roadmap for strategic, business technology projects. To help define the reference and implementation architectures for… https://t.co/2Y8a7usgNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer (C/C++): Embedded Software Engineer (C/C++) My client, a world-class image processing company, are looking to hire an embedded software engineer for their HQ based in Dublin City Centre This company offers the chance to work… https://t.co/A142t2rRne https://t.co/kTzN2Cozwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Application Developer: Job Description BAE Systems is looking to hire a Jr. Software Developer to join their team in Washington, DC. This developer will work under general supervision of a Lead Programmer or a Project Manager and will perform… https://t.co/uDfSNO7DJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer – Android SDK, Studio, iOS – Bath – DOE: Android Developer | Android SDK, Studio, iOS| Bath | Competitive Salary Do you have experience of building bespoke Android Apps? Do you have experience with Android SDK and Android Studio? Are… https://t.co/ovQJZ3aVY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: For Trump, defeat at home and battles abroad: Four years ago, the world greeted the centennial of the start of World War I with idle curiosity — a bygone catastrophe from a time of dukes and empires, dangerous grudges and doomed alliances. https://t.co/xd76OVzfAu https://t.co/9zrkAvcft9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Senior Application Developer, Arlington, VA, (ID#13097) Arlington, VA and surrounding areas Minimum Active Secret SECURITY CLEARANCE LEVEL required’ The Department of State’s (DOS) Information Resource Management (IRM)… https://t.co/HjkQArt3f2 https://t.co/YW1sSalhen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Risk Manager: Job Summary Responsible for the facilitation of IT risk management processes. Collaborates cross-functionally to help mature and execute the IT Risk processes which include; governance, risk assessment, risk analysis, risk metrics, risk… https://t.co/gSAW4eHFpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect – Customer Success, Amazon Connect: Job Description Senior Solutions Architect – Customer Success, Amazon Connect Location: US-TX-Dallas Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Company/Location (search) : Country… https://t.co/N0HgLVa0Ph https://t.co/qwsrAafvfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President arrives separately from other foreign leaders at the centenary ceremonies in Paris: Marking the breakout of peace after World War I, President Donald Trump on Sunday will honor a century-old transatlantic alliance that some fear is fraying. https://t.co/OJS4vdpeQV https://t.co/ayoatPF2KL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Manager: Our client is an exciting young Fintech business with big plans. Working with the country’s leading employers, they aim to turn the UK into a nation of investors, using their innovative online savings and investment platform. With… https://t.co/ggeGT1j096]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migration Network Engineer – Network Migration: Migration Network Engineer – Network Migration + £250-£270 per day + Indepth knowledge of WANs and LANs + DV Cleared role + Basingstoke based Migration Network Engineer Reporting to the Migration SPM and… https://t.co/gkFgTnYNsQ https://t.co/dB3DFxclWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['SNL' brings on congressman-elect to get an apology: A week after "Saturday Night Live" comedian Pete Davidson was criticized for mocking the appearance of Dan Crenshaw, the NBC variety show brought the congressman-elect on to receive an apology in person. https://t.co/ot8nPZmlrN https://t.co/2j1HTm3L3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Ruby Developer: Lead Ruby Developer This is a fantastic opportunity for a Lead Ruby Developer to join one of the strongest Ruby teams in London and become a key part of their team and move from a Ruby Developer to a Lead Ruby Developer This a great… https://t.co/gJAakpQF7t https://t.co/F1sSkcrZa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 35922BR Domain Analytics Retail ,CPG and logistics Skillset Datawarehouse and ETL , Country USA State / Region / Province Florida New Jersey North Carolina Rhode Island Texas Work Location… https://t.co/pvRWWZDbI9 https://t.co/zTsUFXZ4Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer: Maxwell Bond have recently started working with a brand-new client to Manchester city centre, they have expanded their tech operations to Manchester to attract some of the UK’s best data engineers and developers. This business handles… https://t.co/ZYsso9XHaP https://t.co/LPm2kGB70b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad sings to daughter as they drive through flames: Joe Allen, a California resident, sang and consoled his daughter as they fled their home that was threatened by flames. https://t.co/o4TRrsBbYI https://t.co/mGBo9SJ5L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: Our established IT support Client is currently seeking a skilled IT Support Engineer to join their growing team. This will be a multi-skilled role involving scheduled service visits to commercial client to complete ICT related tasks.… https://t.co/2mInV8N91u https://t.co/IFYtBTtG8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Account Executive – SaaS: Enterprise Account Executive 1st UK Enterprise Sales Hire for Innovative SaaS company Digital Workplace Solutions | Enterprise Collaboration | Enterprise Content Management (ECM) £70k – £85k Basic + Double OTE +… https://t.co/Vw5fGT1eWo https://t.co/z7j48RdtsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Consultants: This successful business software consultancy headquartered in Hemel Hempstead are looking for 3 Application Support Consultants who has supported commercial business software such as ERP, Supply Chain, Accounting,… https://t.co/eSWCg9uWQb https://t.co/2RBFsBg89Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SE Cupp: History replete with greedy presidents: CNN's SE Cupp criticized President Donald Trump, as well as former presidents, for attacking the rule of law and the Constitution. https://t.co/Dir3nMqall https://t.co/CJPCvX4cp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Service, Content &amp; Experience Of Manager: Digital Service, Web Content &amp; Experience Manager-Agile/ITIL Digital Service, Web Content &amp; Experience Manager is urgently needed to lead and manage a complex web environment including website builds, CMS… https://t.co/4LFwRvbW4H https://t.co/G0868XjkyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Develoepr: Front End Developer * Dublin * 6 month contract * Software Company Excellent front end development role available with a large software company who are expanding in Dublin. You will work as part of a newly formed Agile team building… https://t.co/HiSYEp9kYR https://t.co/2ALq0nLZ6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Sales Account Manager: The Company: Exertis is one of Europe’s largest and fastest growing technology distribution and specialist service providers, partnering with over 400 global technology brands and over 45,000 retailers and resellers. This hugely… https://t.co/OdiOYK3nA9 https://t.co/dERXoGT8JF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top 10 cities for $100M VC rounds in 2018 so far: Crunchbase News recently profiled a selection of U.S. companies’ largest VC raised in 2018, and no surprise here: the 10 largest rounds all topped out well north of $100 million. https://t.co/5i4rYBIz3f https://t.co/hNPNRsLs8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gillum withdraws concession as recount begins: Democrat Andrew Gillum withdrew his concession to Republican former Rep. Ron DeSantis in the Florida governor's race on Saturday, hours after the secretary of state announced a recount of their race and two… https://t.co/g0A7iAES64 https://t.co/dwmSekVvpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist (Machine Learning / AI / Python) Our client who are one of the largest Data Analytics companies in the world are seeking the best of the best Data Scientists for one of the most exciting programmes in the market today !!… https://t.co/WahE8VlwEm https://t.co/oXz4DX9owr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Senior Business Analyst with Capita ICTDS in Birmingham: Capita is an exciting place to work. Join us as a Senior Business Analyst to work with our customers, internal teams and third-party suppliers to understand and document… https://t.co/InvnnK1OYm https://t.co/eRNUdVBJRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Florida races head to recount: More than three days after the polls closed in Florida, the secretary of state announced that the razor-thin races for governor, senator and agriculture commissioner will be reviewed in a series of recounts. https://t.co/brDU91AFrQ https://t.co/GJCBQ3MSWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist: Senior Data Scientist/London/£600-£700 We are searching for a Senior Data Scientist for a SME healthcare organisation, based in London. Ideally looking for someone to start ASAP, but will to wait for the right person. Paying a very… https://t.co/JCRerBgggT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's busiest shopping day has fast start: The biggest shopping day on the planet has started with a bang. https://t.co/w1MXvgpoU9 https://t.co/z6ib99rxdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer- Full Stack: Requisition Number: ****** Position Title: Software Engineer (IV) External Description: Employer Labs is looking for candidates interested in solving next generation big data problems leveraging modern and open source… https://t.co/jP8nXAD0t0 https://t.co/DPhcw0UOyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Functional Business Analyst: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search… https://t.co/86cfyPJuBA https://t.co/t5flz6iMb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Validation Engineer: Onboard Software Validation Engineer: We are looking for a highly motivated engineer with good experience in embedded software development. You need to be enthusiastic, passionate and eager to apply your excellent software… https://t.co/GojSnOgrbx https://t.co/wwHwYUmJmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raging fires spread on both ends of California, killing 9: • Why the fire spread so quickly | Photos • See family pray as they drive through fire https://t.co/BbXeMojmis https://t.co/WVZyHv9aDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist/Risk Modeler @ Cyence – San Mateo, CA: Guidewire’s Cyence Risk Analytics products help the property &amp; casualty (P &amp; C) industry to model new and evolving risks such as cyber. By combining internet-scale data listening, adaptive machine… https://t.co/s4tEfdR2J4 https://t.co/2d2JQQ2m4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer – Bath – Objective-C, iOS: iOS Developer – Bath – £dependant upon experience An exciting opportunity to join a successful and growing developer of outdoor pursuit video content for a global audience of millions. This company are expanding… https://t.co/gvHnHcXyub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge Domain Expert Application Platform Support: Location US-NC-Raleigh Posting date 7 hours ago(10/17/2018 3:29 AM) Job ID 62093 Category Technical Support Company description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers, partners,… https://t.co/lN2hNre3JW https://t.co/RX62LFUUSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: C#/ASP.NET Software Developer £50k + good benefits Surrey Permanent The company: Fantastic opportunity for Software Developers that are looking to be part of one of the top trend setting technology companies in the UK working on the… https://t.co/bdSuyelPvC https://t.co/NVYrR8WW8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular Developer: Angular Developer Columbus, OH 10-28-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is crafting… https://t.co/Si3ARgUGb2 https://t.co/P1gOrIwOzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utah man pleads guilty to causing 2013 gaming service outages: A Utah man has pleaded guilty to computer hacking charges, after admitting to knocking several gaming services offline five years ago. Austin Thompson, 23, launched several denial-of-service… https://t.co/BH8wGy3cif https://t.co/QH80Nzj6Cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US President meets with his French counterpart hours after chiding him on Twitter: US President Donald Trump began his 48-hour visit to Paris on Saturday meeting with his host, French President Emmanuel Macron, a onetime friend who he chided on… https://t.co/okMpqPLsoc https://t.co/dgJWo1uHBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Azure Developer: NET Azure Developer – CRAWLEY – Contract A big UK client of mine is looking for a .NET Azure Developer based in Crawley on a contract basis The role will include carrying out development tasks, hands-on application development,… https://t.co/YsxnITORFp https://t.co/kS0vqIlr4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Developer: Securities Data Service is a provider of reference and market data to many business lines within BNY Mellon. ‘ As part of our Technology Roadmap, we are focused on the modernization, re-engineering, and delivery of our software and… https://t.co/RfP8ORih9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Developer: I am looking to recruit a number of experienced permanent Developer Testers who are highly skilled in both writing and testing code. You will be office based, joining an experienced development and testing team working on some very… https://t.co/L1XQbZbCWC https://t.co/O2oASrsLpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Officer (IAO): 126991BR Job Description: This contingent position is being considered &amp; hired for all non-management levels (G08-G10) based upon selected candidate’s applicable experience Raytheon Blackbird Technologies is looking… https://t.co/XPsjVGCtD1 https://t.co/7l9Y7UBgQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interaction Designer: Interaction Designer – Government Client – Outside IR35 An Interaction Designer is required to come on board with a consultancy who are based on site with a large government client in Feltham. This role will fall outside IR35. The… https://t.co/uU6vd5tzD9 https://t.co/mhDoi2tBLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead Software Engineer: Our client is a global organisation, who look to hire positive and energetic people who want to make a difference to their products. They encourage an environment of continuous improvement in practices and self-development.… https://t.co/kiJ2lylOqO https://t.co/rynWg5E3bI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuomo: Trump gets too many breaks for lying: CNN's Chris Cuomo takes a look at President Donald Trump's history of lies and hypocrisy. https://t.co/c0dpmvcLNy https://t.co/AmGa7kCw5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Project Manager (IT Security, Re-Platforming/Upgrades): Infrastructure Project Manager with proven full lifecycle delivery and senior stakeholder engagement is required to coordinate and deliver multiple IT Infrastructure, Re-Platforming… https://t.co/tR8Bw3s6M2 https://t.co/jp3BVZSApp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT &amp; Network Support Engineer – Windows/Cisco – London – £32k: IT and Network Engineer – London – £32k – INTERVIEWS HAPPENING ASAP! If you are looking for a fresh challenge in a vibrant IT dept, where the challenges are varied, ranging from desktop to… https://t.co/p8SJMdrqON https://t.co/Oo0lzwIEiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop / Network / Helpdesk Support Analyst: Desktop / Network / Helpdesk Support Analyst An exciting opportunity has become available for a support technician with some experience. We are looking for someone to provide day-to-day desktop and network… https://t.co/TmBnOdPxeC https://t.co/j8xeNuQDD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toobin says 'racial dimension' to Trump's attacks on black female journalists: CNN Chief Legal Analyst Jeffrey Toobin on Friday criticized President Donald Trump for his recent attacks on reporters -- particularly African-American female reporters --… https://t.co/HNjAtPrPPj https://t.co/BsAMMJNKnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK SECURITY ARCHITECT – ANTWERP (12 MONTHS +): NETWORK SECURITY ARCHITECT – ANTWERP (12 MONTHS +) Senior Network Security Architect with a general background in network and infrastructure is needed by my client in Antwerp to start in January. Role:… https://t.co/u6fEYZWcx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayPal shuts down accounts for Proud Boys and founder McInnes as well as antifa groups: PayPal has shut down several accounts, including those for far-right group the Proud Boys and their founder, Gavin McInnes, for the promotion of "hate, violence, or… https://t.co/izbLN8Rf0H https://t.co/7wEjAFcUUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump picks a fight with Macron as Air Force One lands in France: President Donald Trump picked a fight with French President Emmanuel Macron over European defense just as Air Force One landed in France on Friday. https://t.co/HlfRbzoQSh https://t.co/dVB8rTYv9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – ELIGIBLE FOR DV CLEARANCE: Project management * Define and agree the scope and deliverables of specific work packages with your Work Package/Project Managers * Identifying issues and recommending solutions to the Programme Manager or… https://t.co/wwTeVzGX1j https://t.co/iZHY6NpFRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Are you a Front End Developer looking for a new challenge? Are you passionate about learning new tech, such as React Native? Then this is the perfect opportunity for you! We are currently looking to hire a Front End Developer to join… https://t.co/2vGn8uf3Jq https://t.co/SkACT9qUVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Line IT Support: We currently have a vacancy for a First Line Client IT Support Analyst to join a leading, global organisation based in Milton Keynes. THE ROLE The First Line Client IT Support Analyst acts as the 1st line for all Client IT related… https://t.co/MXTEqtjrGR https://t.co/d940ogIgnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst My client based in Suffolk are a leading global construction company who are recruiting for a Business Analyst. As a Business Analyst your role will be to elicit, analyse, specify, and validate the business needs of… https://t.co/MvMbd2ovcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDI Developer: EDI Developer Bracknell Initial 12 month contract I’m recruiting for a global manufacturing company who are looking for an individual who has strong experience working with SAP. You will have the following skills: ·EDI &amp; SAP experience… https://t.co/PDNpd0XenI https://t.co/U37Ncu4OHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Test Engineer: Senior Software Test Engineer We are currently looking for a Senior Software Test Engineer to join our client, based in Cambridge. This role is offering the opportunity to deliver automated and manual software testing as… https://t.co/TUnwRFCqJf https://t.co/iEFlsqetH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York is the new hot spot for Big Tech: In the summer of 2013, Michael Bloomberg, then the mayor of New York, held a press conference to announce that Spotify would open an office in the city and hire more than 100 engineers by the following year. https://t.co/0lEnjnYb7Y https://t.co/8cDK2F6CpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – SQL – Junior / Midweight: Web Developer – SQL – Junior / Midweight – Yachting Governing Body Hamble-le-Rice, Southampton SO31 up to £30,000 per annum plus a range of benefits including: pension scheme, free life insurance, 23 days holiday… https://t.co/PUxY98LyTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Job Title: Data Engineer Location: London Start Date: ASAP Contract Length: 6 months Jefferson Frank are currently seeking an innovative Data Engineer to work for a consultancy specialising in the financial industry. Require skills; · Good… https://t.co/NdgN5RIjGm https://t.co/hLtj25Cgv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior Associate: West Creek 6 (12076), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Employer, were building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank,… https://t.co/oTK6T9s4QQ https://t.co/ET0Y0Z2Znp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist – Amazon Go: Job Description Senior Data Scientist – Amazon Go Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Data Science Company/Location (search) : Country (Full Name): : United… https://t.co/M5ZjlQwGn9 https://t.co/Hz2CmwhBSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deployment Support Specialist: Req ID 98962BR Business Title Deployment Support Specialist Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Chantilly Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Logistics Support Services Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is… https://t.co/kugujrogHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olho do Dono is the winner of Startup Battlefield Latin America: Fifteen startups spent the day presenting onstage in São Paulo, Brazil. For the finalists, that meant presenting twice — once in the initial rounds, then again for our finalist judges. This… https://t.co/ODkbzgYBqE https://t.co/LcTyVJ8Qem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: PHP Developer position available in Commerce, California | Advantex Professional Services – Job Search – PHP Developer – Job Title: – Location: Commerce – State: California – Job Number: ****** – Job Class: Full Time – Category:… https://t.co/VaO6kVHCUv https://t.co/a3oIs7669b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Senior Mission/Operations Data Analyst: Req # 2018-52213 Category Intelligence # of Openings 1 Job Location US-Chantilly-VA Clearance Top Secret/SCI w/Poly Overview Every day at Perspecta, we enable hundreds of thousands of people to take… https://t.co/5fiaBDsXYA https://t.co/jlHC1KBtny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (Java): Senior Developer (Java) – Dublin €60K – €70K p/a Skills Java; Docker; Microservices; Spring; AWS; AngularJS We are searching for a Senior Java Developer to join a talented dev team in Dublin who are working on an innovative… https://t.co/OEuZgJVhfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Mgr Commodity Management: 125660BR Job Description: The Senior Manager of Strategic Sourcing and Partnering for IIS will be responsible for leading all efforts to identify, build/maintain relationships, and partner with critical IIS suppliers that… https://t.co/qKQIfyqSBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Residents flee walls of flame as huge wildfire races across Northern California: Tanah Clunies-Ross woke up in the dark to what sounded like lumps of coal raining down her Northern California home. Within minutes, her family and thousands of people were… https://t.co/8ig5CakKNG https://t.co/MgnFkJF8GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Columbus, OH Full-time $95k – $120k Posted 10/30/2018 We are a commercial construction company that is considered to be one of the best in the great state of Ohio! Located just shy of Columbus, we are looking to bring on an additional… https://t.co/aKMnr4LKDT https://t.co/Iv4ou9jep2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Management Analyst Lead:   Job Description – Data Management Analyst Lead (18024659) Data Management Analyst Lead Requisition ID : 18024659 Location : United States-California-Monterey US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/wsdaH1Nduo https://t.co/63ZXO7iBps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer – Tooling SME: Some careers grow faster than others. If you’re looking for a career that will give you plenty of opportunities to develop, join HSBC and your future will be rich with potential. Whether you want a career that… https://t.co/9nCIigiDVf https://t.co/ULuuTNq0gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disaster Recovery System Specialist: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location California-China Lake/Ridgecrest, United States Posted By CH2M &amp; Jacobs Date Posted 7 hours ago Expires 30 Nov 2018 Qualifications None Disaster Recovery System Specialist in… https://t.co/9R2Mdw3Q45 https://t.co/SWLtNmGjf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer: SoCode are proud to be working alongside an established Cambridge based start-up. Our client works on highly secretive projects for some of the largest organisations in the world. Due to an intense period of growth and expansion, they’re… https://t.co/swxl8zUH1K https://t.co/DWnW6JyS7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broward and Palm Beach counties are at the center of a brewing Florida recount. Again.: Broward and Palm Beach counties in Florida are once again at the center of a brewing controversy over vote counting as two of the highest-profile races in the state… https://t.co/1U5GiDjxdM https://t.co/xC9IlTDTWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Akshaya Inc. (formerly SNW Infotech, Inc.) Software Engineer (Pleasanton, CA). Analyze business requirements and deliver new and complex high-quality software solutions. Identify and select tools and processes to address issues related… https://t.co/HfkiFQnupC https://t.co/5j7PXKFlFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Software Developers Required in Bristol, Various Backgrounds Considered as training offered 40/55K Plus bonus and package.  We are looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join one of our teams as we continue to work on the… https://t.co/0D6TkWRE5x https://t.co/BkyGWsZLV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer £40-£45k + Flexible Working + Career Progression Our client is a growing IT company based in Segensworth, due to planned growth they are seeking an experienced and personable Software/Web Developer to join their… https://t.co/iiBOdHc1c5 https://t.co/cI50s7zjyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect – Payments: My client provides a leading cloud based Payment Processing Platform on the Issuer side. This platform is for Credit, Debit, and Prepaid card issuance, authorisation and settlement. They're aim is to replace legacy bank… https://t.co/IcFLwQHG5v https://t.co/pcNceFZwp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Buckle up, it'll be a bumpy ride: A fundamental question for President Donald Trump, as he moves forward after the midterms, is this: what role does he want to play? If he seeks to be the great negotiator he has always claimed to be, there could… https://t.co/Jjf8WiUFp7 https://t.co/GsjnZa3rMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Prince, MS Project: Project Manager – Prince2/PMI, MS Project – Canary Wharf, London- to £55,000 plus great benefits Major client, a global £18 billion turnover organisation has a great opportunity for a Project Manager to lead, oversee… https://t.co/hlPPviia0J https://t.co/YAsFnwc9Ip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[81% of VC firms don’t have a single black investor — BLCK VC wants to change that: There's a new group focused on supporting black investors. https://t.co/6wSVt0brMd https://t.co/CF7zZO0X4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Application Architect: Our client based in Watford is seeking an Enterprise-level Application Architect: This is a unique opportunity to join a greenfield UK Enterprise Architecture function and help define and deliver the Future State… https://t.co/5UATcWuWvB https://t.co/KiG9k1b5tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The former Marine who killed 12 people in Southern California met with a mental health specialist in April: The gunman who killed 12 people at the Borderline Bar &amp; Grill in Thousand Oaks, California, was a 28-year-old veteran of the Marine Corps who had… https://t.co/JvroM9YDSB https://t.co/WAh1kDzZoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support: About Company: With over 40 years experience, here at Harvey Water Softeners we are the UKs number 1. Our factory in Old Woking, Surrey has a full production and R&amp;D facility that both sit alongside our head office.We invest heavily in people… https://t.co/mkrofI8xWk https://t.co/WAt0ShtIEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect: SharePoint Solutions Architect Cambridge £50,000-£55,000 I am currently working with an award winning organisation who specialise in providing both on-premise and cloud solutions. My client is looking to grow their team with the… https://t.co/hkbOVs682W https://t.co/WTWyO6G7Rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US hits Russia with new Crimea sanctions after Trump blames Obama for annexation: The Trump administration announced additional sanctions against Russia Thursday over its ongoing occupation of Crimea and its interference in eastern Ukraine. https://t.co/llNeuTuux0 https://t.co/sAMIvBOqvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevSecOps Engineer: Senior DevSecOps Engineer – AWS, Azure, Terraform, Security, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins You will be helping build the future of company and work directly with micro services architecture that utilizes blockchain technologies that are… https://t.co/hBx65w4d17 https://t.co/d3iFKuKtvH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>