<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a dream. Check out ‘Buford Tea - Lemon Jelly-MLK - Come, I Have A Dream’ by Buford Tea on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/AdKddyOGEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check this out David Guetta &amp; Showtek ft. Vassy - BAD (Teaser) by David Guetta
 http://t.co/ZKUPqfWCMg on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Secondcity - I Wanna Feel (Radio Edit) (Out 25.05.14)’ by Secondcity_uk on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/5IjLTxe35i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTV_Television how much of @Toyota fine goes to the 5 families of those who died? #cashgrab or #justice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right here right now #EnglishBay http://t.co/8Nlis1U5ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin does what he wants, where he wants, to who he wants and the world stands by impotent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New art installation at #Canada Place in time for #TEDtalks in #Vancouver http://t.co/X7VV1FjjVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePaulGenesis what? Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I kinky drink it if there is booze in it" http://t.co/WuLsrWAnIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to feel your heart and soul inside me baby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akirokazu: Anticipate the difficult by managing the easy. - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret to change is to focus all of your energy, not on fighting the old, but on building the new" - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walkin to Motomachu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where we find our most profound intelligence is after all, in the heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can't fly, then run. If you can't run, then walk. If you can't walk, then crawl, but whatever… http://t.co/5M15WkYe2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEllenShow: If only Bradley's arm was longer. Best photo ever. #oscars http://t.co/C9U5NOtGap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HeritageClassic #NHL #Canucks wtf? Why would anyone want to sit so far away? It's barely outdoors!! No wonder still tickets avail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat work eat work workout eat sleep survive repeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a man's determination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be the one if you want me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let it be said that 2 dream is a waste of 1's time.  4 dreams are realities in waiting. In dreams, we plant the seeds of our future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a desire to make it and are willing to take some risks, it is all possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats #TeamCanadaHockey on another #gold #Sid #Sochi2014 #CBCOlympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much like regular season the #Sedin #twins are non existent #GoldMedalGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamCanada total dominance! #GoldMedalGame #Sochi2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some breathing room 3:0 half way through the 3rd #GoCanadaGo #CBCOlympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made good progress this week. Onwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be tolerant not ignorant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Breathe Canada breathe" @CBCOlympics #GoCanadaGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid win #TeamCanadaHockey vs USA 1:0. Going for gold! #CBCOlympics #Sochi2014 #GoCanadaGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calemazoo: #socialmedia explained. Soon you can add Calemazoo; When I'll be available to eat a donut #saas #iOS #android http://t.co/59…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calemazoo: Facebook Sets Its Sights On Your 'Private Content'  http://t.co/RzA7HW9diI via @forbes  Calemazoo ensures your schedule rema…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day ask, push, drive, pound, press, tell, insist, incite, solicit this: If it's not the best, it's not from here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this what paradise is? It is certainly what happiness is. Enjoying the first of many. It doesn't get better than this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counting down the hours to supreme happiness :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing week so far! I love it when a plan comes together. #inspired #excited #HappyEaster #onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I'm Happy...Can't nothing bring me down. Pharrell Williams - Happy (Official Music Video): http://t.co/5AadvUa6Y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really happening. Dreams are coming true. Counting down the hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LattaUSA thanks for the follow. I'd love to try. Where can I buy in #Vancouver #Canada ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LattaUSA: Food is #medicine. Start healing at a #farmersmarket near you. http://t.co/g9TQLe2Hln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[310 push ups in 30 minutes. Not bad for an old guy #healthy #fitness #workout #stillgotit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to this text and pic "I like your hat uncle Chris! Love KATE". Hope your day starts with a… http://t.co/M5EPJ8yaSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheeKruger: "Above all, you want to create something you are proud of." - A quote from a brilliant man's autobiography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing u isn't about how long it's been since we've spoken. It's about that moment when I'm doing something &amp; wish you were by my side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to call it a day, crawl into bed and try again tomorrow #Onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing in the world is worth having or worth doing unless it means effort, pain, difficulty..." - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@40billion: Top 10 Crazy Donald Trump Moments ... http://t.co/uUAPbV0FuA” how $, celebrity &amp; poor taste can = bloated ego &amp; no credibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @high_on_glitter: http://t.co/mbv5oYBGnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@dennisthetang: Could this be it? The permanence of spring??” Yep, I woke up wet. Time to put the pjs away til next winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sincere condolences to Jim Flaherty's family on this sad news. You gained my respect and I thank you for your service #RIP #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Mr. Jim Flaherty. You will be remembered as an honourable and respected Finance Minister and MP. Thank you for your service #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful spring day in #Vancouver #innukshuk #welcome #openarms #englishbay http://t.co/PLvVds0CuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Heartbleed Bug" affecting many of world's SSL encrypted sites. Has been in existence since end of 2011. RevCanada shuts down website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness often sneaks in through a door you didn't know you left open #truth #IWokeUpLikeThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per•sist•ence noun 1. Firm or obstinate continuance in a course of action in spite of difficulty or opposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whoever is careless with the truth in small matters cannot be trusted with important matters" - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone else getting tired and insulted by the arrogance and denials from #cpc over need for amendments to #UnfairElxnsAct ? #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Senator_McInnis says personally witnessed 1000s of questionable votes &amp; remained silent til now? Makes u #complicit or full of #bs #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ô Canada! Le Nord Vrai fort et libre! Merci Québec pour choisir l'unité sur la division. Bienvenue à la maison. #strongerensemble #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Canada! The True North strong and free! Thank you Quebec for choosing unity over division. Welcome home #strongertogether #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheJeetBanerjee: The dark untold side of entrepreneurship that nobody ever discusses - http://t.co/YYJfRIQPfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What lies behind us and what lies ahead of us are tiny matters compared to what lies within us. #inspiration #patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TGIF lots of great meetings and progress this week. Have a great weekend everyone! #persistence #patience #passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping this is the second to last Friday night like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be my Claire without the infidelity #powercouple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I look at the keyboard I see that "U" and "I" are always together :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FairElectionsAct provides opportunity for @SenateCA to demonstrate importance of sober second thought #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@margaretresin @PierrePoilievre if you listen you will hear the footsteps of voters walking away from #conservatives #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre Minister of Democratic Erosion serving best interest of #conservatives and the #Harper #Government #cdnpoli #pnpcbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evansolomoncbc @PnPCBC vouchers are least of concerns over this bill. There are many amendments needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now for some happy thoughts....16  days and counting down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power of truth never declines. Denial may be effective in the short term, but in the long run truth prevails #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And lead us not into temptation, But deliver us from evil. For thine is the kingdom, the power, and the glory, For ever and ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incredible first in #Harper #government congratulations after 8 years, finally some #accountability #cdnpoli #broken #promises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitterverse. Passion, persistence and patience. I repeat this every day. One step forward one step closer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who spends too much time studying history imagines his place in it. Instead he should be more focused on forging his future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should laugh we should cry we should love we should dream we should stare at the stars and not just at screens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuddling with you would be perfect right now. http://t.co/KIX1kPa2se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre how when you are trying to prevent Elections Canada from communicating with Cdns? @PnPCBC #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counting down the days to living happily ever after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: If you dedicate yourself to helping others, you’ll be happier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While governments talk, we can take action #boycottRussia #Putin #intolerance #corruption #ukraineinvasion #powerofthepeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SupremeCourtCan shows it is above politics and @pmharper, he is not above the law.  Long live #Canada #Constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#iphone #zoom #handheld #blacktusk mtn from #Whistler #bc #canada #volcano #lavaflow pierced the… http://t.co/ZroVeq8Uzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking north from #Whistler mtn over to #7tHeaven on #Blackcomb mtn - #Amazing day! http://t.co/gwTgr20rnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic day - Blackcomb Glacier http://t.co/NbiYWN2oNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Silence is a source of great strength." -Lau Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence. True silence is the rest of the mind; it is to the spirit what sleep is to the body, nourishment and refreshment. -William Penn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On top of the world #whistler #glacier #innukshuk #blacktusk #inspiration http://t.co/3oqPvzQUmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current state of mind - morning yoga by the lake before heading into the alpine for a hike #no filter… http://t.co/R9upxR5l90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying some relaxation in #beautiful #Whistler. Looking forward to Scandinave spa tomorrow. It's a long overdue mini escape #onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for the many years of rotfl! You said what others didn't have the balls to say. You are a legend #RIPJoanRivers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprisingly clean taste #notasadvertised #filthydirtyipa #lovethepackaging #Vancouver #parallel49… http://t.co/cKj73VMA9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be true to who you are. Be brave and wild at heart. Your life is now, seize it and make it amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not worth anything, unless you find something to live for. Let your heart be your guide. Be fearless. Make every moment count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeldawilliams: http://t.co/UEtjQ1f2zS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IJasonAlexander: Ah Robin, I'm so sorry the earth couldn't stay worthy of you. Hope happiness awaits you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tritonal: He was pure brilliance, one of our absolute fav's.   Hollywood has lost an absolute Legend.   RIP @robinwilliams!

http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @high_on_glitter: RIP Robin Williams 
We will always love you. You live in our hearts now. http://t.co/JFCIvGj3g3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>