<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganNewsYVR Nope! Just abbreviated :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every lawyer regardless of seniority should be prepared to answer "what makes u great lawyer?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 yrs with @cibc and I get THIS "service" opening new account? Should have gone elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brutal! "MT @sladurantaye: Wow. Families missing plane informed of deaths via text msg just ahead of press conf. http://t.co/QuCRdPMejB"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LindsayGriffith: In our inaugural installment of the General Counsel Corner -factors considered when hiring an outside law firm: http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple, yet profound "@News1130radio: #Local radio host’s story of #kindness goes viral http://t.co/jDPguqwFd7"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes sense - many U.S. pens r a for profit biz. @rossfishman #mental_floss #lawyers #lawfirms #law #LMAMKT #LPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossfishman #mental_floss #lawyers #lawfirms #law #LMAMKT #LPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBA_BC: Join a Conversation with the Chief Justice  Robert James Bauman and the Municipal Bar http://t.co/CNXRt1yM1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL!! "@rossfishman: At #fly2Ohare: I don't think she bought the pants and bag together. http://t.co/4qKMeSP9hh"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debating: switch to online newspaper + drop paper delivery? Will I miss turning pgs, clipping client ads + stories? What to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: How White House correspondents feel about Jay Carney and the W.H. press office http://t.co/kb5b8DL6w7  via @POLITICOMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBA_BC: Early Bird Savings end TODAY! Register now for the @CBA_BC / VBA Golf Tourney @UniversityGolf Club on July 16. http://t.co/uo0i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ontraccoach: Success of a great leader boils down to great communication skills http://t.co/26WyRfALfb #coachinglawyers #lawfirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice! MT "@donnyvandyk: @sharwhite taking break from @Campaign_Dog to update @bcliberals  on new initiatives! #BCL14 http://t.co/h4dxIP1rgW"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say good bye to @VancouverSun Keeping Track page (moves + kudos) - just learned one of my fav pages was retired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @caroloffcbc: "I must contain my emotions and have smart conversations. Not confrontations on the front page.." CBC Prez on @cbcasithapp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawSocietyofBC: News Release: Law Society statement on recent comments about Chief Justice Beverley McLachlin -  http://t.co/WMEBlLR4jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaffePR: RT @WSJ: 43% of hiring managers who used social media to screen job candidates found reasons there not to hire them http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...democracy has to be more than 2 wolves + a sheep voting on what to have for dinner." A must-read. http://t.co/oWo4ZZRIe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Shocking. Men + women across Canada should object loudly to Ford's comments if true. Yes #disgustingpig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did u know the Chief Justice of Supreme Crt of Canada is the Administrator of Canada? ("Understudy" to the Governor Gen)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music to my ears listening to 100s of @vsb39 band students at Elementary Night of Bands. http://t.co/IHDsNRNFEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A long walk with my dog around False Creek saw many courteous #VANCOUVER   drivers yielding to us. Nice huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no. RT @GlobalBC: BREAKING: Shooting at mill in South Nanaimo: Several people wounded - http://t.co/Xu0eLLd06h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Miss604: The @armyandnavyca Shoe Sale is coming up on Wednesday: http://t.co/kwjzrIUsvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! RT @CanLawMag: The Canadian Lawyer Daily is out! http://t.co/TZnCVVIzXu Stories via @lawyerPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbolan, feel like I'm sitting in crtrm beside you. Fascinating live tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed your thoughts on this topic, Ian MT @ianmulgrew: What will a TWU law degree be worth? – Slaw http://t.co/T488V3P68u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting comments on my recent column @slaw_dot_ca on the value of a TWU law degree and #diversity. http://t.co/OTJLC6j8x9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @autismspeaks: RETWEET @ElsForAutism: @autismspeaks we're trying to get 100 #RBCELS retweets to help win $125K for #autism. Please help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinokeefe: Amazon employs 18 women among 120 most senior managers, none with line to Bezos ~ @juliettegarside f/ @guardian http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@betsiroach I just wish u were going me, Bets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweetest firm ever? MT"The happiest of days @helpslaw: our beloved articled student Jas Mangat marries Ayna Gill. We love u both! xo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: N.S. law society rejects Trinity Western as long as it maintains same-sex covenant http://t.co/ydPlk4iJxZ http://t.co/oiT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! Might just trade a glass of red for white on the patio tonight now that it's *almost* summer in Vancouver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How lovely! "@HicksMorley: Thank you for Lorenza for 23 years! Enjoy your retirement! #bestwishes #retirement http://t.co/2aMyof7urb"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mediatebcsoc I'm wishing you the best candidates to choose from!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab gal! "@rebeccawissler: I usually know everything, but when I don't, I call @NancyMyrland. Thank you for your Twitter genius! #lmamkt"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @proctor_jason: Former BC RCMP spokesman Tim Shields facing second BC Supreme civil claim for sexual harassment. Civilian member also su…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonvanRassel Well put, Jason. My thought exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasonvanRassel: It's true hope was slim Nathan O'Brien &amp; grandparents would be alive after 2 wks, but hard to convey the sadness upon h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx CI !"@CI_Legal: Challenging a Few Myths About Legal Marketing http://t.co/XPD9scptQQ by @lawyerPR"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot dog? Puppy popsicles - layering frozen water with dog treats - keeps my pooch busy, happy and cool. http://t.co/hQZo3mr0hV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lululemon: Make sure you wake up rested and refreshed on Monday with these 10 tips to beat the summer heat in your sleep: http://t.co/E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilNugent Love SF! Lucky you! Oh yeah, the WC...too nice here to be inside watching! Hope you enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilNugent Stunning weekend in #vancouver ... Biking to farmer's market, backyard BBQ party + baseball game. Classic weekend! You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's LeBron? MT"@sallyschmidt: most ludicrous stmt @lindacohn: "We'll all remember where we were when LeBron decided 2 return home." @espn"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilNugent: What are you doing this weekend? Check out the Top 7 Successful Weekend Habits via @SanFranciscoVC http://t.co/QFtywOjRgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieSimpson24: Nathan O'Brien's dad is sitting in the front row of the courtroom. His son disappeared 12 days ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my! Does he know he's about to be prosecuted? "@CharlesFinch: The best http://t.co/xbFPNAETzs"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shananigins15: Gas company owned by #AlvinLiknes, #NathanOBrien's grandfather, went bankrupt a few days before the 3 disappeared. http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ontraccoach: Development of individuals in your #lawfirm builds loyalty + commitment like nothing else. http://t.co/IoOtOmzQR0 #coachin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering the same with all media still reporting on him"@alan_rae: @theprovince I don't know why you guys bother with this guy?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention rural Calgary prpty owners: "@MCSCanada: #AMBERAlert UPDATE for Nathan O'Brien. Please read &amp; RT! http://t.co/dhlk5PRZa0"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NancyHixt: Police urging landowners outside of #yyc to search property and bldgs to help in search for missing 5yr old Nathan O'Brien &amp;…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @crisfran: Amber Alert still in place and continues to generate tips.  Today 20-30 people from estate sale have shown up today. #yyc #cb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Rescue shelters overflow with healthy pets while pet shops sell sick puppy farmed pups #wheresmum #adopt @pupaid http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BUcrimlaw: Parents of Missing Nathan O'Brien Plead for Return of 'Angel' http://t.co/qoGuyzUlW8 via @NBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevwrites: “@tmousseau: Looking for a Content Marketing genius to join the team. https://t.co/DKmkPCGweO” @GDgeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanBurritt Good luck with this story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come ON give up those *?!* #hardbite chips! - Tory The Dog http://t.co/UArhRxEATO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@News1130radio Ironic typo: "...*except* students ..." (Thinking you're not *expecting* failure, right? ;) ) #smileworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed @seatoskygondola down way more than climbing up the sea to summit trail. #grousegrind now easy! http://t.co/2sm0Rnhk39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanfowlie: Only five hours to go before the only people I can legally email are my parents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good 2 see @douglasbing "@BCGovNews: PIX: #Firefighters learn imp skills @ the JI#MapleRidge: http://t.co/x7EcvZ7sAI @JIBCnews @AmrikVirkBC"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strombo: The best!

"Eminem Terrified As Daughter Begins Dating Man Raised On His Music" 

http://t.co/LBiCNN0bjS via @TheOnion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DepressedDarth: I'm getting ready for penalty kicks #CRCvsGRE http://t.co/iM75wdZTnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And ruin all the fun? "@ElevenPR: Now that Rob Ford is emerging from rehab, perhaps he should consider a few weeks in media relations camp?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atta girl! MT"@kirstinestewart: Don't know how I'll vote- But amazing pic @oliviachow: Saluting #WorldPride. #WPTO14 http://t.co/lj6Fl6ZfEW"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOO "@NSRescue: @NorthShoreNews story on rescue gear theft. See pic for the type of gear to be on the lookout for. http://t.co/f75zFl4xBw"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAH! "@CUrquhartGlobal: At 6 tonight, my story... @LondonDrugs makes a generous donation to @NSRescue @GlobalBC @BC1 @PeterMeiszner"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HA! "@VPDHorses: We call this our Horse Oreo cookie formation with #Stanley Park as the back drop. http://t.co/2PYeuSNwS2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBA_BC: The inaugural recipient of the @CBA_BC Innovative Workplace Award is Vancouver firm @ClarkWilsonLLP  http://t.co/qFSG68Tl6w #la…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NeilChantler: Update on #TWU law school: benchers to consider adopting overwhelming results of SGM at their Sept, 2014 meeting - http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids home = chaos #strikedaycare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouvermetro He knows we have ferries and flights to Victoria, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charming MT"@cbcnewsbc:Chilliwack Cattle Sales owners already invest'd 4 injured cows, E coli http://t.co/2wS8mlyzwZ http://t.co/vtCFHo2Mx3"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lawheadhunter: Bigger question following BC #lawyers vote to oppose accreditation of #TWU law school is whether it will sway benchers f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!"@post_haste: Approx 38% of BC law society members voted. Massive turnout 4 short notice. Of them approx 77% voted against #TWU accred."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about, "would you help an injured VPD officer if you could?" "Were u there and a witness?" #Yaletown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm... the media and rhetorical questions such as,"do the recent Yaletown shootings worry you?" Really? #Yaletown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david_bilinsky My slaw column on #TWU generated 30 comments. Most were very interesting  http://t.co/eUpIDYOaLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nrusse: Nicely put MT @bcsecuritieslaw: #twu More exciting to see people taking action (whatever their view). Staying silent is no opti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BourassaJohn @CBCNews Common decency shouldn't require legislation, but evidence like this makes one wonder. We. Must. Do. Better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Shame on Chilliwack Cattle Sales. If only those animals could speak... and defend themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @goclio: Jurors: don't make Facebook comments about your trial. While on duty. And then lie about it: http://t.co/qnGTSffWMz via @ABAJou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @News1130radio: BREAKING NEWS: Three people hurt after gunfire in #Yaletown and near Science World http://t.co/VLQi3uTQwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to client + pal Renee Collins Goult on CBC interview w @AndrewChangCBC re mediation http://t.co/5kcjz5Lcl8  #bced #cbcbc  ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenhansman Ahh, yes, there it is again. Thanks, Glen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmhenhansman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@glenhansman Ohhhhh, a Lamp of Learning?! Of course (silly me). @keithbaldrey, did u know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever noticed BCTF's logo? A teapot. Not kidding. Not even smart-looking. There's a story while u wait @keithbaldrey! #bced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @News1130radio: Missing Person @VancouverPD needs your help finding 88-year old Kwai Hei Yan last seen near W 16th Ave and Trimble. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @fionaanderson + @BIVCommunity on bea-u-tiful new website: http://t.co/S3TqbgGgJV. What 2 do w spare time now??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very strange MT"@MacleansMag: Mike Tyson among odd celebrity endorsements of Ford: http://t.co/yYJ7K5F7QL #topoli http://t.co/PuDjVHj0Qk"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make that @constantcontact ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting *two months* for a fix to @constantcontacts social media share functionality. What's up @ctcthelp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @susinsky: Did Toronto have to pull those anti-littering ads? Could they have been defended as satire? http://t.co/aZdHq31FzD http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YesVoteScots: Scotland : "I'm leaving you..."
Britain : "You can't!"
Scotland : "I'm leaving.  It's over."
Britain : "... I'm pregnant!…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>