<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Piece of Art In Your Home: http://bit.ly/FdS6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Grow Barley Grass from http://bit.ly/PU1Ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaseous Pollution: 
In areas where oil and gas development is prevalent, air, water and soil resources can becom.. http://bit.ly/Ob4am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard B. Alley: Richard B. Alley (born 1957) is an American geologist and Evan Pugh Professor of Geosciences a.. http://bit.ly/boa2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How Gaseous Pollution Contaminate Kids Health" http://bit.ly/6YIaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research: Indian Almond Effective For Hair Growth From http://bit.ly/AOQr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guide For Unique Bone Candle Holder from http://bit.ly/23YVKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advantages of Stainless Steel Pots from http://bit.ly/9H8rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How You Make Papercraft Without Cardstock Paper from http://bit.ly/KkfhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special User Reviews of Royal Enfield Bullet 350 Motorcycle in http://bit.ly/Ok8N6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming Increases Rainfall in England from  http://bit.ly/1d8jZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Gifts This Diwali from http://bit.ly/2hOLe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tropical Regions To Be Hardest Hit By Fisheries Shifts Caused By Climate Change: Major shifts in fisheries dist.. http://bit.ly/1CeJKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nitrogen Cycle: Key Ingredient In Climate Model Refines Global Predictions: For the first time, climate scienti.. http://bit.ly/14JhEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Third of Dinosaur Species Never Existed?: Many dinosaurs may be facing a new kind of extinction-a controversi.. http://bit.ly/vytv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Never Fading Charm Of Wooden Toys from http://bit.ly/t62IO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving Forests Five Times Better Than Carbon Capture for Climate Action: WWF Sweden is urging its government – .. http://bit.ly/2rkofr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dramatic Footage of Walruses Highlights Threats From Climate Change: The retreating sea ice of the Alaskan and .. http://bit.ly/ctWIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming Film Draws Luminaries: Movie stars, politicians and environmentalists were expected on the green.. http://bit.ly/9RVXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama: Government to Set Global Warming Example: President Barack Obama wants the federal government to set the.. http://bit.ly/17Xf4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reenergise Yourself With The Power of Mantras from http://handicraft.indiamart.com/products/religiousproducts/mantras.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Contemporary Sofa Sets from http://bit.ly/Ff8k9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panamera: New Luxury Car By Porsche from http://bit.ly/34NWUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Availability of H1N1 Vaccine Under Scanner: A new survey carried out by researchers at the Harvard School of Pu.. http://bit.ly/264qQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Search For Dark Energy Begins: Scientists will measure the spectra of a thousand galaxies and quasars.
Th.. http://bit.ly/pToyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsunami Hit Indonesia, Samoa: Is Oregon Next?: The powerful earthquake and deadly tsunami that struck the Samoa.. http://bit.ly/w8rl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Sprint New Electric Two Wheeler From Hero Honda from http://bit.ly/wIfrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Look of Kawasaki Ninja 250R from http://bit.ly/vfkgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect Jewelry For Your Neck from http://handicraft.indiamart.com/products/jewellery/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Threat Increases As Gulf Hurricanes Get Larger: Tornadoes that occur from hurricanes moving inland from.. http://bit.ly/28UDba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Garbage The Solution To Tackling Climate Change?: Converting the rubbish that fills the world’s landfills in.. http://bit.ly/PvTuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Could 4 Degree Warming Mean For The World?: A leading climate scientist has presented new research finding.. http://bit.ly/1Vmth4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combining Sun, Sand And Science In The Bahamas: It is well known that people from all over the world come to th.. http://bit.ly/2NEXEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valuable Sofa Sets For Home Furnishing from http://bit.ly/Ff8k9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glass Painting For Your Drawing Room from http://bit.ly/7wQVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supertyphoons to Strike Japan Due to Global Warming: Increasingly powerful &#8220;supertyphoons&#8221; will str.. http://bit.ly/JyV9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tropical Trees Cool Earth Most Effectively: Planting a tree for Earth Day may do more good if you live in Bueno.. http://bit.ly/8GnzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford Figo Another Hatchback From Fords from http://bit.ly/QkYB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Images of Jupiter&#8217;s Red Spots: Astronomers from the University of California, Berkeley, and the W. M. .. http://bit.ly/rU4Yt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Images of Jupiter’s Red Spots from http://bit.ly/P22eP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Exclusive Look of Karizma ZMR FI from http://bit.ly/1rUwAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envrionment Inventory Reporthttp://bit.ly/1Sxf37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming Could Cool America in a Few Decades? http://bit.ly/b6sUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essential Barwares For Your Home Bar from http://bit.ly/2DPtQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2009 U.S. Greenhouse Gas Inventory Report: INVENTORY OF U.S. GREENHOUSE GAS EMISSIONS AND SINKS: 1990-2007
(Apri.. http://bit.ly/185NP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wide Range of Stainless Steel Kitchenware from http://bit.ly/1BHCGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review & First Look of Land Rover FreeLander 2  from http://bit.ly/xRFjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent Garden Bench For Your Garden from http://bit.ly/yjwyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quilted Wall Hanging Patterns from http://bit.ly/2E0l0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling And Land Reuse Practices Can Help Fight Climate Change: There is much potential to reduce the nation&#.. http://bit.ly/uyCqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobiles Could Be Harming Crops Too: Mobile phones have grabbed the headlines for a number of unpleasant reasons,.. http://bit.ly/kRVau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World&#8217;s Oceans Warmest On Record This Summer: Sea-surface temperatures worldwide have been the hottest on .. http://bit.ly/ZgQgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Look of New Yamaha VMAX Motorcycle from http://bit.ly/2vU0a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Facts About Yamaha VMAX from http://bit.ly/M8kMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portable And Precise Gas Sensor Could Monitor Pollution And Detect Disease: In the air, it is a serious pollutan.. http://bit.ly/18OB6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Officials Offer Tips To Stave Off Flu: In response to a growing number of reported cases of swine flu on .. http://bit.ly/2o8Pu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tree Cheers For Our Environment?: Nature can be the biggest ally in our fight against climate change, that’s the.. http://bit.ly/2RboRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oldest Writing Material Which Also Exist Today from http://bit.ly/qVehH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explore Indian Handicraft Industry from http://bit.ly/3c5K7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe Dolls For Your Toddler from http://bit.ly/GEWBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religious Products For This Navratri from http://handicraft.indiamart.com/products/religiousproducts/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Valuable Nautical Instrument from http://bit.ly/TSfre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Valuable Nautical Instrument from http://bit.ly/WzSRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acrylic Smoking Pipes For Your Style from http://bit.ly/4EIaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Varieties of Decorative Items from http://bit.ly/13vBQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colorful & Trendy, Tie & dye Fashion Apparels - http://bit.ly/Z6fhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep Your Special Memories In Photo Frames from http://bit.ly/3cjLGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Look of Mahindra Rodeo Scooter from http://bit.ly/ECFQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming Could Cool N. America in a Few Decades?: Global warming could actually chill down North America w.. http://bit.ly/trOUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Guide to Cell Phone Radiation: Over 4 billion people in the world have cell phones. They’re handy, portable,.. http://bit.ly/1q3FhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killer Whales Die Without King Salmon: Some killer whale populations favor king salmon so much that the whales w.. http://bit.ly/15AZ4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovered: First Rocky Planet Outside Our Solar System: The confirmation of the nature of CoRoT-7b as the first.. http://bit.ly/KNRZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tingling and Glistening - Wind Chimes for Your Home: http://bit.ly/ZFKGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Look of Yamaha 2009 VMAX from http://bit.ly/JzbPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aluminum Crafts For Your Home Decoration from http://bit.ly/4l4cy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encourages Recreation By Hanging Lanterns : http://bit.ly/1kHnOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shahid Kapoor Buys New Range Rover 2010 from http://bit.ly/2DLfEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expand Length Of An Antique Bed from http://bit.ly/2Hcx59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essentials For A Luxurious Bathroom Setting from http://bit.ly/2EvoTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Wallpapers Of New Royal Enfield Bullet Classic 500 from http://bit.ly/jo1ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Official Look Of New Range Rover 2010 Model From http://bit.ly/3B0phH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style Your Home With Exuberant Thanksgiving Decorations ! from http://bit.ly/k4QTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Look Of New Honda CR-V from http://bit.ly/2arjTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Look Of New Honda CR-V from http://bit.ly/lQ4bH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decor Your Home With Beaded Lamp Shade from http://bit.ly/O4le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All New Stylish Bajaj XCD Bike from http://bit.ly/15DZ1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Popular Small Cars in India from http://bit.ly/2z8lpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything You Need For A Well-lit Space from http://bit.ly/1gL5BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way of Water Conservation: Our ancient religious texts and epics give a good insight into the water storage and cons... http://bit.ly/3mFlRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Aluminum Lighting Fixture Parts from http://bit.ly/1w31s5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strike A Chord With Personalized Gifts This Thanksgiving  by http://bit.ly/cQq3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galileo&#8217;s Notebooks May Reveal Secrets Of New Planet: Galileo knew he had discovered a new planet in 1613.. http://bit.ly/44cBKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robot Armada Might Scale New Worlds: 
An armada of robots may one day fly above the mountain tops of Saturn&#82.. http://bit.ly/9gx10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outdoor Hanging Lanterns by http://bit.ly/1kHnOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanksgiving Dinner Table Decorations from http://bit.ly/SZO4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting Halloween Home Crafts and Decoration Ideas from http://bit.ly/39i3kZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Garden Lanterns Effectivey? from http://bit.ly/ECgQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing The Right Color For Your Room from http://bit.ly/3UTNMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aesthetic Handmade Paper Stationary For Your Workplace http://bit.ly/4BxjaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style Your Homes With Halloween Decoration Crafts from http://bit.ly/2hnXL3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>