<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[everyone politely clapping so their country isn't added to the list #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i needed this out of my head https://t.co/i3jEAl1Y2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is rife with factual inaccuracies #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triplebozzmun I'm genuinely angry that he might not get relegated this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyroneLewis22 *follows your bot*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lleuadau: opened a DM picture from a man expecting it to be a dick pic but it was a poem, which is somehow worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick How dare you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving More Robbie in action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAO @strongmisgiving https://t.co/WTeLVheSbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched all the Police Academy movies for £25, so the bar is low here. https://t.co/R9y538Vvx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate There is an argument against this but it involves spoilers for infinity war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate @Neil_Syme ...go on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate Miles and Loki?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esp0ntaneo The volume they yell abuse at can't help either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakingfiction A lot of Doctor Who, most recently Donna and Bill with the Doctor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the worst Rowling retcon yet. https://t.co/uAdurbAIMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InterrobangEdin: Today's your last opportunity to help @poetryasfuck and @InterrobangEdin go all #teamscot1977 at @SabotageReviews' #sa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @isthismusic: Worrying news, please RT https://t.co/bSsEgPIgrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryGiles @strongmisgiving @davepoems I will look into this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @davepoems The ambient music will be me singing "do you wanna buy a mattress?" To the tune of do you wanna build a snowman but slowed down 5000%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems Challenge accepted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a baller move terfs are now claiming you are transphobic if you disagree with them https://t.co/TTicbqWQSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @naxuu: i am become jimmy, eater of worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg I tweet with an encyclopaedia next to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg God did jamiroquai make it that far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this lad has been told there are wasps in the guitar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg Better than an actual love child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOND THEME 
#eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lokster71 Once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone said Eurovision was moribund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind you I'm still not over the end of Brooklyn 99 series 4, so might not be the best judge of these things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still not recovered from macedonia's decision to splice an absolute banger with sub UB40 nausea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davepoems: Hey poetry pals! If you're voting, could you vote for Jade Cuttle for Best Reviewer? She's an excellent critic, and just sta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tkingdot: https://t.co/bwUFJnDu40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine i write human poems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: The Ambassador's Reception needs your votes @poetryasfuck @InterrobangEdin https://t.co/N37NdRBIjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving And a moving tribute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it me https://t.co/dmnV1LPWC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cubmoth: What if Pokémon were just men? https://t.co/w7VarHwCPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Freeyourmindkid: Retweet this if you aren't black but you think that America needs to discuss it's past and current atrocities against…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacPoet Would recommend the novella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacPoet Big finish and a malorie Blackman novella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacPoet This has genuinely been done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor Who pitch: #notalldaleks - a lone Dalek argues that it isn't responsible for the behaviour of all the other Daleks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InterrobangEdin: Wanna see a #Sabawards18-winning show @hiddendoorarts this year? Here's what to do:
1. Go here 👇 and vote for our coll…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving la papa podría ser rebanada y frita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruthie_why Dental too. But we only hear the winner's side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruthie_why Saruman takes care of his orcforce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruthie_why Do you have a headcanon for orcs knowing what menus are?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josherick3 studio ghibli animate a poetry night using only animals to represent the poets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would watch a studio ghibli film that was just 90 minutes of animals reacting to things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to send it to a serious poetic journal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very moving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[finished a poem for the first time in a while, it's about the sense of relief when you order too hot a curry and finish shitting yourself the next morning #writingprompt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving has there ever been a flashmob projectile boaking before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alex_c_lee: Extremely fucking stupid of the Blues Brothers to hear Aretha Franklin singing in her diner and then not getting her to be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving where is this so I can avoid it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg @periwinklewine K9? I haven't heard that name in a long time...logical extrapolation of living under false identity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine I hope one day the two can be edited together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringo_starrrr And they all have towers where they cut about like Saruman, arms aloft, incanting the shit out of something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please be about robot dogs https://t.co/F7YQKNZYEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @captainrant: Getting death threats. https://t.co/pbvlH8pByH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Josherick3: So. I have a pamphlet! 

It has a website - https://t.co/YuymRz2sFR

It's launching on May 24th at @Lighthousebks - https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving just a conversation someone had at the vape shop ross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aeonofdiscord ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therubykid thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeah alright then
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[salted caramel
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what do you have
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'shrek'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'used harp salesman leaves eton empty handed'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'glenn hoddle discreetly using a disabled toilet'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'age at which you think you've stopped fucking up but here we are again'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'ending of infinity war'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'we don't know where the blanket came from but they won't let go'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'Jose Mourinho at 5am'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'pick up the flowers, stare at nothing, put down the flowers'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'wet dream in a hostel dorm'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'never held their hands again?'
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'Jose Mourinho at 4am'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'reflections on the phrase "one that got away"'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Vape Shop:
do you have any 'childhood friends don't follow you back on twitter'?
no
#LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Like morrissey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Christmas carol is hot false imo. There's no way one man could change that much structural inequality by not being a dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Are these a reference to tiny Tim in muppet xmas carol saying "the goose, the  GOOSE"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_kellyQ: A room in every workplace where Stanley Tucci is waiting for you with tough but fair advice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RussellBennetts: band name https://t.co/UuPk6arjlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Restaurants with House Chutney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCKING YES https://t.co/rGcWTqliTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving  https://t.co/fbpdWRjQF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving This explains a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo it gave us this and for this reason alone it is blessed https://t.co/lqdUAZZXMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbrew You are not alone on this, even though I liked a lot of Infinity War. I also enjoyed Thor: Ragnarok more than it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @supermathskid: I just realised if The Incredible Hulk was English he'd be called The Absolute Unit and now I'm sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FKTH Playing aloof geniuses is his bread and butter, just needed a better script]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FKTH At least one and cumberbatch is good for it anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FKTH Wait for the most bankable ones to come back in the next film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jenlikespizza: Sorry but I love this badly phrased memorial bench so much https://t.co/oe6gj6BUEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving On Tuesday]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>