<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have." - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we get too caught up in the busyness of the world we lose connection with one another and ourselves." - Jack Kornfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One sees great things from the valley; only small things from the peak." - G. K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't build a reputation on what you are going to do." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The height of your accomplishments will equal the depth of your convictions." - William F. Scholavino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Give your dreams all you've got and you'll be amazed at the energy that comes out of you." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some men see things as they are and ask why. Others dream things that never were and ask why not." - George Bernard Shaw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is in the heart, not in the circumstances." - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is achieved by development of our strengths, not by elimination of our weakness." - Marilyn Vos Savant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing we learn in this world is ever wasted." - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never mistake activity for achievement." - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must be the change we wish to see in the world." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And no one will listen to us until we listen to ourselves." - Marianne Williamson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A good leader takes a little more than his share of the blame, a little less than his share of the credit." - Arnold Glasow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Attitude is a little thing that makes a big difference." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The noblest search is the search for excellence." - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The key to the ability to change is a changeless sense of who you are, what you are about and what you value." - Stephen R. Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are all born originals - why is it so many of us die copies?" - Edward Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing - that's why we recommend it daily." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great effort springs naturally from a great attitude." - Pat Riley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To accomplish great things, we must not only act, but also dream; not only plan, but also believe." - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you think education is expensive, try ignorance." - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I quote others I do so in order to express my own ideas more clearly." - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cleverness is not wisdom." - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ability to simplify means to eliminate the unnecessary so that the necessary may speak."   - Hans Hofmann]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't build a reputation on what you are going to do." -  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude." -  Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy that makes happiness." - Charles Sprugeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Improvement begins with I." - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of success is consistency of purpose." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rather than wishing for change, you first must be prepared to change." - Catherine Pulsifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Age is whatever you think it is. You are as old as you think you are." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is amazing what you can accomplish if you do not care who gets the credit." - Harry S Truman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing that interferes with my learning is my education." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn't do than by the things you did. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You accomplish victory step by step, not by leaps and bounds." - Lyn St. James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People demand freedom of speech to make up for the freedom of thought which they avoid." - Soren Kierkegaard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing much happens without a dream. For something really great to happen, it takes a really great dream." - Robert Greenleaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is always one moment in childhood when the door opens and lets the future in." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen." - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I always prefer to believe the best of everybody; it saves so much trouble." - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is steady progress toward one's personal goals." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody can make you feel inferior without your permission." - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell me and I will forget, show me and I might remember, involve me and I will understand." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Giving up doesn't always mean your weak; sometimes it means you're strong enough to let go." - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't be afraid of the space between your dreams and reality. If you can dream it, you can make it so." - Belva Davis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is the good fortune that comes from aspiration, desperation, perspiration and inspiration." - Evan Esar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are unrepeatable. There is a magic about you that is all your own..." - D.M. Dellinger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nurture your mind with great thoughts. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never discourage anyone.....who continually makes progress, no matter how slow." - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sprinkle joy." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Either you deal with what is the reality or you can be sure that the reality is going to deal with you." - Alex Haley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only real valuable thing is intuition." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most of us are just about as happy as we make up our minds to be." - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything changes when you change." - Jim Rohn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A clear vision, backed by definite plans, gives you a tremendous  feeling of confidence and personal power." - Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're going to be thinking anything, you might as well think big." - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be what you are. This is the first step toward becoming better than you are." - August W. Hare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Vitality shows not only in the ability to persist, but in the ability to start over." - F. Scott Fitzgerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is an obstacle unless you say it is." - Wally Amos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Respect yourself and others will respect you." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I do not like to repeat successes; I like to go on to other things." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest discovery of my generation is that human beings can alter their lives by altering their attitudes of mind." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let a man lose everything else in the world but his enthusiasm and he will come through again to success." - H. W. Arnold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You need to find a way to live your life, that it doesn't make a mockery of your values." - Bill Ayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Goals are like stepping-stones to the stars. They should never be used to put a ceiling or a limit on achievement." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Enjoy the little things, for one day you may look back and realise they were the big things." - Robert Brault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's never too late to be what you might have been." - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whosoever desires constant success must change his conduct with the times." - Niccolo Machiavelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anticipate the difficult by managing the easy." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The person born with a talent they are meant to use will find their greatest happiness in using it." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A lie gets halfway around the world before the truth has a chance to get its pants on." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I dwell in possibility." - Emily Dickinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who hesitates is a damned fool." - Mae West]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is not to be pursued; it is to be attracted by the person you become." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Waste no tears over the grieves of yesterday." - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the midst of winter, I found there was, within me, an invincible summer." - Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now is the time. Needs are great, but your possibilities are greater." - Bill Blackman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is the line of least persistence." - W.A. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want freedom for the full expression of my personality." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Action may not always bring happiness; but there is no happiness without action." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is a bad plan that admits of no modification." - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our intention creates our reality." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great things are not done by impulse, but by a series of small things brought together." - Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man is a success if he gets up in the morning and goes to bed at night and in between does what he wants to do." - Bob Dylan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your attitude is more important that your aptitude." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Four steps to achievement: Plan purposefully. Prepare prayerfully. Proceed positively. Pursue persistently." - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All that glitters is not gold." - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make a mistake." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we have learned from others becomes our own reflection." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things which matter most must never be at the mercy of things which matter least." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If it fails, admit it frankly and try another. But above all, try something." - Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is nature's plan to prepare you for great responsibilities." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If your ship doesn't come in, swim out to it." - Jonathan Winters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Words are only painted fire; a book is the fire itself." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most delightful surprise in life is to suddenly recognise your own worth." - Maxwell Maltz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We build too many walls and not enough bridges." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>