<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[‘What is a Robot, Anyway?’ https://t.co/MSX4PT0pfg

With that question, Adrienne LaFrance launches into a fascinat… https://t.co/UIQ8ByyFFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Openings on the Rise https://t.co/NJ2VWD3ZTb

The Bureau of Labor Statistics’ monthly report on job openings a… https://t.co/O41fwI7JOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Retirees Should Work? Then Hire Them! https://t.co/7uSMFl3bw7

Charles Hughes at the Cato Institute, a liber… https://t.co/Ier1Nzu0OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Build a “we not me” culture where change happens fasts https://t.co/Bv7kNw82FI https://t.co/I6sEPy3p8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to transform the traditional performance review process https://t.co/plRZX5CnwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Flexibility the Secret to Overcoming the Gender Pay Gap? https://t.co/eLwqOMDH0M

Some members of Parliament in… https://t.co/xqH3mrOqtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick Takes: HR’s Individualized Future? https://t.co/GNvDH5JJX1 

In a post at HRE Online debriefing from a meeti… https://t.co/GJQV0Hb9qo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Insider’s Edge in CEO Recruiting https://t.co/A7QYnxziFp

Earlier this month, Joann Lublin reported for the Wa… https://t.co/LHLCBejjzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Do You Stand on Standing Desks? https://t.co/gS0DshWKDg

In an article at Personnel Today on how employers c… https://t.co/UfcGARcIGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_TlntMonitor: Listen to @briankropp's podcast for a deep dive on labor market trends &amp; guidance for talent-focused executives https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paying Less for ‘Women’s Work’—Whatever that Work May Be https://t.co/Je9a2Ion0A

Those who still contend that the… https://t.co/2gpHAr7APS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Think About Talent and the Next Recession https://t.co/OiZ19cNWGW

Will there be a recession in the United … https://t.co/pxPMK5JoRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MA is the New BA—Or Maybe It’s Just A Competitive Job Market https://t.co/TWP1XpfV9v

A recent survey from Car… https://t.co/PhGSgqxsdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC: Amazon Should Put Pay Gap Resolution on Ballot https://t.co/q6wLbFRYsI

Arjuna Capital, the activist arm of i… https://t.co/c9EvtdR9id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diversity Apps Are Great, but They Don’t Catch Everyone https://t.co/QdZB8bXfoJ

Sherrell Dorsey at The Root shine… https://t.co/2D8xRZzKPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parental Leave: The Tech Sector’s Pride and Joy https://t.co/Z3Vmbm3fsF

Technology and online service companies h… https://t.co/ql6gm7pNeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is There a Cure for ‘Diversity Fatigue’? https://t.co/cZGQvgRtZJ

In a recent article in The Economist, columnist … https://t.co/JIQD6Elu7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NLRB: Chipotle Must Rehire Employee Who Tweeted About Low Pay https://t.co/QvCgMLm5V6

An administrative law judge… https://t.co/lcBZgDu4aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teamsters Plan to Contest Lyft Settlement https://t.co/woICVTkuaQ

Five Lyft drivers, backed by the Teamsters unio… https://t.co/N1HEEevAPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: “A useful question to pose is what can HR learn from Marketing?"- @BrianKropp #DataAnalytics https://t.co/XLregsOvKx https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fidelity Expands Parental Leave, Adds Student Loan Benefits https://t.co/yiDl1CJwIO

Fidelity Investments has join… https://t.co/qYI7WeT0V3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Uncomfortable Questions HR Is Going to Have to Answer About the New US Overtime Rules https://t.co/NmimoLHQzr 

… https://t.co/ehyHUxyxAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Employers Brace for Living Wage Law https://t.co/IL7hU2FPuY

The UK’s National Living Wage goes into effect on … https://t.co/9fbJUjDY7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Medium Dropped Holacracy https://t.co/yx8qCvgZmJ

Last week, the online publishing platform Medium announced t… https://t.co/liwJSBVW09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etsy Goes All-In on Parental Leave with Gender-Neutral Policy https://t.co/fPGaQr7zNN

The online handicraft retai… https://t.co/m2t859HXPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empowering Employees to Deliver Better Customer Service https://t.co/hTKRPvoFWj

At McKinsey, Dilip Bhattacharjee,… https://t.co/IKSFNn02jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depressing News About Burnout https://t.co/BZ2ICLbVd1

A recent study suggests that burnout may be more closely ti… https://t.co/B2FvuJic8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganiSolutions: A well-written thank you note from a manager has as much of an impact as a cash bonus @briankropp @rzgreenfield https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Would Brexit Mean for Your Organization? https://t.co/byYZYX8T5S

On June 23, British citizens will vote in a… https://t.co/HWSD69clgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mansplaining the Gender Pay Gap https://t.co/qZi1YBVw73

The Cut‘s Dayna Evans is sick and tired of men seeking to… https://t.co/v8n0VrQDmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PwC Accused of Age Discrimination in Recruiting https://t.co/xbPTwh44K1

A lawsuit filed on Wednesday in US federa… https://t.co/HLhl4POqhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennial Maladies https://t.co/9TS3RdCLCo

At Fortune, Katherine Reynolds Lewis explores the rising rates of men… https://t.co/KaBUdMeu4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campbell’s New Parental Leave Policy Is Gender-Neutral, But Not Quite Equal https://t.co/7O6qtQcsGV

Campbell Soup… https://t.co/MJmhw7CicJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving London: A Capital Idea? https://t.co/vtuBqcZPIH

Workforce Insight’s Sara Bean flags a new report from pro… https://t.co/I35Hix0096]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slack and its Bots Are Coming For Your Apps https://t.co/2L1GLnuKYq

Bloomberg’s Jeremy Kahn takes note of the wor… https://t.co/6jqw1Aa4ST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Taking a Stand on Transgender Rights, Target Makes Itself a Target https://t.co/mLQLG4RPFh

The New York Times‘… https://t.co/2aJHtKEhIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can India Handle a Billion Workers? https://t.co/MEYvZqWIZu

The United Nations Development Program estimates that… https://t.co/FE05ZR4twA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Not About Millennials, It’s About Company Strategy https://t.co/GBq4u1oSFD

My colleague Matt Dunn made a goo… https://t.co/CpbluaZkhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching Top Talent By Setting Them Loose https://t.co/3SeNDuITIe

In an effort to retain the best and brightest o… https://t.co/ihGLyJLmvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chobani CEO Will Give Stakes to His Employees https://t.co/Nqeto0Maos

Hamdi Ulukaya, the CEO of yogurt-maker Chob… https://t.co/PO6BSnCXeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Doesn’t Want What Millennials Want? https://t.co/MmdXTzxeSV

Much has been made of the supposedly unique prefe… https://t.co/IbJTX6vo83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Cuts Contract Recruiters as Revenue Drops Off https://t.co/Lx0cXwBM6s

In its second-quarter earnings report… https://t.co/TMAkgPLtti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If the ‘Gig Economy’ Is Just a Part-Time Economy? https://t.co/ASjwmEIH6A

The US labor market has been sendi… https://t.co/GANStzkm4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Penguin Random House UK, Ditching Degree Requirements Is Part of Broader Recruiting Shakeup … https://t.co/cb8wCqBhWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Case for Socioeconomic Diversity https://t.co/48ALw1z601

Marah Lidey argues at Quartz that it’s long past tim… https://t.co/sPG0MzRwVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuition Reimbursement Pays Off for Cigna https://t.co/EvXrFq3NLA

We know that student loan benefits are a major b… https://t.co/PSoe1jvJEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Lessons in Googler Grievances https://t.co/AQyTlelegu

Google is generally considered a great place to wo… https://t.co/cJX4rpPJsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Do You Want to Know About Your Employees’ Fertility? https://t.co/hsNabWSZ49

Privacy concerns are a majo… https://t.co/IB6U01CKJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Skills the German Way https://t.co/KEr7q8vWRL

At Fast Company, Katherine Newman and Hella Winston discus… https://t.co/90WH7UQrjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Issues Zika Guidelines for Employers https://t.co/HqrvN4MlZ0

The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention… https://t.co/fn98N7plcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mostly Good News for the Class of 2016 https://t.co/XwT6SklkHQ

CareerBuilder says this year’s batch of college gr… https://t.co/fPzzNoOrxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Wants New Rules on Wall Street Bonuses to Curb Risky Behavior https://t.co/kMExzPHyDf

US regulators proposed n… https://t.co/bhQ5MvcQzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber Agrees to Settle Driver Lawsuits for $100M, Deferring Reclassification https://t.co/jFvXHVvfpf

The rideshare… https://t.co/HcGSw6vz9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shared Parental Leave Turns One Year Old https://t.co/GHnpHJtNe3

The UK’s Shared Parental Leave policy, enacted a… https://t.co/kyowZH0G8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gig Economy: Fact or Fad? https://t.co/EW5X3uxcjJ

Writing at HRE Online, Peter Cappelli questions whether the… https://t.co/sv6FCJ24Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading the Labor Market’s Tea Leaves https://t.co/cdtXgf68Cz

Jobless claims fell last week to their lowest level… https://t.co/B1avEFCkwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schilling’s Last Straw: Why ESPN Finally Fired Him https://t.co/E9bnfDxfeb

ESPN baseball analyst and former major… https://t.co/IlMKIVxuaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lies, Damned Lies, and Résumés https://t.co/uSWoUwEgHH

Anne Fisher at Fortune highlights a new survey of 3,500 em… https://t.co/SqBYM3qWoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Downside of Downsizing https://t.co/Uk9FmyGQiv

An interesting article at KnowledgeWharton makes a case agains… https://t.co/dJK8JVy16Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s Employers Are Over the Bell Curve https://t.co/CmoWQ3nQRT

India’s largest IT services company, Tata Consu… https://t.co/iouabnROxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsider CEOs Are Becoming More Popular https://t.co/Q2Kd6wfpCj

In general, large organizations tend to prefer in… https://t.co/cIuyk2jUJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Sense of Intel’s Mass Layoffs https://t.co/1vXlcSP5jt

The chip giant announced on Tuesday that it was cutt… https://t.co/QJIjB5IMWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equity in the Talent Equation https://t.co/59DXX75YJY

On Monday we learned that investors are getting nervous abo… https://t.co/cDOiogvDBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hail to the Algorithim: The Wharton People Analytics Conference https://t.co/ZZAPHgkfn9

Earlier this month, I att… https://t.co/3mQBlggNXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second Acts: The Promise and Peril of Returning Founders https://t.co/N2PPYGicVy

Sequels are hard to get right, b… https://t.co/HXoglvu9VL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbiasing the Interview https://t.co/PBj1DshVew

One of the biggest challenges in designing a recruiting process t… https://t.co/o72bpNrE17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Time to Prioritize Career Development https://t.co/diLLfZlL9x https://t.co/eKc7ykBruk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Things to Look Out For as Slack Chases Diversity https://t.co/fe1Uq83FJd

The fast-growing workplace chat st… https://t.co/vVK7vKKsYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young, Scrappy, and Hungry for Profit Sharing https://t.co/W9KAlLMqTa 

A photo posted by Hamilton (hamiltonmusica… https://t.co/Kzt9Fn6y9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Gig Economy for Professional Services? https://t.co/M3XspQc0wn

Boston Globe columnist Scott Kirsner shines a sp… https://t.co/Fps3srySQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Stock Options Bubble in the Tech Sector? https://t.co/lks2oji5Of

In the recent startup boom, tech companies lur… https://t.co/mwfCzWVYSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/M2G1rU7UB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Glassdoor Reviews Protected Speech? https://t.co/v4pC7kvZpc

Writing for SHRM Online, Caryn Freeman looks at a… https://t.co/tOo0DCHJhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Holo-C-Suite https://t.co/NSJ1fzrbyF

Earlier this week, Accenture’s France-based CEO Pierre Nanterme appeared… https://t.co/fr4KORq7o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is ‘Maternity Leave’ an Outdated Term? https://t.co/yCLajsDDZn

The professional services giant Ernst &amp; Young roll… https://t.co/Y42MUqTQUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Spain Goes Siesta-Free, So Goes the World? https://t.co/uYcvyQZmYu

Writing in the Harvard Business Review, Mar… https://t.co/9SS1SnuLnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Company Gives Employees a Half Day Off, Because Game of Thrones https://t.co/IT97Kgmquq 

A creative technology fi… https://t.co/HG4JakQ7kE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a Wellness Program and Promoting Wellness Aren’t Always the Same Thing https://t.co/7cMTJgM5Bd

At the Harv… https://t.co/K0NiUmwDiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Flexible Workers Keep More Calm As They Carry On https://t.co/jtnrpM5muR

A new study from CIPD unpacking the … https://t.co/tPnKwj6gRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent Management and the Rise and Fall of American Growth https://t.co/ZNekOrJbhY

In 2012, we published a study … https://t.co/UzL1cSw4pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Women Fill the Cybersecurity Gap? https://t.co/5DXyY5x7H6

We’ve told you before about the shortage in cyberse… https://t.co/rc7n6gwYdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Silicon Valley Leading on Parental Leave Because of its Woman Problem? https://t.co/JyfcS9OCyf

We know that th… https://t.co/QdfIniEzuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving the Robot Revolution https://t.co/tNesPCoSea

At Fast Company, George Lorenzo interviews Julia Kirby and… https://t.co/TGRwucwwpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials Want Different Experiences, Not Different Jobs https://t.co/0gd5LPmXDV

Studies proclaiming that mille… https://t.co/JR58UN5Vvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life in the Digital Sweatshop https://t.co/xVTIqHO5ys

Drawing on his experience working at HubSpot after 25 years… https://t.co/aOxCOTlxKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the Benefit of Referrals Without the Downside https://t.co/m0XXpeQRaU

Atlantic editor Derek Thompson rece… https://t.co/pcDQHfSeCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Mergers and Acquisitions, ‘Culture’ Doesn’t Trump Strategy; ‘Strategy’ Ignores Culture https://t.co/5dzWFS4zz3
… https://t.co/H5MDhfDJ7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Celebrate: It’s Equal Pay Day https://t.co/0E1Bly0RQX

Today marks Equal Pay Day, a symbolic event marking h… https://t.co/1h0sYbpaRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the conversation and making progress on #genderpayequity https://t.co/PiLdu72TF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[join me as the white house live streams a conference on #equalpayday https://t.co/QzyvMsYsGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Fill Tech Talent Shortage, Companies Aim to Bring Women Back https://t.co/EsS1Oy3kaD

Faced with a shortage of … https://t.co/oNhCILzQ1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The More Health Insurance Changes, the More It Stays the Same… For Now https://t.co/f1mnUR5m7I

Last week, the New… https://t.co/xIbZBTLFcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look Before You Leap Into Extreme Management Philosophies https://t.co/O3CTEqVPy2

Recently, much has been written… https://t.co/1JJ1gdARNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanielPink: A Nobel Prize-winning psychologist shares an important insight about hiring the best people https://t.co/OBriKLQdcA via @bi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Referrals Help Minority Employees Get Ahead https://t.co/zc3QidRckn

Lydia Dishman at Fast Company flags a … https://t.co/n9f2Ah8KOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just How ‘Hot’ Are Student Loan Benefits, Anyway? https://t.co/3L2GySfRRb

Student loan assistance is the hot new … https://t.co/81jHB3lzsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Rejects Lyft Settlement, Says Drivers Deserve More https://t.co/h6gsOdYTQk

In January, Lyft agreed to settl… https://t.co/o6SvD1XwRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Price of Gender Inequality—and What We’d Gain By Fixing It https://t.co/5AhTjZ8YNx

A study released this week… https://t.co/SBkqgrFb8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful Talent Management in the Last Recession (Won’t Look the Same in the Next One) https://t.co/e39CPREOIS

… https://t.co/zN2gmaJNQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wage Stagnation Is No Illusion https://t.co/npPDm7IqSJ

In a piece at the Atlantic on why the US economic recovery… https://t.co/vqfGtsc701]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>