<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In Obama's last state of the union no mention of how bad things truly are today. David Simon was right all along. https://t.co/vxKZwV5Zjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the US media won't cover. https://t.co/7ngubhj2Cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of his books would have been published today.  We as humans no longer can be truthful to ourselves. https://t.co/uBwcchOKti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After games, soccer players bitch about the referees, while rugby players head for the pub so they can sing rugby... https://t.co/3BxGM0sLF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReedsyHQ: Take a Peek Inside Neil Gaiman's Library: https://t.co/QUzqUrmj0w https://t.co/7BXaNkfJ6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/g3NPGrsE7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michele Palazzo's Photograph of the NYC Winter Storm Looks Like an Impressionist Painting https://t.co/soZ9z9bHwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pcSlwnHi5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I support Bernie Sanders, and I'm not stupid or unrealistic https://t.co/hoIw39yJlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vtXJZxynB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3iBHAIJk2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My lovely home town under a blanket of snow. Colorado now the 3rd highest economy in the U.S. and a blue state. https://t.co/jzOIxyd6KM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One catastrophic mistake after another across the country ...now the country is in economic free-fall. https://t.co/DNUtbFvnI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2ZfPic7DhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time you're  confronted by a self-righteous and prudent nag... https://t.co/UmbzQ4nqmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GSSFrtffQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb financial reporting. https://t.co/lkgGLWVW16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise and fall of Kevin O'Leary's business career https://t.co/lkPsfizHKz via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden boy investment guru Kevin O'Leary unmasked as a failed dragon. https://t.co/7XWL3RA1su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sRkOdSFfEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/b9bOos6aww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/D0EUSn1F9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce sang it, U2 backed up in a tribute to the woman who wrote it. https://t.co/YTKXgFIjnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patti Smith sing George Harrison's Within and Without You https://t.co/XrQ9SIkZXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tavis Smiley, Patti Smith interrview, amazing: Tuesday, 12/21 https://t.co/1cKyz3mx6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing interview between Patti Smith and Tavis Smiley https://t.co/qEQnce5Sph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahWestMusic Leah, good grief, you've put Kelowna on the map, I bet.  I want to hear your song and story. It's the water, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beach Mike. https://t.co/8ezqPnK6LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generous compensation...as if... https://t.co/n8HzrJDGvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fMyKtX0Psa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've stopped everything to help ordinary people... Stop this. https://t.co/7hOWavtPgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/iiIRv5UNur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brand I was a stereotype, a cliche, then a meme, and a trope, now I am a Brand !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glenn Frey was the heart of the Eagles music. https://t.co/UT1VsFjZxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This savage weather has made this Saxon hungry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dstevens_author A high concept thriller if he is alive. Maybe she is not so glad to see him alive? A sexy thriller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kylo Ren  the Underground Boss https://t.co/CXLlLYm3ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those voting for Hillary will be disappointed not to see a woman as president in this election. The first... https://t.co/xWJXZeqoSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haunting look back to another idiot Republican running for President. https://t.co/U5yuLD9BkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to defy gravity in life. https://t.co/0OKLIUpigE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alvin Lee and 10 years After stole every show from the headliners. RIP. Another rocker gone. https://t.co/EiXQYYkfUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/r3lmlC3KJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cguXrErCP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump beauty secrets unmasked https://t.co/cz9tmvrneZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make your face great again with this amazing "Trumping" makeup tutorial https://t.co/q6GDCttSrq via @HuffPostComedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Power of Showing Up is Important." on @LinkedIn https://t.co/zgsZrcTrXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's American Psycho Patrick Bateman lurks on Wall Street with Twitter and social media https://t.co/9lLfzlnGme via @TandCmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Patrick Bateman is lurking on Wall Street, even more narcissistic and sordid despite his billions. He... https://t.co/wNsnbtqmXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinorRefusals Do you make house calls where]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Does Donald Trump Hate You? https://t.co/TjHUeF4Xfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget building a wall to keep the Yanks out..... https://t.co/iNficaltpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her cat is not into scat, but she can sing to me anytime. https://t.co/1wWULj7lku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/77uYfs411Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gKzbgvwYTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#makedonalddrumpfagain https://t.co/8TTlMPgScO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HihNmNA268]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa I sent you a short message on hangouts about my thoughts on the Oscars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6z8zVFYFdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Tower in Vancouver is now the Maple Leaf Mall, eh. https://t.co/niv3Ppzu9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Amazon falls we are left with Monsanto. https://t.co/eUYuwhq7BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zgbZ1U75XO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nice chat. https://t.co/5O3qdjf7Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP knows that Obama will claim the high road once again and choose oratory over action, reluctant to be the... https://t.co/LiqbKM7rvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have met and we're on Twitter https://t.co/BUYL5qQbsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need Jackie ! https://t.co/guunkWE0Ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuck in gridlock? Examine your choices. https://t.co/9TRW12ohVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Donald fixes all sports. https://t.co/wtQgt65pnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kinder, more gentle Carnival greeted revelers this year. https://t.co/ty9YI1s0aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible honor to the Boss https://t.co/sEmwma8MW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Brazilian painter has caught fire. https://t.co/Kaaf3brknU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait!  Your friends have nothing in common with our friends. https://t.co/VHlGbLp3Qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yi1NfK4jc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We interrupt your blatant stupidity with an important message. https://t.co/VAmK00E1Ee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heavens are orange crush and blue! https://t.co/w4LVPNNFgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pJzE4CHK9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bern feels your enthusiasm... but just not too close. https://t.co/7d8bpXhCGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Income inequality drives joblessness and income disparity. https://t.co/H68vRGIGiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when your life suddenly changes... https://t.co/iT857zVqi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1CWRxLMgnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie is not all he says he is. Now he wants to be President. https://t.co/4zllS0TBbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KSOP93dydV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gona miss you Merle. An original https://t.co/WmZYyPyXYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly leading edge animation merged with historic footage. https://t.co/5dqwgAGG8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A judge's amazing teaching moment in a courtroom. https://t.co/bfN90f19mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a film student I sat in on a full day of editing at Zoetrope in San Francisco to watch the  mix of what later... https://t.co/4YUuLzWUf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HQH0NRjtMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qxFbWZ4uF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa  Jon Krackauer is the one who exposed the scandal. First read the book, then read Krackauer's expose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa by all means give me a call SK. Enjoy the meeting tonite. This is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa we still on for tomorrow? With Catherine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Mexicans won 't pay for Trump's wall. https://t.co/vUZJk77E5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mCJGRLXztP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Proposes Building Wall Inside Uterus https://t.co/AUfGXkvmBg via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2YVU5PHdYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myself and my wife met Tenzing Norgay in 1977, a major thrill to meet this great hero.  Bottom line, the only... https://t.co/aHWcCwLRqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only did drug kingpin El Chopo put a $150 million bounty on Donald Trump's orange head, but now the Brujería... https://t.co/OOyUWkD62G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My amigos climbed Popo, and two others, which most of the time are dormant. Not today. https://t.co/H7f3UA2uS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ETphRpZKIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A short course in subprime. https://t.co/uoweBqy8ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For decades so many young people ask the same question: 
What should I be doing with my life? 

The answer is... https://t.co/18hIenDFw8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>