<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/iWRyG8x2k1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/3H1rymBDiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/dXmKvNKbFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/ClQ1WFedoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/CZCbljkMq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/d0rvKd3JTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/Cwzl1ewQh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/zQQifF2ObP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/JkacCTSLQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/WZYxx2hvmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/ZPMDYnUqeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/LUlSN9kMlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/wbXSZ9B8YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/y9Kpwr6TvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BZrc2YgBSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/W9LUTOIfVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/bhxpIsviRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/N9nnYyFRNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/yNBxZMED92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/IrMuTkFU2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/4krg4Zhhj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/sH2P25Ehwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/xx98Ez6MDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/2dKlawHUOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/9087R1EViy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/eoAYAG3hUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/SKt763qnHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/SzhMv4fyWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/a7JJIBCh0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/Cwm1iZRkvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/kdolNJCZ2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/gqdXBgPEbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/0zOyvXYkxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/85PJAsxlga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/lOppYEYwpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/bLJiV4uZef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/kjns8AB23i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/zjaMicXym1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/C3a9AxOY47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/ZpDPvSDpZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/Z6b5q3ceEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/3lHUdinLMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/Z3TNex3adH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Dog Breeds - theband4: http://t.co/UXbhhgOjY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 20 Cat Breeds - theband4: http://t.co/0SJEAw1RYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/WJ0d5nai22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/TG3Du4gwfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/HBGpnmrKuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/gvRdCP7f3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/ZCXosaUoN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/Cwm1iZRkvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/pjkvxInlda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/dYbC2ierY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/aJmVCGcGzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/CP5xFU4slz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to roll a hard six. Commander William Adama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/EraGVQQyP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>