<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can products with higher levels of #sugar still be labeled as #healthy? One lawsuit against @MDLZ says no: https://t.co/mnUygViSfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person in control of your brand, is not you .... it is the consumer, and here is what you need to know: https://t.co/v67fpj5Gzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you couldn't make it to Chicago last week for #FoodVision, find out what you missed: https://t.co/WbPYeO0XUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA guidance outlines how companies can identify appropriate experts for GRAS notification panels: https://t.co/it6GRnA2kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is tight in California for new olive trees as demand for almonds grows https://t.co/ZRei5vXaTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: Who owns/controls/defines your brand? You, or your consumers? asks Linda Eatherton from @KetchumPR @FoodVisionEvent in C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enzymatic browning in juice is a turnoff, but @CocaColaCo has found a natural solution https://t.co/FsRmMpdn8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturated fat as a selling point? @JacksonsHonest is giving it a go: https://t.co/3X1iD4lksF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Milkadamia move into the chilled section of Walmart substantially boosts brand's footprint https://t.co/z4KVV2Fwym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is next for monkfruit and Stevia? https://t.co/kf4b4tusN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OrganicTrade is taking USDA to court over delayed #organic animal welfare rule https://t.co/C0ZRo8YowM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much are Americans really willing to pay for olive oil? https://t.co/ZRei5vFA1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover how Green-Go Cactus water from an idea to an in-demand brand among Millennials https://t.co/xx8OexrpnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthy #snacks are set to grow at a compound annual growth rate 5.1% this year: https://t.co/erQcKgaEci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My husband gave me this as a welcome home gift from #foodvision. @UptonsNaturals @TheJackfruitCo I need help! #jackfruit https://t.co/A8k8z2D53Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thinking about switching to #organic farming but worry the premium price might fall -- do not fear. It will be there for at least 15-20 yrs https://t.co/n0xzzumITE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChameleonCoffee promises to remain true to its roots and values as it sells to @NestleUSA https://t.co/CQ2ZJefp3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toasting the success of #FoodVision https://t.co/wgiOodOgBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is Post's efforts to remake @PowerBar going over with c-store buyers? https://t.co/oKLKwAQ6cS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are pork rinds healthier than potato chips? https://t.co/fWd8CRdd9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: A MASSIVE thank you to the fabulous speakers @FoodVisionEvent in Chicago! #FoodVision @Chobani @HamptonCreek @sirkensing…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: A MASSIVE thank you to the fabulous speakers @FoodVisionEvent in Chicago! #FoodVision @FarmersFridge @GeltorInc @SunBask…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the growth opportunities for natural sweeteners? https://t.co/kf4b4tM4bG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out why USDA delayed #organic animal welfare rule, again, despite industry wishes: https://t.co/C0ZRo8YowM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumption of California olive oil is on the rise. Find out why: https://t.co/ZRei5vFA1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What sets Green-Go Cactus water apart from the competition is its youthful approach: https://t.co/xx8OexJ0fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take to make a crunchy cassava chip? Find out what works and what doesn't from Plant Snacks exec: https://t.co/erQcKgaEci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move over corn, there is new competition from cassava in the #snack place says Plant Snacks exec https://t.co/erQcKgaEci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CivilEats: “We continue to pay too much to the wrong people to grow the wrong food in the wrong places,”- @repblumenauer.  Today, the O…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eatwellglobal: Only half of trips to supermarkets in the US include produce purchases #CelebratingFRESH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#transparency standards for food and beverages will tighten in 2018 predicts @WholeFoods https://t.co/CO7NGRp7Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are lawsuits alleging companies are misleading consumers w HPP claims 'grasping at straws'? https://t.co/S3qXYEwez1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is oatmeal or yogurt a better breakfast bet? @PowerfulYogurt is counting on both: https://t.co/cfaR3evdvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WineRayZyn turns the tragedy of California wildfires into an opportunity to help &amp; grow https://t.co/zEtJFx3Nza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the biggest opportunities in frozen food? @acosta weighs in: https://t.co/kZgPwFBhVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quarter of @PeapodDelivers consumers are boomers and older -- debunks myth that only young people order food online #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brick and mortar grocery stores are working 'very very hard ' to maintain share says CMO of @PeapodDelivers says at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodVisionEvent: .@CarriePeapodCMO discussed why e-grocers need to focus on more than the
transaction... https://t.co/48FrzmwMOe #FoodV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US #organic farmers are finally cycling past rotational crops, meaning large commodities like corn &amp; soy will be more available https://t.co/n0xzzumITE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodVisionEvent: How clean is your label? Join @gregfleishman @HartmanGroup @foodstirs and @CCDInnovation to find out! #FoodVision #cle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product launches w stevia have grown from 637 in 2011 to 3,300 projected in 2017 says @purecircle at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dairyreporter: SVP of @HartmanGroup: The term 'organic' has become a bit tarnished b/c consumers have seen organic proliferate into jun…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: What does 'premium' mean today?
In a nutshell: 
- Non premium: Legacy brand
- Premium: No legacy branding, 
according…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevia is 400x sweeter than sugar so can be used to cut calories.  It also has strong sustainability story according to @purecircle at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premium is only 9% of total food and bev industry but it has grown 10% yoy over past decade and could double in next 10 yrs says Balanko w @HartmanGroup at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38% of consumers say they are buying more local than a yr ago says Balanko w @HartmanGroup at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers want natural food but don't want the claim on pack w 50% knowing term is not regulated says Balanko w @HartmanGroup at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top ingredients consumers are avoiding include sodium (57%), soda (56%), saturated fat (55%), says Balanko w @HartmanGroup at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[75% of consumers want heart healthy products,  68% want local, 65% want fortified says Balanko w @HartmanGroup at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to help American's eat more fruits and veggies? Make it easier for them then, just like Eat Smart and Frill have done: https://t.co/oy16KxDrwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Importing #avocados from Mexico is a boon for the US economy -- adding $2.2b and increasing labor income by $1.2b https://t.co/uewdxwEPJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#plantbased foods have their own standard and don't have to be compared to animal products to find value, @FieldRoast exec says https://t.co/SOWx0kZYjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodVisionEvent: 'There's been much, too much, innovation. We believe less is more," says Tim Brown, COO @Chobani #foodvision https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On average Americans eat 33 lbs of lettuce a yr making it the no. 1 seller in produce. Tomatoes are no. 2 at 12 lbs a yr. #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CampbellSoupCo  predicts 38% CAGR for online sales of food and beverage from 2016-21 to $6 billion #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CaitlinPlankRD: Brands have decided to take risks, suspect FDA won’t have capacity to enforce, calling things by what consumers want i.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodVisionEvent: What have been your key highlights so far? Send us your pictures and videos of your favourite speakers #FoodVision #hi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CaitlinPlankRD: Nutrition Panel with representatives from PepsiCo: “Science based guidelines driving our criteria for nutrition renovat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: Transparency in the food industry: “It’s not just about what’s the science behind it, but how to make it relevant to c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ardier: PepsiCo wants consumers to associate its name with nutrition. 

“We have a responsibility to make good and nutritious food,” sa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transparency to @CampbellSoupCo means explaining on https://t.co/rATL27H95n why each ingredient is used in its products even the unpopular ones #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Real food' means different things to different ppl. To @CampbellSoupCo it means food that they are proud to serve, has roots and prepared w care #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beveragedaily: 'We have to be thinking about categories outside of beverages to deliver the nutritional benefits of fruits &amp; vegetables…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChameleonCoffee promises bold innovation, while maintaining quality of core products, w @NestleUSA's help: https://t.co/CQ2ZJefp3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#protein, flavors, clean labels and functional benefits top the wishlist for c-stores https://t.co/oKLKwAyuOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do pork rinds stack up against jerky? https://t.co/fWd8CQVCip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @purecircle: We're excited to hear @FoodNavigatorUS’ @ECrawfordwrites speak about the plant-based movement this morning. @FoodVisionEven…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dairy milk consumption in the US is down 22% from 2000 to 2016 according to @packaged_facts What are we drinking instead? https://t.co/1RCBqkdp8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteveDaniells: Children globally behave in similar ways when it comes to food. They look at labels, they shun foods with certain ingred…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The prices for monkfruit are falling, making it more accessible https://t.co/kf4b4tM4bG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: Old #marketing playbook: Disruption, getting attention

New marketing playbook: Permission to have a convo/

@LindaEFo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Transparency  is not the same as more information.  It is about an invitation to access that consumers can choose to accept says @KetchumPR's Eatherton at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: #FoodVision USA Day 2 kicks off with @EWatsonWrites leading the packed room through the today’s line-up, with presenta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If marketers hold a product out as perfect the consumer will perceive it as spin and will shut the brand out @KetchumPR's Eatherton says at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure ppl want "clean" food but also most are ok w processed food as long as they know how and why, says @KetchumPR's Eatherton at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has been a fundamental shift in power so that consumers now control the fate and course of #Brands and that's ok, @KetchumPR's Eatherton says at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA delays #organic animal welfare rule even though only 1 out of more than 4700 comments wanted to go that route: https://t.co/C0ZRo8GNFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US #organic grain acreage is up 30% fro 2016 https://t.co/n0xzzumITE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CaitlinPlankRD: FYI - Insect Protein market projected to be $100 Million in 2017 and $1 Billion in 2022! #FoodVision https://t.co/qNyDv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: Big food brands have to innovate - it’s easier to acquire #innovative brands but it’s not always cheaper, says @Mattso…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#branding  is bigger than a logo and cool package.  It is about an emotional connection between cos and consumers says Wayne Wu at #foodvision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's consumers know that avocado and olive oil are healthy fats but beyond that they are clueless about fats @barbstuckey says at #foodvision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean label is more important than Nutrition Facts to today's consumers says @barbstuckey at #foodvision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beveragedaily: Managing director of @vmgpartners: 'We don't walk a food show to seek discovery; we're focusing on businesses that have…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: #authenticity is only good when it’s real and it’s from the ground up, says Gigi Lee Chang from @FoodFutureCo at #Food…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have the right product and lots of money but in wrong culture you might fail. Welsh govt tho will hold your hand to ensure success as you break into a new market #foodvision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: The @FoodNavigatorUS team kicks off #FoodVision USA 2017. What’s #innovation &amp; who’s driving it? with @FoodFutureCo @s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: Looking forward to meeting our fabulous speakers @FoodVisionEvent USA, which begins today! Big thanks to @chobani @Campb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer to how small cos maintain culture while still tapping resources of big cos that buy them is the same as how porcupines mate: v carefully, Scott Norton of Sir Kensington's says at #foodvision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is driving #innovation  in food &amp; bev?  @EWatsonWrites asks experts at #foodvision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big companies still have hope to innovate in-house and are hiring young employees to make it possible, says @barbstuckey at #foodvision in Chicago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail wasn't ready for savory yogurt, but food service could hold the key to the category's growth in the US says @Chobani exec at #FoodVision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will 2018 be the year that #floral flavors finally breakout? https://t.co/CO7NGRGIOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Millennials are embracing frozen food for convenience, clean label and food waste reduction, @acosta data shows https://t.co/kZgPwFSTjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does the lawsuit against Forager mean for others who use HPP? https://t.co/S3qXYEwez1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PowerfulYogurt got its start courting men, but w $4m fundraise plans to go after women now https://t.co/cfaR3evdvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how a crunchy snack could help the vineyards and others impacted by California wildfires recover: https://t.co/zEtJFwMcHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigger loaves of premium bread are on the rise: https://t.co/HgVq7Cq0fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should #dairy companies try to boost #milk sales or invest in #plantbased options? https://t.co/1RCBqkdp8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Freetrade through #NAFTA w #avocados from Mexico created 19,000 American jobs https://t.co/uewdxwEPJJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>