<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnAvlon: It really is stunning to see that 43% of Republicans do not want to see Roe v Wade overturned (in addition to 73% of Indepen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xenocryptsite: It is incredibly bizarre to me that the lesson some people are taking from 2016-2018 politics is that "there are no swin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan We won't. These controversies don't have any life beyond the bubble of political professionals/activists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kathyprojo This is a process story. The people who care already disliked the Speaker and Democratic Party old guard. This will intensify their feelings but have no impact on 90%+ of voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattBrownnnnnn Why did you do this? Close your eyes goddammit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElectionBabe No, that length frames your face really well. #MyTwoCents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai My sesquipedalian, loquacious, erudition is impervious to this specious, scurrilous criticism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see the mayor of London focusing on those bread and butter issues of....gender disparity in Wikipedia editors. https://t.co/uHo95nEsCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephMurr_Jour: I would like everyone in Boston to know that I’m on the D.C. metro and the train stopped for 5 seconds and they apologi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliseYost @TPUSA No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ilusasha: Nothing says “I’ve given up, but I’m still a sassy millennial” like microwaving an Amy’s dairy free organic burrito.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaayleyCoates What am I now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaayleyCoates Hey! I'm a Gemini!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SonnyBunch: Neil deGrasse Tyson called; he wants his humorless literalism back. https://t.co/c9Kxk86C4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope everyone keeps Larry — one of the great contrast collar shirt wearers in American life and a true #SartorialSolon — in their thoughts and prayers. Whatever your politics, we are all better off to have his exquisite tailoring in the White House. https://t.co/H6M7jcxtKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RantyAmyCurtis: Camping. You’ve invented camping. https://t.co/J6MVBe64n9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai Some people don't have What It Takes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjane87: Baseball is a trash sport that will eventually land in the dustbin of history until some genius makes it full contact https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedNesi I'm on this post-campaign health kick where I just replace meals with coffee. It's absurdly unhealthy but so was the amount of pizza and takeout I was inhaling every week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh and Donna. https://t.co/BCyVQfATVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeCookieMonster: Three things me thankful for: cookies, cookies and more cookies. Me monster of simple tastes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gabrielmalor: Just a reminder that because of California licensing law, these volunteers cannot use their new skills to become firefigh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: It’s wrong for media to describe blue metro America as the bubble. Measured by economic output, racial &amp; religious diver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Redistrict: Dems' fundraising dominance in 2018 wasn't just the result of anger at an unpopular GOP president in a midterm; it was as m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @megansarahj: If anyone sees my son Kevin at the marijuana store opening today plz call me so I can organize intervention https://t.co/X…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blakel3y @HaayleyCoates Yeah, that's a fucking miracle as far as I'm concerned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen It makes sense to me. It's hard to image two people as diametrically opposed as Obama and Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbensnyder: Today in shitty machine learning startups, this company claims to predict IQ, personality, and violent tendencies by applyi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aedwardslevy: This is the thing about Trump's hardline immigration tack -- yes, his base really likes it but at the same time, the publ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aedwardslevy: 86% of voters have heard about the migrant caravan, but...

70% think it's at worst a minor threat or aren't sure, and 70…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThaddeusRussell: Should people who are taking money from labor unions be drafting labor legislation? https://t.co/smtVn95xnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ I don't think they're equal per se, but they usually go together. Bill Clinton is an exception that comes to mind, so is Shirley Chisholm, but if you made a list of the most rhetorically unsophisticated pols there'd be a lot of overlap with populist snake oil sellers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billscher: 5 days ago: "there are currently 17 names on it, but the group is trying to get more than 20 members before releasing it." h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aedwardslevy: glad to see that, with the midterms over, we can return to the issues that normal people care about, like house leadershi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickIber A lot of crime/vigilante exploitation films from the 70s and 80s. The political context is usually pretty clear — regular citizens fed up with crime doing what the liberals are too effete to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ I both believe it's bad that our leaders are speaking less intelligently while also believing it's politically effective and will continue. It's not a coincidence Trump speaks at a fourth grade level in a country where more and more ppl don't read books: https://t.co/iwiArRXQ1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ Personally, much more than ideology, dislike of populism is one of my animating political beliefs. That's different from the descriptive observation of politicians talking at lower and lower rhetorical levels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ Normatively, I think it is a decline but that's just my personal preference. I'm a big critic of "they're just like me" politicians. I want leaders who are better than the average American. Again, I don't think it's a coincidence that Palin was a trailblazer for this style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital media is a house of cards, just like podcasts. There's still no proven formula for news to be sustainable in the digital era — it's not hawking meal services, high-cost low-quality faux-custom clothing, and direct to consumer everything. https://t.co/QnWHzz3HFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ That has a lot of downsides, not the least of which is that it's exclusionary, but the shift to politicians talking "just like me" is one of the major trends in contemporary politics. Not a coincidence it's shared by Tea Party and DSA candidates. 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ Her constituents are, on balance, better educated than the average 1920s Boston laborer. What's changed is the loss of common cultural touchstones and an aspirational culture that essential mandates canonical literacy to engage with rhetoric. 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ I'm making a descriptive point, not a normative one, though I personally far prefer traditional rhetoric to the increasing colloquial language pols use (something Sarah Palin really accelerated.) 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JRBoh: December 4, 1980: a challenge to California's Democratic state party chair-in-waiting, "San Francisco housewife Nancy Pelosi..."…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bpmehlman: Interesting election results for the anti-gerrymandering jeremiad.  Dems' share of seats matched their share of votes nation…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Michael Curley, like AOC, was a populist who targeted his rhetoric to the average Bostonian of his time. Curley would regularly quote Homer, Shakespeare, Milton, and other canonical works, knowing his audience of poor immigrants and blue collar workers would understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing this to FDR's scripted, linguistically beautiful addresses shows how far American political rhetoric has declined. Sometimes I think Obama will be the last politician to give eloquent, traditionally structured speeches. https://t.co/fIoHtmVMOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pkmacdonald: Rice will fail to address disagreements between her offensive and defensive coordinators, and the next thing you know, Bak…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really think Beto is a Top 5, probably Top 3, 2020 contender. It's a fools errand to handicap two years out but he offers what the party base wants, but is more charismatic than Warren, Sanders, et al. https://t.co/FyDRm9oGs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MackinStyle That half is correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TedNesi: “The Census Bureau projects that in 2034, for the first time ever, people 65 and older will outnumber those under 18.” https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot take: Troy is a great movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ @ne0liberal Ranked Choice Voting: in case regular voting is too easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cc: Everyone who laughed at the idea there would ever be a Democratic equivalent to the Tea Party. https://t.co/1pC8Wcfg0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana Can't argue with results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenWern I don't know the context for this but I feel attacked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or criticize her for something other than not wearing sackcloth like "the poors" are supposed to. https://t.co/4r1OXoPbf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell if this is weirder than when Jordan Peterson uses stories about witches to argue for strict gender roles IRL. https://t.co/RmPONHnfIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in "projecting desires onto reality." https://t.co/8hYS8uckkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Dems control every legislative district Hillary won. If there's one thing 2018 taught us it's that progressives do well in Dem primaries but bad in purple/red district generals. https://t.co/zXBIsdcwTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the worst take ever shared online. This is worse than pro-Candy Corn takes. https://t.co/cmCzVSlqSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinrkosar @raylehmann I don't think you need to be in leadership though, just high profile. At the nadir of Kennedy's influence in the party (the 90s, when DLC tendencies combined with his "Senator Bedfellow" persona to render him out of favor) he was the featured Evil Liberal in GOP advertising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinrkosar I'm skeptical of the electoral argument, since I think "elitist liberal" bogeymen are mostly interchangeable, but that's certainly a fair point. I just don't think the Democrats would have picked up more seats if Seth Moulton or Marcia Fudge were Speaker-in-Waiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinrkosar @raylehmann Wouldn't it be easy for Rs to slot some other high profile Democrat (Elizabeth Warren, Cambridge elitist comes to mind) into that boogeyman role? Ted Kennedy filled it for two decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinrkosar My biggest issue with that argument is that Moulton (who I like a lot) et al aren't talking about replacing Hoyer and Clyburn, just Pelosi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePantau: Conservatives: reading about comic book superheroes makes us weak.

Also conservatives: Second Civil War fantasies? *unzip*…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BlanksSlate: This is what happens when you plead with government to “Do something!” Homicides are difficult, require public trust to so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAFrench: Those are astounding stats. It's easy to forget why people were so panicked about crime in the early 90s. https://t.co/3k…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbarro: Incoherent, but then an incoherent “Walmart bad Amazon good” view is probably pretty common especially among people who never r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jen_Migliore Is Saugus secretly part of Florida?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickRuffini: If you're a corporation and you don't hire an oppo firm to do research on your competition you shouldn't be in business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey, can you drink a ton of soda quickly," is both totally innocuous and a classic early teenager thing. #HellIsOtherPeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ask him why he has to be a prick, he (immune to self-awareness) tells me to mind my own fucking business. Then he walks to the end of the car in a snit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism so obvious even a white Republican can see it: angry businessman yelling at black high school kids for talking loudly on the subway and joking about whether one of them could drink a giant orange soda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkLeibovich: "Collins's openness to bipartisanship has, paradoxically, made her a bipartisan target." Susan Collins Could Do Without…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NoahCRothman: Among the things no one should have to say out loud: your chicken sandwich preferences have no bearing on your socio-econ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteveKornacki: In November 1994, Massachusetts reelected two Republicans, Peter Blute and Peter Torkildsen, to their second terms in th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This point. https://t.co/Yd8qy9ZJIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GPIngersoll @ChuckRossDC What part of this is inaccurate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restaurants should still strictly enforce rigid dress codes. https://t.co/Rm8rWCE8Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EsotericCD: SOLID CRITICISM of Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez: "she doesn't understand basic economics and her policy ideas, such as they are…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like the criticism of AOC is designed to force me to defend her. "How dare a Congresswoman try to look professional instead of dressing like an extra from the crowd scene in Les Miserables," is a garbage opinion. https://t.co/Ro5FH8XOgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama's memoir is one of the best books I've read by a politician who isn't at the end of their time in public life. Also, it reminds me that until Barack miraculously won a Senate race because the two front runners imploded in scandal, she was far more accomplished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CydMckenna: Looks at commuter rail conductor this morning

Brain:
Don’t say it!
Don’t say it!
Don’t say it!
Don’t say it!
Don’t say it!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I go back to this: it's crazy to stick with someone through three defeats and then firing them after they win, and just when their legislative acumen will be helpful again. https://t.co/22LXoGCV0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katielannan: The funniest part of wedding planning has been learning (conveniently always from someone available to sell you an upgrade…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen @Reagan_Airport It's insane how much mild cold/snow just paralyzes the South.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mschmitt9: The internal politics of the Congressional Black Caucus, which are rarely covered, are going to get pretty interesting, as t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Bill Galvin just declare Electoral Martial Law in Florida like he did in Lawrence and Lowell? #mapoli https://t.co/R3u5YSXMls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Yair_Rosenberg: This is an instructive example of left-wing anti-Semitism: person replies to FBI statistics showing AMERICAN Jews were…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baffling to see someone citing fundraising acumen as a negative for a Speaker. Fundraising for the caucus is practically half their job! https://t.co/qE7k30LaN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news: I can't sleep so I've been browsing Twitter.

Good news: Nowadays, this is among my most Presidential character traits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @conor64: One thing I can never relate to in these controversies: I had lots of strongly held views at 18 to 22. But it never would’ve o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biggestlilpopc @DanMcGowan Second, I wish the people concerned about the unsightliness of this major, high-quality development were concerned about the scrap metal yards that are a festering wound on the city's appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biggestlilpopc @DanMcGowan I don't accept the premise it's a blight on the landscape. I think it's a marquee development that will boost the city in the short term by creating jobs and in the long term by adding tax revenue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mviser: Even the most boosterish Democrats never thought they’d win all those seats in Orange County, the place Reagan once said was “w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond this, the logic of sticking with someone through three defeats, then tossing them after a victory proves they aren't a major liability, is baffling. 

Pelosi can't be that much of a political millstone or nonstop GOP ads tying Dems to her would have worked better. https://t.co/MjkBiTZ9tG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RWBranca: Juul pods out here getting banned before AR-15s “ #woke “]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan It's absurd that any mayor would block good jobs at good wages, property tax money, and the buzz of a major development. The municipal policy equivalent of shooting yourself in the foot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeathMayo: If Trump is willing to sign his name on criminal justice reform, both parties should work together to give him a good bipart…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ltthompso Politically I understand why you want to deny her bipartisan legitimacy, but fundamentally why is the idea so bad?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>