<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should restaurants bring in penalties for ‘no-shows’? - https://t.co/tBh3tPidZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I never gave a damn what the Church thought about me being gay' - https://t.co/tmZJAyj3es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Firefighters and soldiers battle Algarve fires as temperatures hit 45 degrees - https://t.co/eYA1XT6Erb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Lithuania's capital is billing itself as 'The G-Spot of Europe' and Catholics are - https://t.co/5XOUkHBjMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'When I got the text about where my blood was used, I actually started crying' - https://t.co/OFvTKhkZ1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish climate scientists are warning that the drought in Dublin is far from over - https://t.co/Q0LhHx1k1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should older people be 'incentivised' to downsize their homes? - https://t.co/y8ZwL8k4EB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'They had nowhere to go': Mother and six children spend night on chairs at garda  - https://t.co/uFHgjoheHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 70% of female students in Ireland experience sexual hostility or gender harassmen - https://t.co/5hxYqgFaiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Two dead in Spain as Europe wilts under record heatwave - https://t.co/ecbO0XC6yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Grandparent grant a 'novel idea that can be thrashed out' - Ross - https://t.co/fOelIUkbWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Women defiant as Denmark's full-face veil ban comes into effect - https://t.co/L2qhSEnfvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Warning issued as four cases of measles are reported in Dublin   - https://t.co/2qSyohQIhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: US 'crypto-anarchist' sees 3D-printed guns as fundamental right - https://t.co/pmUz1zDPoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Families move in to cooperative housing scheme in Dublin  - https://t.co/xAVApLCw8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'An attack on rural Ireland': Over 160 post offices to close nationwide - https://t.co/sGdCdenknp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Grave concern' over missing evidence in du Plantier murder investigation - https://t.co/Em9KgOuqCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Medical school altered test scores to keep women out - https://t.co/ly44MIKM2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish researchers have developed a 'game-changer' for tired sportspeople - https://t.co/Z1vmp0bMyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Are the strike days making you wary of booking Ryanair flights? - https://t.co/YCfuQ8GAgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ready to burst: 12-pack Durex condoms recalled over fault concerns - https://t.co/VMUwcCvhYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Grave concern' over missing evidence in du Plantier murder investigation - https://t.co/Em9KgOuqCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Sausages recalled due to presence of Salmonella - https://t.co/gv7zD46cTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New 'Baby on Board' badges launched - for pregnant women on public transport - https://t.co/6UkUEf7ypV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: NUI Galway repays students fees after complaints about course  - https://t.co/7RQHtcnTx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Woman sees €20 sticking out of man's wallet in garda station - takes it - gets  - https://t.co/LfZdOOUD6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Did you watch Love Island?  - https://t.co/5ufTLoybB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Sipo's order that Amnesty should return €137,000 grant is quashed after High Co - https://t.co/laeYyy9qvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'What's wrong with a President who wears wellies?' - Independent candidates vie f - https://t.co/O2RzyLpvsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'When I got the text about where my blood was used, I actually started crying' - https://t.co/OFvTKhkZ1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Parents turning to moneylenders to cope with back-to-school costs  - https://t.co/M8tuawgtxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Sandwich ingredients safe: Taoiseach rules out 'food stockpiling' in the case of  - https://t.co/HlzuWCgHeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should frontline gardaí be given tasers to protect themselves? - https://t.co/tose2mqOhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Tickets for Pope's Mass not sent out because of concerns that too many cars will  - https://t.co/jsXXARegr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Employee awarded €8,000 after colleague linked homosexuality to child abuse - https://t.co/b7TQLAclSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: International manhunt launched after thieves use motorboat to steal Swedish natio - https://t.co/Ui4gCY0oBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Hundreds of dead fish wash up on beach in Donegal  - https://t.co/6Vd9ty8JYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Two people injured in chemical incident at laboratory in Waterford - https://t.co/DNE8GJDhKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'The time for apologies is over': Facebook launches inquiry following Dispatches  - https://t.co/GwsbTXdYC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí find cannabis worth €135,000 after stopping man's car in Leitrim  - https://t.co/g6K0NfTmiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Women defiant as Denmark's full-face veil ban comes into effect - https://t.co/L2qhSEnfvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Some hospital bacteria growing 'tolerant' to sanitisers - https://t.co/1MFKPlG6bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Zimbabwe government vows to enforce security crackdown to prevent further protest - https://t.co/JKdExpSJ8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: US 'crypto-anarchist' sees 3D-printed guns as fundamental right - https://t.co/pmUz1zDPoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you think grandparents should get cash for helping out with childcare? - https://t.co/ycecpMUdKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí track down driver who made 'choice hand gesture' at officers carrying out - https://t.co/ZGR633i0sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Parents report going hungry over cost of sending their children to school - https://t.co/cV5BRh7bm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Taoiseach says there's 'no evidence of a land bubble' in Ireland - https://t.co/ScEhxL5l0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí target nightlife figure they believe is directing rickshaw drug dealing s - https://t.co/UeeLhqZyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Not drinking alcohol in middle age has been linked to an increased risk of dement - https://t.co/sMx6OTloqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Not drinking alcohol in middle age has been linked to an increased risk of dement - https://t.co/sMx6OT3Nzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Colm O'Gorman: Pope should 'tell the damn truth' about abuse cover-up when he's h - https://t.co/gV0NKN78uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern returns to work 6 weeks after giving bi - https://t.co/r1HlD9peoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland 'completely off course' on climate change targets, watchdog warns - https://t.co/HeQDJBa1EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: This is what Dublin's new U2 visitor centre would look like - https://t.co/t4GwfcIXMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Shane Ross: 'I sometimes think he's got a picture of me and he's throwing darts' - https://t.co/NrgIGTyb5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Three years since it was launched, do you use Eircode? - https://t.co/gWndo7qZox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Public transport will be free across Dublin for anyone travelling to see the Pope - https://t.co/7rzaYIgHvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Spider eats native Irish lizard in first recorded case - https://t.co/JWqmLATObl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Up to 150 homosexuality convictions could be overturned under Government proposal - https://t.co/XrbL9kTLB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Exclusive first look at the new Republic of Ireland away kit - https://t.co/gghKKk41Oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Kit Kat told it doesn't legally own shape of four-fingered chocolate bar - https://t.co/pR7OzSH0uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Coroner calls for parental vigilance after 10-year-old boy dies from allergic rea - https://t.co/aCF4TbM8kM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man takes bullet to leg after two shooting incidents in 30 minutes in Ballymun, n - https://t.co/KrVxYsZ87C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland 'completely off course' on climate change targets, watchdog warns - https://t.co/HeQDJBa1EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Study finds 40% of people have a fictional first childhood memory  - https://t.co/TYOdD0EegA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'A removal of stress and worry' - Fair Deal scheme to be extended to farms and fa - https://t.co/yVQTukFdIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Thai soccer boys' head shaved for Buddhist ordination  - https://t.co/cw5c71a7Pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you think it's beneficial to be in a union?  - https://t.co/bQ8WbImyZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: This former Amazon manager suffered a mini-stroke after working continuous 16-hour days, sometimes without days off for two…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CankertCallan @lauramartin_95 Never mind, maybe some day someone will introduce you by name to each other, and you won't need to resort to general nicknames to have a conversation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Fears raised after Ebola reemerges in woman one year after all-clear - https://t.co/Hla6c8Pl6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Venezuela heading towards 1,000,000% inflation, according to IMF - https://t.co/BZAD84JIEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I’m out'- Noel Whelan will not contest the presidential election. - https://t.co/Yq0rHMzxSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ticket touting: New law to ban above-face value resales approved by Cabinet - https://t.co/Q9YPrDPqLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Extremely dangerous': Warning after children seen 'tombstoning' from Co Clare cl - https://t.co/rYmFORQzLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Race for the Áras: Joan Freeman asks councils to convene special meetings  - https://t.co/WhE2FCAZKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Study to aid pregnant women by giving them Viagra stopped after 11 babies die - https://t.co/gGfThwMmHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Organisers of disastrous Fyre Festival settle €24 million fraud case - https://t.co/ZlI6vxncLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Art dealer buys storage locker full of 'junk', finds six priceless paintings - https://t.co/GaDqMp28Kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Three Irish authors have made the longlist for the Man Booker Prize - https://t.co/TFqouxY8xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChazzyB31: I've never flown with RyanAir because of the horror stories. I can't believe they're still getting away with this despicable…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lbcnvk: There has been a culture of fear for years now @Ryanair . That has changed now. People are talking. See the full story about ca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mary_cray: Come on #ryanair sort this out quickly. Show you care for your customers. https://t.co/ktmRgR1Zti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Toronto gunman had 'severe mental health challenges', according to family - https://t.co/JuFgv3ccff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Will you go out and vote in the presidential election? - https://t.co/qNfuXLtELd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Should we extend the HPV vaccine to boys? Public asked to give their views - https://t.co/DOm5YTt6oT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 200 elephants to be moved to Mozambique as part of effort to prevent falling numb - https://t.co/i1OPADZwe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Police use 'tear gas' on Tour de France protesters who blocked route with bales  - https://t.co/GHogUudGsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Hundreds missing in Laos after hydropower dam collapse - https://t.co/3vquIazWa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Speak Irish? The EU wants 72 translators - https://t.co/oq4fCW1Lvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'No family should be living in a shed': Warning over plan to allow log cabins as  - https://t.co/14PLRAwoPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Organisers of children's event Playstival with the Happy Pear apologise over gard - https://t.co/kPVYaaJnMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Rain and breakdowns on the quays cause heavy traffic in Dublin city - https://t.co/SZNsGsn8jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: FactCheck: Did the Taoiseach threaten to ban British planes from Irish skies? - https://t.co/HybRcXdXEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Couple who used stolen credit card details to buy hotel stay and sex toys ordered - https://t.co/z3gctRE2VG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí stop driver who was going 158kph on 100kph road. - https://t.co/TjhyvNo0o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Krispy Kreme to create 150 jobs in Dublin  - https://t.co/MYXRM5b6Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Just 93 prosecutions after 6,000 rubbish bags dumped in Dublin city's 'worst litt - https://t.co/U6m7NnaEau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Woman dies in Galway farm accident - https://t.co/2ruTOE550q]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>