<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Computer Methods International Corp. (CMiC) is a Software Development firm specializing in enterprise financial and cost management systems designed for the Construction and Engineering industries. About CMiC CMiC is the leading provider… https://t.co/K3OqOhaI7v https://t.co/LgTa2vu2xX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Position Description * Conducts application analysis and design for end users * Demonstrates up-to-date expertise and applies this to the development, execution, and improvement of action plans * Develops team member capabilities *… https://t.co/fg9EP5piUB https://t.co/izN3YlZvOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Specialist I – Kronos: Business Systems Specialist I Kronos HCR ManorCare seeks an individual to be the functional and technical lead through process and configuration improvements. This candidate will also excel at problem solving on… https://t.co/nBkP4Pax0J https://t.co/h9UQ97LXTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (FRONT-END): Department: Product Engineering Reports To: Director of Product Engineering Position Summary As a Front-End Software Developer, your main responsibility is for the production, modification and maintenance of websites and… https://t.co/6BB09kl8aD https://t.co/63Y6a0ZM7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer: Sr. Web Developer at eBay Skip Navigation Press tab to begin typing your search or press escape to close. Search Site close MenuHeader Logo – Our Company – Overview – Who We Are – Connected Commerce – Our History – Our Leaders – Our… https://t.co/3AU6eye1SX https://t.co/ZENni0tE78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROR (Ruby On Rails) Lead Developer: Location Santa Clara, CA Job requirements: * Proficient in Ruby on Rails and Node JS Total 78 years of experience in IT * At least 2 years of experience on application development and deployment on Amazon Web Services.… https://t.co/t9LsakHM7H https://t.co/CSQTBAKkkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsSQL,Perl,Groovy,Hibernate,JPA,AIX,Solaris,ORMTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview Responsibilities include: * Developing code… https://t.co/sY8t0iMNGo https://t.co/PP9NwBoavh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: JOB TYPE: Full-time SQL Developer – must be local to MN and able to work in the US with no sponsorship required. JOB DESCRIPTION: Looking for a SQL Programmer/developer to wear a few different hats in a small company. Ideally someone with… https://t.co/6AzyfFMfjE https://t.co/4U5J67GLLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NetSuite Architect Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/ivRqprx8or https://t.co/A7OKSHC1VW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Analyst and SQL Database Administrator (#3585TB031518): COMPANY DESCRIPTION * Company has over 60 years of industry experience * Creates chemical additives for the manufacturing industry * Established and remains headquartered in the Cleveland area… https://t.co/ijwG57He8S https://t.co/R2NB12Hy3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET / SQL Server Developer (Presentation Layer): C#/.NET Developer (Presentation Layer) In search of a C#/NET Developer with focus on the presentation layer and conversational user interface. In addition to C#/.NET, applicants must have or quickly… https://t.co/qeCsc5xg5J https://t.co/STixApQjLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/Kj51xbeaRA https://t.co/PAcPs5No0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: RELOCATION PACKAGE AVAILABLE; CAN SPONSOR A US CITIZEN FOR A DOD CLEARANCE ISS is seeking an MS SQL Database Administrator to support the operations and maintenance of a large number of database servers for the US Army… https://t.co/nVYsAQUyMP https://t.co/pBOuLPtEAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: SQL Database Administrator ========================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Bragg, NC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an… https://t.co/x1ia9Ric5i https://t.co/9Ri5ZblNHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer III: Client Reference Code: 215448 JOB SCOPE: This position will be part of a software development engineering team responsible for analyzing, testing, implementing, and documenting new and existing processes. Participation in full… https://t.co/8dqLamI9j5 https://t.co/qK4Xo30ufH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/U0GpSdYTAI https://t.co/ec1CAwSqlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Computer Methods International Corp. (CMiC) is a Software Development firm specializing in enterprise financial and cost management systems designed for the Construction and Engineering industries. About CMiC CMiC is the leading provider… https://t.co/aTsDvc1Fjg https://t.co/kGTUfLvr4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Engineer: Senior Staff Engineer (job location is Seattle, WA) Design &amp; write code for video services designed to enhance HBO’s video streaming capability &amp; content associated w/ company’s interactive endeavors. Perform site architecture &amp;… https://t.co/rv5a8Be59h https://t.co/mtbzyK5aMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Description We are currently seeking a PHP Developer to join our team of software engineers.  Candidate will work both collaboratively to help maintain and modernize our company’s multi-platform transactional databases and systems.  This… https://t.co/Fwo0pDuDdE https://t.co/lysf8ArnGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/0KVmWfdmtG https://t.co/HkC1r88bzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA: PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA – Sriven Systems Inc. – Boston, MA – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career… https://t.co/xHGJzn1O26 https://t.co/7DF7fbAP1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior AWS Engineer With Strong MySQL For Massive LifeStyle Brand: Are you a Sr. Software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you view infrastructure as code? If you want to help take our DevOps culture to the next level, then read this! WHAT IS THE… https://t.co/LFr3DVFki5 https://t.co/jecZk4QHLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL – PL/SQL Developer (Top Secret Clearance Required): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified ETL Developer with TS clearance to join their growing team. This person will be… https://t.co/qn4Cf6rPpW https://t.co/6Nej0vnYNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java Developer (Spring): In the R&amp;D world, speed and quality are sometimes two competing factors. On the one hand, there is the sprint to delivery – and on the other hand, there is the standard of excellence. Our Senior Developers balance the… https://t.co/yHVjwPfMjS https://t.co/HLgTP4D9fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer With Strong AWS and MySQL: Are you a software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you want to work for a lifestyle brand powerhouse that is highly profitable and backed by some serious technology? If that sounds like you then check this… https://t.co/NYaMiazyK1 https://t.co/NipdEvPaBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation &amp; Technology Senior DevOps Engineer: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/qMmDN6EtXk https://t.co/12fmIFAMe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer (SQL Server or RPG): Immediate need for a well-rounded PHP Developer with strong front-end web skills; as well as, back-end development using either SQL Server or RPG. REQUIRED – Back-end/ database experience (not just front end… https://t.co/8s8RwrCxWB https://t.co/2kqhT5ocfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Associate, Salesforce Marketing Cloud Solution Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/jhCeMTmEwy https://t.co/MrUeA9PFPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Marketing Cloud Technical Architect Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/7sg6ArGrdY https://t.co/lDdYRU8l1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42201: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R42201. Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA. Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/iZDJntoANb https://t.co/Ypx4r4X08U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job Description: Parsley Energy Operations, LLC seeks Software Developer to work at its office in Austin, TX. Develop new software solutions, including responsibility for components of medium size and complexity and… https://t.co/5dyyQwmesX https://t.co/jBcozvHdyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL Developer DSS86528656 *Richmond, VA* ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very… https://t.co/XbNu4aTcqa https://t.co/WpGKnmhCyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify puts bank IPO paydays under fund manager scrutiny: LONDON (Reuters) - After shaking up the music industry, Spotify is now prompting investors to question the value they get from investment banks underwriting new listings with its low-cost IPO. https://t.co/pojVWIJLad https://t.co/HT9jko6hG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Programmer (248): Creates and maintains SQL database applications to facilitate the data collection and submission of information to internal and external entities. Provides system documentation, including instructions, workflows, and data diagrams.… https://t.co/IuirgQhan0 https://t.co/MFPW06j76y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Data Analyst (SQL): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10177 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software… https://t.co/ZtNsk9uCoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oracle applications developer: * 8+ years of Oracle Applications development experience with at least 5 years as Oracle Financials Applications Developer * Oracle EBS modules: * Accounts Payables (AP) * Accounts Receivables (AR) * General Ledger (GL) *… https://t.co/YUeek7qyLp https://t.co/NrLX5mpF8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Software Engineer: RDM is looking for a Senior .NET Software Engineer to facilitate ongoing maintenance and development of our SaaS application platform along with other application development. Our platform supports the fastest growing area… https://t.co/glf95tGnzG https://t.co/v9CQen00l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Job: Java Developer (Job Number:434949) Description: Job Description: SAIC is looking for Software Developers to support the NATSS program in the maintenance and modernization of 30+ key legacy applications (mostly Java, SQL and PL/SQL,… https://t.co/iBFlucI5TS https://t.co/MzoJmKGQiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Interoperability Software Developer/Architect: Note: this job is open to US Residents only. Foreign nationals can apply but only if you live within the US. What we do actually matters. CareEvolution’s HIEBus platform creates better patient… https://t.co/cJgLsdg1hL https://t.co/WUviKVjpSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Big Machines CPQ Technical Analyst: Oracle Big Machines CPQ Technical Analyst Ref No.: 18-00594 Location: Tampa, Florida Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/28/2018 CPQ is Oracle Big Machine Quote to Cash product Require strong hands on… https://t.co/lwhP4gMwwC https://t.co/akAkhYcqVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/ZYYr8nOd00 https://t.co/JKVkmgxYC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET SQL Developer: The Senior SQL Developer creates the overall structure and workflow of a software solution and is responsible for leading and/or handling the development of one to multiple components. The Senior Developer will work with the… https://t.co/JwTrkStVHK https://t.co/b3Ocatlxdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Customer Contact (PHP, JS, React,SQL): As a member of the Customer Contact Funnel engineering team, youll help us develop and maintain software to support our clients various customer contact channels, providing world-class… https://t.co/GC9U8fVNkh https://t.co/fCaT1Pm04E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6 MVC / MS SQL Back-end 16371: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical… https://t.co/bq1twLAXpW https://t.co/XLruucvEVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concept Development Ideation Lead, Cardiology – Telecommute: As the rules continue to change, one company continues to lead. No industry is moving faster than health care, and no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward than… https://t.co/RpuZ5rcYrB https://t.co/Ky49nWBzIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Specialist I – Kronos: Business Systems Specialist I – Kronos HCR ManorCare seeks an individual to be the functional and technical lead through process and configuration improvements. This candidate will also excel at problem solving on… https://t.co/0Dqyd2AHq5 https://t.co/3vJjOwWzNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: Job TitleSQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: R233) Location: Warrington Salary: up to 50,000 Contract Type: Full time,Permanent SQL DBA for the Optionis Group in… https://t.co/jKqDy6HiOP https://t.co/sJW4Py1QC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Architect: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/qbFxvfW6AM https://t.co/fDNkdETWnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server DBA Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsSQL/DBATax TermsC2C,W-2,Full TimeOverview Job description Location:- Houston TX Position Type:- Contract Looking for Onshore SQL… https://t.co/9FDAdjXxHb https://t.co/rRzJUhLgOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Economic Consultant – San Antonio, TX: Some people take things as they come. Others relentlessly push themselves to go farther. Combine health care and technology, which are two of the fastest-growing fields on the planet, with… https://t.co/bVoO2xLZsC https://t.co/eBD2HGExkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Treasury Systems Developer: Description The Senior Treasury Systems Developer will support the development and maintenance of the ALM, Integrated Stress Testing and FTP models for Treasury and Capital Management platform. These models describes… https://t.co/qSdVUfu9kA https://t.co/rowxynYfon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber CEO says company still believes in future of autonomous vehicles: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Uber Chief Executive Dara Khosrowshahi said Wednesday the ride-sharing company still believes in the prospects for autonomous vehicles after a company vehicle… https://t.co/Vvi4gyQ7yJ https://t.co/CZNUrkgald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP REST Web Services: Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP &amp; REST Web Services | CareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise… https://t.co/chor3pf0MX https://t.co/G2b75nyc7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Test Engineer #2018-43044: Senior Software Test Engineer Ref: 2018-43044 Sought by Dish Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Lead &amp; contribute as part of a team of onshore &amp; offshore testers in a fast paced IT environment for multiple… https://t.co/3o30CL2dLQ https://t.co/zm16Mr91iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sql Developer: Sql Developer HI,Hope you doing great,?Greetings from Amiga!!URGENT New Position ?SQL Developer?We have an urgent opening as a SQL Developer . I?ll send you Job detail Please have a look on Job detail and revert back with your updated… https://t.co/cohnzrndgN https://t.co/IVYcESPNl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ETL Developer – SSIS, SQL, .NET: Have you worked with SQL Server, SSIS, tape, bubblegum and related technologies to enable ETL and replication between disparate environments? Perhaps on-prem to cloud, cloud to on-prem, and so on? Workstate seeks… https://t.co/T4m74507fq https://t.co/D1NB3uVBlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Lead: The Software Developer Lead will oversee &amp; lead a team of software developers who work closely with the Product Managers, Solution Architects, Business Analyst, and Quality Assurance to produce high quality enterprise level web… https://t.co/jImDHk3t8x https://t.co/humV6kh4Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Ant ups fundraising target, valuation could hit $150 billion: sources: HONG KONG/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - China's Ant Financial Services Group is in talks with investors to boost its fundraising target to at least $8 billion, which could see its… https://t.co/QXwgOL4Be8 https://t.co/epTmRhvmaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/cWqg52menv https://t.co/eBraxOclkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior business analyst with SQL experience: Primary point of contact for interface between the business users and IT teams. Formulates and defines systems scope and objectives through research and fact-finding, combined with a basic understanding of… https://t.co/r0b5heiaao https://t.co/C0cJq6q40Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW OF THE PL/SQL DEVELOPER: We are looking for a talented PL/SQL Developer to join a team focused on developing and maintaining various databases and database applications. Are you a creative problem solver with experience… https://t.co/r3XmzmImJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer (SQL Server or RPG): Immediate need for a well-rounded PHP Developer with strong front-end web skills; as well as, back-end development using either SQL Server or RPG. REQUIRED – Back-end/ database experience (not just front end… https://t.co/uGuluWVCM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/SQL Developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/SQL Developer – ID:31001 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL-SQL, Data Warehousing, UNIX Servers (AIX 6.x), Shell Scripting LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted02/15/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS,… https://t.co/5n4qQV95Qt https://t.co/ZIcSNWigJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Energy, Communication &amp; Services Technology Lead US .NET Full Stack Developer Are you looking for a change? Do you want to collaborate with some of the best talent in the industry? Are you ready to join a company whose… https://t.co/Kg46xHcErk https://t.co/EoMhleS8F4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli agency investigating Apple over handling of iPhone slowdown: JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Israel's consumer protection bureau said on Tuesday it was investigating Apple over a failure to disclose to consumers that its software could slow performance in… https://t.co/PP2iEm3QyI https://t.co/JYCpDHDRHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Remedy Developer (Lead) Ashburn, VA: Senior Remedy Developer (Lead) Ashburn, VA ========================================== Req #: ******Location: Ashburn, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be… https://t.co/2duHohOyQd https://t.co/Cl1YIY0gou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems / Programmer Analyst (SQL ERP experience): Systems / Programmer Analyst (SQL &amp; ERP experience) Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 1 Role Description Arcadia University Programmer Analyst As a Programmer Analyst, you will interact… https://t.co/jJSPccLugR https://t.co/K3DUz6SOuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Data Architect – Multiple Locations / Telecommute Considered: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward. We need attention to every detail with an eye for the points no one… https://t.co/SCD4APdwKm https://t.co/NZPRjIRJSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence / ETL Developer: Benton PUD is looking for a Business Intelligence / ETL Developer with strong competency in Data analytics and ETL development and a passion for creating a data infrastructure and building data visualizations to… https://t.co/4hB8zJ9e8j https://t.co/QP5A25QQEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote – Senior SQL Database Developer: REMOTE – CONTRACT We have an immediate opening for a SENIOR SSIS/SQL DATABASE DEVELOPER who is a talented problem-solving developer with the ability to develop and implement ETL processes and production databases.… https://t.co/PadHPZTc2O https://t.co/046P1nzwWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai's Alibabacoin says Alibaba has no monopoly on 'magic' name: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The Dubai-based cryptocurrency firm Alibabacoin Foundation on Tuesday said Alibaba Group Holding Ltd cannot monopolize the "magical" Alibaba name, and asked a U.S.… https://t.co/kfEhTKa9M9 https://t.co/wh3zX4gCUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – C#, https://t.co/hQSAXGaBJi, SQL, HTML: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US .Net, *******, C#, HTML Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/cdYKRMBPe0 https://t.co/Wsy2aoMrYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6 MVC / MS SQL Back-end 16371: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical… https://t.co/CJJc7s9swk https://t.co/Re96NEHHko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PostgreSQL Database Administrator: GreenZone Solutions, Inc. is seeking an Operational PostgreSQL DBA who will support the Federal clients data programs through the development and support of the clients databases. Responsibilities * Ensure operational… https://t.co/wP5d1gYtSx https://t.co/8lXBNBMZsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Administrator: Senior SQL Server Database Administrator Lincoln, Rhode Island United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Amica Location: Lincoln, RI… https://t.co/tx10GkCatO https://t.co/RNw4lFgAEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: T-SQL Developer memphis, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/27/18, Posted Date – 03/27/18 Primary **********,C#,T-SQLTax TermsC2COverview Position: (SQL Server with C# or ******* experience) The Packaging Systems Application… https://t.co/s0sydqqcNx https://t.co/wcyvpw7gzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber loses EU court case in fight against French criminal charges: LUXEMBOURG (Reuters) - France is entitled to bring criminal proceedings against local managers of ride-hailing app Uber [UBER.UL] for running an illegal taxi service, the EU top court… https://t.co/q7eH8kNy67 https://t.co/qw793rQvSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: Job TitleSQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: R233) Location: Warrington Salary: up to 50,000 Contract Type: Full time,Permanent SQL DBA for the Optionis Group in… https://t.co/5u1UPqb5fS https://t.co/lpE9QZZ81L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer With Strong AWS and MySQL: Are you a software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you want to work for a lifestyle brand powerhouse that is highly profitable and backed by some serious technology? If that sounds like you then check this… https://t.co/mbM8e39IgS https://t.co/9mVLBnrsFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree (May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a… https://t.co/hkcH4IpchB https://t.co/j48uVKe5I0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: MUST HAVE SKILLS: * MIRRORING * ALWAYS ON DESCRIPTION: * Ability to manage multiple projects at once * Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support * Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills * Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/Nnn9XMpd7Q https://t.co/UXueI2nQRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree (May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a… https://t.co/WvEcQHPstQ https://t.co/kZV6dHxoxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, Sales Technology: Company Description If you are looking to be a part of a highly collaborative organization that motivates its employees to seize exciting opportunities and make a difference in the way we do business, then Commvault is the… https://t.co/a5kahyZCdK https://t.co/5YGXvinRlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel industry eyes blockchain potential for fees, delays, lost bags: BERLIN (Reuters) - Blockchain technology has the potential to shake up the travel industry by giving airlines and hotels a way to bypass controlling intermediaries like Expedia or… https://t.co/kZ6O3RoCO2 https://t.co/aiO0fanrtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA – Chicago Loop (Great team and Manager!) 100K: We are seeking a SQL DBA who will be responsible for maintenance, enhancement, designing of data dictionaries, physical and logical database models, and performance tuning. This is a great… https://t.co/kBdQYIUwRK https://t.co/SlAn9ial7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Modeler â€“ PL/SQL Developer: Job Details: * Job Title: (WEEKEND DRIVE) Data Modeler PL/SQL Developer * Hire Type: Full Time / Permanent / Direct Hire * WEEKEND DRIVE: Walk-Ins for local candidates and Webex video call for non-local candidates. Job… https://t.co/hcGFj3hZ8H https://t.co/UAD3Ce2Afb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Payments (PHP, T-SQL, TDD): AN IDEAL CANDIDATE HAS * 5+ YEARS of professional experience as a FULL STACK, full lifecycle software engineer. * Bachelors / Masters degree in Computer Science or related field * 3-5+… https://t.co/oVKrtxoKOC https://t.co/FLvrzSTgBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: IT Positions available at Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: SYSTEMS ANALYSTS: Analyze, design, develop &amp; test applications. Prepare test plans. Create &amp; automate test scripts. Perform risk analysis.… https://t.co/0qlZ0fkefI https://t.co/qPOxG23ZMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Tech Specialist 5 (Lead Data Warehouse ETL Dev/Tester): Info Tech Specialist 5 (Lead Data Warehouse ETL Dev/Tester) at DSHS-Children’s Administration (CA) Finance &amp; Performance Evaluation Division (FPED) (unabbreviated full text job desc. @… https://t.co/qt2Yj5o666 https://t.co/AwVOJZ8ROY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Developer- Eden Prairie, MN or Telecommute: Automation Developer, you would work as a part of a dynamic team with a focus on writing code and developing applications leveraging multiple tools, languages, processes, and technologies.   … https://t.co/2pchtkLBRN https://t.co/euW6g6f6xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verifone to be taken private for $2.6 billion in cash: (Reuters) - Payments technology company Verifone Systems Inc on Monday agreed to be taken private by an investor group led by Francisco Partners for $2.58 billion in cash. https://t.co/4ohlObQZJV https://t.co/BcSlMIVTQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer (Strong SQL Required!!): This is NOT a contract or contractor role – PLEASE DO NOT submit your resume if you are not interested in full-time employment (FTE). Will be directly supporting software engineers using our clients… https://t.co/x2iCPmqEnp https://t.co/gIy5ovc1jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/yiS1Y7ok9X https://t.co/Pu71zii6oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics:   Job Description – SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics (1801865) Job Description  SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics – (1801865) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-MOLINA300 Job : Business &amp; Strategy Analysis… https://t.co/VWsSKAODpC https://t.co/HX6DBdnBOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Database Developer (Oracle) 16449: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/qmRpbJgFxO https://t.co/pwNRzqVEad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Data Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here,… https://t.co/ABscIGUwM1 https://t.co/p7iDtOiwc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber agrees to buy electric cycle-sharing startup JUMP Bikes: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Ride-hailing company Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] said on Monday it has agreed to buy electric bicycle service JUMP Bikes, allowing Uber to offer U.S. passengers… https://t.co/zrtn9iA0Rd https://t.co/vgH5MvHAcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Director Healthcare Economics – California: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward than UnitedHealth Group. We need attention to every detail with an eye for the… https://t.co/SeoxJnCQZr https://t.co/bJfD4LWD7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior SQL Developer: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed Search – IT Staffing – Our Story –… https://t.co/bT7Gv8di4w https://t.co/yIk1MGIWHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design, develop, &amp; support trading &amp; risk management applications covering securitized products. Design &amp; develop application components using SDLC, C#, .NET,… https://t.co/3d0a1Z4TmO https://t.co/F7KALLQRC3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>