<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/gP2GTuscID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/QEFxFgrQhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/ofF3iI8aKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/okaIzZ2zQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/fDPQUz7vwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/LIa6iINWDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make a rock'n'roll record, technology is the least important thing.  -  Keith Richards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/kfWy5zlMVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/TtCQ4BKfvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire character. Train skill. - Peter Schutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/XGWRhlEO3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/l3Z4MhsFLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/isExbmmWl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/FKfCvkXYEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/rfXHuoQuOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love sports?  Read about the great sports teams of the Northern California Bay Area!  http://t.co/CcEoxROpNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/KrXv3wQ7JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/h9Yc16qj7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/p1Bg5TAMbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/pQwssJxOOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/QBHZKuxFBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/E0Qu84pxVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/xsKoHXsAHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spencer Davis Group  http://t.co/dNDM0gYdsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/hl0AhNrVgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/ZfnClW5Vq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/JKJdl5OppX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/mZZO5Wi7Ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/mNxs3Jbn5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/RPNVnzSIVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/iWYBVK4zbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/ks7qEaPC3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/c2YtaYuYG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/Oc7jaNN8BA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/8u5vvCVGnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/RBZQxIThgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/glcYX3fHrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/8IoeLB0qaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to being a good manager is keeping the people who hate me away from those who are still undecided. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget how fast you did a job - but they remember how well you did it. - Howard Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/Ms2qjMh68B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/TvWrt6bev5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/TOfzEBUFSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/L1vzwUTvSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/6pOD3bskK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/A6EnPxkheE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/aA1XN8Fos2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/tj1ospzAdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/Bj2xiDpWOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/VwF8kGtoFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/yL4w89OX6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/GgOo2NdQq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/RXNyAgbY5z]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>