<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/jDZS90ep0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/upnyqPHRXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/vsYg3OLFZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/1H7kciereY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/JoEQfdaDgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/xEnqrxqT6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/jiZ9ngKctP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/lA8p2WaX6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/BSQuFMPAWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/v2Q38r4VXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/ClWE8BCrwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/G5Nnu0hdlE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/cKPKYPQfU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/IushkPaSrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/ONG0huhfjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/8rFaHCsUt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/9mvZ2MY0N8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/SsaXebcBTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/6s6WuwFbev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/vcWmuSAhQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/RFJRoYqV5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/kGXDUAzTHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/aL5nuuMad3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/8cwbYeqqBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/dNgiPmRdap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/cvO3d3woeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/lVwHqtNGTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/adNtHwr3rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/RDwhBeppFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/VvoNAMYW1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/oYphvTJDVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/8AqxKj3Crr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/qxUQS9tQcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/EcK3GnxTXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/lNHXOFIs1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/ezDa7ktc4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/O0FJXZp2BL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/QjBxXmXYIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/oELYpzXe3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/FPzgjGUqBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/um57cTt6zY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/SQffLPCQIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/04HU0nzoqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>