<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Birthday doing a very chilly Qigogng, taking in water, fire, earth and wind at Burrard Inlet Vancouver http://t.co/6YJqRCoukY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 years ago today I received my first 1-A from the local draft board in a call-up to go fight in a country that... http://t.co/ROisF3Z0Hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If women disappear there is no life. http://t.co/cd9I4LkP5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Great Blue Heron recently watched me throughout my Qigong. Nice addition. http://t.co/HJQqTzy80D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super cool bees raised in chill hives. http://t.co/bt2W6Y0Czc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7jkB52Jhqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going organic vegan will take down Monsanto. http://t.co/XyORiFo7CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The words to the American pledge of allegiance. http://t.co/W3fz82M5CW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurt the Yankee capitalists where it hurts most - an opera on the golf course 56 years later. http://t.co/l6Teu1Lpzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great way to start the day! http://t.co/24QEwNs92Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos of Volcano Fuego Erupting” by @500px https://t.co/Ni6bT2xE6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was running this morning. I found a thousand small daisies on my path. It's official - a panorama of the first... http://t.co/dp5ljFxCZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was running this morning. I found a thousand small daisies on my path. It's official - a panorama of the first... http://t.co/HPERu4ucKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week it's winter. Next week, who knows. http://t.co/35Ejya7Ptt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new work by Gabryel Harrison at her hobbit hatch studio in Southlands, Vancouver. Fully grounded in the spirit... http://t.co/i57aleujZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I found my people. http://t.co/ZXdtmoC09n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! two weeks since Stefan Sagmeister blew into town with his sold-out exhibit and talk at the Vancouver Museum.... http://t.co/JkeicT2uAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame it on multiculturalism, an all-too inclusive state of mind that chooses the least best choice so that... http://t.co/J3pkFxe4wZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the controversial new symbol of Canada's 150th birthday http://t.co/YGk3JyEijr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art that is inspired. http://t.co/LMfxHFKAtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 89-year-old Mom, Betty Lou (Barr) Shandrick, now has new digs and today was hosted with a high tea and roses.... http://t.co/dldctgZ6bU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jmWwzTaXum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baltimore is no place to raise a family but neither is America. http://t.co/rdLVWrdcAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Show: America Is a Horror Show | Moyers &amp; Company | http://t.co/xE2iRsFh23 http://t.co/67sZTnMbRd via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeeTheRoses irresistible rose with no thorns,promise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dalai Lama still cannot deliver his words to devastated parts of the Himalaya. Free Tibet! http://t.co/36ByvjY5FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend shaking your booty today! Start a fire within! http://t.co/IbXc8S0Nx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece #1 from my life drawing class will be among many Arts d'Oeuvres at Vancouver's gritty 3rd floor Parker... http://t.co/xVzTQ0Dufa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day another step to the summit. http://t.co/w7gcbX2TQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Make Friends With Affable People” by @planetapeman https://t.co/9gJnFXsRkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marlene in her classic tiger pose. http://t.co/O3Ss9Xe4PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellishly &amp; consistently provocative film making. http://t.co/M9kMQPZkuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An earthquake was inevitable. What will be lost are thousand year shrines and artifacts and of course thousands... http://t.co/QOzVso7m6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool remembrance of the amazing Bob Marley who would have been 70. Yah, man. http://t.co/lkiULYX5GV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Pull the dawn from the night” by @buckhouse https://t.co/otHysSGonA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad "Canada Day"as Bill 24-C set to derail democracy and intimidate voters with a gag order on any protests. http://t.co/YULtN5iCe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/9jQCGsriib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BizBuzzAmerica Thnx for the follow !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gettysburg was fought 152 years ago this Wednesday. What will manifest from old wounds that need to heal?” https://t.co/TYkeG7BStE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “The South Will Not Rise Again” https://t.co/ie2eLr3FZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaLIVE You are already a brand advocate for both you and the company. Good luck in your internship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spot we created at Mirthwerks in 2006. http://t.co/Vhuj24kHmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/zO5SCYGor3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathtaking crespucolo over Rio. http://t.co/YcNXKaFZug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countries, states and provinces are now fighting over the right to store rainwater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/qR1FUlh89K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hnTxA39G6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hz4EANtEH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Three Things Being Heartbroken Says About You” by @HilalIsler https://t.co/4U2FPJHTmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What it is... http://t.co/V4V9xqylyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch John Oliver's Message To Jack Warner That Aired On Trinidad TV http://t.co/k9TkhEHUMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch John Oliver's Message To Jack Warner That Aired On Trinidad TV http://t.co/chTnhBtVh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in Vancouver is Int'l Day of Yoga a grotesque egoic spectacle of excess and vulgarity. This is disgusting.... http://t.co/TyszozIYxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“50 Pushups” by @suneel https://t.co/hNb2ZyqJvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “A New Kind of Hell for FIFA” https://t.co/AC0PBRkmYs #FIFA #Brazilian soccer # World Cup 2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a box on your to-do list. I am not an empty space on your calendar. Do not plan to fill... http://t.co/jHn9Nmb4fX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifa officials arrested on corruption charges as World Cup inquiry launched http://t.co/zPF2i83u56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World-wide corruption scandal reaches deep into soccer culture for years to come. Now let's see the FBI take on... http://t.co/Ldr0KQkRFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 74th Charlie! http://t.co/8yJxRs0uW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suppose they gave a protest and nobody came to protest Harper's C-51 legislation?
All acts of protest are now a... http://t.co/d0LNn4BWyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suppose they gave a protest and nobody came?

Under Harper's C-51 legislation, Canadians will not be able to... http://t.co/FTLjcGMx2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all benefit from the monks' prayers, even the brutal Chinese invaders. http://t.co/58APocCeDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/pqnYZGRWbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Africa will one day be free of wealthy, white people who kill animals. http://t.co/LMGRfk9RaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/J57tbE1A7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@princess_scribe @londonswf He must have been good in a room. Sorry not to meet him. He's kept me and my scripts in motion 6 years later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pending tragedy as São Paulo emergency water supply project postponed again" on @LinkedIn https://t.co/PBGrKnjcZQ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rio's lake, rivers and bay too dirty for Olympic events. http://t.co/PzHKkr3T6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kick white hunters out of Africa. http://t.co/IsCdVp3pLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lion and a man at play. http://t.co/2dfZTGFfC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A moment of still life. http://t.co/3Yq78jWJg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stranger feels at home in Rio. http://t.co/NZeU0rdfsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Harper tried to set up an impromptu campaign "moment" for photographers by forcing tired... http://t.co/WOhVVj0JGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausted forest firefighters refuse to sing O Canada for Harper http://t.co/tuASPc4fxf via @thelapine #douchebagHarper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A voice of truth from the grave. http://t.co/yy5yyvBisk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to stop Zimbabwe from letting hunters kill wildlife, just put this man's head on a stick. That would stop... http://t.co/J2IJuzK5x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoga and a friend got this vet back to life. http://t.co/A4jWnJqRxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This American is tone deaf and obviously irrelevant. Where can I donate money to put a bounty on his head? http://t.co/2SHWEfZFAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/eeE43cMnHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smokin hot gal from Montreal is becoming a sensation in Montreal. Her cover of a Sia tune. http://t.co/ItE2IpqjwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A songwriting friend from Montreal sent me this. It's a cover, uniquely her own style. Wow! Her career is going... http://t.co/qMinTqSk9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend, a hardworking gal from Montreal breaking out,  MaryDee - Never Fall (Lyric Video) https://t.co/thxtIIwFvc via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lady is incomparable for nearly five decades. We may not have her long now. http://t.co/oiYM0BpxN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/FYbfyvrOxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never get tired of this photo. http://t.co/gRzPN5WWFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realsethhorus love this. great antidote to FB furry kitten syndrome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realsethhorus: There are 2 unassailable truths: 1. Success comes from hard work and 2. You can always purchase hard work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rio de Janeiro presented by DR1 Images http://t.co/Z4oKFx5L1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delmagodoy @FineArtAmerica lovely work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/PZ9BKtjT59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/TG7R0xzpAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple at the lake. http://t.co/djTKTSLYLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry's still working it from the beyond. Grateful Dead's 'Ripple' in new video http://t.co/v06AYTJvkQ via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry has God as a producer on this track. http://t.co/xhGiCnCiMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeShandrick Rebels in House cast secession vote instead of Confederate flag vote.#confederateflag #SouthCarolina https://t.co/N13ohSnp8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A New Kind of Hell for FIFA” by @MikeShandrick https://t.co/Y3fcliLf3X #FIFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A New Kind of Hell for FIFA” by @MikeShandrick https://t.co/arGdr3FnVK #brazilianFIFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. trillion $ fighter still not operational. http://t.co/igYSnhilfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @warisboring: When Is the F-35 Not a Dogfighter? When It’s Convenient @FranticGoat http://t.co/mb9Wn7pmwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/XMuIuJm4Q2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>