<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer/Programmer: Principal Systems Engineer/Programmer-&gt;&gt; Serves as subject matter expert in leading the design and development of the most complex application problems, system administration issues, or network concerns. Performs… https://t.co/NUyig9bMGr https://t.co/j5dRZX4coy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager (ITSM/ServiceNow): Job TitleSr. Project Manager (ITSM/ServiceNow) – ID:31801 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsITSM, SERVICENOW LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted05/24/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY… https://t.co/ERlYDuedJl https://t.co/VtWK5zAp16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT) – PSH IT: Penn State Health Shared Services Location: US:PA:Hershey Work Type: Full Time FTE: 1.0 Shift: Day JOB SUMMARY: Responsible for leading high-impact enterprise IT projects frequently involving multiple technology and… https://t.co/lCPwCSZS5T https://t.co/HNs2K1V6mH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineering Project Manager: Senior Engineering Project Manager Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Be part of a team assessing and driving achievement of program specific performance within Honeywell. You will partner with… https://t.co/ahpCBSi928 https://t.co/FkdCrxbCAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Service Management Analyst: Job Title: Associate, Service Management Analyst (JC0326) Job ID: ******* Location: Jacksonville Full/Part Time: Full-time Regular/Temporary: Permanent Return to Previous Page Corporate Services Corporate Services… https://t.co/sUvmXYnO52 https://t.co/dzlmLEoCEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. API Developer: Sr. API Developer Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth – Other U.S.… https://t.co/qWBlckBqZA https://t.co/2ugeS9VboT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Networking Software Engineer: Were looking for a dedicated and passionate Sr. Engineer to join our cloud networking team. If you have experience building scalable, cloud based, web applications, are excited about impacting millions of users, look no… https://t.co/rp4lLWRt0O https://t.co/60ctTitLR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Backend Developer: NCM – Careers CONTACT US THEATER LOCATOR Careers Browse Open Jobs Search Open Jobs Edit Your Profile Resources Watch our Great Place to Work video Employee Rights &amp; Responsibilities disclosure For our Affirmative Action Report… https://t.co/wtS72yTD3j https://t.co/v68FvpVG1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Starry is looking for a tech-savvy Project Manager who will excel in helping to redefine how users access the internet. You will act as the face of Starry Internet Services to both building owners and internet users, and be… https://t.co/1qVhtgfwjp https://t.co/z7VNgqLwR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3: Software Engineer 3 (Server)The Software Engineer 3 is functionally competent and working toward functional expertise in the field of software engineering as it relates to the business objectives of Asurion. The Software Engineer 3… https://t.co/5KubdjjBGG https://t.co/YiJNVNSez9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing VP, Research Business Analytics, Research Director:   Job Description – Managing VP, Research Business Analytics, Research Director (00019955) Job Description  Managing VP, Research Business Analytics, Research Director – (00019955) Description … https://t.co/FzMxHGn2XD https://t.co/34xv94ewpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Java/Middleware: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions in the financial… https://t.co/hCvCNlo8jw https://t.co/6BwJohkVkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer (Integration Lead): Overview Are you skilled in Java and object-oriented programming? Have you built integrations with enterprise-level applications such as ERPs, CRMs, and HCMs? Were looking for a highly technical self-starter… https://t.co/uwC3d0c9aq https://t.co/AIIAbQb9TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Project Manager: IT Technical Project Manager (Securities) * Duration: Long Term Contract * Location: Greenville, SC * Pay rate: W2 Hourly About the Job Our client, an innovative automotive manufacturing company, is looking for talented… https://t.co/j7EHAaaeYM https://t.co/UJ8xtZLljE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Software Engineer: Search Display **************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5199 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=1-INDEED… https://t.co/8BvdFDMjg5 https://t.co/q0fIFNMrl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer, Cloud DVR- Home Entertainment: Job Description Job Description This position will be a member of the team responsible for the design, development and implementation of the video delivery ecosystem. This position will set the… https://t.co/qBsxqvv1JB https://t.co/BgQDrpMFkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avionics &amp; Electrical Power Engineer: Req ID : 429816BR_3 Job Code/Title : E1383:Electronics Engineer Sr Job Description : Be a part of the team developing the hypersonic technology that could forever change our ability to deter and respond to conflict.… https://t.co/Wn5N4jp5xC https://t.co/GysUO7cLPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Threat Manager Job: Cyber Threat Manager (Job Number:437528) Description: Key Responsibilities: The Lead Cyber Threat Manager will manage a team to evaluate and improve SAIC’s cybersecurity resilience and defensive capabilities through active… https://t.co/tmD0YHN3VQ https://t.co/QaWRgrJU19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: QA Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-30499 Location: McLean, Virginia Role : QA Automation Engineer Duration : 12 Months Location : McLean, VA Job Description : – Ability to do regression profiling – Ability to design and create… https://t.co/J4MrQ27GQD https://t.co/rOuy7Kz3yt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCL Developer: Our client, a well-known Healthcare System is looking for a solid CCL developer with the following experience for a direct hire (they don’t sponsor)! – Experienced in the Cerner Data Model and CCL. – Strong working knowledge in Cerner from… https://t.co/I9fiAWwLmi https://t.co/aXTDHew33f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst: Computer System Analyst (Full-time) Diksha Technologies, LLC Mount Laurel, NJ. Duties: Code, design, develop, configure; Troubleshoot, test system &amp; software performance; Create documentation of software, systems &amp; solutions;… https://t.co/FnL1xQ1hxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Solutions Analyst: Advanced Solutions Analyst Sentinel Technologies, Inc. – Seeks an Advanced Solutions Analyst in Downers Grove, IL. Must have a MS or BS &amp; exp. Applicants must apply online at: https://t.co/DhPYntq9Dc. City , IL No phone calls… https://t.co/yqrGyyjN4w https://t.co/uRESSL2wnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer must have Retail experience: Anaheim, CA Full-time $70k – $150k Posted Today If you are a project engineer please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us #20 General Contractor in the United States! **Competitive Salary **Bonus Structure… https://t.co/BgHXG3l5uA https://t.co/KCLdZ1HI7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Ruby on Rails Developer: Northridge, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted Today Do you have a strong background with Ruby on Rails? Then you should take at look at us….. We are a leading telecom provider (NOT VERIZON OR AT&amp;T) for the U.S. and Canada,… https://t.co/rPuQFegDYL https://t.co/nSXPe7zOj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GMP Systems Specialist I, Engineering: Job ID 11022 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Manufacturing Overview Cures Start Here. At Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center, home to three… https://t.co/fDxw3qm5wr https://t.co/68rCUCY4G8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Desk IT Sales (Acct Mgr)/Recruiter: Job TitleFull-Desk IT Sales (Acct Mgr)/Recruiter – ID:32125 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsIT Staffing, Business Development, Staff Augmentation, IT Recruiting, Account Mgmt LocationBoulder, CO Date… https://t.co/mtDB1FNRqS https://t.co/fNoeV4CHOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SaaSOps Chief Architect – $100k/yr – REMOTE WORK: We’re running an Online Hiring Tournament on July 28th to hire SaaSOps Chief Architects (USD $100K/yr). This event will include testing. Upon grading the deliverables from the event, we will set up… https://t.co/nlUc4Q9yrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER. Dev’p process/rept’ing apps use Java (JavaSE, JMS, Spring, JDBC); jUnit, Mockito; Oracle, SQL,, Maven. etc. Cary NC Loc. CV to HR Dept, Luxoft USA, 100 Wall Street, Ste 503, NY, NY 10005. recblid… https://t.co/YZMnCse0vz https://t.co/XnezxO7vlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Specialist: The Dayhuff Group, LLC seeks Senior IT Specialist in Worthington, OH and other unanticipated locations to consult with business users to gather info about specific needs, objectives, functions, features, input and deliverables. Must… https://t.co/cjJanGwtgB https://t.co/w2EiLH7ljd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Analyst III: QUALITY ANALYST III (Mt. Laurel, NJ) – Create, update or review test cases. Requires Bach &amp; 7 years experience. Other specific experience required.  recblid hnx1rn2eaovvx2giqahxtv5mh09sbs https://t.co/3ERYwsPCdF https://t.co/4mjX9YVuPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Provisioning Specialist: Bell Bank is seeking candidates for a User Provisioning Specialist in Fargo or Minneapolis. If you like to work with people in a family atmosphere, enjoy great benefits and provide unequaled personal service to every… https://t.co/8hwggOt26j https://t.co/xXnoULfCdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Professionals: IT professionals Forte Consulting Group, Chicago, IL has multiple openings for IT professionals to provide services for clients located throughout the U.S. in the following skill sets: .Net Development, JO-800; Quality Assurance,… https://t.co/LfzzmLBUEC https://t.co/CvT1joBlvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator- TS/SCI Polygraph Required: DESCRIPTION: The Cyber and SIGINT Solution Ops under Defense and Intelligence Sector of Employer has a career opportunity for a System Administrator with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in… https://t.co/BUIQOxUAkZ https://t.co/zXMMgcpJjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Position Summary Coordinates, processes and resolves incidents and requests related the support of technology products, infrastructure, business processes and enterprise services. Takes full responsibility for handling customer… https://t.co/OAnCbMUdNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer: Senior Front End Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in… https://t.co/SZu30mwq24 https://t.co/tYfqkRMUER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Research Analyst: Market Research Analyst Paul Yoo &amp; Associates Co. Analyze data to evaluate service market. Bachelor’s in Business, Economics or related.  recblid kc24cpvzzapf86x2fbk6q21dzjphdy https://t.co/VxRKtsCBed https://t.co/VipaWfoyd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Manager #XGGS19FC0718RIC1: Technology: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Manager in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Provide technology-enabled consulting… https://t.co/Fi55qXKAW7 https://t.co/IIb1Gze2x4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Provisioning Specialist: Bell Bank is seeking candidates for a User Provisioning Specialist in Fargo or Minneapolis. If you like to work with people in a family atmosphere, enjoy great benefits and provide unequaled personal service to every… https://t.co/XU5tMuoMv3 https://t.co/NXU3RNKEBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Actuary: Certilytics offers a suite of innovative analytic solutions including Big Data Services, Total Population Health Management, Financial Risk Intelligence and Customized Prediction Models. These solutions are configured upon our open… https://t.co/m8jjK7LgkO https://t.co/2CelSxcKZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS Programmer/ Health: Careers Center | SAS Programmer/ Health Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/Ph0TKbEp1x https://t.co/6517I5twxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposal Content Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/20/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/PuW3BbmbXS https://t.co/zyXzQIZUCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Leader, Engineering QA: Who you’ll work with The position is for a Software Engineer for Data Center Software QA Team. You will work on latest hardware and software feature on Nexus 9000 data center switches. You will work in one of the best… https://t.co/UySJjYJ3AZ https://t.co/FgArcZRrFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer: Senior Java Software Engineer at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High… https://t.co/9MWRaS6sOD https://t.co/lV9iCiWXVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the most… https://t.co/k0s46vSZAo https://t.co/cp1oaMimAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Software Engineer: Senior Systems Software Engineer at Becton Dickinson &amp; CompanyAsset 1 Skip Navigation – Offerings – Company – Clinical Excellence – Support – Investors – United States – Company – Careers – Opportunities – Veteran Job… https://t.co/rgDKiQp7ir https://t.co/BonWU9pqno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Specialist: Job Description Transforming the future of healthcare isn’t something we take lightly. It takes teams of the best and the brightest, working together to make an impact. As one of the largest healthcare technology companies in… https://t.co/4LDLs3PXzU https://t.co/vaeVFXF3gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Applications Analyst (Store Systems WFM): – Location: Dublin, California, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: June 27, 2018 – Position Title:Senior IT Applications Analyst (Store Systems WFM) – Company Name:Ross Stores, INC – Job… https://t.co/8EeelIe4gD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Web Developer Solution Specialist USDC: UI Web Developer – Solution Specialist – USDC in Orlando, Florida, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in… https://t.co/PcYC5n7DNI https://t.co/yLrwIUj4Cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer Python: We are looking for a full stack Web Framework developer to work on upstream R &amp; D projects closely with a data science team, performing functional prototyping and facilitating the transfer of successful prototypes to… https://t.co/FCTzv4fttg https://t.co/4BBDcPVjtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR BUSINESS ANALYST: Quest Diagnostics Inc seeks Senior Business Analyst in Lenexa, KS to liaise b/w business &amp; IT depts for all aspects of business &amp; product changes, &amp; to understand scope, solutions, constraints, &amp; risks of system changes w/i a… https://t.co/2r3GmrHnFt https://t.co/JwO1p2FyFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC Network Support Tech 3/4:   Job Description – PC Network Support Tech 3/4 (18008516) PC Network Support Tech 3/4 Requisition ID : 18008516 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/My4Waon7uT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tactical Operations Program Analyst: Req ID 99061BR Business Title Tactical Operations Program Analyst Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Alexandria Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Programs &amp; Operations Job Duties and Responsibilities Basic Program… https://t.co/ZolYvaoFxo https://t.co/42lBcKfSz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Careers Center | Project ManagerPlease Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/D4hheuzh6z https://t.co/hTZjJxMoqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Department Mobile – ReachMobi Employment Type Full-Time Minimum Experience Experienced About ReachMobi ReachMobi is more than just one of the world’s largest mobile content providers. Our audience of over 20 million plus subscribers… https://t.co/6u8Uw51Hb5 https://t.co/tgqmNzzggi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial Hygiene Project Manager: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a global consulting, engineering and construction management firm that provides technology-enabled solutions to the power, oil… https://t.co/sCST4mNA36 https://t.co/Mn10JUDMTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Engineer: Job Description Embedded Systems Engineer (17051) The Johns Hopkins Applied Physics Laboratory (APL) is a national leader in scientific research and development. APL is actively seeking an Embedded Systems Engineer, for the… https://t.co/AtHbGRbtMu https://t.co/4tQnSqnhQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WCS Developer: WCS Developer Ref No.: 18-27431 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position: WCS (Websphere Commerce Suite) Developer Location:Charlotte, NC Duration: 12 Months Contract Job Description: 5+ years hands-on experience in developing… https://t.co/evhTsq7DmB https://t.co/N8hb69CbJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Data Center: Solution Architect – Data Center (71378) Ref No.:18-00072 Location: Rancho Cordova, California Skill Type:Service Delivery Job Type:Full Time Career Level:Senior Level NWN is recognized as one of the top 18 Cisco… https://t.co/4H1Gtw3CUn https://t.co/vtdAVVK9AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer- Advanced Java: Performance Engineer- Advanced Java Ref No.: 18-28395 Location: San Jose, California Developer Assurance : Performance Engineering, Foundation : Advanced Java Concepts, Communication, Apache Web Server, BPS : Network… https://t.co/QszxEMMl3N https://t.co/z8VvzLo1GJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully * Position… https://t.co/yCPCl2XmdF https://t.co/vTp4PAz0c7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging the status quo for PAC management solutions. We do healthcare differently and we are changing healthcare one… https://t.co/htxaylOsWT https://t.co/SrGmbzrJEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager Length of contract: 6 months – could go longer Role is open as it’s a new position. Project that will enable customers to modify their shopping cart. 100% app based. Will work along side the Program… https://t.co/CYE138KBnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React-Native Developer: – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact Menu – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact – Follow us – Twitter – Facebook – React-Native Developer Dallas/Fort Worth, TX &lt; Back to Careers… https://t.co/KKNYXWRUOj https://t.co/NQ2PaSc6Wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Developer – IOS: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place… https://t.co/GZDskVNsoE https://t.co/PDp0wawzgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Director, Data Science: Senior Director, Data Science at Centene Corporation Skip Navigation Contact Returning Applicants Menu – Who We Are – Why We’re Different – Products &amp; Services – Careers – Why Centene? – Benefits – Students – Continued… https://t.co/QCH3If0Xv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Devops Engineer Raleigh, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/26/18, Posted Date – 06/26/18 Primary SkillsDevOpsTax TermsC2COverview Responsibilities: * As part of the DevOps team, you will be responsible for design and… https://t.co/SJ2CSbieYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Supplier: Req ID : 437922BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : The GIMS (GEOINT Information Management Services) Next Program provides critical capabilities to help enable efficient and timely GEOINT… https://t.co/kFKD8G91fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MetaData Analyst: MetaData Analyst Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 07/23/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Metadata Delivery Solutions Team Metadata Analyst The metadata analyst will partner with… https://t.co/Pg0i9elLCS https://t.co/3pOfxxOIzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: BroadSoft, now a part of Cisco, is currently the leading global provider of Unified Communications and Collaboration (UCC) services to operators worldwide, specializing in Enterprise communications and collaboration. As… https://t.co/0WvZ3TUncT https://t.co/rGaU8V0QTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer Remote: This OSS Automation Developer (Engineer II) position in Network Business Intelligence – Engineering Applications (NBI-Apps) will be working in a fun, challenging, fast-paced environment using Agile methodologies to develop… https://t.co/32lVllAqRW https://t.co/AsmEYgPXrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Software Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Cloud Software Engineer(s) (Job #461) &amp; Software Engineer(s) (#457): Dsgn, dvlp &amp; build sw for ntwk security firewall prods.… https://t.co/43EK2luol7 https://t.co/scjhyN7icD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Account Strategist: Account Strategist (Multiple Positions); Mountain View/Palo Alto/ San Bruno, CA; Perform market research and technical analysis in connection with growing Google products and services. #JUN2018MVSBPA AS2 Exp Incl: web… https://t.co/yeZnq5mkua https://t.co/NK1R63IF1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire Alarm Designer Project Systems Specialist II: Job Description Fire Alarm Designer – Project Systems Specialist II (WD***********) What you will do Johnson Controls l is a global leader in the design, manufacture, installation, and service of a… https://t.co/DJ8otA6UQG https://t.co/EfR1ClpRHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineer Selenium and Java: Senior QA Engineer – Selenium and Java in Naperville, Illinois, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – –… https://t.co/j0t8UY4kV1 https://t.co/1c6rxVsbFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Erwin, TN Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/40vaqTZrVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Company Summary =============== First American Title Insurance Company, the largest subsidiary of First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF), traces its history to 1889. One of the largest title insurers in the nation, the… https://t.co/5ccA9uDlcP https://t.co/c1UlAwu9eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent (Military): Jacksonville, FL Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent with Military experience, please read on. We are an industry leading company that specializes in commercial/industrial construction projects. We… https://t.co/kfoTK3CeH8 https://t.co/kAL4VZQ2hY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDM Tester: Req ID 99160BR Business Title CDM Tester Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Reston Clearance Level Needed Public Trust Category Systems Development Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech seeks a motivated, career and customer oriented CDM… https://t.co/qFaQ47XKDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Solutions Architect – Global Technology Practice: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/u2ANnyw2Eb https://t.co/v1VS29GhEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic Design Consultant: Strategic Design Consultant for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) work in a dedicated project team which supports other multidisciplinary teams in a particular project area that involves analysis &amp; investigation of design issues… https://t.co/8yDSpAMec5 https://t.co/TjL1k98JgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: Project Manager II (Interiors – Fremont CA) Tracking Code 5088-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/GXqJtpw9eJ https://t.co/JQvRHeFeUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Associate: Service Desk Associate Business Stores – Kmart Hourly Job Description Provides "World Class" Member Service by surprising and delighting our members every day. Performs daily responsibilities including, but not limited to:… https://t.co/3nXhmyivFe https://t.co/roT2WS2PF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer: ADAS: Company Description The Chassis Control – Driver’s Assistance (CC-DA) group at Bosch is developing cutting edge automotive systems and algorithms in order to make the driver’s experience more enjoyable, convenient and safer. We… https://t.co/4oa4LjZknA https://t.co/7ifiKnwUXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[165-Application Developer: GENERAL DUTIES Individual is responsible for employing agile development processes for building new and migrating legacy applications to a cloud environment. Use established agile processes and tools to capture themes,… https://t.co/BoCIcqkjJW https://t.co/Mi1WDf8ARs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer IT Marketing, Reporting: – Location: Brentwood, Tennessee, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: June 13, 2018 – Position Title:Senior Developer IT Marketing, Reporting – Company Name:Tractor Supply Company – Job Function:IT https://t.co/Aq5OlxGM6B https://t.co/gXQynLE191]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Systems Administrator: UPM is seeking a Jr. Systems Administrator to help execute and support the company’s technology and customer support strategies. Our Information Technology operations and strategy execution rely upon a stable computing… https://t.co/NilpATtzdm https://t.co/HE7mpHI90b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Scrum Master: Job Description Make a Difference Every Day with Team Applied The people of Applied are making a difference every day through innovation and a commitment to help safeguard and protect what matters most. With first-to-market… https://t.co/Domen1WlA9 https://t.co/PfMeMQHblK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: Quality Assurance Engineer Job Description Job DescriptionAre you passionate about building amazing software? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that drive meaningful business results? Do you want to make a… https://t.co/NBPJYxGI7e https://t.co/gUOAWbGpKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Rockville, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/21/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/XjHmmjk5ps https://t.co/RtiFnL0WBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Apple worker charged with stealing self-driving car trade secrets: U.S. authorities charged a former Apple Inc employee with stealing trade secrets on Monday, accusing him of downloading a blueprint related to a self-driving car to a personal laptop… https://t.co/xJC8aqWaVA https://t.co/YEpW9BDwV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer SIO: What You’ll Do Cisco’s Advanced Services (AS) Software Integration and Orchestration (SIO) team is looking for an experienced Software Developer to lead the design, develop, build, test and integration of Automation &amp;… https://t.co/LQw16zpoxm https://t.co/xs3AzDPRPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Backend Developer Jersey City, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 07/03/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsBackend developerTax TermsC2COverview This is NOT Fullstack. We talked to the manager on Friday and he wants a… https://t.co/WI9eXkFl7n https://t.co/X1FSH1FCBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Participant – BIG: Business Intelligence Participant – BIG, #16203BR, St Paul, MN, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced… https://t.co/HjbynnrvjS https://t.co/GQpvNMEUXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R48474 Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/Wmhxjm7xCM https://t.co/93viepi0kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER III: Applications Developer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Develop cost-effective information technology solutions by creating new and modifying existing software applications. Apply at https://t.co/vJMIHGMNDd, Req #… https://t.co/hpTQNLQuU8 https://t.co/pWswbmTvpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer Research and Development: Location San Jose – CA, US Level Master Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 2/20/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering Background Physics, Information… https://t.co/lTBLSQyYPS https://t.co/utGjWkip5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Eningeer IT: Req ID : 417523BR_1 Job Code/Title : E6463:Systems Engineer-IT Sr Job Description : The PQS program is looking for a dynamic Systems Engineer-IT to enabling cutting edge solutions for our customer. You’ll work with fast-paced teams on… https://t.co/td5vZLBv9s https://t.co/gPv1sMdlSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member of Technical Staff, Applications: Maxim Integrated – Job details ? HomeSearch openingsSearch resultsCurrent pageJob details Job details Job 1 of 1 to job Requisition Number5695BR External Posting TitleSenior Member of Technical Staff,… https://t.co/8muCXZyynF https://t.co/3s3MPkyrXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager CRM: Job Description Tracking Code 7417 Job Description Product Manager CRM The Jackson Laboratory (JAX) IT team is looking for an experienced leader in Product Management. As a leader, this role will require working across IT with… https://t.co/nmftkM4ELA https://t.co/1VteLXytkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verification Engineer: Verification Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Work with specifications for memory controller, cache, and input/output designs in microprocessors. Develop test benches in software to emulate processor design stimulus. Check… https://t.co/0VWvS3QaWU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>