<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LandmarkTrust: Congratulations to Nick Blake who won Gold in an underwater photography competition for this photo of a #Lundy seal http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhodri oh no. Sorry if I've now made you self conscious about it. Taxi theme excellent by the way. Always a favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rhodri: A rendition of the theme from Taxi. It's been requested at a wedding in a couple of weeks. Pretty much got it. https://t.co/aLS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhodri yes, on closer inspection, it was beard. But that didn't stop me laughing heartily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhodri for a moment, I thought you'd written "slave" on your face while recording Songs of Praise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jakewaring: Say what you like about Eubank. This was an amazing thing he did that may have saved a life. https://t.co/E39ElN9q5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket it's a certainty. Unless Wayne has a diplomatic injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket it's ok mate, he'll bench half of them and play Wayne Rooney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Liverpool was just thinking exactly the same. "Out of favour". First question, "Why?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lygd those lips though. Get well soon X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Danny_McMoomins: I'd say you probably are a bit racist, Jean. https://t.co/BH7wgJvoa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KeetPotato: me: "we commemorate the day you died every year"
jesus: "thats nice, what's the day called?"
me:
jesus:
me:
jesus: "keith?"…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, another Cloete decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Susan_Rae1: My friend took out membership of Dignity in Dying. Joint membership. She omitted to tell her husband. He recently received …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaJane13 always thought they should use "Stir it up", or "Wonderful World, Beautiful People", rather than some stiff anthem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alicewhitey: I'm not into Donald Trump jokes. I'm into mango scrub jokes https://t.co/ku6QZ0a41x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alicewhitey: The most offensive sweeping statement I've ever heard about women is we all like that Body Shop mango body scrub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertpopper aurora is also superb, if you've not heard it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch https://t.co/kbHOARci6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isaguha sounds very romantic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lurie_john: Whoever did this is clearly an idiot. They are also my hero.  https://t.co/oDVzEdHooR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Vitu_E: PLAY AND MISS - keeper as a shy.... AND MISSES! ENGLAND WIN BY 1 WICKET! #WWT20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah! RT @Vitu_E: WIDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @damiangarde: Johan Cruyff, magnificent livestock (via @sidlowe) https://t.co/UVhOWAs5q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RorySmithTimes: Cruyff once said, at 4-0 up, he tried to hit the bar rather than score because it was more fun for the fans. That's my …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @josbuttler: Recreating Atherton and Fairbrother 94 years later! @root66 #TajMahal @ Taj Mahal https://t.co/NqAdwWPY11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, really. RT @RevRichardColes: Moses and his favourite spot on the back of the telly sofa. https://t.co/8UzuNtvNOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too RT @suttonnick: Thursday's Daily Mirror back page:
I wish I had never signed
#tomorrowspaperstoday #bbcpapers https://t.co/GkbuFvmQLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CroydonAd: Man who 'confronted' Muslim woman over Brussels attack arrested on suspicion of inciting racial hatred https://t.co/yIiHHaNB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCStumped: Fred Trueman at altitude. Hidden snakes. @BackpackBatters Tim Abraham on cricket in Mexico
https://t.co/3F34q5H2bb https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @coospiah: these are the kids you sell a gram of oregano to for $25 https://t.co/o8xhIKPveO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just catching up with the cricket from earlier. Chris Gaffaney has had a bit of a mare with the Root run out, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natluurtsema if you want to see adorable, check out @RevRichardColes new moggy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RevRichardColes: I thought I had lost Moses but he was down the back of the sofa. https://t.co/DHb30vA15X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tickerscricket: David Willey tells children that santa isn't real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimbrunsden went to IB you to check all was well, then noticed you'd upped sticks to the FT! You ok mate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonblackwell: In S4 of Veep we came up with the most meaningless election slogan we could think of. Now adopted by Australian PM. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jane__bradley: Clickbaiting important debunking info during an unfolding situation like Brussels sits v uncomfortably for me.  https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeredithFrost: This is the last sun Antarctica will see for six months https://t.co/Riff5K0tHN https://t.co/lyJDx1WqKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michelle_amaria: Thinking about the time Mia Farrow searched "Mia Farrow and her black children" to wish her daughter happy birthday ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @willis_macp: Australia 4-4. One of those great moments when it doesn't matter if you're using English or Aus scoring system: you're in …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elisjames @paperclipracket why is it that only full backs may "bomb on"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @behindyourback: Someone drew a swastika on Trump's star on the Walk of Fame &amp; there's no way to know if it was done by someone who hate…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Jon Flanagan, captain of Liverpool. Yes. Yes, the universe approves of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @owenjbennett: Next PMQs: 'I've got a letter here from Iain from Chingford...']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamieRoss7: Alan Johnson says Chris Grayling "lights up a room when he leaves it". He adds: "If men were dominos he'd be a double blank…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SachinNakrani a very odd and deliberate misinterpretation of Carra's words from Pardew. But I guess he knows he's preaching to the choir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @liz_buckley: Just telling Meep about your crab jokes. https://t.co/V3VxTtRPoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JolyonMaugham: Something for Osborne's tombstone: "Too lacking in common humanity for Ian Duncan Smith" https://t.co/DW0YgXnDHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Eoin16: Unbelievable Jeff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pettigrew: Knocked out a competition you think you're too good for, by a team you hate, managed by a bloke you wanted. That's got …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We love United" sing the remaining few dozen fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket and it's not like he sees the red mist, that's just his technique for heading. Elbow the guy in the head, nod the ball down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket I honestly don't know how he isn't sent off in every game he plays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JimmyRiceWriter: First piece of analysis at HT on BT Sport is from a referee about a referee. Bore off. Analyse the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nickw84: Indiana Jones and The Free Parker Pen Just For Enquiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Vitu_E: That's what happens when you get your domestic Twenty20 competition right #WT20 https://t.co/JSpPSo9TTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paperclipracket: Googled 'Donald West' for something entirely benign and look https://t.co/iiQnRZavGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lygd filth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lfenner it's nearly ova.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melindafarrell cuties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pettigrew: Wait, I've not watched the Palace game. After his Liverpool tantrum is he defending a suspect penalty decision? Well, f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens the scalp tattoos put me off. Was a fan of Lagertha until she cut the knackers off a dying man. That is cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens Joe Aethelstan Allen. It's uncanny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens does Joe Allen feature this week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomwfootball: "Fellaini was one of the best players on the pitch." Louis van Gaal, March 10 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elpedrovski eh? Not following you there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens well, I would say he is usually, hence my surprise. Some excellent red smoke going on there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrick there. Blimey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely stuff. One more please lads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pettigrew: The two ex-United players don't think it was a penalty. What's the point of this kind of punditry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beijingcasuals: COME ON #MUFC LET'S DO THIS IN HONOUR OF SIR ALEX! #RIP #LEGEND https://t.co/ybNHVFRIQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinNYC75 and we are very generous at times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that the commentators think that Jason McAteerian is playing for Dortmund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ggatehouse: Thereby betraying a misunderstanding of how the press works in the West, and insight into how it does work in Russia https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket you've got to be so careful with these superfine tablecloths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket where are the whites going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaJane13 "turned into"????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levante v At. Bilbao. One team wearing blue and red, the other black and red. Impossible to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @irarchaeology: Wise words....Ancient mosaic featuring a skeleton &amp; containing inscription "Be cheerful, enjoy life" found in Turkey htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket should have been yes. But I don't think I've ever seen a ref actually do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinNYC75 you sound surprised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket tell you what though, I know you're not a huge fan of milky drinks, but that is gorgeous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket coffee shop.... free Rorschach tests available]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket my latte art needs work. https://t.co/1TA40QkhaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket whole bean eh. Get you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lfenner eating his, no doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinNYC75 been on Kolo's slimming pills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crwbanod Irish, you see. And there's no saint Stanley. So they had to be creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Roonbiz @crwbanod should really have copied @lfenner into that. How are you Lynds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crwbanod big fan of Athelstan, although thought it was spelt Aethelstan? Also, my grandad was called Stanislas, on the Stan theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LevParikian @paperclipracket ahhh. I only glanced at the headline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LevParikian @paperclipracket I had to look him up. Good knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket @LevParikian Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMT39: My Facebook has gone peak yer da. "Proudly wear my British blood" https://t.co/Ng8z1JMhVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProfBrianCox: I have an idea. If we vote for normal people without ‘strongly held views’ but able to understand evidence and uncertaint…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket @LevParikian go left field, Bond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lfenner Garfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amycookehodgson: It's what they both would have wanted.. #RIPVictoriaWood #RIPPrince 🎶🎭 https://t.co/4A6JN6jwhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other guitarists on stage "lads, we've been rumbled"

https://t.co/BOPnCCwl8t]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>