<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Senate committee is very skeptical of this; see footnote 41 of the report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone could sue Trump in a court in Argentina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to prevent bribery, this is an efficient system. It gives prosecutors leverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quoted from the Bloomberg transcript.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Tyler Cowen says: "There is no right to an upper middle class lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Twitter gets more terrible in an effort to become Facebook, Facebook is outflanking it by becoming even more terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been a little puzzled about why Uber has been doing new billion-dollar funding rounds every two weeks, but I guess now we know why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other side of the list, America's third-most-beloved corporation is Samsung, okay, and Microsoft is also wildly popular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or are they talking as part of their jobs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I figure about $4 billion from Dell equity investors is the right ballpark number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the SEC order: Between December 2009 and November 2010, UBS issued approximately $190 million of Notes linked to the V10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't that all seem tawdry and second-best compared with building a business that just profits directly from oil-price volatility?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(We've talked about them before but, honestly, the details aren't that important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cut it back? Or attract all the best junior bankers and become the leading banking powerhouse, except on Friday nights?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The cycle of misbehavior is difficult to break," ha. I'm sure there are lots of simple solutions available for this problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Push its price up a bit, not a ridiculous amount.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomberg Markets did a big profile of Bill Ackman, and it came with a big picture of Ackman in his office, and if you shout "enhance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're like "I need to hear more about blockchains" then I can't really help you. Maybe you'll enjoy this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two popular ways to issue corporate bonds in the U.S.: "registered" and "144A."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand the impetus for Twitter to attract new users who don't already like Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the thinking here seems to be: I see the logic, but I don't buy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New York Fed is not short of interesting ideas on bank capital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to a Goldman banker's testimony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What that tells you is: You don't see that particular breakdown of roles all that often!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when banks reported false Libor numbers to make themselves look less risky, that made Libor work more like it was intended to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see how that would be frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Would they have said it before broad legalization, when it would have been an accusation of a crime?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Radio Shack.

Here is Steven Davidoff Solomon making fun of Radio Shack, which has had a long and varied and comical history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, great for investors, I guess, though the word "bubble" has come up. But for companies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also to give more impetus to things like a strict Volcker Rule, which was being written when the Whale losses came out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also if this is how HSBC's lawyers behave on their day out, maybe it has bigger problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, Robert Litan defends his research on the Labor Department's proposed fiduciary standard for retirement advisers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gox, the most prominent online location for stealing Bitcoins, has apparently stolen more Bitcoins. How were there more Bitcoins to steal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One or two hotbeds of insider trading might be an anomaly, but three's a trend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't want to subscribe, but you want the data, so you steal my password when I'm not looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. "The Next Meltdown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinkering with shareholder democracy always ends up looking like a silly exercise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2016, some of my colleagues and I have E.F.F.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This has caused the email server queues to back up,” the report said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FTC has been investigating for 17 months. If it was an obvious pyramid scheme, it would have been obvious by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If you stay on the current path, we believe the potential penalty for being wrong is just too great,” Starboard wrote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Suits are replacing hoodies and ripped jeans at blockchain conferences," says another guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 
Name of the Year
 time. Will Denver Beanland pull off a shock first-round upset against first seed Curvaceous Bass?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or by adding "a cash fixed allowance payable bi-annually," whatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stock is down quite a bit since the announcement of the rights offering so I guess ... has its short-squeezy effect run its course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some worry, however, that a large draw of funds from the Treasury could set off a knee-jerk political reaction with uncertain consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People familiar with his Merrill training sessions say they feature bongo drum playing and meditation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like it is not the name "hedge fund"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite rightly: Again: This seems like the real point of the stress tests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: 

Technically the SEC's conflict minerals rule does not apply to diamonds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather, his incentive is to get all his shares out before converting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And ... this ... I ... umm there's this potato salad thing that I'll just put here; maybe that's the next phase of whatever this is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am one of the worst offenders; I wrote yesterday about Pimco and liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'd been in since April, and really four months in jail sort of seems like the right punishment for spoofing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similarly, only Nasdaq can do the Nasdaq closing auction for Nasdaq stocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have nothing against rich people, some of my best friends are rich people, but why would you join a social network for rich people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What blockchain? It seems to be a more general problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broad pronouncements about the ethics of and culture the industry worry me a bit; ask a banker sometime about recent regulatory failures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M&amp;A types are not happy about this; one says "The measures were clearly thought up by people living in the last century." At least!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One could imagine a trading business that selects for a slightly different personality type (could one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously that is not what Bank of America's directors think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. If factual, it’d be better than the rate posted by any institutional investor in America between April and September.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lawyer __________: "____________ __________ ________________ by ________________."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Regulated Entity" is a "mid-sized New York bank" regulated by the DFS, the New York Fed and the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it keeps happening. Is this one of those cases where the media simply doesn't appreciate the realities of the industry that it covers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just that sometimes those purposes include trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, the hacking is presumably illegal, but is it insider trading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's probably the easiest thing. *** what I'm saying is, look, that if you've got a mate who will like do a flat switch basically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part of the reason for this distinction, incidentally, is the regulators' concern about reputational risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in the form of an FBI raid, but with Wall Street bankers paying millions to take over the action. It's all like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-- and not as a rebuttal to Shiller, who is probably right that the difficulty of short selling increases the risk of housing bubbles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But insider trading does seem a little different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But there are two fun points in Tormar's counterclaim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Most Expensive Bond Market in History Has Come Unhinged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also it's not like investors are calling up airlines and telling them to raise fares and avoid treading on each others' routes, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "misappropriation theory" of insider trading does not seem to me to be obvious on this point, but I guess I wouldn't do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Whenever you have a challenge, that is in itself an opportunity,” said Ari Bergmann, founder of Penso Advisors, a global macro manager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it doesn't actually change anything fundamental about market structure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually, according to his complaint, Schroen was fired in retaliation for his efforts to warn California of the overcharges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even worse is this Moment about the Nobel Prize in Physics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I guess the extra money, plus the need for Cohen's love, drove people to insider trade, is the idea. I don't know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters describes them as "the Financial Information Authority (AIF), the Holy See's financial watchdog."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Wall Street regulation, no matter how tough, will be good for some elements of "Wall Street."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiglitz:  When we last discussed it I cited Cliff Asness and Austin Gerig as advocates of HFT's efficiency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: He also used the counter-party fund he controlled to invest in various private ventures without his investors’ knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgepearkes Though then there is this: Rachel Shasha, 34, a New York-based retail trader, picked a good time to stay out of the market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come hang out on Twitter with the rest of us goons. Related: Why would you join a dating site that's only for elites?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does your hedge fund 

say about you

?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone else seems to have utterly freaked out, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some high-end malls are still doing okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If factual, it’d be better than the rate posted by any institutional investor in America between April and September. Why not, why not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So no one corrects the prediction markets' odds with new information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[has a better safety record than human drivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the Fed certainly knew about the risk-hiding Libor manipulation where banks submitted lower Libors to improve market confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might be like "umm by guaranteeing all its liabilities?" but, while the headline is underdetermined, that is not the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters describes them as "the Financial Information Authority (AIF), the Holy See's financial watchdog." What a cool job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It also found that people are getting these pitches constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those bonds are Japanese yen exchange bonds, and their prospectus is easily available on Bloomberg. Here it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This is a big deal, not just for us, but for the entire Bitcoin industry,” says itBit’s chief executive officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to tell Jamie Dimon and James Gorman 
apart
.

This is just a really good description of bank earnings calls:]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>