<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“@The_Gospels: If the world hates you, keep in mind that it hated me first. -John 15:18”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@SaNniMmairura: Do you wanna know who I am?

I am "chosen" 
Ephesians 1:4”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nicklaparra: How much does a hipster weigh? An Instagram.

You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tissydrizzy Gunna favourite this tweet in case you forget ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tissydrizzy yeaaaah buuuddy! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tissydrizzy Did you know its #KuyaAppreciationDay tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tissydrizzy its only once in a while yooo. Be nice to your kuya, ya know im the best ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tissydrizzy wanna bake your kuya soome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be me one day!  haha http://t.co/fcZEoZdJps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieQuitoskyy Pwerple!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to learn how to rap soon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: For I know the plans I have for you, declares the LORD, plans to prosper u &amp; not to harm you, plans to give you hope &amp;…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does long and maquade have to be closed on a Sunday? I was getting stoked to either get a ukulele of a new pair of headphones....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: I am with you always. -Matthew 28.20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MatthewParker2: My mom is awesome. She dances to my music even if it's not her style. #MomSwag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emilee made my day once again. I have taught her well! hahaha #UnicornBuddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Churches around the world are crying "Why are young people are leaving the church!?" Yet still fight to keep their old wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PAGUGUWHAT gotcha! Ya want some chicken joy? Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait til next weekend. Off to the states! Leggi get some Jolibee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieQuitoskyy It was really good cake! =P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: O LORD my God, I called to you for help and you healed me. -Psalm 30:2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Never hold onto anything, tighter than you're holding onto God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @group1crew: God sometimes uses rejection 2 change our direction to lead us 2 where we're supposed 2 be. Don't get stuck wonderin y #tru…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanMahey Wanna give me a shoutout? ;) haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmZ_N_EmZ Sucks how im not going to choir tour. Lets suck it up together!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyMineo: Follow my friend @Javajock and he'll send you a link to download the best study Bible ever created... free! GET IN THE WORD!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amy_barzilla: Faith is the art of holding on to things in spite of your changing moods and circumstances. #CSLewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andrewvirts: "There is but one good; that is God. Everything else is good when it looks to Him &amp; bad when it turns from Him." -- #CSLew…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: “DANCE LIKE DAVID” IS NOW ON YOUTUBE. CHECK IT OUT!!! http://t.co/01kJdbs858]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to upload the new track once my bro, Ed finishes up some new art!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad company leads to bad character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Unicorn Buddies For Life" - Emilee just made my day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to finish up the song tomorrow and if Im satisfied, im going to upload it. So stay tuned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awkward moment when relatives you don't know start messaging you. #FilipinoFamilies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to Ate JoyJoy! Cousin talk!!!! #ItsBeenSoLong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: I was finally able to capture some photos so here are some spring sunsets.  http://t.co/1FIO3nAu9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pissed off..... Why did you break my guitar.... huuuuh!! #NotInTheMood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive been getting invited to a lot of things lately... Should I go to them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello, my name is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I've been doing the past few hours: Guitar with a side of working on some songs. http://t.co/TEFJOoylUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot cocoa on a hot day. No big deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still have to bake cinnamon buns for biblestudy later... I should start soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: For God so loved the world that he gave his one &amp; only Son, that whoever believes in him shall not perish but have…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta get back in the weight room. I need to start working out again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Gentlemen, we can't be the right person for a woman unless we are first the right person with God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make people smile.... How do I do it?! O_o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircut! About time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz night is hosted at my school and its on my birthday. This is gunna be interesting =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Knock, &amp; the door will be opened. -Luke 11:9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven_Hutchins I got a car xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my drafting teacher bought everyone a Kinder Surprise so we could have "inspiration" for our project... Isnt that awesome?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: I love Jesus. And the only reason that I can even say that is because He first loved me..while I acted as His enemy, He loved …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: Will you forsake your life for Christ? Or will you forsake Christ for your life? May God help us to choose the narrow way. The…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: His voice is a whisper. Not thunder. And you will certainly miss it if your life is too noisy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It should be #ABDC season right now.... Why does it have to be cancelled?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoelOsteen: Keep your trust in God knowing that He will not fail you. He will fulfill every promise He has put in your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: If you have faith when you pray, you will be given whatever you ask for -Matthew 21:22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My RJ guitar broke again... ='(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Scarred....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Beat Making - All For The King (Intro)’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/bYdvrsmdgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Beat Making - Dance Like David’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/ZIfVtQcgfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only I had an Ipad... And Garageband... And FL Studios Mobile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im either pushing myself to the next level or Im just bad at this...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why haven't have I gotten any homework for past two weeks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Tita told me my ex misses me. I Totally saw that coming hahaha #OhhTita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Cast all your anxiety on him, because he cares for you. -1Peter 5.7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @youngchozen: Gods plan for your life will not make sense to other people. Don't waste time chasing human approval.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solving the rubiks cube is not the same anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nerd level has increased. #RubiksCube #5x5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tedashii: O LORD, be my strength! http://t.co/N8tSP9yzQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOAL: Try to get 2000 plays on soundcloud in 3 months time. #LetsDoThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna do a cover of Fly Me To The Moon. Anyone wanna collab? hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 plays away to get 1000 total #Soundcloud plays. #Achievement #MileStone https://t.co/BFx0CiASzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fly me to the moon,
And let me play among the stars
Let me know what spring is like
On Jupiter and Mars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot chocolate from Tim Hortons. Thanks dad!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: John 14:6 http://t.co/fge48NCIr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealYoungNoah: If you dont set aside time to spend with God... You won't spend time with God...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyMineo new album.... Just wooow! #SoGood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHy am I up soooa earlyy?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hillsong: "YOU WILL SEEK ME AND FIND ME WHEN YOU SEEK ME WITH ALL YOUR HEART." Jeremiah 29:13 (NIV)

http://t.co/bp94BOPDtK #ThisIsRevi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concert tomorrow... I should start doing some last minute practicing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to me, all you who are weary &amp; burdened, &amp; I will give you rest. -Matt 11:28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just jad a flashback of the time I was walking with the girl I liked in the most perfect scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesVNguyen: I love falling in love with new music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debating whether to make music, play paper mario or make lunch....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: I have faith that God is living out a divine plan through me. Have faith in God. -Mark 11:22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Jesus can change your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will turn back to me &amp; ask for help, and I will answer your prayers. -Jeremiah 29:12”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RighteousMen: Temptations come when we're tired, distracted or bored...also when we're discouraged and no one's around...the same old t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: When you are tempted, he will provide a way out so that you can stand up under it. -1Corinthians 10:13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PauloApolinar: You know you're a whitewashed Filipino when you call it "all you can eat" while your parents call it "eat all you can"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @CKrushel he desperately need 15 followers by Saturday. #noob #follow #TeamFollowBack #Follow2BeFollowed. #needfollowers #noobie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is in Christ, he is a new creation: the old has passed away, behold, the new has come. -2Corinthians 5:17”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive got our year end choir concert next week and jazz night on my birthday also next week.. Started learning my vocal line today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeannePineda #BadChoicesMaiMaiMakes tsk tsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Godly_Life: I can do all things in him who strengthens me. -Phil 4:13”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeannePineda at least its not 2 weeks of procrastination #BadChoices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know any plugins for FL Studio thats good for EDM? #Plugins #EDM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>