<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dev Ops Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/BhVr6A7V5U https://t.co/anuDxrcgq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wireless Network Engineer 3: Client Reference Code: 215476 Company Overview:Charter Communications is America’s fastest growing TV, internet and voice company. We’re committed to integrating the highest quality service with superior entertainment and… https://t.co/CUzuPnN1CL https://t.co/DCHsABTuS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia's cryptocurrency arbitrage boom fizzles, but profits persist: SHANGHAI/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - When China closed its local cryptocurrency exchanges late last year, an underground ecosystem of bitcoin "mules" and peer-to-peer platforms sprung up to… https://t.co/enHb3BXt1c https://t.co/7lwwAe7gEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Top Skills: Python programming experience Web Services development experience Oracle database – PL/SQL COMMENTS: * Story behind need: New need for the PPNR automation project, regulatory compliance. Would be working on multiple… https://t.co/brssfPyM46 https://t.co/EfT29D3Epc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer: Python Programmer Location: Hillsboro, OR Position: Contract/Full Time Experience: Any Graduate Job Description: 1-2 Yrs of Scripting experience in Python Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python (or) Perl Programming Able to develop Test… https://t.co/8Gvmyj78YB https://t.co/hbR5DwCa8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window Server Systems Administrator Manager: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Window Server Systems Administrator Manager at Scott AFB, IL.… https://t.co/HCEGamB5zk https://t.co/jHyDjWkZBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/DiK5vPeTeb https://t.co/XdUBidzRKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Engineer, Systems Design- Ansible/Python/Openstack: Job Description: Description The System Design Engineers role is to design, validate and deploy technical solutions to maintain, enhance, and evolve the T-Mobile Network and Systems. Specific tasks… https://t.co/LE3Z4izxC0 https://t.co/Ba9I6IdU8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Req ID : 410768BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Orion Test &amp; Verification Engineer. This person will be responsible for writing test success criteria, developing test procedures, scripts and… https://t.co/eMLyt3kcT1 https://t.co/8u6w8mwFxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/Pg7rP4SsD7 https://t.co/MlWPfY0RKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/Tq9y6VbVzt https://t.co/jhUC6hqvd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: Understanding of PC Platform and mother board architecture Good understanding of different power states of system and devices (ACPI S-states,… https://t.co/2GbdkWy3G9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSO / Security Engineer: Description: The Leidos Advanced Solutions Group has an exciting opening for an ISSO / Security Engineer at our customer sites in Bethesda.  As our Information Systems Security Engineer you will work as part of a team… https://t.co/8DtHeK5lc2 https://t.co/3J5kOwKv2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: As a DevOps Engineer at Athlinks, a division at Life Time fitness, you will be an embedded member and hands-oncontributor of an Agile/Scrum Delivery team. You will be in an environment that fosters cross-functionalcollaboration as… https://t.co/y9pLl7NMJf https://t.co/rBMskSKhIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/sIlYtdoDWb https://t.co/YECF9hj449]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: We’re looking for an experienced Rails developer to join our team. Build great products while contributing to our community with open source, writing, speaking, events, and more. In addition to solid software development skills we’re… https://t.co/sriMeEMehr https://t.co/9hOkvc8qCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/8g2obO8ytX https://t.co/AYoQKM7rlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/AIgEm1HBJZ https://t.co/6nHOaMMcLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer-Finance Engineering (Ruby-on-Rails, Closjure, JVM): This client is searching for a Senior Software Engineer with 5+ years professional Backend Enterprise Application engineering experience with Ruby-on-Rails, Closjure).… https://t.co/VJKs6bECpJ https://t.co/R6KF8TzQKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Ref No.: 18-10432 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Role: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Location: Washington DC Duration: FTE – Responsibilities The… https://t.co/apuPIMuXLw https://t.co/AqMy5yW8v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: We are looking for a Mid Level Python Developer for a full-time direct-hire role with our client in North Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Operate and develop within enterprise data environment hosted on AWS. Preferred experience/skills:… https://t.co/dEsmqIm3q5 https://t.co/ODttT0qRsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/E9rKyA4cs5 https://t.co/L2lqkzWb74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist (Boston): QuantumBlack helps companies use data to drive decisions. We combine business experience, expertise in large-scale data analysis and visualization, and advanced software engineering know-how to deliver results. From… https://t.co/vd8ZZiZjXK https://t.co/U9EfvV5JCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Application Engineer: HEALTH[at]SCALE is a rapidly growing healthcare machine intelligence startup founded by machine learning and clinical faculty with strong ties to MIT, Stanford, Harvard and U-Michigan. Our goal is to transform healthcare… https://t.co/hptgM4ICWS https://t.co/pH5TNkpiXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Software Engineer: Title: Senior Python Software Engineer Location: Milpitas, CA The Company: FireEye is the intelligence-led security company. Working as a seamless, scalable extension of customer security operations, FireEye offers a… https://t.co/0gGK3ZHl00 https://t.co/ZlvmdoQEI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippine banks on alert after cyber attack at Malaysia central bank: MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippine central bank has sounded an alert to local financial institutions following a cyber attack at the Malaysian central bank, in which hackers sought to… https://t.co/nJ0DYQjsYB https://t.co/Byy2gz9mmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/hx2yBQzeub https://t.co/pnkFFFCM9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Associate IS Business Systems Analyst: The Senior Associate IS Programmer Analyst position for Amgen’s Analytics and Knowledge Management (AKM) team will be based at Amgen’s Tampa, Florida site. The Senior Associate will be responsible for… https://t.co/x4uAdvC4ou https://t.co/HbhFqH46U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Full-Stack Developer The Motley Fool is looking to hire a software developer that has a knack for implementing deployment and automation tools for web applications. Does this sound like you? Great – you sound like a good fit for our… https://t.co/oiQTwxzau1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Propulsion Systems Interface Validation Engineer: Role Summary Embedded Controls interfacevalidation between Global Propulsion Systems (GPS) and Vehicle Platform toensure proper interfaces &amp; communication between propulsion and platformcontrol modules,… https://t.co/YhUQhuc955]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Software Engineer: We are now hiring a Senior System Software Engineer. NVIDIA is looking for a world-class engineer to join its mobile system software tools team. In this position, you will be part of a dynamic crew that develops and… https://t.co/xzJkrfzIfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Python: Job Description Job ID: R46273 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/9bSr2nsxcE https://t.co/CPlVEahW1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Data Scientist: What is Crisis Text Line? Crisis Text Line provides free, 24/7 emotional support and information to people in crisis, by text. We aim to move every texter in crisis from a hot moment to a cool calm. Crisis Text Line… https://t.co/z3t03XjjyP https://t.co/UFUHJgyaVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): Software Developer (Python/Django) Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture… https://t.co/tb41qSAXJE https://t.co/z4GuIQX8Sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join our… https://t.co/YadPxI0FBV https://t.co/jKKumLg4Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): 106428BR Software Developer (Python/Django) VA – Herndon 106428BR Raytheon Intelligence and Information Services (IIS) – Raytheon Cyber Solutions(RCS) is looking for an experienced Software Developer to advance several… https://t.co/VuL9EZeWLK https://t.co/EgZmiExvos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: At https://t.co/ZJgHz9iFwv, were honored and excited to be a part of what God is doing in the United States and around the globe. Were pushing the boundaries of what the Church can accomplish as we lead people to become fully devoted… https://t.co/bifch7JcZB https://t.co/5Gvls3jjcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Data Engineer Job Location USA-TX-HOUSTON Position Type Full-Time DESCRIPTION At QRI, we are crafting high-end visualization platforms and supporting databases for each of our patented products. Our fast-paced programming environment is… https://t.co/bFGQI70Hvg https://t.co/GDuizgvuMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/eNe6FtyMfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/Infrastructure Engineer: About LendKey LendKey is solving a complex challengeto improve lives with lending made simpleby helping financial institutions compete in the digital age and provide a delightful customer experience, while providing… https://t.co/y8ccLRJKrM https://t.co/tEmsC5q3DJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – DevOps: Metova CyberCENTS is looking for a DevOpps Engineer to join our team of talent! In this role you will: * Performs under general supervision as a member of the development and integration team charged with the integration,… https://t.co/vFyt80e0vB https://t.co/Rcw6RDQhkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/t5e3Zeoyya https://t.co/2gsExlggwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python – TS/SCI with polygraph required: DESCRIPTION: ABOUT EMPLOYER At Employer, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/ywV70lHKgr https://t.co/cmRAWPWkHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Python Developer: Description Responsibilities: * Work closely as part of our small engineering team to build and maintain our HIPAA-compliant platform and back-end that will support our mobile and web applications * Work as a high-productivity… https://t.co/9i9srPvMs4 https://t.co/nXIMBRLF0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Modeler Intelligence Analyst, Senior: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology… https://t.co/LyAMuS8myB https://t.co/tROODeGbe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Performance Engineer: P2 Solutions Group is currently searching for a Sr. Performance Engineer to join our client for a contract opportunity located in Seattle. You: Think big and have experience with the performance of systems with scale. Expert… https://t.co/Ce4QDNGcbw https://t.co/ZZtTxrAUEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Support/ Middleware Supervisor/ Lead: Responsible for the day-to-day performance of a diverse middleware team Allocates resources appropriately to meet business needs Ensure appropriate team coverage to support the timely response and… https://t.co/D9I0FyvAdC https://t.co/UmA3h4vsLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Engineer: Description Dealertrack, a Cox Automotive brand, is seeking a Sr. Systems Engineer/Site Reliability Engineer to join the Release Orchestration team located in Sandy, UT. The Sr. Systems Engineer position with emphasis on Site… https://t.co/VhRDa2LuWD https://t.co/YlaU2PJ0mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/tV8bWxIMXq https://t.co/yh8hTpd7rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/V7QYgBCNuw https://t.co/Gxft1lZjoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Analyst – MATLAB / Python / C++: Job Description Research Analyst – MATLAB / Python / C++ (13286) Introduction: The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located… https://t.co/towcGjPk1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/A7ErNQ8g1l https://t.co/z1X8jQeSaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python and MVC] = TOP School or Tech Company!: ABOUT OUR CLIENT Candidates should be from Top School or Top Cloud Technology Leader! Our client is transforming the private funds industry, one of the largest and best-performing… https://t.co/YYHYooKUqO https://t.co/EKjJsaPi4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Application Developer, Mid Key Role: Join a highly successful, award winning team supporting work with an Intelligence Community (IC) client in Central Maryland. Support… https://t.co/NtNQuM46W1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist- Reporting, Enterprise Customer Intelligence: Job Description Job ID: R45628 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still… https://t.co/sNGqcpQ3Bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Metron | Careers |Data Scientist Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/9quh2s2NeS https://t.co/VKYqfMZaWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/ViKPvCc2te https://t.co/d3IRx9mN2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signal Processing Engineer: Description:Unleash your talents at Leidos! Grow and advance rapidly in your career by letting Leidos challenge you with some of the world’s toughest technological challenges.  Our Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) has an… https://t.co/tIKj6F8zbq https://t.co/MxmlILXAPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description: Leidos currently has an exciting career opportunity for Mid-Level Software Engineers to work in our Beavercreek, OH office. 　 POSITION SUMMARY: This is an exciting opportunity to use your experience to support AFRL’s… https://t.co/FTYkQ3I0bM https://t.co/olFnq1qVfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++, Python): Software Engineer (C++, Python) San Jose, CA Fulltime Position Job Description: We require candidates with C#/ C++, Python, PowerShell Well experienced software development, SDLC skills Candidate should be capable of… https://t.co/nSzuTJqPBt https://t.co/Cfr5C9zlhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window Server System Administrator: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Window Server Systems Administrator at Scott AFB, IL. JOB SUMMARY: Leidos… https://t.co/0sdqxTP1NG https://t.co/4J24xc91gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GPU Development: Description:The Advanced Solutions Group at Leidos currently has an exciting opportunity for a Software Engineer to perform GPU development, real-time software development, and hardware/software integration in… https://t.co/w0SdBPwPDD https://t.co/pWk4fbefOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++, Python): Software Engineer (C++, Python) San Jose, CA Fulltime Position Job Description: We require candidates with C#/ C++, Python, PowerShell Well experienced software development, SDLC skills Candidate should be capable of… https://t.co/AywInhrtu5 https://t.co/DNMAvQCqjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Entry Level, Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/13/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of… https://t.co/EB5ulu7azX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/lEpTSpmKO8 https://t.co/W4EJLlVXPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Application Security Engineer Primary Skills LINUX,AWS,Saml,CI/CD,OAuth,SCIM Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Application Security Engineer for location DC Metro for one of our Top… https://t.co/B2BRcuAeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – (C++, Linux, Python- Proficiency): Req ID : 430589BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Member of the Military Support Programs (MSP) Flight Test and Simulations (FT&amp;S) team that operates, develops and… https://t.co/lAmxeQxQbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer: Description:The Civil Health Operation is currently seeking a Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful candidate will work within an ITIL… https://t.co/5oIgdZ4hkD https://t.co/ncxFkrMu8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Python &amp; Machine Learning: San Mateo, CA Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Data Scientist with Python experience, please read on! Based in San Mateo, CA – We are a well-funded, VC-backed startup inventing predictive… https://t.co/zqSnhwRXhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance Innovation &amp; Technology – Senior DevOps Engineer: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/Lz4lxFA6d9 https://t.co/WZAqxcvEru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – EDS Guardium Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/ZnpWYTOZtr https://t.co/cu4eruRBuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Data Scientist: 7900 Westpark Drive (12131), United States of America, Tysons, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard… https://t.co/MVc71FhR7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/j3QOeBw0h0 https://t.co/WEnZp16yIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/sGDXKEpZcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoC Performance Modeling Engineer: Description:Leidos has an excellent opportunity for a System-on-a-Chip (SoC) Performance Modeling Engineer located in our San Diego, CA office.   The successful candidate will participate in an SoC computer processor… https://t.co/rZM61EmaNS https://t.co/dQcUjLTkkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and engineering… https://t.co/ztLATUxVYa https://t.co/mu0gHdDFx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst – Multiple Locations: We seek for a Business System Analyst with Agile testing and automation background to join our organization.   This is a rewarding opportunity for the right candidate to make good use of his/her analysis,… https://t.co/rAy34UFiDq https://t.co/3UOHpdkE42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage Engineer (cisco MDS): Storage Engineer Santa clara ca Fulltime position Job Description: Provide hands-on server, storage administration, system maintenance and operations support. Build, configure, and troubleshoot vSphere. Diagnose and correct… https://t.co/2FJkqDRoer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/5t9bNX0YbV https://t.co/rO7W6WBMFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Architect: Description:Join a fast growing, solutions driven, dynamic organization and take your experience to the next level! Leidos has an immediate opportunity for a Systems Engineer to provide engineering support to the Airspace… https://t.co/QwTArFtXi2 https://t.co/t1e74MlQMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehouse Architect: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Data Warehouse Architect… https://t.co/UHesvo77BX https://t.co/AWgkztdiPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Integration Engineer: Description:The Civil Solutions Group is currently seeking a Data Integration Engineer to support a large healthcare contract   Design and Implement Data ingestion framework and pipelines into a Hadoop Data Lake for a UK… https://t.co/Qzvs6a21cR https://t.co/JttgCr5qmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Development, Lead – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 216286 Who We Are: Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed… https://t.co/dtscjNryZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Automation Architect: Prestigious Organization is seeking a Network Security Automation Architect who has a strong security skill set as well. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very detail oriented, possesses strong written and… https://t.co/R4HoVS8noi https://t.co/Mua3tpMlUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Professional Services Engineer-COE: Job ID 2018-3765 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Sales About the Job Job Description: You will be responsible for creating customized prototypes during the pre-sales engagement phase (Proof of Concept) which… https://t.co/ooHNOxCUVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Associate, Data Science: Job Description Job ID: R44000 McLean 1 (19050), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive… https://t.co/nIcazux0gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting: Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting jobs in 08057 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/Q3lTQ56001]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Adminstrator/DevOps Engineer: Description: Leidos is seeking a DevOps engineer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for the CEGS system, a real-time operational SIGINT processor. The CEGS applications run under a virtualized… https://t.co/ZyKlGFyfrx https://t.co/wHz4zYxUux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Integration Engineer: Description:The Civil Solutions Group is currently seeking a Data Integration Engineer to support a large healthcare contract   Design and Implement Data ingestion framework and pipelines into a Hadoop Data Lake for a UK… https://t.co/YaAPyvAYpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer III- Python Developer: Required: Python development, Django, REST Desired: Grails or Ruby, Angular, Docker, ELK stack, Jenkins Develops and manages software tools in support of Enterprise Management. Formulates and defines… https://t.co/BmX79nKUoz https://t.co/MxQy6iILTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer II: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/d0agG0w7JX https://t.co/ekmZlLeLO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Platform Engineer – Orchestrated Energy: Are you ready to join a software team whose work is revolutionizing the way consumers interact with and use energy? If you love solving complex problems and building highly scalable, distributed systems, then… https://t.co/X37SU2W7UE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Software Engineer – Modelling and Sim: Job Description BAE Systems is seeking talented, experienced senior principal software engineers to join Survivability, Targeting &amp; Sensing Solutions rapidly growing work force. If you are someone… https://t.co/tvaeCeaf7B https://t.co/YpQsILgLlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Test: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/TSA3Pf4f6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/0fOU1wfWja https://t.co/jymwixXwD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/FqHvv0xIuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Woodland Hills, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Data Analyst, Digital Marketing with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position At Least 3 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Quantitative… https://t.co/xGdaWrN4Yv https://t.co/s52T5GkgVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Title: Software Engineer Duties: * Oversee internal infrastructure for systems and services responsible for data ingestion, processing and consumption channels * Monitor capacity trends to prevent incidents, create and maintain… https://t.co/1GXcMnrSpm https://t.co/0UoOzkjMq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER – LEARN PYTHON/DJANGO! Exciting opportunity for a Software Developer to join a fast-moving and high growth SaaS company in Norcross! Our client has an immediate need for sharp Software Developers with solid Object… https://t.co/Ejy6G3vW4c https://t.co/wgBSGEvotF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist (Python, R, SaaS): Redwood City, CA Full-time $140k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Due to massive growth and demand for our services, we are currently… https://t.co/UssZws20Gh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>