<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty @jessierelephant @josuelaboucane Ba-ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @josuelaboucane It was an amazing Hallowe'en breakfast-dinner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Belated Friend-iversary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @josuelaboucane And did you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleMsCant @jessierelephant Yummy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for the public presentation of the workshop of Residential School this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleMsCant @jessierelephant She went to sleep!  Cookies for breakfast tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @gayvancouver @scizzorwizard Awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorginaPatko: West Side Story @vancouveropera #opera #vancouver was brilliant last night!  If you can still get tickets, do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bren67: Waiting for Vancouver Opera&#39;s version of West Side story to begin and can&#39;t wait to see this an an Opera!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @urbanmommies: West Side Story @vancouveropera #opera #vancouver was incredible tonight! Was I the only one bawling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpusHotel: OPUS Concierge Tip: Don’t miss West Side Story by Vancouver Opera. Last night is tonight: http://t.co/LyyP54rT @Vancouver ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IglikaIvanova: The set at the QE. Vancouver Opera does West Side Story. http://t.co/uS4vF33v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Thanks, babe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story closes at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre this evening. Only one chance left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @LittleMsCant Indeed he will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamanthaCarly3: West Side Story at Vancouver Opera was beautiful! #Theatre #Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story plays at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre until October 29. Only three chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverOpera: Summary of raving reviews for #WestSideStory: http://t.co/Vyt6WOpm, http://t.co/uLNssk79,  http://t.co/n8w1RNb2, htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabeth_Ball: A memorable show, #WestSideStory by @VancouverOpera http://t.co/OQ3m3ZUd, http://t.co/zdJVtlWd, http://t.co/ZIfs4JYp ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephen_rees: West Side Story still has 4 performances at QE (Vancouver Opera) You should try to catch one if you can. Excellent sho ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver Awww...thanks.  Thanks for coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story plays at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre until October 29. Only four chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Broadway_Blog: http://t.co/xYbNVv6y: Opera meets &lt;b&gt;Broadway&lt;/b&gt; in West Side Story: This Vancouver Opera… http://t.co/A ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story plays at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre until October 29. Only five chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Benjielliott Interesting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverOpera: DG Duke, in the Vancouver Sun: "Lucia Cesaroni is perfectly cast as Maria". Read his WSS review at http://t.co/6y8hNDOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmiratesUpdate: #Opera Vancouver Opera's West Side Story is an edgy hybrid: When Leonard Bernstein put together a cast to record...  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @calebmcmullen: West Side Story: Vancouver Opera. A beautiful production!!! A must see if you are in the Vancouver area. #theatre #VA ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverOpera: Another record! Greatest ticket sales day in our history! But lots of seats left for West Side Story. Try Wednesday. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarouselTheatre What a dork!  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Well, tidier, maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleMsCant @skwallin Yay for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story plays at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre until October 29. Only six chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moneyball was amazing.  Even more amazing was the incessant chatter of the two old ladies sitting behind us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Thanks, babe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilliansReviews: Just back from seeing West Side Story at Vancouver Opera. Great show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VanSunCelebrity: Review: Wonderful West Side/Wonderful Opera: Vancouver Opera’s first production of the season takes the company ... ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's production of West Side Story plays at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre until October 29. Only seven chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spennynub @paulhillsdon Well, some tickets are expensive, but they do start at $35.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverOpera: Vancouver Opera continues West Side Story phenomenon http://t.co/4IKQ6NaL via @theprovince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverOpera: RT @VanObserver: Vancouver Opera steps it up with Jerome Robbins' original choreography in West Side Story http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alisonroberts12: Vancouver Opera stages West Side Story http://t.co/cDXG6A6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adrian_ver: anyone interested in seeing this? looks awesome! RT MyVancouver: Vancouver Opera Performs West Side Story http://t.co/qh ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Denisenahvy: ! Vancouver Opera dons its dancing shoes for West Side Story http://t.co/Je8bYIpm latin dancing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobertEG_Globe: In Vancouver, even West Side Story can be a risky show: http://t.co/Gpgey5tu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RLPVancouver: Looking for something to do this weekend? @VancouverOpera opens its season with West Side Story tonight. http://t.co/I ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLois Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @christinequinty It was amazing!  Nom nom Nom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty @jessierelephant @mackgord @littlemscant @lessthnprofound It was a lovely gathering, with (most of) my favourite people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielLegend @jessierelephant @christinequinty Oh, most definitely.  He scares very easily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuietHumTheatre @jessierelephant I was spoiled rotten!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Opera's West Side Story opens this evening at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre at 7:30 pm.  Only eight chances to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a fantastic birthday yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennieneumann @carouseltheatre @christinequinty @tappinmeg @josuelaboucane Thanks, friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey_Victor @carouseltheatre Thanks, buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant They've got the best neck scratches in heaven.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @christinequinty @josuelaboucane @joelgrinke @smlois So good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelgrinke @mackgord Negative, but true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessieRelephant: Did you know that Carousel has an industry rate? Actors, designers, theatre students, arts admin, tech - call box o ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scienceworldca: Please tell everyone you know: @scienceworldca closed today due to a power outage. Free day postponed. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarouselTheatre 's The Wizard of Oz opens this evening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danwithatwist Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnieBreaden Because the songs don't move the plot along, it could be argued that it's not a musical, but a movie with music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord I smile at strangers dogs way more often than I smile at strangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Company Theatre's You Are Very Star was very interesting.  #theatreiscool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty @lessthnprofound Oh, okay.  Well, enjoy the concert!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty Why?  I though you were going too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theArtsClub: RT @alliancearts Welcome and congratulations to Rob Gloor, the Alliance for Arts and Culture's new executive director h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see Electric Company Theatre's You Are Very Star this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DressingUpAGDX: The Wizard of Oz- Costume Madness! | Carousel Theatre for Young ... http://t.co/mWnGB8Ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hollywoodnews7: Wizard Of Oz - Cowardly Lion's Wizard Of Oz Costume Added To Big Hollywood Auction: The Cowardly Lion's c... http:// ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YOURBOYEDDIE: Wizard of Oz is the ultimate chick flick. 2 women trying to kill each other over a pair of shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josuelaboucane Wait!  We're writing an adaptation of Love Story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @carouseltheatre @christinequinty Well, yes.  Anything using kryptonite is obviously mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: Playing Dorothy in The Wizard of Oz a dream come true http://t.co/wJpUhPRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarouselTheatre: Our Wizard of Oz Musical Director Steven Greenfield will be speaking about the music of Oz and Oz trivia on CiTR 10 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@LABeatartsmag: Treelines impress with tight set of indie-rock http://t.co/iJBMln8U” I know these guys!  They're awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarouselTheatre 's The Wizard of Oz began previews this morning.  So far, excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hugo was amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanParkers This is a terrible idea. Not for the minority of people using it hands-free, but for the majority using it to tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gayvancouver: A q&a with @josuelaboucane who plays The Cowardly Lion in the upcoming @CarouselTheatre Wizard of Oz - http://t.co/Mvy ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverFringe: In 2003, culture industries contributed an estimated $43.2 billion to Canadian economy: approximately 3.8% of GDP.  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone have a pair of old tux pants and/or shirt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord http://t.co/jxKS7fyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord Oh, I had forgotten about Chief O'Hara.  That has filled me with so much joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SocialMediaLaw1: “@TweetSmarter: Yes, really: 15 years in jail for clicking "like" on Facebook: http://t.co/ltoP94Kx”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, my piano shell for @CarouselTheatre 's The Wizard of Oz looks like a kryptonite Fortress of Solitude.  Wait!  What?  Emerald what-now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @machinefair: Help the Chop create theatre! http://t.co/v6kgv5Dw #theatre #vancouver #pushfestival]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Congratulations to Jack!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLois Yup!  Today went excellently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant What?  Don't I get a say in this?  What if you don't have my shade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLois I'm in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Q2Q of @CarouselTheatre 's The Wizard of Oz, I get a Batphone to Ben Cheung. This effectively makes me Commissioner Gordon. Awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dwpihlainen @f_c_productions You're most welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLois As far as I'm concerned, any time is a good time to put cookies in the oven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephenfry: This is a petition that really needs huge numbers, or the wild tiger is doomed. http://t.co/qzirPDYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Spartiago: It's sad how Wile E. Coyote is remembered for his violence, and not for his brilliantly realistic paintings of tunnels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day in the theatre for @CarouselTheatre 's The Wizard of Oz.  Exciting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@F_C_Productions ' The Temperamentals is very good!  Theatre is cool!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>