<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Poliovirus is being used to combat brain cancer: There's a surprising upside to the virus that causes crippling polio disease, new research indicates. https://t.co/C9FS5xBtQo https://t.co/xc0Hq01yqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server DBA Ref No.: 18-27622 Location: Rolling Meadows, Illinois Job Description The SQL Server DBA will be responsible for the implementation, configuration, maintenance, and performance of critical SQL Server RDBMS systems, to… https://t.co/6E9nwXfeYJ https://t.co/v95eqBIsp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump reacts to Justice Kennedy's retirement: President Donald Trump responds to news that Justice Anthony Kennedy is retiring from the Supreme Court. https://t.co/cqPzANQmYk https://t.co/DVQCD0WnaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge says government does better job of tracking 'personal property' than kids: A federal judge lambasted the Trump administration for its lack of a system for keeping track of migrant families separated at at the border, saying the government does a… https://t.co/Z4MKkIHNru https://t.co/17nZohtqXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sys Admin-Programmer/PowerShell and SQL: GDIT is currently seeking a Sys Admin / Programmer – Powershell &amp; SQL at Lackland AFB to support the IAFNOS contract, which supports the 690th Cyberspace Operations Group performing 24/7/365 Air Force Information… https://t.co/douKWtjJ9B https://t.co/GbumQfzex7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Server BI Developer: MS SQL Server BI Developer ========================== Req #: ******Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI is… https://t.co/VCwfZ5Qvb4 https://t.co/TqStYp2qi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Fallon responds to Trump: 'Why are you tweeting at me?' https://t.co/Qegx9uD3wH https://t.co/fcM3Aqk3UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBOL SQL programmer: COBOL/DB2/SQL programmer st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 05/14/18, Posted Date – 05/14/18 Primary SkillsSQL,COBOLTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard linked in skype buying rate upto 55/hr Job Overview: Leads… https://t.co/fsJzkz4ZJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer LTSS: Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer – LTSS Ref No.:18-00086 Location: Columbia, Maryland Experience Level: 3 Years Start Date: 05/09/2018 Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer – LTSS FEi is a leading IT company… https://t.co/NUQm3JA02N https://t.co/rDkSvoWg34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary Software Developer: Principal Software Applications Developer (Temporary) Position Overview: The Principal Software Applications Developer will take an active role in the architecture, design and development of the ECS cloud based platforms,… https://t.co/o6Qg9ZSPg2 https://t.co/r6e8lPGlCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the sketch with 3 late-night hosts: Late-night hosts Stephen Colbert, Jimmy Fallon and Conan O'Brien team up to address President Donald Trump's rally attacks. https://t.co/QH41lO08RK https://t.co/qLH9vk7aw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer – Corptax: Senior Database Developer CSC Employer is a market leader in leading-edge commercial tax software and process solutions . Through our unique ERP solution, we unlock the value of the tax function, transforming it into a… https://t.co/YCXtmSWfmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Job Description – Data Analyst (SQL) Job LocationUS-VA-Reston Job ID10301 Job LocationUnited States CategoryInformation Technology/Software Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a… https://t.co/r1f9aJcIIQ https://t.co/LuCbCIy7hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop star trolls Trump in music video: Russian pop star Emin Agalarov, who is said to have requested the 2016 Trump Tower meeting, takes multiple jabs at Trump in his new music video. CNN's Sara Murray reports. https://t.co/Oe2ph6kr4g https://t.co/eZLUJrLdJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer/Analyst Microsoft SQL: Excellent opportunity with this industry leading, Fortune 500 Corporation in Dallas, TX. RESPONSIBILITIES: – Participate in development team for mobile and web applications – Provide end user support for a specific… https://t.co/4B7kStnDLZ https://t.co/sYq1JIOMVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roberts: Proclamation is within the scope of presidential authority: The Supreme Court has upheld President Donald Trump's travel ban. https://t.co/bUGOkDnvQp https://t.co/GzqIUNUCsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Data-Migration-with-Oracle PL-SQL: SR. DATA MIGRATION WITH ORACLE, PL/SQL HOPEWELL, NJ Project Description: A seasoned data engineering consultant is needed to design, develop and deliver high quality data migrations and data integrations for… https://t.co/JwYcWN88kY https://t.co/JfvGfJMFvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBOL SQL programmer: COBOL/DB2/SQL programmer st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 05/14/18, Posted Date – 05/14/18 Primary SkillsSQL,COBOLTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard linked in skype buying rate upto 55/hr Job Overview: Leads… https://t.co/vmyIwWvyq7 https://t.co/Bg5xbdp3Lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$2120: Luxe Crystal Cruises, New Orleans to Riviera Maya https://t.co/20XEi8m95r https://t.co/jSaRhJtwWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Associate Software Engineer at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High Tech… https://t.co/N5CqXZC61M https://t.co/DPl1i9S6PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Server-DBA: We are hiring a SQL Server DBA Location: Columbia, SC Duration: 12+ months (with a possibility of extn) Candidate Type: W2 Only; Unfortunately NO Corp-to-Corp or 1099 DAILY DUTIES / RESPONSIBILITIES: – Identify the requirements for the… https://t.co/hD1ou94WoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ayesha Curry dominates 'Family Feud': "Celebrity Family Feud" pitted NBA stars Stephen Curry and Chris Paul's families against each other. https://t.co/Mn79T0H2Fy https://t.co/7yvR8EJHkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test – Mid Level: Software Development Engineer in Test – Mid Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT… https://t.co/yCNrRoEQs5 https://t.co/SY0b5rSe3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. SQL Database Administrator: Greensboro, NC 27408 #2018-26522 Description Overview The Fresh Market currently has an opening for a Jr. SQL Database Administrator at our Corporate Offices in Greensboro, North Carolina. Responsibilities – Provide… https://t.co/mNhfQL9M30 https://t.co/G0OMBgCDxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toys 'R' Us will close for good this week https://t.co/9shU3r6L39 https://t.co/me7JffpFdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Data Scientist, Data Scientist Assoc, Sr Application Developer,: Capitalogix LLC has multiple openings to work in our office in Coppell, Texas. Sr Data Scientist to translate business needs into data reqs to prototype, develop &amp; launch knowledge-based… https://t.co/bO8kbaGcCg https://t.co/Oi89K9NbHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Award drops Laura Ingalls Wilder's name: After months of deliberation, the organization behind a prestigious book award has decided to remove the name of author Laura Ingalls Wilder because of her portrayal of Native Americans. https://t.co/fQTptBTNeV https://t.co/6tBGHizkly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: PL/SQL Developer Project: Audit/Regulatory Compliance Reporting Team Duration: Long… https://t.co/WJrUdLcQMO https://t.co/ymSUh1B6cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sprint car racer Jason Johnson dies after crash https://t.co/hHQfmZGuXN https://t.co/5NXi2AWy4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer: SQL Database Developer ====================== Req #: ******Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI seeks a… https://t.co/5X1xPjqr4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The real reason Sanders was asked to leave a restaurant: This week we saw two different ways people sent messages that they passionately oppose the Trump administration's policies. And both involved prominent Trump officials and restaurants. https://t.co/dID0smcsqH https://t.co/PjBBpoxGfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS amp; SQL Data Analyst: SAS &amp; SQL DATA ANALYST * Performs data collection, analysis, validation and reporting. * Designs, tests, and documents processes, and SQL queries. * Extracts and analyzes data from various sources, including databases, manual… https://t.co/fYiHIZgQsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Voynich manuscript: Will this medieval mystery ever be solved?: Naked women in pools of green liquid, strange looking plants, and text written in an unknown alphabet; they can all be found on the delicate parchment pages of a mysterious manuscript… https://t.co/scSAv1WnzD https://t.co/v2Kz10RKZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Developer Engineer Angular JS, Node.js, JavaScript CSS SQL Server: BDC is a clearance and settlement platform handling government securities mandated to replace GSCX as a service provider in this domain. BNYM clearance and settlement platform… https://t.co/cz8j9scXuI https://t.co/UIcGHiyoeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Fitness International is a well-established, respected fitness company with over 600 state-of-the-art sports clubs throughout US and Canada. Based in our Irvine headquarters, our IT department is expanding to support new… https://t.co/LLGgBZwEVW https://t.co/enGYayWsHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Careers Center | PL/SQL Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/GmVUmKT4q2 https://t.co/S2GLpDrARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead SQL Server DBA: Job ID 13713-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Leon Leonwood Bean (L.L. Bean) founded his business on a passion for the outdoors, a profound belief in honesty, and an unwavering commitment to quality and customer… https://t.co/zLauYNFHbz https://t.co/GI1AN0FOOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/sql developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/sql developer – ID:31484 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL/SQL, Billing LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/13/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for GIS… https://t.co/ZvYi91xhMy https://t.co/Ysl35rvBKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst III(Excel, SQL, Finance ): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of the business unit. Handle… https://t.co/fNJXHNd6WZ https://t.co/9xlwFeAF6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He died in 1950, two years after they married, now she wants to bring him home: As a child, Ruth Hebert would run on the beach at the edge of the Pacific and look to the horizon knowing her father was out there, somewhere. https://t.co/85mpP53exV https://t.co/6rioQfm8MK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time editor defends controversial cover: Time Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Felsenthal weighs in on the controversial cover featuring an image of a crying toddler superimposed next to President Trump, who is towering over the child. Critics claim the… https://t.co/zveZebJ8T8 https://t.co/O6uTfke0N7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How bad is it in the countries these families are fleeing? This bad: We've been bombarded by arguments about whether parents and children crossing the US-Mexican border without documentation should be separated. But we seldom hear how dire life is in… https://t.co/PIpOvQa8Cp https://t.co/BAnX36bf1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders says she was kicked out of restaurant because she works for Trump: White House press secretary Sarah Sanders said she was kicked out of a Virginia restaurant by its owner because she works for President Donald Trump. https://t.co/d1tzotRyoD https://t.co/CwqIleQo8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL: IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies.… https://t.co/6RtHiRCd03 https://t.co/sgGorJNauh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erdogan faces tough challenge as polls open in Turkey: Polls have opened across Turkey in a snap vote as President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest electoral threat in 15 years of rule. https://t.co/Dq6YF7EqYg https://t.co/bP40ocS96g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Ruby on Rails Developer: Retail Benefits, Inc: Senior Ruby on Rails Developer We Work Remotely See more Programming jobs Back to all jobs Senior Ruby on Rails Developer Posted Jun 2 Retail Benefits, Inc Headquarters: Tampa, FL… https://t.co/TKb0U2u1Y5 https://t.co/mbRgM82tYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MLB home run derby is becoming a joke https://t.co/ryiIW2R5Be https://t.co/mdAl5ZH4Qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL SSIS Developer: MS SQL SSIS Developer Ref No.: 18-23310 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- MS SQL SSIS/SSAS Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More… https://t.co/G9HwPCVcTR https://t.co/aYDW4nwqDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: POSITION: Database (MS-SQL) Admin LOCATION: Charlotte, NC DURATION: FULL-TIME SHIFT TIMING: 3RD SHIFT (11:00 PM EST- 8:00 AM EST) REQUIREMENTS FOR A MICROSOFT SQL BUILD RESOURCE * PowerShell experience o Ability to… https://t.co/StuxRgFH0H https://t.co/ZGSabmGXcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead SQL Server DBA: Job ID 13713-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Leon Leonwood Bean (L.L. Bean) founded his business on a passion for the outdoors, a profound belief in honesty, and an unwavering commitment to quality and customer… https://t.co/RzBkPRSFNh https://t.co/yLVzCXO266]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let XXXTentacion's death be the end of his fame https://t.co/tg1ngIJDz2 https://t.co/0Y0YK1XwOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET – Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience: SDET – Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience in Charlotte, North Carolina, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – –… https://t.co/07X0d0DExd https://t.co/fO5GkrhUmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Carolina candidate hospitalized after car wreck: South Carolina congressional candidate Katie Arrington is in the hospital with serious injuries after being involved in a fatal car wreck Friday night. https://t.co/DNt5OYA6BR https://t.co/OKHZ3hXcpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics: Careers Center | SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Welcome page Returning Candidate? Log back in! – SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Job Location: US-MD-Columbia ID 1957 Overview IMPAQ International, a… https://t.co/hkbRqDv8iZ https://t.co/AbbQ4Z7xZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: MySQL Database Administrator MySQL Database Administrator Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power… https://t.co/4C9OZWal9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Our Client in Atlanta,GA is seeking a SQL Developer for a full time Permanent position with them. ****Only US Citizens,Green Cards and local to Atlanta,GA apply!!!**** JOB DESCRIPTION: Seeking a Database Developer to join our Technology… https://t.co/aNbXZ3eMr7 https://t.co/65QaRFdNbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This team is biggest surprise of the World Cup: Perhaps the biggest surprise of FIFA 2018 is the Russian squad. They came in as the lowest ranked team but have outscored their opponents 8:1 so far. CNN's Frederik Pleitgen visits their training center in… https://t.co/Y6AJ3gEYBE https://t.co/sDFOn2Y5j6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Database Administrator: Location US-NC-Research Triangle Park Job Description Biogen has a large SQL environment with thousands of databases under support, the successful candidate will need to be organized and able to work with multiple… https://t.co/xWIZ2HT7eE https://t.co/XJnrlcD9NJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Advansoft International SAP Services Partner Risk Free Implementation SAP Implementation IT Project Implementation Follow Us on : Toggle navigation Careers – Home – About Us – Services – Industries – Careers – Clients – Training –… https://t.co/hq8NRMLxxl https://t.co/vXop3Fhx6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Database Engineer – SQL Server: Senior Principal Database Engineer – SQL Server at Becton Dickinson &amp; CompanyAsset 1 Skip Navigation – Offerings – Company – Clinical Excellence – Support – Investors – United States – Company – Careers –… https://t.co/5LWo5X85It https://t.co/HU6u5vrl67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp clarifies his pricey wine tab: If Johnny Depp fans have been feeling curious about the eccentric actor, a new Rolling Stone profile on Depp may give them reason for concern. https://t.co/c2ddzNswpL https://t.co/Nu1Ix6tMmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House donates canceled picnic food to Walter Reed: Perishable food from the canceled congressional picnic was donated to Walter Reed National Military Medical Center, the first lady's spokeswoman Stephanie Grisham confirmed Friday. https://t.co/WKvrEWG1RY https://t.co/aZsUCw0kwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Developer | minimum of 5 years of related work experience with database programming, preferably using SQL PL/SQ: Oracle Developer | minimum of 5 years of related work experience with database programming, preferably using SQL &amp; PL/SQL with TOAD or… https://t.co/pHuWH0yHA0 https://t.co/7ZfNFgpQ2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC cancels 'Timeless': The clock has run out for sci-fi drama "Timeless" at NBC. https://t.co/vYJebnxHaN https://t.co/zKhSQZbaAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience: SDET – Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience in Charlotte, North Carolina, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – –… https://t.co/knAtUxx1Ls https://t.co/b8kURlxWIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/de4WY8Lohn https://t.co/cN9AF4YcTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr SQL Server Database Engineer: Job Description About this Role Smart Solutions is in search of a Sr SQL Server Database Engineer to join our hard-working team in Madison, WI to help facilitate developing, creating, and administering assigned databases.… https://t.co/u5sbw9YnHH https://t.co/fG5UW3T7Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neymar in tears after Brazil's dramatic win https://t.co/4Y12nMHinh https://t.co/QPSYNSy5AV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica and SQL Server Developer: Informatica and SQL Server Developer: 18-02111 Ref No.:18-02111 Location: Burbank, California Akraya is looking for a Informatica and SQL Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit,… https://t.co/FnL9c1afjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to be an ally to LGBT friends and relatives https://t.co/7aCHhTVbCj https://t.co/aMdsFiO90s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do… https://t.co/WXI6A3NW8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-DHS secretary: No formal policy of family separation during Obama administration: Former Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson said Thursday evening that there had been no formal policy to separate the detained families of illegal immigrants… https://t.co/MO8zEKi8wl https://t.co/WsiTLsAYsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL SSRS Report Developer: SQL SSRS Report Developer Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 05/15/18, Posted Date – 05/15/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 6-12 months contract. Phone and Skype interview. Must have good… https://t.co/oYIwP47dPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator DBA SQL Oracle NoSQL Finance Banking Tradin: SQL Database Administrator (DBA SQL Server Oracle Database Administrator SQL Clustering Always-On Mirroring RAC Finance Banking Trading) required by our trading software client in… https://t.co/XwTiKljv0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Krauthammer, legendary conservative intellectual, dies at 68 https://t.co/qjZTvCdTav https://t.co/v4cGotEn2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational SQL Server DBA: DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking an Operational SQL Server DBA for a 6-month contract, with possible extensions, for our client in Itasca, IL. RESPONSIBILITIES: * Provide support for the Senior SQL Server DBA. * Manage the… https://t.co/dHwwKEvej1 https://t.co/WBypXX9er9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pediatrician: Separated children 'trying to find ... anyone to hold on to': A pediatrician in Colorado examines young children newly separated from their parents and shares her observations with CNN. She says that while their physical condition was fine,… https://t.co/m3BwZsu42y https://t.co/fJg0MXh3s7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (SQL and C# exp.): Software Developer (SQL and C# exp.) Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 1 Role Description Design IT solutions for higher education! At Ellucian, we deliver a broad portfolio of technology solutions… https://t.co/FRS64JX7XN https://t.co/nXyJUAqJlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst — GRS — Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/TjNv5xfTBL https://t.co/jPj9qqwDoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that… https://t.co/YvGeB7Bfqo https://t.co/ShpJJZevvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Application Development Advisor: Job Description Job Description As a SQL Server Software Developer, you will be responsible for end to end, full-stack development of both internal and client facing applications for Wellpartner’s Contract… https://t.co/t47r7iQgN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: Requisition ID 2018-41177 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Here’s an opportunity to join a dynamic company, GDIT, on one of our engaging… https://t.co/q6rzFtPzTr https://t.co/sI2QGr5YG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job ID: ********-10050-LEK Company Name: Argus Description: LCI is an industry leader at analytical and technological services to the financial industry. Founded over 25 years ago, we handle over 1.3 billion accounts a year for the… https://t.co/hUMs4vbbVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why there are so few pictures of migrant children https://t.co/ijnTu7E7d9 https://t.co/XxHnHS7HfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Warehouse Developer (MS BI, MS SQL, SSIS): ETL Data Warehouse Developer (MS BI, MS SQL, SSIS) job in Hudson, New Hampshire, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems… https://t.co/aV70k2WLM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why 'truth decay' made Obama's reading list https://t.co/6YlAZd8Mvn https://t.co/DVUUC4j2fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing… – Work autonomously with Marketing, Finance, and IT to interpret business requirements to SQL code in order to anticipate, investigate, and resolve issues related to new and ongoing projects. –… https://t.co/822s66xjaX https://t.co/kO2eOu0M5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen resigns from Republican National Committee post: President Donald Trump's longtime personal attorney Michael Cohen has stepped down from a role with the Republican National Committee, multiple sources confirmed to CNN on Wednesday. https://t.co/vZaJcIwUlN https://t.co/BHmXHuBnnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer in Alexandria, Virginia, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers… https://t.co/jaRlIdlev9 https://t.co/gyB1cra9o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer: SQL Database Developer ====================== Req #: ******Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI seeks a… https://t.co/pQmRFW0DyC https://t.co/plH6hqvfBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronaldo breaks international goal record https://t.co/UjtkLXSZ2d https://t.co/Ml0ri8B7xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooper defines the word 'infest' for Trump: CNN's Anderson Cooper breaks down President Trump's recent trip to Capitol Hill to meet with Republican lawmakers over his administration's practice of enforcing a policy that separates families at the border. https://t.co/Qlh8RvAiFE https://t.co/vvQl4xL0yF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Systems Analyst – Associate: Job Description Job Title: SQL Server Systems Analyst – Associate Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: UPMC Health Plan Department: Admin Finance Location: 600… https://t.co/A6Ouvy3NGO https://t.co/SFGIzQFcQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer Health Data Analytics: Careers Center | SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Welcome page Returning Candidate? Log back in! – SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Job Location: US-MD-Columbia ID 1957 Overview IMPAQ International, a… https://t.co/ANcQ1HGDOL https://t.co/OoOFw6V9zL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Integration Engineer: Costa Mesa, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today YOU ARE A passionate SQL Engineer that loves solving problems! In this role you will be analyzing and integrating data from many sources with minimal documentation. We are… https://t.co/R4DMIPcvON https://t.co/o8V9yAF4sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada becomes 2nd nation to legalize pot: Recreational marijuana use will soon be legal in Canada after the Senate passed a "historic" bill on Tuesday with a vote of 52-29. https://t.co/RF2eTv36UD https://t.co/wfJmpvqUDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Lumatrak, Inc. is a Gartner recognized best-of-breed, growing supply chain visibility software provider offering a SaaS (Software as a Service). Lumatrak provides a cloud-based supply chain visibility toolset, enabling… https://t.co/ZFI3HHYVf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA w/ MySQL or Postgres: SQL Server DBA w/ some MySQL and/or Postgres DC Kamis is searching for a Database Administrator to fill a direct/permanent position with a company located in Washington DC. The DBA should have expertise with large SQL… https://t.co/JF0wn3gnsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly a quarter of Americans have no emergency savings https://t.co/UecUXOW12W https://t.co/rgll9Tmmgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior MySQL DBA: *This role has some 2nd shift duties either 2:00pm to 10:00pm or 3:00pm-11:00pm the first 6 months* Prestigious Financial Institution is currently seeking a MySQL DBA with strong Automation Scripting experience. Candidate will implement… https://t.co/LCN40Ol1uQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>