<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Hey it's David Bowie's birthday today. Here's the free @barrelhouse e-book, THE STARS LOOK VERY DIFFERENT TODAY, that coll…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: 9 spots left in @SheilaSquill's Found Poetry workshop for @barrelhouse! https://t.co/BxgH1PodPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alejandrobot: I am the very model of a stable genius president
Improvident, incompetent, and wildly overconfident
I'm getting rich dest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a New Year's resolution that includes finally getting that book published, this is a great place to start!
Registration Is Officially Open! | Washington Independent Review of Books https://t.co/vea9gML1XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: Throughout January, we are open for subs for:
1) Comics
2) $1500 Amplifier Award for emerging lit mag
3) Innovative NF boo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lostballoonmag: Last day to submit for January is Sunday! But never fear if you're not ready this week. We'll be open again for subs on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my happy place #SKIING https://t.co/ouGsbCQg7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KavehAkbar: "A murder / of crows for those of us with eyes / keen yet uncurious. A murder of crows / for those who cooperate / and are…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: having read these submissions last year, I will note: the best ones were very specific, not just in how the money would be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What better way to start 2018 than with #Resistance #poetry ? 

I base my poetry on science
in contradiction to the commander’s standards and wishes
I sing of diverse transgender fetuses
write evidence-based verse...

Read the rest at
https://t.co/BK4PvcxbeO

@PoetsRTN #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: Listen, we have $1500 we need to give away. If you run an emerging/newish lit mag or small press, tell us why you need it.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: @mcarphil @killianczuba @MichaelKonik @ginamyers @nicolebrett Oh wait! The most important one, the one I had intended to e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeingram00: Full announcement coming soon, but I’m about to start looking for the next book for @barrelhouse to publish. Specifically…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, @loki_writes , and thanks @boinkzine for giving it a home! https://t.co/C5huuEvFWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: Hey, remember last year when we partnered with @submittable to grant $1500 to an emerging literary organization? We're doi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fiyahlitmag: Our submissions open up again for the month of January. Check our guidelines: https://t.co/INPyAVdiLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TroyLWiggins: Nobody told me that @TaraCampbellCom had a piece in @strangehorizons earlier this month! https://t.co/fEZHH8UqGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @themoneyiowe: would like to start a subway poetry club in nyc where we gather at one end of a subway line &amp; board the train &amp; read each…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @A_WritersStudio: Would you like $5000 and a month or more to write in Paris?
https://t.co/XKauhPAPW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haay, y'all haaay! Join me for a 1-day intro to #flashfiction @writerscenter 
Get yo' flash on! 
Sat, 24 Feb, 2018 10:00 AM - 12:00 PM 
Registration: https://t.co/okUh75wrpX https://t.co/GI4Il0ENc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReallyJennB @realDonaldTrump I dunno, isn't bullying just *saying* you're going to hurt someone? Actually beating up on them is something else, so the anti-bullying platform is still solid. *Insert truckload of sarcasm here.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndianaReview: Undergraduate writers! IR Online wants your poetry, prose, and art. The editors are especially interested in work from p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricKleefeld: There's already been a Trump parade. https://t.co/wpxOXeSELx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jemelehill: Quincy Jones: I can’t talk about this in public:

Also Quincy: https://t.co/kkhncWM7co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @councilofdc: The DC government will open on time today.
DC Public Schools will open on time today. 
Sadly, the Giant Tank Parade is can…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReeAmilcarScott "Legs," apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MuthoniGarland: Please RT. So you want to get published in 2018? Sign up for this course asap. @startalibrary @barryonyango @EbosoAnne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pubgen: New poetry! "Strange Children" by @danbrady82, available now for preorder! 

https://t.co/16anT7RSg9

"You can never know / how…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeRBlackman: If Donald Trump really wants Democrats to applaud, couldn't he just resign?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pattonoswalt: The DOW is plummeting, the government is about to shut down...

a president: cn we has a parade for Me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bourgeoisalien: I feel depressed today. Think I'll make the country throw me a parade so everyone knows I'm definitely not fat stupid g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@livesinpages All fine choices, sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@livesinpages "Shipment" implies more than one box, right? What kinds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I look at photos of my dad in his #AirForce days and think he could have been in the movies. More info at https://t.co/duyM7HRvcS @airandspace #BlackHistoryMonth https://t.co/S6FwdJHkna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CafeMFA: Still giddy from last week's @WriteinDC annual benefit reading (feat @dolen, @rlswrites, @patriciapark718, Stephanie Grant, an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: Right now the Pennsylvania GOP is threatening to impeach the state supreme court for ordering them to redraw their wildly…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[List: Four Norwegian Immigrants With Their Eyes On the American Dream - McSweeney’s Internet Tendency https://t.co/WWYBsMOPGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenDuckworth: We don't live in a dictatorship or a monarchy. I swore an oath—in the military and in the Senate—to preserve, protect and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @airandspace Archives has been acquiring documents about my father's aviation career &amp; now some of those items will be on display! Come see them at the celebration of #AfricanAmerican Pioneers in Aviation and Space this Saturday. 

https://t.co/zpuQ5XLG7j

#BlackHistoryMonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichalskiJen: Great new fiction from @MacTaylor89 today at @jmwwjournal! https://t.co/oL6Blwp06v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know about you, but the best Valentine's Day present for me would be if we could collectively retire this tired-ass trope that women are objects to be "won" with other small, sparkly objects. I'm looking at you, jewelry industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Free_KGD: Tonight. Let's maintain this important conversation.

https://t.co/yhGD5QSc1J https://t.co/YfXaV96C8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacTaylor89: I have a new story up @jmwwjournal about cleanliness, worry and anticipation. Check it out here. https://t.co/PGDmlZwfEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AsteadWesley: OMG someone overlayed that ridiculous Dodge/MLK ad with what King actually said about capitalism and car commercials http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marccold: COLLEAGUES: You're very young. You must know Snapchat!

ME: I'm 35!

STUDENTS: It's so weird you remember before the Internet…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelSteele: The folks at @TheOnion after reading the #NunesMemo have sent a cease and desist order to the House Intelligence Committ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lady_Star_Gem: A comprehensive list of @BarackObama scandals in 8 years:

.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ggreeneva: What if America — hold on for a crazy thought — paid school workers enough to make covering a Costco membership an afterthou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danbrady82: Poet friends! @Barrelhouse is looking for craft sessions our annual DC conference. I'd love to have you there! https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like an amazing novel! https://t.co/MdzGbf5asp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambernoelle This thread prompts me to thank Darkhouse Books for being proactive and consistent with their royalty payments--no matter how small they may be: https://t.co/d4H8NYWJrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KateAronoff: Boomers, 26: It's great to be 4 years into my union job with great benefits, a pension and job security

Millennials, 26:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thoughtful take on #OwnVoices by @EvenEd74 @wirobooks Washington Independent Review of Books https://t.co/dBQqT7dkn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karaoakleaf: excited to see translation as a new NBA category: National Book Awards Add Category Honoring Works In Translation https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @2040Books: Let us introduce ourselves! We're an imprint of @SFWP publishing #multicultural voices! Read this interview with our editor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because why would you need any relevant knowledge or qualifications to head a council? 

"Trump re-nominates environmental pick Democrats called 'extreme' and 'embarrassing'" https://t.co/xGCp7ykgb5 via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Powerful. Do yourself a favor and read @NancyHightower's latest #poem at @HeavyFeatherRev #Poetry: "Ouroboros" by Nancy Hightower https://t.co/ytweqGscv9 via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, get on this! @UncannyMagazine #submission opportunity: https://t.co/IKWN2gJWbX #criplit #Disability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#flashfiction #writers, here's another #contest for you, low entry fee and a chance to win $500: https://t.co/mi43v5V9Ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my #flashfiction #writers: Dreaming of #Greece? Enter your #story for a chance to win a vacation:

https://t.co/FLgaYPer9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AllisonWynifred: This president’s meter of success is whether or not he stayed in script. Ah to be a white man. https://t.co/3nacdJLoC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JellyfishReview: Poets - Indiana Review @IndianaReview have a contest coming up soon they'd like to spread the word about, so tell your…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @826dc: Are you ready for the February lowercase? Meet us at Petworth Citizen next week for our monthly open mic.

https://t.co/xLrV5nzK…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelSkolnik: Las Vegas Shooter:
Not an immigrant
Sandy Hook Shooter: 
Not an immigrant.
Charleston Church Shooter:
Not an immigrant.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly I'm up way too late... https://t.co/LXzimKEish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upload cover of a great book without saying why; mention who invited you (@abby_serino) invite 8 others to do the same @juliascribbling @CarrieCallaghan @AABastianWrites @raimalarter @DeMistyB @HSmithWrites @RichardAgemo @EvenEd74 https://t.co/3beIB7pYs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PrairiePhlox: Lately I’ve seen a number of posts requesting woman raise their voices if they enjoy SF/F and others asking “Who the next…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @isabelzawtun: Tonight at work a creepy dude asked me "what's your secret to staying so slim and perky?" I responded "I'm a thousand yea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ghetsuhm: I have this theory that cycling is as close as a middle-class straight white guy can get to understanding Being Female. Peopl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Yo Writer, Editor, Publisher people! @barrelhouse is looking for craft workshop and panel discussion proposals for our con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RLSWrites: Alums of @WriteinDC send me yr latest publication news so we can announce @ our annual faculty benefit reading @ @826dc this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: We have $1500 we want to give away to an emerging lit mag/small press, and you have 5 more days to apply:
https://t.co/Iqf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattPerez18: Somewhere there is an evil dragon atop a nest of phone chargers and wires eating all of our forgotten passwords and userna…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SheilaSquill: I'm taking submissions for POP Love! a February blog series at @barrelhouse. Send me something awesome! https://t.co/sAgQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: If you'd like to buy these shirts:
https://t.co/WVVs4GExY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndreaMHahn: “I skied back to the Pole again … to take this photo for all those men  who commented ‘Make me a sandwich’ on my TEDX Talk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Wigleaf: Friday morning PSA: we are now open for no-fee subs for the Mythic Picnic Fiction Prize. An exciting time :) @MythicPicnic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DelishDotCom: Maple bacon brie bread is everything you've ever wanted. https://t.co/8QwRO8UAMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barrelhouse: Hello, if you see another magazine advertising or selling a design very similar to this one, please note that we've been s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cnnbrk: The US Olympic Committee's CEO tells USA Gymnastics it will lose its status as a sports governing body unless the entire board…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bookbent Right here with you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CottonXenomorph: EXCITING NEWS‼️

We're all about giving back. For the month of February, donate $10 or more to a charity of YOUR choic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Hey writery people: @barrelhouse is currently open for a whole lot of stuff:
-- Amplifier grant
-- book-length NF queries…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kimbiliofiction: Applications to Become a Kimbilio Fellow are Now Open! https://t.co/cat3TsumUq https://t.co/3sxO3azleC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fakemikemulloy: If you didn’t like the Judge’s tone with Larry Nassar wait til you hear a sentencing for a black teenager with a 1/4 ou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karinbrulliard: Hey, journalists! The @washingtonpost is hiring a science reporter. The lucky person will work on the most collegial de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simoncholland: Is it weird that more is being done to stop teenagers from eating laundry detergent than shooting each other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYTHealth I vote for "Dr. Worm"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NYTHealth: This tiny robot can walk and swim -- inside you https://t.co/tN7JHtMQGM https://t.co/6CizkSvh3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[List: Things That Begin a Sentence That Indicate You May Need to Refrain From Finishing That Sentence - McSweeney’s Internet Tendency https://t.co/akmMojB9HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lnnie: Beech trees they grow smaller branches towards those other beech trees they are "friends" and try not to steal their sunlight.
B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FallfortheBook: We're now accepting #submissions for our post-publication book prize for Immigrant Writers. Postmark deadline March 31:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_celia_marie_: Sexual predator Larry Nassar assaults over 150 girls over the course of 30 yrs, sentenced to 175 yrs in prison &amp; men are…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SmokeLong: What's that? Our first-ever #flashfiction contest? You heard right! We're celebrating our 15th birthday with 15 Weeks, $1500…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raimalarter Ah, I get it. I sometimes think about my journals that way, except the opposite--the earlier they are the more excruciatingly embarrassing they are. I might just have to burn them soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dozen Camels Disqualified From Saudi Beauty Pageant Over Botox Injections https://t.co/Zx7apyrGj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raimalarter Why throw them out? Someday you might look back on them and feel the same way you feel now about your high school and college journals. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Hey Writer/editor/publisher people: @barrelhouse is open for proposals for craft workshops and panel discussions for our c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @suemonkkidd: “We are volcanoes. When we women offer our experience as our truth, all the maps change. There are new mountains. That’s w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Writer Types! Applications are now open for @barrelhouse Writer Camp, a super laid-back, productive, fun retreat in Centra…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>