<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer * Job Category: Software Development / IT * City, State: Louisville, KY * Apply Method: Email Apply * Email Address: jobs@rainbowdesign.net * Employer Name: Rainbow Design Services Job Description ABOUT US… https://t.co/J5WRKcgjwg https://t.co/ROVPwof99d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA): Selene Finance | Job Description Page Requisition Number: 2018-024-FL-5100 Job Title: SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA) City: Jacksonville State: FL SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA) Email Description/Job Summary Job Title: SQL Developer… https://t.co/tlSkc2PRMq https://t.co/xD80lDtzxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server / Oracle Database Administrator: Req ID 94687BR Business Title SQL Server / Oracle Database Administrator Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Bethesda Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Systems Development Job Duties and Responsibilities… https://t.co/5k0OZanNCD https://t.co/QWKSA5BaHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: INTERVIEW PROCESS: Hiring manager is in need for a SQL DBA Ability to manage multiple projects at once Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/jCneddnkr6 https://t.co/lQ8a2u7EgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla says crashed vehicle had been on autopilot prior to accident: LOS GATOS, California (Reuters) - Tesla Inc said on Friday that a Tesla Model X involved a fatal crash in California last week had activated its Autopilot system, raising new questions… https://t.co/Qf0tUyQzu2 https://t.co/O2gAiwrwf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (PHP/MySQL + React): About Us Refersion is a fast growing, bootstrapped, and profitable B2B app development company located in New York City. Our flagship product is a sales tracking and marketing (SaaS) platform in the e-commerce… https://t.co/wosQkpPHWy https://t.co/9z3hJmmfjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: Position Purpose: Administer, maintain, develop and implement policies and procedures for ensuring the availability, performance, and integrity of the company database. Mentor and act as the go to person for other Database… https://t.co/cekjZBV6VY https://t.co/MZnKnSwxcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET / SQL Server Developer (Presentation Layer): C#/.NET Developer (Presentation Layer) In search of a C#/NET Developer with focus on the presentation layer and conversational user interface. In addition to C#/.NET, applicants must have or quickly… https://t.co/Ijj2eJQD80 https://t.co/hsck4T5p6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Engineer II or ABOVE (Java, Python, SQL) – Digital Innovation Team: Product Engineer (Java, Python, SQL), Digital Innovation TeamAt Company, were building the future of payments. As a member of the Digital Innovation team, youll be part of a team… https://t.co/lufLhJwWrz https://t.co/E5HQK0stfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: This is a MS SQL / MySQL Server DBA role largely responsible for providing operational database services to the organization. We are looking to fill a need to have a highly competent and highly motivated individual in this… https://t.co/SE8kflVKqR https://t.co/sbQDRGvFeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Backend: JAVA BACKEND- COLUMBUS, OH, DURATION : 6+MONTHS We are looking to hire 2x Core Java developers strong backend ( multithreading, hibernate, SQL, Messaging ( Kafka/ JMS/Rabbitmq) immediately for a financial services client. The team would be… https://t.co/GnHllkXhUB https://t.co/msqY6gj0B5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator approves SpaceX plan for broadband satellite services: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The top U.S. telecommunications regulator on Thursday gave formal approval to a plan by Elon Musk's SpaceX to build a global broadband network using satellites. https://t.co/M3LWbvoT6g https://t.co/KqCF2DmYGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer: SQL BI Developer – Smart Folks Inc. – Ann Arbor, MI – 02-21-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career Toolkit… https://t.co/vmQL8r2ydd https://t.co/MuCtpbGQNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: The resource will be working on integration projects using SQL 2008/2012/2017, Workload Automation (Scheduling tool). We are looking for a DBA who can provide SQL Server development skills mostly around stored procedure development… https://t.co/8ojClMub3Q https://t.co/fdjURONfPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6 MVC / MS SQL Back-end 16371: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical… https://t.co/EGbgnXaJg8 https://t.co/CAAomhaTpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP REST Web Services: Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP &amp; REST Web Services | CareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise… https://t.co/7iKRM9tWrm https://t.co/hJMEyMnRTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer – C#, Node.JS, and NoSQL: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed… https://t.co/hSJixiqjjw https://t.co/xViGlb6Q6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba says unable to meet end-March deadline for chip unit sale: TOKYO (Reuters) - Toshiba Corp said on Friday it would not be able to complete an $18 billion deal to sell its prized chip unit by an agreed deadline at the end of March, as it had not… https://t.co/vDl88Ju9mK https://t.co/Lar1QfueTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Java Developer: Acadaca is looking for a passionate, smart and articulate Java Developer to help build and support our core software products and services. We are a ~70 person interactive technology company specializing in ecommerce, Content… https://t.co/stD2W3ZevT https://t.co/gypO1v4r6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Technical Support Engineer, MCS – (San Diego, CA or Horsham, PA): NextGen Healthcare has a legacy of building software that improves patient care and reduces healthcare costs. Now, were bringing the best of the cloud, social media and mobile to… https://t.co/yvynMA8yqv https://t.co/1y7Hnj3gwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Teradata Systems Analyst: (2) SQL TERADATA SYSTEMS ANALYST DETAILS LOCATION: Dallas, TX/Stephenville, TX – Position will require an initial 3-6 weeks (depending on experience) in Stephenville, TX for knowledge transfer. After that knowledge transfer… https://t.co/3NpXMFNsdd https://t.co/P4eJkCH2ag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (PHP/MySQL + React): About Us Refersion is a fast growing, bootstrapped, and profitable B2B app development company located in New York City. Our flagship product is a sales tracking and marketing (SaaS) platform in the e-commerce… https://t.co/X6v6AtG1l6 https://t.co/h1OMPUgntH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: INTERVIEW PROCESS: Hiring manager is in need for a SQL DBA Ability to manage multiple projects at once Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/vkBhhC5PIS https://t.co/LJ063OQSOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businesses, consumers uncertain ahead of China VPN ban: BEIJING (Reuters) - Businesses and consumers in China are bracing themselves ahead of a March 31 ban on non-state sanctioned virtual private networks (VPNs), saying regulators have not provided… https://t.co/lsqL5Rpugh https://t.co/pqSeK5azfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Director: TECHNOLOGY It’s work that matters. It’s what we do at Symantec. Symantec is the world leader in providing solutions to help individuals and enterprises assure the security, availability, and integrity of their information. In essence,… https://t.co/GBlUKhtLyX https://t.co/afeAqmlext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: OCR ensures compliance for international trade through a comprehensive solution that improves operations, complies with government regulations, saves money and provides a competitive advantage. OCRs solutions enable global corporations to… https://t.co/gtHWPyikJM https://t.co/uoqumahmyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer: SQL BI Developer – Smart Folks Inc. – Ann Arbor, MI – 02-21-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career Toolkit… https://t.co/JPVV8cXFym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal Developer: LCG Inc. is seeking a Drupal Developer to support web-based content management systems for a Federal agency. The Developer will have broad experience in web application development, requirements, and design. He or she will be… https://t.co/ntEkPEzpMr https://t.co/QAuojG37ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: IT Positions available at Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: SYSTEMS ANALYSTS: Analyze, design, develop &amp; test applications. Prepare test plans. Create &amp; automate test scripts. Perform risk analysis.… https://t.co/sdQ6Zsg8yI https://t.co/mYhTAZTAZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn fourth-quarter net profit estimated T$71.66 billion, up 4 percent from year ago: TAIPEI (Reuters) - Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and a key Apple Inc supplier, reported on Friday 4.2 percent growth in fourth… https://t.co/Phk2E5zHAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (DBA)-SQL: Join our team of SQL Professionals and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Experience with SQL… https://t.co/wSV8HtVNql https://t.co/AKvKbdiBjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: REQUIRED SKILLS Experience in relational database design, development, and support (MS SQL Server T-SQL preferred) Experience in complex database objects in T-SQL and/or PLSQL Experience with SSIS and/or ETL tools Experience with Visual… https://t.co/1Ga6BprtvT https://t.co/AmxPVKVYKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Programmer – Remote 15697: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology,… https://t.co/c8xiy8XUCA https://t.co/8vyIR5vX9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Data Science – Requisition ID R41471: Requisition ID R41471 At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a mission to… https://t.co/AJd9UcBYQA https://t.co/0hVWfa1GFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst III(Healthcare, Hedis,SQL): Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of the business unit. Handle complex data projects and acts as a lead for other Data Analysts. Provide advanced analytical support for business operations in… https://t.co/BDpRb8tXqv https://t.co/0NLZLvsNs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore watchdog says Uber-Grab deal may have infringed competition: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Singapore's competition watchdog said it had reasonable grounds to suspect competition had been infringed by Uber Technologies Inc's [UBER.UL] deal to sell its… https://t.co/qhHnP8R3WE https://t.co/REiCcjyzET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects: Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects | CareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security – Interactive –… https://t.co/ehOjVdzaO1 https://t.co/mVKpdbytc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – C#, https://t.co/hQSAXGaBJi, SQL, HTML: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US .Net, *******, C#, HTML Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/0TMxYNbhmb https://t.co/wc4JarpRxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Tester: SQL Server Tester Ref No.: 18-09717 Location: Florida, Massachusetts Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for SQL Server Tester in Florida, MA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can… https://t.co/d4W6PMHnEs https://t.co/GDvORj6ab3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Spring Developer: Job Description: Java/Spring Developer will be responsible for designing, developing and implementing custom services for the Records and Information Archive application. Requirements: * 7+ years of professional Java development… https://t.co/0cCmJ85iu6 https://t.co/ibgf54doSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer Title: Oracle PL/SQL DeveloperPosition Type: ContractLocation: Phoenix, AZWork Authorization considered: EAD Greencard H4 US Citizen Description:Qualifications:??? ?Bachelor’s degree in computer science or… https://t.co/Cl0RR10BLj https://t.co/8D6oLH9LQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle/ETL Informatica Support Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We… https://t.co/9ZBNZIZGJX https://t.co/RgknHt85fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg disavows memo saying all user growth is good: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - A Facebook Inc executive said in an internal memo in 2016 that the social media company needed to pursue adding users above all else, BuzzFeed News reported on Thursday,… https://t.co/bzHGt7U2ah https://t.co/yE0Nbz2oRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: SQL Server Philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary *************,SQL,.net,T-SQL,IBM MQ,MSMQ,advent MOXYTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview Functional Skills: * Must have experience with Order… https://t.co/n70jnG876m https://t.co/bHqsXaDAX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Risk Analytics Consultant 2- Data Infrastructure Analyst: Job Description ** This position is open to any location in the Wells Fargo footprint** It starts with you. We must attract, develop, retain and motivate the most talented people – those… https://t.co/bqfeZuaqxi https://t.co/FfRXmIengb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Programmer/ Analyst: Information Technology Services (ITS) The ITS unit exists to provide comprehensive information technology delivery and support in the form of personnel, desktop and mobile computing, multi-media equipment, hardware, network… https://t.co/TFMCVzcWm1 https://t.co/3mxyjvRIPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Support Analyst 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers more than 12… https://t.co/ObZyVkg4zb https://t.co/821E0rvcJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA – Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/NoNaNTYlCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook begins 'fact-checking' photos and videos: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Thursday it had begun "fact-checking" photos and videos to reduce the hoaxes and false news stories that have plagued the world's largest social media… https://t.co/D729Eht2CR https://t.co/gfqoTeuvag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer (NOSQL /J2EE / Spring / JavaScript /HTML): Company is a global leader in investment management, risk management and advisory services for institutional and retail clients. At December 31, 2016, Companys AUM was $5.1 trillion.… https://t.co/PHxWiYfV4K https://t.co/gYv7ZmSk4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Risk Analytics Consultant 2- Data Infrastructure Analyst: Job Description ** This position is open to any location in the Wells Fargo footprint** It starts with you. We must attract, develop, retain and motivate the most talented people – those… https://t.co/78Z3RwYUds https://t.co/9sHc1aXq9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III(Buisness Operations, Claims, SQL) (Pittsburgh or Harrisburg): Position Purpose: Perform various analysis and interpretation to link business needs and objectives for assigned function. Support business initiatives through data… https://t.co/5LENwf5Cyq https://t.co/f4B175Ax2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst:   Programmer Analyst (Fort Worth, TX): Operate Candor (IT business intelligence and data analytics application) with a focus on agile development methodologies leveraging capacity management, configuration management, storage, and… https://t.co/lzCaa1V93u https://t.co/F4TRdHGwIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysian central bank says foiled attempted cyber-heist: KUALA LUMPUR/LONDON (Reuters) - Malaysia's central bank said on Thursday it was the victim of a cyber attack in which hackers sought to steal money using fraudulent wire transfers, the latest in a… https://t.co/nW8G1HlD7h https://t.co/ydVdeeWQys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst:   Programmer Analyst (Fort Worth, TX): Operate Candor (IT business intelligence and data analytics application) with a focus on agile development methodologies leveraging capacity management, configuration management, storage, and… https://t.co/k4prKkQGWk https://t.co/C3WcEGe0n6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 5 Compensation Systems: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center… https://t.co/d0mT2KCX15 https://t.co/g6U3eGJjP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer: SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer THIS IS A W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE OPPORTUNITY. CORP TO CORP REPRESENTATIVES OR APPLICANTS NEED NOT APPLY (NO C2C) ALIS Software is seeking an experienced SQL Developer for a contract to hire opportunity with an… https://t.co/N4tsLsGMzL https://t.co/yu7ZykX6QD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/NeD45SfoPd https://t.co/F6l1aGl1zJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: This is a MS SQL / MySQL Server DBA role largely responsible for providing operational database services to the organization. We are looking to fill a need to have a highly competent and highly motivated individual in this… https://t.co/mNGzc8UFMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banner Programmer: Department: University Computing Services Salary Range: $66,360 – $105,228 annually Class: C1464 Recruitment #: S1808 Review Date: Review of applications begins March 23, 2018. Position open until filled. This is a regular, full-time,… https://t.co/bkppjnesce https://t.co/7pbXTZLYks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysia's central bank says foiled attempts at unauthorized fund transfers: KUALA LUMPUR (Reuters) - Malaysia's central bank said on Thursday it had detected and foiled an attempted cyber attack and efforts to transfer funds without authorization using… https://t.co/uQof4zk4Cd https://t.co/bomEKkC4Bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: The resource will be working on integration projects using SQL 2008/2012/2017, Workload Automation (Scheduling tool). We are looking for a DBA who can provide SQL Server development skills mostly around stored procedure development… https://t.co/0BeNQOYBnI https://t.co/aekWBLhZ9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead/Sr. Software Engineer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Fairfax, Virginia, United States Position ID: J0717-0716 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: CGI is looking for a… https://t.co/WYP4QYiprR https://t.co/lfB0PkV7Uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – C#, https://t.co/hQSAXGaBJi, SQL, HTML: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US .Net, *******, C#, HTML Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/U1bvj7P2yI https://t.co/ReZImwI7qK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Modeler â€“ PL/SQL Developer: Job Details: * Job Title: (WEEKEND DRIVE) Data Modeler PL/SQL Developer * Hire Type: Full Time / Permanent / Direct Hire * WEEKEND DRIVE: Walk-Ins for local candidates and Webex video call for non-local candidates. Job… https://t.co/3TA8dlFAA6 https://t.co/7Yf2dRv29R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Description * Understanding the customer requirements in detail and developing the application design and architecture. * Taking care of Customer scalability and security requirements to develop robust architecture, which is more secure… https://t.co/HkbYfzCj0P https://t.co/4UT6I7SCky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GameStop tops revenue estimates on robust Nintendo Switch sales: (Reuters) - GameStop Corp , the world's largest video game and gaming console retailer, reported revenue that beat analysts' estimates for the fourth straight quarter as sales of Nintendo… https://t.co/z7ipiCnZ7F https://t.co/e1x7eOWJKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: SQL Server Philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary *************,SQL,.net,T-SQL,IBM MQ,MSMQ,advent MOXYTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview Functional Skills: * Must have experience with Order… https://t.co/ZZnueBwGdC https://t.co/HXMxAT0nRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Site Reliability Engineer – SQL Server: SR. CLOUD SITE RELIABILITY ENGINEER – SQL SERVER TYPE:Permanent RESPONSIBILITIES * Works on all Microsoft SQL strategy, design, troubleshooting, and operations. * Responsible for maximizing system uptime… https://t.co/7oSDHam0Fz https://t.co/CxcKDa34Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Risk Consultant 5-Data/Predictive Analytics: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/pOx1SfDnIR https://t.co/NxxDN8JRIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst III(SQL, Healthcare, Business intelligence): Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of the business unit. Handle complex data projects and acts as a lead for other Data Analysts. Provide advanced analytical support for… https://t.co/N1dm6MwhOe https://t.co/BxN5egavkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 5 (ProfitView Business Implementation Lead): Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/vBJvdhg1wL https://t.co/srqO3DkfT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL specialist: Ekleft is an international IT outsourcing company which has provided high-quality services to blue chip Companies since 2008. Ekleft specializes in the establishment of IT DDC from the scratch in across the Globe. The company has… https://t.co/bRdkjcLuo7 https://t.co/tLYVjBbWDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook privacy debate is tip of the e-commerce iceberg, U.N. says: GENEVA (Reuters) - The scandal over data privacy that is causing a headache for Facebook Inc shows just one aspect of the huge task of preparing the world for e-commerce, the United… https://t.co/nuKItzWPdC https://t.co/mYS66o0heQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Risk Consultant 5-Data/Predictive Analytics: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/JWXIHVZ6QW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Analyst – Job ID R42043: Job ID R42043 Updated date 02/08/2018 Location Richmond, Virginia West Creek 7 (12077), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company.… https://t.co/VzILhpiuws https://t.co/q3QiAYYGBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/vsozPcyUgF https://t.co/MUd6Jm7ZRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apps Programmer/Analyst 3: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers more than 12… https://t.co/9bZyPEtC0H https://t.co/WO4f01OoYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer – C#, Node.JS, and NoSQL: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed… https://t.co/3zdT8azUq4 https://t.co/LdOiBndjKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber seen girding for battle with Ola in India ahead of IPO: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - Uber's decision to exit Southeast Asia, where it was bleeding money, should give the global ride-hailing giant more firepower to focus on India, where it's locked in a… https://t.co/8eU5wVJaDG https://t.co/RaxLr5NAvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Why would a SQL Data Base Administrator ever want to work for a mortgage company? Well, let us tell you why! What You Need To Know * Develop operational policies, procedures, controls, and standards * Develop, implement, and… https://t.co/XkLtvXTz2H https://t.co/AWyozXF1WO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ETL Developer – SSIS, SQL, .NET: Have you worked with SQL Server, SSIS, tape, bubblegum and related technologies to enable ETL and replication between disparate environments? Perhaps on-prem to cloud, cloud to on-prem, and so on? Workstate seeks… https://t.co/i5hgnsxJMa https://t.co/dtL1Kg9fV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/QshXHHnf9z https://t.co/FTeoCoan1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist II: Position Overview The Finance and Analytics group is an innovative internal service provider to Tacoma Water and Tacoma Public Utilities, and is responsible for budget and rate development, financial planning, demand forecasting,… https://t.co/l3mlffJ4fA https://t.co/8AzoB9knVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: The resource will be working on integration projects using SQL 2008/2012/2017, Workload Automation (Scheduling tool). We are looking for a DBA who can provide SQL Server development skills mostly around stored procedure development… https://t.co/ggTWylo531 https://t.co/Ho4PXUUMn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: REQUIRED SKILLS Experience in relational database design, development, and support (MS SQL Server T-SQL preferred) Experience in complex database objects in T-SQL and/or PLSQL Experience with SSIS and/or ETL tools Experience with Visual… https://t.co/gCYlMPQquD https://t.co/RJi2Y2bhr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Geely calls for caution in self-driving tech after fatal collision: BEIJING (Reuters) - The Chinese owner of Swedish car brand Volvo said on Wednesday that the autonomous driving industry should move forward prudently in the wake of a deadly… https://t.co/MqWEy6gkPa https://t.co/Fz0w2Krom0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer / Problem Solver: Triad Learning Systems is a online education company with locations in Post Falls, ID and Ventura, CA. We are seeking an experienced Full Stack Engineer to help us on various projects including all of our web based… https://t.co/GhqeI38VWd https://t.co/7UO8Ea1Lq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Roanoke, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 03/07/18, Posted Date – 03/07/18 Primary SkillsSSRS,ETL,SQL,.net,SSIS,T-SQLTax TermsW-2Overview Job Description : Looking for a Senior SQL Developer: SQL… https://t.co/p1ek0XuZdi https://t.co/Yfa5QWoqHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Administrator: Senior SQL Server Database Administrator Lincoln, Rhode Island United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Amica Location: Lincoln, RI… https://t.co/BYY0l4XsPH https://t.co/zZqIsvYxZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Job Title: PRINCIPAL SOFTWARE ENGINEER Salary: 130-140K Location: WINSTON SALEM, NC Extremely dynamic, rapidly growing technical services company has an immediate opening for a Principal Software Engineer for a permanent… https://t.co/dtcrXMioJd https://t.co/OKCBAjL7f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Tech Firefly is partnering up with one of the hottest companies in the world who specializes in electric automotive, energy storage and solar panel manufacturing based in Palo Alto, California. Were looking for that one person who can… https://t.co/tj0HNGKuoD https://t.co/tyrzJnTaxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Facebook users sue over collection of call, text history: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Three users of the Facebook Messenger app sued Facebook on Tuesday, saying the social network violated their privacy by collecting logs of their phone calls and… https://t.co/bUaASB7XJP https://t.co/JT6VmAoY1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II (Intermediate) – Big Data: Job Summary Independently code complex, n-tiered applications. Apply principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing and evaluation of the enterprise software and… https://t.co/2DchmUvTy1 https://t.co/2GFKoWTrjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer: Since 1938 E.W. Wylie Corporation has been a leader in open deck transportation throughout North America. Now a part of the Daseke Group we are the largest asset based open deck carrier in North America with an extremely… https://t.co/fl5Dn502W1 https://t.co/mwlGs1nyvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Administrator: Senior SQL Server Database Administrator Lincoln, Rhode Island United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Amica Location: Lincoln, RI… https://t.co/L90N8d8jjr https://t.co/8CFDZ5EGj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA): Selene Finance | Job Description Page Requisition Number: 2018-024-FL-5100 Job Title: SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA) City: Jacksonville State: FL SQL DEVELOPER (SELENE NDA) Email Description/Job Summary Job Title: SQL Developer… https://t.co/mqPLVsjMBY https://t.co/PGgmbtaKeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: Position Purpose: Administer, maintain, develop and implement policies and procedures for ensuring the availability, performance, and integrity of the company database. Mentor and act as the go to person for other Database… https://t.co/bUsPBsrMP3 https://t.co/XfxeizCHHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III(Buisness Operations, Claims, SQL) (Pittsburgh or Harrisburg): Position Purpose: Perform various analysis and interpretation to link business needs and objectives for assigned function. Support business initiatives through data… https://t.co/Kd6DqlhgFZ https://t.co/z8mXpNNPAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple bid for education market: new software, same iPad price: CHICAGO/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Apple Inc on Tuesday rolled out a new iPad and classroom software aimed at grabbing more of the U.S. education market, but did not cut the price of its… https://t.co/TLg3omkuPX https://t.co/dE5IwFrEQa]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>