<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/WGq9EtSngY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/xzjE37jtJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/POXJ9YmylP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/Z8UDjc1zWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/KvIbJklz37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/HmCdmYTljb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/JKFvVj5kQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/iglEPfJCbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/fKnbKFCmUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/mYni8LRpTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is good for nothing unless you know the value of it by experience.  P.T Barnum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/vXYsvwD5Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/zjs2MrSRR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/ODNpHXoXfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/2gZl3N6jkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/L1qIVEAZls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/ASBAmc993Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/j5YbxtugTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/ZHlMHMwhIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/86umx1D8jh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/qgsvEBXGNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/VR7gcsQ2El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/5ymhLfcPNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/1KKZ2pdust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/sBYtugNlP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/FBoQKcDRUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that when things seem to go wrong, stay calm and wait till you see the bigger picture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/SoEgH7lCAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/nc1bqaznVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/rvY3iRrjJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/U8ZVVUZHaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/iXUyWH0lEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/J8F6YrFgsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/OgPP1CrQJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/NbqAYSYIWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/9HIwFE4zv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/4kRcw01DyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/uEzCB4F6qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/qqlOsgC2Cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/1sZjCzWf75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/nVxfUv3DBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/hMH5e4q0Z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/LMNAtvnYu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/8Y0caEiy6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/FAY3Kn7fXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/1eHcu3BEvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/2CFgy5ZYoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>