<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Project Manager: Contract Project Manager – Job ID #: 13572 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Technology Services Group – Department: Technology Services – Operations – Primary… https://t.co/p9BB4bSK1N https://t.co/PRdXRFpVst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Consultant – Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing… A Contact Center Services (CCS) Principal Consultant is a Professional Services Executive Consultant and is viewed by the customer as a subject matter expert responsible… https://t.co/3zEPkITwwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Automation Engineer: Process Automation Engineer Site Logo – Markets &amp; Solutions – Agriculture – Automotive – Building &amp; Construction – Consumer – Electronic Materials – Energy &amp; Water – Industrial – Infrastructure – Packaging – Product Finder –… https://t.co/yTR0tGKUYg https://t.co/ani9v8fAI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware Developer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: Costa Rica Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 21239 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and… https://t.co/YYRrSiw2CW https://t.co/JlAnP56yLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH: For Siemens User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard –… https://t.co/ISjSuzQ7oE https://t.co/xwWZO4yBUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Entry Level: Software Engineer – Entry Level Jobs in Plano at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services –… https://t.co/pctDbl49mZ https://t.co/ZPNH7ioKuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst I: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Business Intelligence Analyst I for our San Antonio, TX facility. Analyzes complex business problems and issues using data from internal and external sources to provide… https://t.co/Vjx9fSxfwl https://t.co/CSAN985sqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Software Development Delivery: Project Manager – Software Development Delivery at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBillingBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck… https://t.co/zFFd9oxQ97 https://t.co/IgXxIFG9g0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Analyst: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960’s, is a national engineering and environmental consulting firm that provides integrated services to the energy, environmental and… https://t.co/0zQ4uFdzY2 https://t.co/rP2l01i68U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DATA ANALYST: Data Analyst at Under Armour, Inc. Skip Navigation Under Armour Careers Menu – Life At UALife At UA – Overview – Mission &amp; Values – Benefits – Culture – Talent AreasTalent Areas – Overview – Corporate – Retail – Distribution – Technology –… https://t.co/nT6cDCIUTx https://t.co/HMlu645nJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering, construction,… https://t.co/z3cEJgmtj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Automation Engineer: For Siemens Software Quality Assurance Automation Engineer job – Information Technology – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard –… https://t.co/1WSC8u2pVV https://t.co/59uS2A6a68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer/Senior Engineer, IT Access Management: Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20747 Overview Join us for a career with endless possibilities. Looking for a job where a passion for innovation, a culture… https://t.co/mEOfOaD3YC https://t.co/R07IgeyW6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety: Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety ======================================= The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and… https://t.co/30IvaLRPb0 https://t.co/kqaqO3csHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator Data Management Services: Summary: Implements and administers Intel based servers (physical and virtual), storage, and related technologies, and performs project and maintenance tasks associated with those systems. Location: This… https://t.co/1MVcMauzgK https://t.co/LWZLb7CC4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Systems Analyst Level 2: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:09 Req ID: 27044 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/umrl0tec9t https://t.co/tQD7okXQza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, DevOps PMO VMO: Director, DevOps PMO &amp; VMO HARMAN International Date: Jun 22, 2018 Location: Richardson, TX, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Job Title: Director, DevOps PMO &amp; VMO Manager: Senior Director,… https://t.co/hRlZtNgfwT https://t.co/t5wpPUhSgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Project Manager I, II or III: Employer Sam Houston State University Location Huntsville, TX Posted Jul 05, 2018 Institution Type Four-Year Institution You need to sign in or create an account to save Requisition Number: *********S… https://t.co/vzHvrKvOjM https://t.co/l0ejBGoMie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing Monopoly: What Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg Can Learn From Bill Gates: Harvard dropouts. Precocious whiz kids. Beleaguered titans. The parallels between the two tech moguls are startling. Will history repeat—or just rhyme? https://t.co/LG2BsiZyce https://t.co/D9RvJXtJqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer job in San Antonio, Texas, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp; Graduates… https://t.co/je92zSk12A https://t.co/lZAiScJ2q3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety: Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety ======================================= The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and… https://t.co/gHRp02Uu2V https://t.co/x8ifMbLqn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Applications Developer: Careers | Ethos Group Login Toggle navigation – Home – Services – Consulting – Recruiting – Training – Compliance – Technology – Product Administration – Dealer Participation – Careers – Connect – Login Search Careers \\\\\… https://t.co/hZMk5Ppgwd https://t.co/bkJ45p0L4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Public Safety: Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Public Safety =========================================================== Incode public safety provides a full offering of integrated suites… https://t.co/4hJXJEMoGN https://t.co/1H02dMG6h2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering – Programmer E: Job not found | ********** Skip to Job Description, SearchClose Find JobsCompany ReviewsFind SalariesFind ResumesEmployers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in : WhatWhere Advanced Job Search job title, keywords or… https://t.co/dcPM3Sd6gC https://t.co/aBLPz3EVSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Shift Network Administrator- TS cleared: Requisition ID 2018-43585 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description *******Active TS/SCI Security clearance required*******… https://t.co/gjspqLaUwP https://t.co/4L228vSsre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Embedded Software Engineer Job – Why Work For Us – Get to Know PACCAR – A Great Place to Work – Equal Opportunity Employer – Job Opportunities – Engineering Jobs – Finance &amp; Accounting Jobs – Human Resources &amp; Admin Jobs –… https://t.co/gtA89IJU9d https://t.co/1dnyZrjOK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director IT Security: **Director IT Security** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle Management-PLM **Requisition… https://t.co/0TeGhpcGzT https://t.co/vIWsnSsPhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS DEVELOPER: IOS DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-30012 Location: irving, Texas Responsibilities – Design and build advanced applications for the iOS platform (Swift and Obj-c ) – Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features. –… https://t.co/hwrdptQOKw https://t.co/4RFzkwVsGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Job Description BAE Systems’ F35 Lightning II program has an exciting opportunity for a data analyst to develop and deliver process functionality and data analytics, with respect to Prognostics and Health Management (PHM) data. These… https://t.co/rBP4dmJodR https://t.co/x9hS9ogbkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications / Network Manager – TX: Communications / Network Manager – TX ===================================== Req #: ******Location: Lackland Air Force Base, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance… https://t.co/djGrnH7izX https://t.co/HpKayHAwJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tableau Developer: Tableau Developer Ref No.:18-11826 Location: San Antonio, Texas Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/05/2018 Role: Tableau Developer Location: San Antonio, TX Contract Position Skills Required: – BI Data Visualization – Tableau –… https://t.co/gYwURWVsJD https://t.co/u8rjDsnjN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst – II: Job TitleBusiness Data Analyst – II – ID:31609 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsAIX, Machine learning LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/30/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking… https://t.co/SoILlTSAxh https://t.co/SxkS6owvAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager IV: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Senior Manager Jobs Aviall, A Boeing Company is the world’s largest provider of new aviation parts and related aftermarket services. Aviall markets and distributes… https://t.co/ut1KuAUp9u https://t.co/CMXkpmwr2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead System Administrator: Lead System Administrator now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now Email Please wait. Date: Jun 26, 2018 Location: Company: Tesoro Companies Inc. Requisition ID: 74264 Summary: Responsible for highly complex… https://t.co/D3Wfa6weth https://t.co/jox4F0LjyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court Lubbock, Texas: Job Description Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court This role provides basic-level software support for Tyler clients in the use, functionality, and understanding of our… https://t.co/CZ7IHRFWnX https://t.co/HUVYflbSZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Solution Architect: Lead Solution Architect now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now Email Please wait. Date: Jun 25, 2018 Location: Company: Tesoro Companies Inc. Requisition ID: 74263 Summary: This role is responsible delivery… https://t.co/blFrRiqhs3 https://t.co/cB6ocLTL9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist IV: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Researcher Jobs Aviall, a Boeing Company is the world’s largest provider of new aviation parts and related aftermarket services. Aviall markets and distributes… https://t.co/JTnEqoUNDi https://t.co/HSBuoCu3BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Cloud: Job ID #: 13404 – Job Category: Software Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Web Services Engineering – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location: Austin (TX)… https://t.co/iJjgRb63Ax https://t.co/dagwkGeG1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst II IVR: Business Systems Analyst II – IVR in Fort Worth, TX at National General Insurance Toggle Navigation – Home – About – Benefits – Training – Our Values – All Jobs Join Our Talent Network Search Our Jobs Keyword: Location: –… https://t.co/orD4TZa1HQ https://t.co/8E6OtYdAai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpdesk-Service Desk Associate – Austin, Texas: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Austin, TX, US Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/4/2018 Job Description TTEC is seeking a Service Desk Associate to… https://t.co/9isUg2od3n https://t.co/Dp1afKcDC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst Digital Health Services: Job Description =============== Senior Business Analyst – Digital Health Services The Senior Business Analyst – Digital Health Services is responsible for coordinating process and system analysis required… https://t.co/tqCg7Kjwcy https://t.co/BuVP7YsrRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer III (Mobility Development): Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Office Jobs Aviall, A Boeing Company is the world’s largest provider of new aviation parts and related aftermarket services.… https://t.co/lNILEa5Pjy https://t.co/fMaqyKwdqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Engineer – (DevOps | AWS) – Remote: Senior Cloud Infrastructure Engineer – (DevOps | AWS) – Remote at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support… https://t.co/2e9YOKXKoT https://t.co/bcFORh0TbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tango — Application Developer: Tango — Application Developer Ref No.: 18-31013 Location: Irving, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors… https://t.co/U8Rl1wNLuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Careers Center | Sr. Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/WssUJJiE8e https://t.co/o12Z2ZkL0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Solutions Architect: Network Solutions Architect – Job ID #: 13860 – Job Category: Product Management – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Infrastructure – Department: Infrastructure Marketing – Primary Country: USA – Primary… https://t.co/r7gADRwb2s https://t.co/7tqyQvzC1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Primary Skills Spring,FRAMEWORKS,JAVA/J2EE,REST API’s,Scrum/Agile,API lifecycle management Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Senior Java Developer for location… https://t.co/56gaJy7Fxw https://t.co/ixQ9DksAOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congos/Tableau Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Plano, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/27/2018 Job Description We have an immediate need for a Congos/Tableau Developer with extensive… https://t.co/faFeyO0UAP https://t.co/XIdG77N0Cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer, Full Stack: Thermo Fisher Scientific – Java Developer, Full Stack Job in Austin, TX – Home – Discover Our Stories – Career Areas – Engineering – Field Service – Finance – General Management – Human Resources – Operations &amp; Supply Chain –… https://t.co/GOVkrQsY5i https://t.co/1uB9xNe74c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Utility Billing – Lubbock, Texas: Job Description Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Utility Billing Tyler’s Incode Utility Billing suite of applications are a perfect fit for both municipal and… https://t.co/hdb0Ep5FHx https://t.co/ARTFdE3uhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Conversion Developer: SQL Conversion Developer ======================== The SQL Developer converts client data into Tyler s courts and justice software in a way that meets our clients business needs. Location Plano, Texas Responsibilities * Design,… https://t.co/tVN22xYDZN https://t.co/a4ZYlzJoBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer, Flight Service Web Based Training: Location: Integrated Operations Ctr (DFW-IOC0) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20049 Overview Join us for a career with endless possibilities. Looking for a job where a passion for… https://t.co/4WNkHzQesw https://t.co/1A1lQvFwva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Senior Level: Full Stack Developer – Senior Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA – Careers – / –… https://t.co/TZXLPXdOqn https://t.co/kAbu3k65LJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software and Architecture Support Team Lead: Job ID #: 13640 – Job Category: Applications Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Partner Enablement – Department: Partner Enablement – Engineering – Primary Country:… https://t.co/in9SnrmN2P https://t.co/XMv5z1k1RV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Delivery/EnerGov: Software Engineer, Delivery/EnerGov =================================== Engineers build, design and write scalable code to enhance the product or resolve issues within the product. Expectations for this professional… https://t.co/Wxfc3m342n https://t.co/Zswb76Ltbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst Information Systems: Arconic Fastening Systems (AFS) is looking for a Business Analyst to work closely with business stakeholders to understand business challenges, gather requirements, then develop and deliver effective solutions… https://t.co/V9g4xU35IN https://t.co/1ZpCwk7vWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer/Developer, IT Applications: Associate Developer/Developer, IT Applications View Profile – Join Our Talent Community – Featured Jobs – Jobs at the Airport – Professional – Technical Operations &amp; Maintenance – Customer Service – Pilots… https://t.co/84waFsDRio https://t.co/9mOHKOyaHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Linux Storage/NVME Storage: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing,… https://t.co/WZ9X7JfeB9 https://t.co/C3XhG2dPS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-Solutions-Architect: GuideIT is a is a US based technology services company focused on providing value to its’ customers through technology alignment and optimization. We are currently looking for a Senior Solutions Infrastructure/ Convergence… https://t.co/5LRMHVx37p https://t.co/RduKpJWtsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Systems Engr: 110556BR Sr Principal Systems Engr TX – McKinney 110556BR Lead Systems Engineer for Electronic Protection: This position is responsible for representing the interests of the MFRFS product line through total technical ownership… https://t.co/0MheU6lADD https://t.co/vAET8Hf6yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Full Stack: Job Title: Software Developer – Full Stack Location: Austin, TX, South-West United States, USA Company: Farmers Edge Inc. Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Precision Ag Career Type:IT/Software Development Job… https://t.co/cTri1YAx4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP Product Engineering – Machine Learning, Product Scalability: Austin, TX Full-time $120k – $175k Posted Today If you are a VP Product Engineering with product scalability and industrial IoT experience, please read on! Based in Austin, we are a 20… https://t.co/1lX0U2U0Q3 https://t.co/brHUSiDA55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Summary:Design, develop, test and maintain a responsive UI based web application using Angular JS, JQuery, HTML5, CSS and ******* MVC, WCF and Entity Framework. Work on multiple projects in a Scrum based agile team and utilize… https://t.co/L8k65mRfSU https://t.co/88XAu32ueq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with React/Redux: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Java Developer with React/Redux Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX Campus Java Developers are engaged in all phases of the software development lifecycle which include; gathering and… https://t.co/Ag529b51Oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAFF SOFTWARE ENGINEER RELIABILITY ENGINEERING: POSITION PURPOSE As a Staff Site Reliability Engineer you will be responsible for building and supporting the application infrastructure of one of the largest eCommerce sites in the world. This will… https://t.co/YtvAGCeCFA https://t.co/tFYpqWRuCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Full Stack Mobile Developer: NO SPONSORSHIP Expert Full Stack Mobile Developer Looking for a candidate with 7 plus years Full Stack Mobile Development JOB DESCRIPTION The Full Stack Engineer Expert will be responsible for the development, testing,… https://t.co/2BYzSBDtJg https://t.co/2AYbcqejYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer ====================== The Lead Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting complex applications in a manner consistent with department standards and procedures. This position… https://t.co/hlGlwN8BdO https://t.co/eoFDcEmWpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst/Senior Analyst, Decision Support Systems: Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 19941 Overview Join us for a career with endless possibilities. Looking for a job where a passion for innovation, a… https://t.co/apbQHchvxX https://t.co/V71ubuIFAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer II Building Technologies: For Siemens Software Developer II – Building Technologies – Austin, TX job – Research &amp; Development – Austin, Texas Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/eMKmojMKAp https://t.co/7Eb16MUI2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Engineer: Company: Schlumberger Skills: IT – Programming &amp; Database, IT – Software Development Experience: 5 + Years Education: Bachelors/3-5 yr Degree Location: Houston, Texas, United States Status: Active In order to apply for this… https://t.co/mbULEu61fx https://t.co/q2hQKZ1nLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst II: Job Title Business System Analyst II Job ID(Requisition ID): 3693 Job Summary Works closely with Development Engineering Technical Program Managers (PMs) and Development Engineering functional management to deliver tools,… https://t.co/vrdpzlHngu https://t.co/4uMlat1eGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst III(Healthcare, SQL, Excel, Business intelligence ): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of… https://t.co/OsfhTg3aw0 https://t.co/geoGT096Gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Real Estate and Finance (IFRS Senior/Principal Consultant (HOU): SAP Real Estate and Finance (IFRS 16) Senior/Principal Consultant (HOU) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP… https://t.co/EubB7IYsir https://t.co/2CabbEXQyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist, Hosting Operations: IT Specialist, Hosting Operations ================================= Tyler Technologies has an IT Specialist opening on our hosting operations team in Plano, TX. The IT Specialist position provides Tier I system… https://t.co/YlrvugVRAa https://t.co/kaqB3cZjjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Job TitleSalesforce Developer – ID:32071 Duration3 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job ******************** Apex, Visual Force, Salesforce Lightning LocationRichardson, TX Date Posted07/03/2018 Comments/Special Instructions – Should… https://t.co/mKuxte0rF8 https://t.co/mLiZmEvNPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[{quot;IDquot;:null,quot;Titlequot;:quot;Senior Software Engineer: [{‘ID’:null,’Title’:’Senior Software Engineer Senior Software Engineer Nice Systems is currently seeking a dynamic individual with high energy and drive to join Work Force Management… https://t.co/T6GOS1ZJwJ https://t.co/32baZ7mGaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager Senior: Technical Project Manager Senior Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants Project-Process Management Jobs at… https://t.co/W3TjusNJoB https://t.co/651Wbf2SxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular/ UI: Angular/ UI Ref No.: 18-30989 Location: Irving, Texas Job Description: years of IT experience as a front end developer – The candidate should have prior experience on front end technologies involving advanced JavaScript implementation – The… https://t.co/wd3euXrt5B https://t.co/VQm76WL6vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Solutions Architect: Job ID #: 13860 – Job Category: Product Management – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Infrastructure – Department: Infrastructure Marketing – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location: Austin (TX) We are… https://t.co/LahSy9LKrC https://t.co/351h4vNcxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CA Identity Manager, Sun Identity Manager Developer: CA Identity Manager, Sun Identity Manager Developer Ref No.: 18-32500 Location: Plano, Texas Hands-on experience of CA Identity Manager 14.x &amp; Sun Identity Manager 8.x – Experience on configuration of… https://t.co/sTKsLlgYxs https://t.co/OvS6b9WgbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Drupal Developer: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Employer serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/NUlLym68Gu https://t.co/BFGNX2i3hM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT QA Analyst I Info Systems: Summary Investigates and resolves software problems of computer users by performing the following duties. Essential Duties and Responsibilities include the following. Other duties may be assigned: Answers, evaluates, and… https://t.co/Zz1kmIgsvi https://t.co/HqhOte4TIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Business Systems: Job Description Job Description This position is responsible for gathering, analyzing, and creating comprehensive work products documenting requirements, including validation and traceability, for existing and new… https://t.co/eXWBfuWeP9 https://t.co/pBirvsfyl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer, Flight Service Web Based Training: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Flight Crew Category: Instructors &amp; Trainers Jobs Location: Integrated Operations Ctr (DFW-IOC0) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20049 Overview… https://t.co/XiRgwJ1XVJ https://t.co/n8DVZ0ToU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer III: RealPage Careers – Browse and Search Openings Consumer Support Client Portal Contact – 1.************ Search Careers Company Services Contact Sales Cancel 1.************ Support – Asset Optimization – – YieldStar Overview – About Us –… https://t.co/6eG5Lkrfds https://t.co/jvgtANCSCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Java: QA Automation – Java Ref No.: 18-28564 Location: Irving, Texas Knowledge and experience with automation development techniques, methodologies and best practices. Understanding of the SDLC process and principles. Understanding of Agile… https://t.co/Mkb1kjh5Yb https://t.co/SkQqUzd4Vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Administrator End User Support: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing,… https://t.co/KYi339oMry https://t.co/SqwxJxxVxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-24743 Work Location US-TX-Midland Department / Discipline Project Management Additional Work Location US-TX-Seminole Position Type Staff / Permanent Overview / Responsibilities Wood is currently seeking a Project… https://t.co/ChFP8fFaVx https://t.co/ji4lvj25C5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Workforce Compensation Consultant: Oracle Workforce Compensation Consultant Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 06/12/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsOracleTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12 months contract. Phone and Skype.… https://t.co/nSlsQACw4M https://t.co/wffbr3vYQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Architect – CTIOS / Finesse Solutions, Anywhere in the US / Telecommute: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dallas, TX, US Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/2/2018 Job Description Ttec,… https://t.co/XYQUZobiQ9 https://t.co/XtX0PTy3My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer: Booster Stage, Inc.: Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer We Work Remotely See more Programming jobs Back to all jobs Full Stack Ruby on Rails Developer Posted Jul 2 Booster Stage, Inc. Headquarters: Austin, TX… https://t.co/tK70rjsUFH https://t.co/n4caMJTli1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test: Job Description Software Development Engineer in Test Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you’re helping to create a better world. Our customers operate the largest electrical transmission… https://t.co/tCZsMTfIVX https://t.co/knx9sv4G7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal/Associate Director Software Engineer: The Senior Developer will play a key role in the design, development, and testing of world class front-end business web applications. This includes researching, designing, documenting, and modifying… https://t.co/QQJaTQtJpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Purpose of JobPurpose of Job IMPORTANT: Applicants When filling out your name and other personal information below, DO NOT use any special characters or ALL CAPS. Use only standard letters in the English alphabet. Including… https://t.co/dSVh0kR3LD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Engineer Senior – Milford, OH or Plano, TX: **Cloud Software Engineer Senior – Milford, OH or Plano, TX** Multiple Locations:Milford, Ohio; Plano, Texas Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description**… https://t.co/w2iuoTMqmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer Inside Plant: Careers Center | Senior Network Engineer – Inside Plant Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/5S0wyWRNDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Search Developer – Apache Solr or Lucidworks Fusion: Enterprise Search Developer – Apache Solr or Lucidworks Fusion Irving, TX. Company is seeking a well-qualified, experienced, and talented Application Developer to serve as Technical Lead in… https://t.co/vPdvEcRqQd https://t.co/r8QvwxDqMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS Dynamics (CRM) Developer: Looking for an MS Dynamics (CRM) Developer Location: Irving, TX Microsoft dynamics, C#, JavaScript, agile, CRM, develop code for med to complex modules, case management, workflow automation, dynamics MS2015 REQUIREMENTS The… https://t.co/eMcmD89nAx https://t.co/6IHQQGZ1bM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Engineer IoT AE: Cloud Software Engineer – IoT AE – Job ID #: 13325 – Job Category: Software Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Solutions Engineering – Primary Country:… https://t.co/ctlPQI6m5c https://t.co/D1s76d6E8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Primary Skills Spring,FRAMEWORKS,JAVA/J2EE,REST API’s,Scrum/Agile,API lifecycle management Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Senior Java Developer for location… https://t.co/UOU5qK8kyk https://t.co/IMh7F5qcvg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>