<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[MediateBC invited me to speak to their mediators about marketing. Assured that any topic conflicts will be resolved swiftly ;) #BCLegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ianmulgrew: US Supreme Court rules GPS tracking of vehicle constitutes search under 4th Amendment http://t.co/TLoy7i4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonishaMartins That I gotta see!  In the meantime, lemme recmd a patent agent ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonishaMartins Seen u listen 2 speakers & (1) take notes (2) live tweet (3) photogrph subjects. Pretty sure u have only 2 hands. Impresive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holdencalgary OUCH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawScribes Hmmm, nope, sorry. Anyone else know a female BC lawyer w/purple couch theme on twitter.com ? (Bracing myself for responses)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! RT @goclio: Good read. From @lawyerPR on @slaw_dot_ca: How to avoid resource-draining marketing activities http://t.co/MkfGG7Tr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey LMA Chapter board members! Check out Outstanding Chapter Award. Entry is easy +  award-winner gets lots of goodies http://t.co/zq8OKDmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this holiday video by Blakes -- Blakes Gives Thanks (English) http://t.co/QkSXVqkA via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SusanLazaruk: A Freudian slip is when you say one thing but mean your mother. via @WomensHumor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_bilinsky: hot:  Mr. Justice Sigurdson's just-released 78 page Judgment  on Constitutionality of BC's roadside screening: http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Sooooo, if it's not a secret, it's not a prob and I should just carry on, right @matwilcox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that make me crazy: why do Adobe  PDF files always open at 173%?  I am not 98 yrs old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Even if that relationship involves food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So classy. One law firm to another: RT @Beckerlawyers: @McQuarrieHunter Welcome!  I think we can see you from the north side of the Fraser!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law student alert! @McQuarrieHunter RT @catejca: Reminder: Accepting 2012 Summer Articled Student application… (cont) http://t.co/oSV5qISR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyVBehar show not renewed for 2012. A sharp, witty, fresh show that's relevant + entertaining. A unique TV space  I'll miss. Bummer, Joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @McQuarrieHunter for bringing firm's twitter page to life! Follow them for Surrey news, legal updates and more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terrybecker ... and do the hokey pokey and turn yourself around ... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbolan But whoa ... if the gun's in the dining room, that's wrong and offensive. Not to mention, just plain bad manners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hang on National Post, just who qualifies as a Muppet? Only SOME Sesame Street characters?http://t.co/3vn5flT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @News1130radio: JUST IN... The province was granted an injunction.  #Occupy Vancouver protesters have unti… (cont) http://t.co/X91z8v1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't avoid the media. Build them into your litigation strategy & amplify or manage your msg using sound strategies and advisers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilNugent: "Just because you’ve heard it before doesn’t mean you know it. Just because you know it doesn’t mean you’re doing it." v ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Just signed up, but getting error msgs, so I'll try again later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you except LinkedIn invitations from people you don't know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJohnBecker: Great day door knocking in South Bonson. #pittmeadows residents dismiss developer's "developer friendly" candidate reco ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJohnBecker: Thx (MLA) Brenmer! Hope #pittmeadows residents agree w/u! RT @hectordbremner lookin' forwar… (cont) http://t.co/5wuNvMTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJohnBecker: Thx (MLA) Brenmer! Hope the residents of #pittmeadows agree with you! RT @hectordbremner lookin' forward to calling you ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that make me crazy: When choosing a password TELL me your minimum requirements upfront. Duh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM deserves to know! Six days + counting to disclose if you've accepted developer $ for your campaign and why #electpm #PittMeadows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJohnBecker: #electpm #electmr All candidates should be disclosing donations from developers BEFORE we vote.  http://t.co/j6euFMpT T ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @terrybecker: Mayor MacLean's tribute breakfast this am in #pittmeadows  20 years of service to the City was celebrated. Your #legacy ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillKrop: It's confirmed! Barry Deley and Squire Barnes' Ellen show appearance will be Monday. Taping in LA tomorrow. Bet she thinks ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@douglasbing Calling #fourseasons now! Hands up, who's joining us? Oh wait. Make that "Occupy Maui from ...Th… (cont) http://t.co/kOAilkUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Vancouverites, waddya say: Occupy Maui? #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well-stated: Mayoral cndte sets recrd strght. RT @CityCaucus: New Westminster Candidate 'in it to win it': http://t.co/NJDk59qD via @AddThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MapleRidgeNews Just messin' with ya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: On Tonight's "Report": my guest is Seth Meyers, anchor of SNL's Weekend Update. It must be exciting for him to meet a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sgt. Jennifer Pound should refrain from commenting RT @GlobalNational: Prominent #BC #RCMP Cpl.  Galliford all… (cont) http://t.co/3teunJTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have policies ..." stmt not enough when actions show otherwise RT @cbcnewsbc: More #RCMP complain of harassment.. http://t.co/J1rrEE1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MapleRidgeNews is on a  twitter roll tonight!  TweetDeck column looking like pretty wallpaper :) #pittmeadows #electpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @terrybecker: @EJohnBecker ZERO Tax Increase Process http://t.co/Booy4JDO #electpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SelfStorAll So true!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good PR in practice. RT @CKNW: Watts says rioters don't represent her community http://t.co/qCGoALO2 #PR #Surrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charmaineds: He declined yest but @Lamarche called 2 give "statement" on new web postings he says aren't his, then hung up on me. #b ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man... this is SO true! Good post, Cheryl! RT @CherylBame: Big News In Your World, Not In the Media http://t.co/EeqPeAFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karendyck: This is all about how to avoid malpractice claims: What Clients Want in Their Lawyer http://t.co/LxdjFyzW #in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elliottmarkc Thanks, Mark! Glad you enjoyed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My slaw column: What Clients Want in Their Lawyer just posted: http://t.co/eyc3Irpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's too young! RT @syladurantaye: One-year-old son wearing sister's underwear as a hat while in bath. I've lost the house. Send bourbon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy client = fabulous Friday! Woo hoo! (Seriously, I'm NOT writing those myself. But if I did ... no, kidding).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! RT @Beckerlawyers: @terrybecker RT  Thank'g @lawyerpr for expertise &amp; amazing talent! Watch for an exciting new launch! #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx TB! RT @terrybecker: The end of another busy mth. Thanking @lawyerpr 4 her expertise + amazing talent!  Watch for an exciting new launch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job opportunity: Director, Marketing and Communications at BCIT - Vancouver, Canada Area #jobs http://t.co/uMy9NKF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delight a client by anticipating + delivering on their needs, send note of encouragement b4 a stressful event, say tx for the work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanLawMag : Enjoying your April issue. Cover story + Regional wrap-up particularly interesting, but reading whole issue #BCLegal #solosmall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad impression: recptionsts in law firms  who ask  "who's calling?" Just curious or are they screening callers? #BCLegal #solosmall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_bilinsky: Great stuff! RT @TinaCook: Promote your Linkedin profile on your website with a button Copy and Paste: http://t.co/L ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoughtonLaw: Get tickets today for The Lawyer Show 2012 at Carousel Theatre. This legal fundraising performance is Guys & Dolls! htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client perceptions matter! RT @McQuarrieHunter: @lawyerPR @DCHalkett #clebc some, like how can charge more if right brand like Louis Vutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheering on media savvy, risk-taking, entrepreneurial Vanc lawyer Lisa Ridgedale : http://t.co/nikKppCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope they're covering marketing + PR! RT @DCHalkett: At #clebc course MBA Concepts for Lawyers, very interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to recent Translink cutbacks, the light at the end of the tunnel has been turned off. - P. Morgan #translink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready to give a social media workshop to a client. As I blow the dust off Hootsuite, I'm realizing how great it is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WilkinsonGroup: #PR tip: involve wise people arguing various options on strategy and develop a plan before implementing 	http://t.co ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinokeefe: With New Timeline, a New Look for Law Firm Publications on Facebook - @adrianlurssen http://t.co/ZQLtVfSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ianmulgrew: B.C. lawyers withdraw duty counsel service - No representation for entire month http://t.co/DBWJmgD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious win - congrats!  RT @FaskenMartineau: Historic Win: Intern'l corp. lawyers, litigtors + gov't relations help... http://t.co/swW43PYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time, my beloved pooch is spending morning at the dog spa getting fully groomed. Is it normal to be this nervous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck, Deb! RT @DebScaringi: DIY Marketing… Making Choices » Scaringi Marketing http://t.co/rrLpHXCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCLawWeek: Come to "CBABC Vancouver Fun Run" Sunday, April 22 from 10:00 am to 1:00 pm. The BC Branch of the Canadian Bar... http:// ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just phoned a client law firm who's receptist wld win "sales-prevention" award, hands down.  Must send her the "clients matter" memo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank YOU! RT @cdrsaint: Thanks @lawyerPR for an AMAZING presentation on #marketing for Mediate BC mediators! So much to do, but so doable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MapleWashing: @thriveorg @GaraConstruct @walkerparkmedia @cakelicious_hk  I'll join u from Vanc in spirit :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you REALLY looked at the BCTF logo? Yup, that's a tea pot in the centre. Seriously. #bctf #marcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BRILLIANT!!! RT @JCottin: Loved this Coke video on happiness. Watch it again. http://t.co/YuLZxvnp #briteconf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still thrilling to hear when a client is "beside himself" with excitement.  It's akin to caffeine for a day!  #nevergetsold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kbolan: SFU Prof’s “Friend” Arrested in Her July 2011 Slaying http://t.co/vMHFv34L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thriveorg @MapleWashing @GaraConstruct @walkerparkmedia @cakelicious_hk  I'll be attending! See you there @thriveorg? Will miss others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one regrets going! RT @betsiroach: #LMA12 Testimonial: “It’s rare to find a conference that can have such an impact on business”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running out to get wine now for @GaraConstruct: @thriveorg @cakelicious_hk  to bring to support group mtg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that the *right* thing to serve the Wongs? RT @JeenaBelil: Having the Wongs over for Taco Night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Miss604: MT @parkboard Take advantage of rec activities for kids at comm. centres, pools, rinks in event of BCTF labour action http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tla_bc: The Women Lawyers Retreat Reunion Party is happening Thur, Mar 15 at the #Morrisey ... come one, come all! http://t.co/i12XT ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BH looking oh so fine for 120 yrs old!  & moving? Gd things R happening @ BH! RT @BullHousser moving to TELUS Garden  http://t.co/zItZiM44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My boys plans 4 strike : xbox, Archie comics, xbox, iTunes, xbox. My plans: math, reading, swimming, wlk dog, more math. Need luck. #strike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["90% of life is showing up." - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool shoe! Uncomfortable? RT @thriveorg: Here is today's shoe of the day from my calendar...what do you think? http://t.co/AxZai0Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? RT @cbcnewsbc: Sears to close downtown Vancouver store http://t.co/5H7act1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:) RT @SusanLazaruk: Yay, students, 4 getting political, but ancmt rally full of grammtcl errors. #hopeyouarenotcuttingEnglish #bctf #strike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CLEBC: We'll be tweeting key takeaways from next week's "Family Law Drafting Basics" course. Join the discussion #clebc. http://t.co ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colincameron: “iPad has changed the way this firm practices law. And I think it’s changed the practice of law http://t.co/kuHrUUZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, all you egg faces out there who are spamming me, I'm blocking + reporting you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take five minutes to check an important client’s website for recent news. Better yet, set up Google Alerts for your top 10 -- read them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client service matters: Make a call of reassurance to a client the day b4 a stressful event (1st day of trial, a closing, a settlemnt conf.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law firm presentation ystrday: found they rarely thank referral sources + they acct for 50% of their new files! Risky. #bclegal #solosmall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WestCoast_LEAF: Top reasons 2 go 2 @WestCoast_LEAF's Equality Brkfst: @ChantalHbert talks politics + equality. http://t.co/fAq0r6UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WestCoast_LEAF: Thank you Alexander, Holburn, Beaudin & Lang LLP for providing excellent service and commitment to the community and ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoughtonLaw Well-deserved award!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>