<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PayChen @designtaxi So you have place to put the money you saved from not ever having to buy a wallet again. Or having a social life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RickAnderson: Be good when he learns that it is OK not to chase every passing car... https://t.co/3DQOLOM7o0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well #goshgollygeewillikers at least half of the #sportsnet   #cbc #hockeynight announcing teams have to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is no such thing as #PostTruth There is just lazy thinking. We are more evolved than to succumb to lies as a manner of final debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne @nationalpost    Well just try this.  It may look dark right now but things will break through  https://t.co/QXFNBDoBdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying I Don't Worry About A Thing by Mose Allison ♫ https://t.co/QXFNBDoBdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne @CTVNews In this present Upside Down world of politics this unfortunately is a bad omen. When the balanced few step away. Watch out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the Tenderloin. With grilled French glazed potatos and basil garlic olive marinated… https://t.co/QyKwXJhIPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPER MOON Super Bowl ??? https://t.co/zi65k16BMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the apps for now. Potato Bacon Leek soup and stir fried wontons https://t.co/ZsVX5GBMz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super moon over New England. Soups on Games on https://t.co/SqJzKVsvlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey ? Is that the Monthly AVG or does it report daily % by each day of the period?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Pisces_A7: #Pisces do not have an average mind, it's above average.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeschlossDC: Nixon joins his national security adviser on helicopter in South Vietnam, 1969:          #Stripes https://t.co/EburfPuM5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What has happened to milk. Expiry dates are out of control SAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianNemett Will do. Think about next Saturday for Thelonious Hank??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonDingleyCBC just go out side and start running wild and looking pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Teasing and light hearted way"?
Bullies don't deal in lightheartedness  https://t.co/kyEWtHLtAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinRatchford no there isn't. There is one old Toyota sedan and you might be a little F'd up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robpizzola. I respect what he had done and the solid person he is  But can he be what HABS need?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robpizzola maybe. But the thread is the same. Is he the best coach available  Sans the language issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robpizzola Julien and Therrien are the same style. No win there. The win is Hire the Best Damn Coach Available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @CTVNews OK Let's walk back cat here. The POST visit comm was reported much earlier. Verify. Was the $B a reg. lobbiest? No?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakin: A year ago (almost to the day), @acoyne had this about Bombardier. Good to read in the next 40 minutes. https://t.co/G7HhgkT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally and figuratively had no ideas #BowlingGreenStrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite perfect word is "too" perfect because it has that extra additional helpful O. It helps define itself and i always know usage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy as many as it takes to keep them safe from assholes like you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFugelsang: Jesus came to Terminal 4 but He was brown, Middle Eastern, spoke no English &amp; didn't have papers so the US Christians sh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/3. I am greatly disturbed at what is happening to our wonderful neighbour to the south. This #muslimban is wrong,  If not evil in intent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/3 I was willing to take a wait and see approach to the Trump Presidency. Waiting for a balancing of the fervour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/3I believe I am a fair and reasonable informed citizen. One who balances arguments to arrive at a conclusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@althiaraj @InklessPW This is the only time where Bannon's advice holds true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @althiaraj: Ok this is super inside baseball but also super funny https://t.co/Fs3RD6X5oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joanjett: Rest In Peace Mary Tyler Moore &lt;3 https://t.co/XlK1kzu20W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @Lazarus1940 @AlbertaGrl @DougSaunders And if interest rates move up because of Trump loan protests will proliferate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @towhey: President Trump has already reduced congestion on the Mall by over 85%. #HourOfAction https://t.co/Oz0dturVH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#150GreatCanadianCountry https://t.co/Jtr6phK3qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a Country Song from an underrated Artist. But like Janis said If it sounds Country man that's what it is https://t.co/22h594MMiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are still wearing their ball caps backwards. Or have they started again. Is there a lost decade I'm unaware of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: The Manchurinary Candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshgreenman: Will our first blackmail president succeed our first black male president? https://t.co/DwjRnPo5GT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsaur1 @pucktails Why does Mic have a headache? Cuz he just got DROPPED on his head. #MicDrop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundays are made for Caesars #inastein @ Jack Astors - Sherway https://t.co/4jmifhwQIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #bobcole. Haven't always. But I do. And after the Mennonite call  he says" the man from the players bench over there. Is Weber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bruce_arthur: This reads better on mobile than desktop, but here it is. https://t.co/COtCTe3SN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Happening. Everything is Happening. In the shocking world of Cocaine and Mennonites. #BobCole has made my 2016. Then #HABS SCORE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGarfoose No Never a mistake to lead and mentor others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Ha! 
I'm alive and drunk. 
Fuck you, 2016. I win. 
Happy New Year! https://t.co/G1QKOuKqO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colbycosh: Just so you know, 2016 is 100% not going to be remembered in history or reference books as some kind of especially horrid ye…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellie Leitch is going to be very busy screening all those candidates https://t.co/Wjxprx9xHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Zamfir: Master of the Pan Flute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sn590gbrady  They sure were Greg Vintage ‘Healthy’ Cigarette Ads, Promoted Smoking In The Past https://t.co/TcqMoQgyu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vintage ‘Healthy’ Cigarette Ads, Promoted Smoking In The Past - https://t.co/CDbGlZcMEi https://t.co/7akQykZXMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie you're right. I did. Damn it all to hell. And I was going to write a column about it. But then thought better if it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daemonic3 @Reverend_Scott Cuz we are Canada and we are better value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@z0nbie to the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@z0nbie those that govthrbthe -ly go into the next dimension]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is reinvigorating the new irregardless ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump, who took office with historically low favorability ratings and has continued to lose support since his inauguration. " @APNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yyzsportsmedia: don’t tell McCown, his dream scenario is over - someone send Bob a Justin Smoak jersey @Bluejays https://t.co/Tx0DkPlOV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PayChen I hate that I can't Multiple Like tweets. Because this one deserves it LIKE LIKE LIKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PayChen: Hi. https://t.co/8Ude3Dojmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne Exactly. The factor that rush to analyze ignores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddale8: Wasn't Why He Won, but Trump vow to defend Medicaid was a key way he distinguished himself from regular Republicans. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WKRPQuotes: "You know what we call problems in sales? We call them opportunities." Happy 75th B'day to the incomparable Frank Bonner. #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I luv u #bobcole but you just announced the the PA Announcer was going to announce the last minute of play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DWHauthor what about just because of pure human decency. Oh yeah Forgot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair ha!  That's just plain unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Satire: Sergey Kislyak, the least memorable man in the world https://t.co/9k6T4hWBAh via @petridishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @coyleWERDZ @petridishes This is why we need to read newspapers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we read newspapers or the news WRY  https://t.co/Z9lSPjBACK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell #Ikea didn't need him until they opened in America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daveweigel: When you forget that life is wonderful, remember that there was a Canadian version of "We Are the World." https://t.co/BSD7…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: This truly is demented, in a way that no excerpt can quite do justice. You have to see the director’s cut. https://t.co/0OYdpA2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace hey Kiddo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is so much better than following the wild activity of that other Orange Blob https://t.co/2OoSjgTpAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianNemett done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/OCnIGUSOt2 then the best for last. I'm always in search of a mystery 3rd verse or perfect as is? https://t.co/iP7SVvk0LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5ZQC2YJJ02 can't tell you what this song does to my writing spirit  https://t.co/5ZQC2YJJ02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CHN7ZSJ12o One of the Best  https://t.co/CHN7ZSJ12o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/j4kpWuBo4W Friday Night Tunes. Some of the deep good ones from almost every CBr's favourite homegrown https://t.co/j4kpWuBo4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanFitz_Gerald @JonGatehouse Fiscally Prudent. What's not to like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @TorontoStar And are promising never do it again. This is feeling like an abusive relationship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS : So people will say I get Hard Wood and they'll say Trudeau gets Soft Wood? Make it Yuge Hard Wood and then Deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[raptors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start with 3 Muscadet's  to find a favourite. Just missing the Oyster's https://t.co/VjndfEzTX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting mind to hand to pen to paper https://t.co/Y0phRnuLjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @M_Hedberg: https://t.co/CxdxtSlE56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly https://t.co/xrHWYqzXUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andymoney69: doc emrick calls the rat getting thrown out of a house https://t.co/uFgkBmCFYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddale8: I really think everyone on the left should read Breitbart and InfoWars. Even once a month. They're essential to understanding t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SNL  zentex commercial is an example of the good SNL. Funny Quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countdown to the first Earl Weaver mention #BlueJays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell " a little song , a little dance, a little seltzer down your pants"  Chuckles the Clown - w honourable mention to Letterman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#preakness 9 -4-2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carlbildt: Reports of White House been in lockdown after someone tried to climb over the fence. Doesn’t say in which direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primawesome Still called A Bad Idea unless you are a Farmer. Overalls or Coveralls. But never the Jumper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJenNeale_PD @wyshynski @JoshuaCooper @Sean_Leahy I've enjoyed your content and will find it wherever you go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt It was We- Wee Hands are not a symbol of anything]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>