<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sumo Association cancels recruit fitness test -- because no one applied: For only the second time in Sumo history, Japan's national association has had to cancel a fitness test for new recruits -- because no one applied. https://t.co/HpkV4Wg6NY https://t.co/DLd4hMbyd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference… https://t.co/vivHkyUplx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seremaia Bai: The rugby great giving hope to Fiji's youth: Seremaia Bai is Fiji's second-highest point scorer in rugby union. After a long and storied career he's now passing his knowledge on to the country's youth. https://t.co/z0qiMUKHl7 https://t.co/QIBQOdC8wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer I: Applicant Home Job Description – Ball Corporation Job Title: Software Engineer I – (******) Job ID: ****** Location: OH – Dayton (Fairborn) Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Return to Page Who We Are: Ball… https://t.co/FxGIrMLNr3 https://t.co/oXn5cvJpaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer II: Job Title Web Designer II Applications Accepted From Special Instructions to Applicants This position is eligible for the following benefits: Level 3 – Sick Leave; Retirement Posting Number *******T Job Description Uses current practices… https://t.co/RHDU4fOUZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead IT Business Analyst: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 16 minutes ago(6/19/2018 10:11 AM) Job ID 23729 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance Group. As one of… https://t.co/EnOA353UVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's yuan is falling against the dollar: Here's what's going on: Could China's currency become a new flashpoint in its trade fight with the United States? https://t.co/Dciy7IUVso https://t.co/3H4GqefwH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon wants you to start a business to deliver its packages: Amazon has announced a new program to create small businesses that can deliver its packages in branded vans and uniforms. https://t.co/zyijDY52J7 https://t.co/He37KyOyOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how the travel ban is impacting families near and far: In some cases, families are separated by continents. In other cases, the quest for the "American dream" might be over. https://t.co/S1mCsSjtfx https://t.co/szH7LeDh7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marrying a Syrian means breaking up with America: Anna Lekas Miller writes that Trump's travel ban, recently upheld by the Supreme Court, means she and her Syrian fiancé will not settle in the United States in the near future. https://t.co/kby4ZFokI9 https://t.co/st3kvD4WKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced SaaS Information Developer: For Siemens Advanced SaaS Information Developer job – Engineering – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens… https://t.co/hxJSSSfx9C https://t.co/q4YuQYfc2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Acquisition Manager (Information Assurance Engineer): USfalcon – Careers USfalcon, Inc – Benefits – Employees &amp; Returning Candidates – New Candidate Senior Acquisition Manager (Information Assurance Engineer) LocationOhio Job Description and… https://t.co/0PKBaYvYzu https://t.co/0W83imii2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist Soil Plant Sciences: Dupont | Data Scientist – Soil &amp; Plant Sciences (DataSci/Analytics/Machine Learning)(PhD) in Johnston, IA – Visit – ************** – | – Create / Edit My Profile – | – View Jobs In: – EnglishFrenchSpanishPortuguese… https://t.co/tHpk4EpR1x https://t.co/dQEkB9nM5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell: 'We will vote to confirm Justice Kennedy's successor this fall': Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Wednesday that his chamber will work to replace Justice Anthony Kennedy before the midterms, a decision filled with political… https://t.co/4TWup31WUF https://t.co/44G8fXXYsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Cup curse continues -- Germany crashes out of Russia 2018: Germany became the third straight World Cup winner to exit at the group stage in the following tournament when it was beaten by South Korea while Sweden beat Mexico in Group F. https://t.co/6DtiC5obIU https://t.co/6B3mt2uhcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy's Matteo Salvini says being called a populist 'is a compliment': Italy's Matteo Salvini also said recent elections in Europe that brought populists to power were a sign European liberalism had failed. https://t.co/KBCbD9oE6g https://t.co/jQvOGmQG9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GTAC Teamcenter Application Support Engineer Advanced: **GTAC Teamcenter Application Support Engineer Advanced** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business… https://t.co/Fx4Lf27aVn https://t.co/dUDImnvsP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest night so far for progressives and other takeaways from Tuesday night's primaries: If a progressive war against the Democratic establishment is coming, Tuesday's primaries were the first shots fired. https://t.co/Fy2TMw3jjG https://t.co/NgwIFHW4ZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (IT Early Development Program): Software Developer (IT Early Development Program) 2018b Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – Our Company – Careers Home – Job Search –… https://t.co/EBHV5iYLhD https://t.co/hBLqYDqMV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best and worst US states for children: A new Annie E. Casey Foundation report ranks all 50 states for overall child well-being. New Hampshire ranks highest, and New Mexico ranks lowest. https://t.co/BSxRUsH3cT https://t.co/KiNROtPhUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior XML Modeler/ XSLT Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 days ago(6/18/2018 3:18 PM) Job ID 23720 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/OHagEAVzp5 https://t.co/baST43PmCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a MAINFRAME APPLICATION DEVELOPER… https://t.co/gSYPAAoAIo https://t.co/UI7vJX4Iyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Voice Engineer: Cisco Voice Engineer Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show… https://t.co/VkhK0xyr9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77417BR Job Category Sales, Services, and Solutions Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position Summary… https://t.co/gF9q1k4NqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colbert, Fallon and Conan team up to tease Trump: Stephen Colbert, Jimmy Fallon and Conan O'Brien joined forces on Tuesday night to take some shots at President Trump. https://t.co/pnSVDqhSES https://t.co/LoJ8WghVB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer / Project Manager: Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, systems integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial… https://t.co/Ij1npmm7j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Developer: Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Java Developer in Columbus, OH to design, develop, test, and maintain enterprise software applications for the financial industry utilizing object oriented design, Java, GitHub, Maven, Jenkins, JSON,… https://t.co/bvjUo4IJbE https://t.co/snaysUtCrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report highlights gender discrimination, lack of female representation in Justice Department: A report from the inspector general for the Justice Department painted a stark picture of overwhelming male representation at four key federal law enforcement… https://t.co/JsWmoyI4Ky https://t.co/jNYomQj0hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walgreens pharmacist and SCOTUS have a message for women: There is no question that the assault on the rights of women--in legislatures, in the courts, from the White House, and now at the neighborhood Walgreens, where a woman was denied medication for a… https://t.co/uxaZRfj6g5 https://t.co/irKaghl7xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian pop star at center of 2016 Trump Tower meeting story trolls US: The Russian pop star who is said to have requested the infamous Trump Tower meeting in 2016 released a music video playing fun with about as many risqué Trump stories as he could fit… https://t.co/uvaQICbINK https://t.co/tL9SA9Yyvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware/Web Engineering Manager: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/bCSbOkfv10 https://t.co/tJI3M57b6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avionics Software Engineer, Associate: Applicant Home Job Description – Ball Corporation Job Title: Avionics Software Engineer, Associate – ****** Job ID: ****** Location: OH – Dayton (Fairborn) Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Return… https://t.co/YAAkvGH5iJ https://t.co/7FEDsfXVMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS Access Database Developer,: SpaceBound, Inc. SpaceBound, Inc. Home About Us Careers MS Access Database Developer SpaceBound is looking for an experienced MS Access Programmer to assist the development team by maintaining, troubleshooting, and… https://t.co/F7w6tZP2Co https://t.co/83tUhZRBBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Largest US nail manufacturer 'on the brink of extinction' because of the steel tariffs: Steel tariffs could force Mid-Continent Nail, the nation's largest nail factory, to close or move to Mexico, costing 500 jobs. https://t.co/OIC3JEyy44 https://t.co/LybNN0ImRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 19 people were shot Monday in Chicago, where police for months have touted declining gun violence: On Monday, at least 19 people were shot in Chicago. Two of them -- including a teenager -- were killed. https://t.co/amYmUtS2YV https://t.co/Gil6vI3mwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Tester with WORKSOFT Automation Exp: SAP Tester with WORKSOFT Automation Exp Ref No.: 18-23721 Location: Dublin, Ohio Position: SAP Tester with WORKSOFT Automation Exp. Location: Dublin,OH 2+ years of WORKSOFT Automation experience Expertise in… https://t.co/96wiRliB2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Executive – Software Banking – Pipeline:   Job Description – Sales Executive – Software Banking – Pipeline (018558) Job Description  Sales Executive – Software Banking – Pipeline-018558 Description   Diebold Nixdorf, Incorporated is a leading… https://t.co/qjoo9KnaCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Web Developer Ref No.:18-10101 Location: Mason, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/05/2018 Web Developer – Int PHP or Ruby Java CSS Springboot Javascript SQL 1 Responsible for planning, organizing, writing and editing API… https://t.co/v03qgi7oyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13th century drawing of cockatoo sparks rethink on ancient trade routes: The drawings, found in a 13th century manuscript in the Vatican library, suggest that trade off the coast of Australia was occurring much earlier than previously thought. https://t.co/L31aEbiHfv https://t.co/rkPV3vWlMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Cloud Software Developer Advanced – Milford, OH: **Full-Stack Cloud Software Developer Advanced – Milford, OH** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital… https://t.co/KQvI28fiQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/jNjipxYtQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese stocks enter bear market as trade war heats up: China's benchmark Shanghai Composite is now down more than 20% from its most recent peak as fears of an all-out trade war with the US intensify. https://t.co/uwZcNqN1bd https://t.co/6VHMrtxzii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Sr: Software Developer, Sr Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth –… https://t.co/OP1NoRRAdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby Cucumber Test Engineer: Ruby Cucumber Test Engineer Columbus, OH 05-27-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our… https://t.co/fKJj0nZDKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor in Spain faces court over Franco-era 'stolen babies': Eduardo Vela, an 85-year-old obstetrician, faces court in Spain, accused of abducting a newborn in 1969. https://t.co/rCNQc9TyVI https://t.co/RuxDxBQdWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer: Requisition ID *******Posting Date 02/06/2018Category ServicesLocation Dublin, Ohio | United StatesSchedule Full-timeEmployee Status Day JobEEO Tagline: DXC Technology is EEO F/M/Protected Veteran/ Individual with Disabilities –… https://t.co/zLqfoClm61 https://t.co/07KeqncOlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Description at SUSE Skip Navigation ******** Home Page Grab hold of a dynamic, colorful career. Search Our Jobs Search Our Jobs Keyword Search City, State or ZIP Search RadiusRadius5 miles15 miles25… https://t.co/HUaNm3Qako https://t.co/2BEX2K3frz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: What is expected of you and others at this level – Applies comprehensive knowledge and a thorough understanding of concepts, principles, and technical capabilities to perform varied tasks and projects – May contribute to the development… https://t.co/h6MYt7p0Ig https://t.co/Uuk8D9YxKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 8,000 acres burned by wildfires in Northern California: The governor of California has declared a state of emergency in parts of Northern California due to raging wildfires that have burned 8,200 acres so far. https://t.co/ksGC5Kf7lC https://t.co/vnrBLOMYxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C# Programmer: For Siemens Software Engineer – C# Programmer job – Research &amp; Development – Johnson City, Tennessee Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/M6R3F0SHb0 https://t.co/k7geptTaNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best places to visit in Mexico: Considering a trip to Mexico but don't know where to start? Whether it's the hustle and bustle of Mexico City or a quiet retreat such as Isla Holbox, we can help. https://t.co/VlWiCKlcYU https://t.co/OJ9mB43H7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – PLM Teamcenter – Milford, OH: **Software Engineer – PLM Teamcenter – Milford, OH** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business… https://t.co/bhtm6IG9A4 https://t.co/iD4UTl7xYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil and gas industry is coming for Colorado's sand dunes: Alana Miller writes that the Great Sand Dunes, a national treasure, may be compromised if the Trump administration goes forth with a plan to allow oil and gas drilling nearby. https://t.co/f5CdKNu67E https://t.co/Y475fzUqoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Maxine Waters' low-road strategy on Donald Trump is a very bad idea: On Saturday in Los Angeles, California Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters had some thoughts about the Trump administration. Here's the key bit: https://t.co/ELyYG0WvnZ https://t.co/clmqxQzzyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks are not ready for Brexit, says top regulator: Banks are not prepared for a "no deal" Brexit and must act now to avoid putting financial stability at risk, according to the European Union's top regulator. https://t.co/t2lTmBFaBk https://t.co/LUE4hfhDQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans worked all weekend but still not clear if the votes are there for immigration bill: House Republicans will push ahead this week with a vote on their own compromise immigration bill that still faces long odds in the chamber despite… https://t.co/SWEr7PXcov https://t.co/wXB6uIAfO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Supervisor: This position assists in the oversight of the day-to-day operations of the Corporate Service Desk. It is responsible for providing complete and competent technical support to the end users, for providing technical assistance… https://t.co/PZpPYffm9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Front End Developer: Sr. Front End Developer Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex Systems, the nation s 2nd largest IT Staffing organization, has an immediate… https://t.co/L52Ax2lk8j https://t.co/sbCy4R61Sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's app for everything files for huge Hong Kong IPO: Meituan-Dianping, a massive online services platform in China, has filed to go public in Hong Kong in a move that's expected to raise billions of dollars. https://t.co/iaKsRMUqZv https://t.co/glyLuxMUpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer IT IV: Responsibilities: – Design, develop, and test data integration processes per business requirements, following the development standards and best practices as well as participate in code peer reviews to ensure our applications comply with… https://t.co/2A840MPgN3 https://t.co/gjnmmCyxBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Developer III: The Developer is responsible for designing, coding, testing and implementing solutions on time and within budget. He /she will collaborate with analysts and IT teams to develop solutions that meet the requirements given by the… https://t.co/T4BUyJwLc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Global Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/At1EYoCW35 https://t.co/DAuP8KU6bJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors cancel Stormy Daniels interview, attorney says: Federal prosecutors have canceled their planned interview with Stormy Daniels Monday, according to Daniels' attorney. https://t.co/VvxICM19t2 https://t.co/xorsNWh0a6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See all the highlights from the BET Awards: The 2018 BET Awards, which celebrate the best in music, movies and sports, are happening Sunday night. https://t.co/geRWq6ADZ3 https://t.co/IajCAadyUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Software Engineer: C# Software Engineer Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is… https://t.co/r7sXn3lq4a https://t.co/lyvHYCYZQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Sensing Data Scientist (PhD): Job Title: Remote Sensing Data Scientist (PhD) Location: Johnston, IA, Mid-West United States, USA Company: DuPont Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Plant &amp; Soil Sciences, Seed and Biotechnology Career… https://t.co/TJHAH0DmGp https://t.co/KqxX7tdmoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time editor defends crying migrant girl cover: 'She became the face of this story': The top editor at Time Magazine, Ed Felsenthal, defended the use of an image of a crying migrant girl for its cover last week. https://t.co/sQStRduqjt https://t.co/czbkduyrxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glenn Beck walks off CNN interview over questions about his media company: The conservative commentator stormed out Sunday when Brian Stelter, host of CNN's media analysis show "Reliable Sources," asked about job cuts at The Blaze. https://t.co/zRf8v3RYq8 https://t.co/Vu5m982BZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water Resources Project Manager/Project Engineer: 25-Apr-2018 to 24-Jul-2018 (EST) Transportation Conshohocken, PA, USA Salary Full Time Century Engineering – Conshohocken, PA Office Century is seeking a professional engineer to lead a variety of water… https://t.co/zSpfEudBL6 https://t.co/9CYCCDQyJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Michael Bloomberg may be eyeing a 2020 run: Here are the stories our D.C. insiders are talking about in this week's "Inside Politics" forecast, where you get a glimpse of tomorrow's headlines today. https://t.co/3M7gIalk39 https://t.co/gnHeyqQUcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 5 injured in building explosion and fire in Germany: At least five people were injured when an explosion, followed by a fire, tore through an apartment building in Germany. https://t.co/1dSQfXRXiW https://t.co/ZKNuotPZRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly blast hits rally attended by Ethiopian leader: At least two people were killed and more than 100 injured in an explosion Saturday at a rally attended by Ethiopian Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed, officials said. https://t.co/r8SfxgUk8X https://t.co/UdY6dzO11X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: SR Number APPS/APPS/2018/****** Designation Technical Lead Location Ohio Job Family Domain (Domain) Job Description (Posting). To act as a liaison between the business and technical teams| analyze and document business requirements|… https://t.co/NPTT03qCwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Sensing Data Scientist: Job Title: Remote Sensing Data Scientist (masters) Location: Johnston, IA, Mid-West United States, USA Company: DuPont Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Plant &amp; Soil Sciences, Seed and Biotechnology Career… https://t.co/4lp94tNl8N https://t.co/diEaB0eRoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Voice Engineer: Cisco Voice Engineer Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show… https://t.co/eVuLVeiMpO https://t.co/yNSI9lQxlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince William's Middle East tour will be his most challenging royal trip to date: The Duke of Cambridge faces perhaps his biggest international test to date in his upcoming trip to the Middle East. https://t.co/oXjIhg7sKU https://t.co/iZ4oAzKHu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindsphere – Full-Stack Developer – Greater Cincinnati Area: For Siemens Mindsphere – Full-Stack Developer – Greater Cincinnati Area job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/e32rFPO111 https://t.co/uLbMn2I6G9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Mainframe/COBOL developer with SQL: Our direct Fortune 500 client is looking for an SSIS/SSRS developer who is either familiar with Cobol and DB2 or is willing to learn these skills. This is a one year contract-to-hire position in their Cleveland, OH… https://t.co/1uI5CrQgOA https://t.co/2GojUNqUJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand PM reveals her baby's name: New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern and her partner Clarke Gayford have revealed the name of their baby girl, who was born Thursday. https://t.co/Nt8xeELCmS https://t.co/Y3yEzTQXCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[68 years after the Korean War, hundreds of US families are still searching for closure: As a child, Ruth Hebert would run on the beach at the edge of the Pacific and look to the horizon knowing her father was out there, somewhere. https://t.co/iWecy9DxZi https://t.co/XdKvpnHSS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landmark day for Saudi women as kingdom's controversial driving ban ends: Women in Saudi Arabia can legally get behind the wheel of a car for the first time Sunday as the kingdom lifts its longstanding ban on women driving. https://t.co/zVn6wYss1F https://t.co/Q8CLUsMO5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind Tom Arnold's bizarre anti-Trump media blitz: Tom Arnold is a dedicated Trump critic. So eyebrows were raised when he tweeted a picture of himself with Michael Cohen on Thursday night. https://t.co/7bRVU89whj https://t.co/4yZdLsQsSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 arrested in gang rape of anti-trafficking activists in India; police hunt for others: Six men have been accused of rape in connection with a gang rape this week of five female anti-trafficking workers in a village in eastern India, police told CNN on… https://t.co/9l5XkSukXu https://t.co/FDBeKiJBXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist Soil Plant Sciences: Dupont | Data Scientist – Soil &amp; Plant Sciences (DataSci/Analytics/Machine Learning)(PhD) in Johnston, IA – Visit – ************** – | – Create / Edit My Profile – | – View Jobs In: – EnglishFrenchSpanishPortuguese… https://t.co/IFmv1dqicH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats see Trump's Nevada trip as an opening to focus on immigration: President Donald Trump is in Las Vegas on Saturday -- and Democrats are thrilled about it. https://t.co/woUmdIWKNz https://t.co/b9Cc2IOuYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II High Rise Residential: Project Manager II – High Rise Residential Tracking Code 5145-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across… https://t.co/6fkN7x9cHB https://t.co/1FtBz9CkKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst Salesforce PLM: **Business Analyst – Salesforce – PLM** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/XArDhJOdjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jogger detained for 2 weeks after accidentally crossing US-Canada border: A teenager was jogging along a Canadian beach when she inadvertently crossed the border into the United States and ended up in detention for two weeks. https://t.co/JaTsVUoX49 https://t.co/LBupRklZbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer: Web Applications Developer Job Dayton, OH | Marxent Call Us: ************ Contact Us – 3D ROOM DESIGNER – AUGMENTED REALITY – Furnished – Augmented Reality Furniture App – Q &amp; A: MxT Tracking vs. ARKit – Q &amp; A: Markerless… https://t.co/S2LcyUcJDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GTAC Teamcenter Application Support Engineer Advanced: For Siemens GTAC Teamcenter Application Support Engineer Advanced job – Engineering – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard… https://t.co/DEvoGn57id https://t.co/Rk5QaFRP65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xiaomi wants to raise over $6 billion in Hong Kong IPO: Xiaomi, one of the world's leading smartphone makers, is is aiming for the biggest stock market listing in nearly two years. https://t.co/vc7IEDtbld https://t.co/1a5r8N21UU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US suspends military exercises with South Korea after Singapore summit: The United States will suspend a number of military exercises with South Korea that were due to take place over coming months, amid ongoing negotiations with North Korea, the US… https://t.co/qaGlbCympL https://t.co/cJ1sjv3IgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP sources: Justice Department has not satisfied all House GOP document requests: Republicans said Friday there are still outstanding records requests that the Justice Department has not satisfied in the House Republican dispute with DOJ, according to… https://t.co/DLRT3ftMyL https://t.co/DqbVGFATgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – EDI: Software Developer – EDI / Cincinnati , OH Overview:Seeking a Software Developer to build and maintain Microsoft BizTalk 2013/2016 applications, and C# .NET applications for use within an EDI/SOA environment. Along with… https://t.co/2wozXayKof https://t.co/vfNdu96CSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House approves massive opioids legislation: The House of Representatives on Friday passed the most expansive legislation Congress has taken to date to address the opioid crisis, approving a bipartisan package that combines 58 bills passed in the last two… https://t.co/yPB1lFSjcI https://t.co/wQRTthilzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC rolls the dice, again, with Roseanne-free 'Roseanne': ABC canceled 'Roseanne' after racist tweets by its star. But what was a principled act looks shakier with its effort to revive the show as 'The Conners' https://t.co/oekbUcJVFY https://t.co/pDvuctHTLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Software Engineer: C# Software Engineer Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is… https://t.co/r69e5K61aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump endorses Alabama congresswoman who disavowed him in 2016: President Donald Trump on Friday endorsed an Alabama congresswoman who in 2016 rescinded her endorsement of the then-Republican nominee after his crude remarks on the "Access Hollywood" tape… https://t.co/7B98wMCrA1 https://t.co/oQFVTXwoJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US wants to leave this American in Syria with $4,210 and no passport: After two days of walking in the Syrian desert, one fitful night sleeping in a mud hut and a failed attempt to bribe a local into vouching for him to get safe passage out of ISIS… https://t.co/liTGh2iyMQ https://t.co/Ch4nafONo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Search Jobs – RADcube – Technology Solutions – Enterprise Integrations – Enterprise Integration consulting – API Lifecycle Management – SaaS Integration – SOA – Application Services – Mobile Application Services – Web Content… https://t.co/UadzoyL7Lo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>