<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My new live/work studio has its own loading bay and retractable metal door from the alley to the inside. As I... https://t.co/O7AnNcY8oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea dr doom!! #marvel #painting #drdoom https://t.co/KgMHidhJCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress pic of this painting of Dr Doom! It's getting very close I just want to punch up the highlights and the... http://t.co/FuPlkzEeFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making excellent project on this project for STAEDTLER - finishing tonight! Cassette tape imagery on converse... http://t.co/K6q3In4Za5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful evening studio light! #art #painting https://t.co/oNvmWAjwPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[work work http://t.co/lEw887dOFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work in progress...new art #painting #comingsoon https://t.co/bTjvWmTAMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New painting in progress. About 50% now. Time to start adding lots of tight details, deeper colours, more rich... http://t.co/rglhs6s8NH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alistaircalder theres a good chance, this will be the first one with this collaged element but it's worked very well in other pieces so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming soon! Over the next few weeks this will become a new 3x4 foot painting. It's the first time I'm applying a... http://t.co/Yupp1DvV0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting in my favorite low key waterfront park! Beautiful relaxing morning facing the city http://t.co/jdlNFnZ6gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO rad, starting a commission of multiple superhero images. First up - Ironman...radrad http://t.co/S0XLsrP78X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO rad, starting a commission of multiple superhero images. First up - Ironman...radrad http://t.co/fOQQtdDrnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINISHED - a new painting that I'm stoked about, continuing to explore the urban Labyrinths of the DTES,... http://t.co/pMeGvs4fSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited to paint retro music cassette tapes on this panel that I've prepped.

For a change, I made some loose... http://t.co/GRcPsXKGw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice one! I just finished this commissioned painting of Boba Fett. I definitely have a fond enjoyment for... http://t.co/lEfZZJCb5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketch of a clone trooper while watching fresh prince #starwars http://t.co/iK4VxvfJUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new project I'm developing for Staedtler North America. Working on a pair of high-boot Converse, I'm... http://t.co/GhRb8UDObO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Culture Crawl is next month! http://t.co/RVXD0SGdgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend asked me yesterday how big the Darth painting I just finished was so I figure I'd do a to-ginger-scale... http://t.co/1zoTsJEAVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the day! URBANITY opens tonight, 7pm, at Cityscape Gallery in North Van (335 Lonsdale). Hope to see you... http://t.co/wWmZ3GiSTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreyVancouver: Tonight’s the night for our very own @JonShawPainting – check out Urbanity at Cityscape Gallery from 7-9pm! http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more day until Urbanity opens at the Cityscape Gallery! Hope to see you tomorrow, 7-9pm, @ 335 Lonsdale in... http://t.co/OHsZvDWtdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new alleyway pic I've drawn over the past week or so. I've done all the drawing in the sun these days... http://t.co/ESTtZ9cJoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding some details to this darth vader painting #starwars #Vancouver #art http://t.co/vRm1jBv1t2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks everybody who came to the show last night, it was great! So many people and non stop busy. I loved it all... http://t.co/2BWBSdQOLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new work I just finished that I'm really pleased with http://t.co/HhM3DALZYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All finished! This is my latest piece, "Assemblage". 36" x 48", for exhibition at Kimoto Gallery :) I'm very... http://t.co/p24VtaWo2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I photo-adventured to rail town to document the Vancouver shipping cranes. I think this is going to become a... http://t.co/uY5Ie5oXWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my third painting for next month's show in North Van, I'm happy with this third one (and the set as a whole): https://t.co/YpmQ1MIfoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomidraw hey r u in state of the art this year? i am too..saw your name on the list of artists, wanted to say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sharpie super cool guys - i use sharpie to draw with lots too and i just found this blog :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonclaytor painful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/z8Knot3V Jenny Saville is one of my favourite painters ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC @jonshawpainting ya buddy! if u are there on the second friday to stay overnight, u can catch me at the show painting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC sweet! ill be there both weekends. I hope we can hit up the slopes at the same time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC will you be up at telus both weekends..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yessssss I was selected as one of the five live painters for State of the Art at Telus Fest :) Come chill April 20th :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Friday you should go to Sean Karemaker's opening at the Gam Gallery. Great artist, Great gallery - can't wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmiLaDeDa thx ami!! I really appreciate that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please vote for my design in this competition?? :)

http://t.co/htT4J6g0 http://t.co/GMSh3pjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobLoud thanks for the follow rob!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like the idea of me making t shirts? http://t.co/NNjQcIBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato I haven't gotten into prints just yet. I think it may be on the horizon tho. Not this one tho cuz it's a vommission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato  thanks for the RT buddy! I'm glad u dig the work I do!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterested Panther..??  http://t.co/NlURBTgP via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato @jonshawpainting thanks buddy, i had a very good time making it! There's a good chance im gonna do a 4 foot lion piece..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my latest commission piece, recently handed over to its buyer (although I definitely miss it..) http://t.co/cHqyn8Yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a commission I just handed over to its buyer on the weekend. I had a lot of fun making this one - there... http://t.co/ojgKP0RV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just counted and I've got 12 pieces on the go. Putting them up at cuppa joy coffee early April. I should prob finish these :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnsoeNwk I dig the reubens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling is that an art piece :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_deHaas haha that made my day - I KNEW I'd see you soon!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are into art, and DON'T know about Lucien Freud, you would be wise to look up his work. When  http://t.co/xUG6JgVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC but if my live painting date (should know by tomorrow) is close to the second weekend, ill stick around to board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC you may not, the show isn't up that weekend. so by then my art displayin' and my live painting will be over...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC whooooo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot - I have two openings on April 13th. Can't be at both :S I choose..Whistler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyCorso hey thx for the follow - nice background!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@van_twop_1000 thx for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Darrentifqaklm @ipaddep thanks! I find I'm picking up influences from everywhere, so I started photographin my palettes too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 3 weeks until State of the Art up at Whistler..If you are gonna be there for Telus Fest come see me and my work! #art #telusfest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusArtSupplies @jonshawpainting thanks! im stoked to see some of the other work in the show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be participating in this group show at Gallery Fukai next month, some amazing talent going in there: http://t.co/yEixnxJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artboy68 my painting palette! Realized I need to document them because they are inspiring and cool!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/iphbFEen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I see when I look out of the window at my job http://t.co/1nevuUjM via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - Opus is offering me free art supplies to teach at their store :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest commission is a leopard - starting to paint it tonight http://t.co/o9gpN2Vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMasseyArt Found your work via saatchi, i really like it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wssf its gonna be so much fun to set up these new pieces... :) i made three just for SOTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another new piece:

Cathartes aura
Ink and acrylic on canvas
24" x 48" 
2012

Also gonna up at Telus Fest next... http://t.co/V3AVXDN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece well underway: 

Ara spp.
Ink and acrylic on canvas
30" x 40"
2012

Check it at Telus Fest next month! http://t.co/gSEbdlUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_deHaas dude whats your route (s) ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's one of the three new [finished] pieces I'm exhibiting at Telus Fest next month: http://t.co/7rp34vDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for Telus Fest's State of the Art show - stoked to meet fellow participating artists:... http://t.co/zOrANyrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to draw a hippo soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is definitely the coolest my palette has ever looked while painting http://t.co/uzZUbUtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CroquisMagenta hey thanks for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This flamingo piece is coming along nicely. More line work tomorrow. http://t.co/9lV8GX7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expanding my web presence. Tumblr, you are mine next: http://t.co/EallSX54 http://t.co/E6Ww0CLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm drawing parrots http://t.co/GaY3kL4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andreaarmstrong ya they're so cool!! Have u posted any of
Yours? I'd love to see one in your wicked style.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece in progress (early stages) - Flamingooooo!! http://t.co/Q9eP1Un0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViewArtGallery1 you are certainly in luck in that case!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViewArtGallery1 thanks for the follow! i love victoria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart @YapesPaints @acageybee ART LOVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kyle_Gosselin hey there thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - I will have a piece up at Gallery Fukai in a group show called Design24. Details to follow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT thanks april :) @YapesPaints @acageybee @birdonawireart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome. Love stuff like this :) http://t.co/Stz13TZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dangerpants88 thanks dude - things are super rad. the painting is def one thing that i spend my days doing out in da west. still at mac?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehauntedzoo i cant wait to see your works at SOTA man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PosNegGallery thanks for following guys! love the space :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dangerpants88 hey mannnnnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy night at the studio tonight. Nothing makes for a better night than fellow artists, green tea, Zeppelin and warm sweaters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rickgoldschmidt hey rick thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlolight thanks for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtProfiles thanks for the follow :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>