<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Easter discount sales while it last...
https://t.co/sCf6SsmGiC 

You can also... https://t.co/SQfrqGCSjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Easter discount while it last...
https://t.co/sCf6SsmGiC

You can also join our free membership programme https://t.co/MFAyUKM3Ug https://t.co/FX07dCecwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can see your status? By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: There is a saying that man is a social… https://t.co/lqgpiAFe4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can see your status? By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: There is a saying that man is a social… https://t.co/kGZZshuibF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamilyAffairs05: STEPS TO ACCESS THE COURSE
1. Click on this link: https://t.co/MFAyUKM3Ug
2. Access the website
3. Register for free t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never allow that situation to make you question the love of God for you. That situation came too late, God... https://t.co/6sp5Sa0Lr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STEPS TO ACCESS THE COURSE
1. Click on this link: https://t.co/MFAyUKM3Ug
2. Access the website
3. Register for free to view the course https://t.co/8XQdmxj6A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Romance and Intimacy Online Course

Your spouse keeps complaining about this thing you do…you want to stop... https://t.co/mH0P4cOSFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romance &amp; Intimacy Online Course Series: Romance Busters: Your spouse keeps complaining… https://t.co/Xc1xNlxYOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romance &amp; Intimacy Online Course Series: Romance Busters: Your spouse keeps complaining… https://t.co/lE5COOJSZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PressPray This Easter: I have seen spouses who deserted their homes return. I have seen… https://t.co/jECUXiNkFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PressPray This Easter: I have seen spouses who deserted their homes return. I have seen… https://t.co/ZZOBhVvmPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have seen spouses who deserted their homes return. I have seen wife-beaters become so sweet and protective of... https://t.co/YHAaVYgRTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 30. I pray you experience the power of His resurrection! #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 29. Nothing can beat the power of His resurrection. #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 28. Speak to those things that seem dead and watch them come back to life; speak to your marriage! #PressPray #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 27. As we mark the death and resurrection of our Lord, Jesus, believe that that which seems dead can rise again.  #PressP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26. Find faith and believe that that condition can turn around.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 25. Sometimes, people give up when they are so close to their breakthrough. #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 24. You may have tried without results, but try again. #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 23. You can have that sweet spouse back, you can enjoy your marriage again.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 22. I've seen wives who can nag like... become the sweethearts of their husbands,bringing him nothing but joy.  #PressPra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 21. I have seen wife-beaters become so sweet and protective of their wives.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20. I have seen spouses who deserted their homes return.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 19. I have seen some very difficult cases turn around to the wonder of everyone who knew about them.  #PressPray #iConnec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18. Before you discount what I am trying to say, can I encourage you to try praying about that situation? #PressPray #iCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17. Can I remind U that for reasons like this, God sent His son to die in exchange for our pain, hurt &amp; sickness. #PressP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16. Your 'strange' spouse can become your lover again.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 15. That marriage can bounce back.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14. ...you may be overwhelmed at the moment, but I'd like you to know that there is hope! Yes, there is hope!  #PressPray…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. It doesn't matter how tough the situation might be, your marriage might be going through a trying phase;... #PressPra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12b. ...she has decided to resign to fate and take things as they come. #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12. Having done all that was within her power to do with no tangible result,...  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 11. Ken is against the idea of seeing a counsellor.  #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10. She decided to see a counsellor and followed every suggestion religiously, but things did not improve.  #PressPray #i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9. "Will I ever enjoy my marriage again?"... More questions... #PressPray #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8. "What happened to this good man? How did things get this bad?" These were some of the questions on her mind. #PressPra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If two are better than one, then our spouses must do better, as married men/women, than they did as singles. #SupportHerDream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/9xTZk6dCnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish my parents told me!

I was privileged to be in the midst of a group of 25 adolescents. The short time I... https://t.co/mOGLYXUQeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliberate Parenting! – Chidi Akunna: I was privileged to be in the midst of a group of 25… https://t.co/wt3bMQWaEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliberate #Parenting! – Chidi Akunna: I was privileged to be in the midst of a group of 25… https://t.co/BwvaqFWOfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a just man falls seven times, and rises up again - Proverbs 24:16a

It doesn't matter how many times you have... https://t.co/5w0DG9Wy0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Need my freedom, I don’t care about my family! by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “Well, it’s not… https://t.co/RIuAIvyMxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Need my freedom, I don’t care about my family! by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “Well, it’s not… https://t.co/GcigxhoXkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Relationship is a living organism, how you nurture it determines how it will grow!"| Victor Akunna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is difficult to emotionally connect with someone who is dishonest. #KeepingSecrets #RomanceQuotient]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heart is the engine room of life, love, romance &amp; relationships.This is where we fall in or out of love. Stay connected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/AbzLJqU8yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bM4EHmrEM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#inspiration #fail #habit #hurt https://t.co/VGlQ2eFtOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Married but lonely by Victor Akunna: Love is sweet! It is a great experience to be… https://t.co/A3Xzu0S3fS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Married but #lonely by Victor Akunna: #Love is sweet! It is a great experience to be… https://t.co/xRJS0NE5MS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60 minutes Romance by Chidi and Victor Akunna: How many of us can spend time with our… https://t.co/Lbdm6QoFOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60 minutes Romance by Chidi and Victor Akunna: How many of us can spend time with our… https://t.co/6kWb9pwwG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/iTGfYoSGPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When listening to your spouse, your priority must be to understand his/her perspective, rather than to correct or... https://t.co/7tYod8MwL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uxVpfXS01m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Escape 3 By Victor Akunna: When Lucy approached me, she asked if I was having a… https://t.co/V3iDe25wRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Escape 3 By Victor Akunna: When Lucy approached me, she asked if I was having a… https://t.co/lTQdRR4mxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is sweet! It is a great experience to be cherished; to be valued, not just for the things you can do, but... https://t.co/DLPIHcjhf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Reflections By Victor Akunna: I want to share a brief thought with us. Are you waiting… https://t.co/KiJ1VcSmtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Reflections By Victor Akunna: I want to share a brief thought with us. Are you waiting… https://t.co/1Vg0d2MPFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Reflections By Victor Akunna: I want to share a brief thought with us. Are you waiting… https://t.co/5RZ4nl6KKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Reflections By Victor Akunna: I want to share a brief thought with us. Are you waiting… https://t.co/WzkfTFa7UI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If your spouse cannot be vulnerable with you, then there is a level of intimacy you cannot experience as a... https://t.co/wkwXaNvkEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us as we bring you this month's edition of "Our Romance Story" by a great couple, Adetunji and Megan Adewumi
https://t.co/1Q9kAwrVXi https://t.co/wN0TZ792K1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our Romance Story"

Join us as we bring you this month's edition of "Our Romance Story" by a great couple,... https://t.co/43Z9491QxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Romance Story – By Adetunji and Megan Adewumi: FFA: Thank you for being willing to… https://t.co/UKxu5wG8uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #Romance Story – By Adetunji and Megan Adewumi: FFA: Thank you for being willing to… https://t.co/K2C0mvJt3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do You Avoid Family Heartache? - Foundation For Family Affairs https://t.co/r74AYWluXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If leadership is influence, then another word for parenting is leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 41. If you are struggling to let go of past hurt despite your best efforts, consider seeing a Therapist. #PastErrors #iCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 40. True healing is an inside job! #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 39. Search within your heart to address any lingering issue that may trigger suspicion and fear! #PastErrors #iConnectHea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 38.There is Grace available if we are willing to open our hearts again,willing to let go so God can do the work. #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 37. Being willing to open your heart and let God know how you feel about the hurt is a good start. #PastErrors #iConnectH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 36. Truth is, there are things that are difficult to forgive, that's why we need the help of God. #PastErrors #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 35. Someone reading this might say, "she doesn't understand. If only she knows the pain and embarrassment". #PastErrors #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 34. At such times,it is needless for her husband to argue. Simply reassure her &amp; do not take it to heart. Tough! #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 33. It is important to weigh the impact of our words before unleashing them. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 32. Some women do not realise the extent of damage such emotional outbursts can cause. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 31. ...yet she still refers to it, especially when she feels insecure about something. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 30. E.g. U gave money to her friend in the past without consulting her because it was an emergency situation,... #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 29.I must state that there are times women make emotional statements,especially when they need some reassurance. #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 28b. Is that really the solution to staying loyal to you? #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 28. Yes, you simply enslave yourself when you try to check out what your spouse is up to each time. #PastErrors #iConnect…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 27. Why the torturous suspicion? #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 25.If your spouse can't be vulnerable with U, then there is a level of intimacy U cannot experience as a couple. #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 24. In the words of @familyaffairs05, "there can be no intimacy without vulnerability." #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 23b. ...and in some cases, that has been like the molten magma in a volcanic eruption. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 23. This is why some spouses would rather keep their errors to themselves ... #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 22. Actually, that would decide if he/she would open up to you again in the future. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 21. Back to what triggered my line of thought, it is important how you react to your spouse's 'confession'. #PastErrors #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20.Focusing on your spouse's past errors will keep you from enjoying a level of fulfilment in your relationship. #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18. Nagging&amp;constantly reminding him/her of the unmet expectation/obligation would not yield a positive result. #PastErro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17. Whatever happened to unconditional love? #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16. You leave your spouse feeling undeserving of love. He/she would have to keep trying hard to earn your love. #PastErro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 15. Giving up on your spouse or refusing to trust him/her again is not the right approach. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14. It might be that their spouses failed in the past or did not live up to a promise. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>