<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShannonFonseca Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about the clip of your son and cat. Can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiphaniemoreau Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vous contacter au sujet cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoraLhaneche Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vous contacter au sujet cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kadikadou Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vous contacter au sujet cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@modelqueen86 @Camden @Newsflare Can you follow me so I can send a direct message please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@savannahloveldr Hi Savannah, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jowishot @BBCBreaking @BBCNews @BBC Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alphamelville @LondonFire Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjDanPropaganda Hi Dan, I'm with @Newsflare Can we have a quick chat on DM about your video please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@modelqueen86 @Camden Hi Lisa, I'm with @Newsflare Can we have a quick chat on DM about your video please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@e1125w @TheEllenShow Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM pls? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doodlewhale Hi Stuart, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat about your video of the dog on the bike. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArgoJosiah Hi Josiah, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMDeLoach @Newsflare Can you follow me so I can send a DM please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kentrazon @chrissyteigen @johnlegend Hi Kenneth, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please, can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaitlin Hi Kaitlin, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Please, can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMDeLoach Hi Nicole, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your videos of Adele last night. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktalbot21 @Adele Hi Kate, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nukotanhshs Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a direct message please? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mbrby Bjr, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter a propos de la video de votre frere. Peut-on parler par DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_xst Hi Shawn, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about the video of your daughter talking to Solange. Can we talk in DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dez0late Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact your video of last night's attack. Can you follow me so I can DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@char_charmie @TheEllenShow Hi Charmaine, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigCatDerek Hi Derek, I work at @Newsflare and I would like to contact you about your housecat video. Please can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustBasicDave Hi Dave, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about these videos. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaymondFrenken Hi Raymond, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about your video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_prieux Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vous contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xensxr Hi Xeni, I hope you're safe. I'm with @newsflare. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaffronDior Hi Saffron, I'm a journalist at Newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Pls can you follow me so I can send you a DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeSchultz21 Hi Jake, I work at a video agency called Newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phil0x0 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daniTX17 @TheEllenShow Hi Danielle, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_6GoLive Hi Destra, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this vid. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyalMc Hi Paul, I work at @newsflare video agency and I'd like to contact you about your hornet v. tarantula vid. Can we talk on DM?Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavGatt @WindyWilson88 Hi David, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this clip. Pls can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciprianilazar Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you. Pls can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottBeale Hi Scott, I'm with @newsflare and I'm trying to contact your brother about his ball lightning video. Can we talk on DM please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChipBeale Hi Chip, I work at @newsflare video agency and I'd like to contact you about your ball lightning video. Can we talk on DM please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smpsbh Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare, pouvez-vous me suivre pour que je puisse vous envoyer un message privé? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nik_dost @YorchJPI Sure, we already have an existing agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nik_dost @YorchJPI Hi Nikolas, please feel free to email me on laure@newsflare.com for licensing. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@03caulfield @SkyNews @itvnews Hi David, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omgkateryn Hi Kat, I work at @newsflare video agency and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeyscarpato Hi Joe, I work at @newsflare video agency and we'd like to work with your video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mcastellanos47 Hi Matt, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with your video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YABOYDMASON Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch with you about this video. Please can you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sam_lewis1 Hi Sam, can you follow me to chat about  your video of @LukeEdwards99's goal please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PotapenkovV Hi Vitaliy, did you film the video of the octopus you posted? I work at @newsflare and I would like to talk to you about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PortmeadSunday @LukeEdwards99 Hi there, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can we talk on DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETFsNI @Newsflare Pouvez-vous me suivre pour que je puisse vous envoyer un message privé svp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETFsNI Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler en DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NinaDetoxPills Hi Nina, I work at an agency called Newsflare and I would like to contact you about this. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeTheRelic @WestYorksPolice Hi Mike, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefoucault Hi Michel, I'd like to get in touch about your video from last night for @newsflare. Can you follow me so I can send a DM pls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grahlinay Hi Graham, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about ur Flying Scotsman video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starmar7 Hi, i hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about you fire vid. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbytran01 Hi Bobby, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saigesmith_ Hi i work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morgan_LeighP Hi i work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FastfoodRights Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your videos of the strike. Can you follow me so I can send a Dm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raffi_tapanian Hi Raffi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tywells_ Hi Tyler, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ginterUF Hi Chris, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaHindle1 @syptweet Hi Victoria, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Saving_History Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about the skeleton exhumation video. Can we talk on DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trenchdetective Hi Colin, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you. Can you follow me back so I can send you a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukedeBelder Hi Luke, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get int ouch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM pls? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrSpace @WWAY @wectnews @StarNewsOnline Hi Ethan, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouTubeMe__ Hi Shanan, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your acid attack video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@negativebid Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DT58EFC @Newsflare My bad! We would still be interested. Can you follow me so I can explain what we do in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenitram1970 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DT58EFC Hi David, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your hurricane Harvey video? Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparky_AD Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video? Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Typecally Hi Malin, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your Trivago video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KMillar15 Hi Kevin, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azou_75 Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter. Pouvez-vous me suivre pour que je puisse envoyer un DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrThomsIzi Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter. Pouvez-vous me suivre pour que je puisse envoyer un DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miramajbour Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreNiekerk Hi Andre, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DP_PaolaBaker Hi Paola, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaliaKaki Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BriceBxl @airtransat Hi Brice, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please, can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FRBako Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JGDBCN @BrusselsAirport Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkerSayers Hi Parker, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please, can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AyerdiX Hi Ale, I'm a journalist with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your fire video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigitalMarvyn Hi Marvyn, I'm with @newsflare. Could we have a quick chat on DM about the video? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shashajade_ Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaChaparro @AmericanAir Hi Daniela, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM Pls? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blmllrc Bonjour, je travaille chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tolukicom Bonjour, je travaille chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olivedufour Bonjour Olivier, je travaille chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@photoshopgirl69 Hi Amy, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your video of Scout with his goggles. Can we talk on DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeeMarks16 Hi, I work at a @newsflare and I would like to contact you about these videos. Please, can you follow me back so I can send you a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holliewood1988 @Newsflare Great, can you follow me so I can send a direct message please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holliewood1988 Hi Hollie, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about the video of your son at the zoo. Can we talk on DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahVave Hi Sarah, I work at @newsflare vid agency. Can we talk on DM about the video of your nephew at the zoo? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anita_Karr @TheEllenShow @Buckitdream @iamjeanniek Hi Anita, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWpgDoodles Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about the video of your dog at the beach. Can we talk on DM? Thanks]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>