<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/2wK6m5A9qF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/MzoL99NwgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/MF4ElZSlbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/JmOrNd89lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/QgMntOGGAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/3H1rymBDiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/IQVUIyGSHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/ydTXn1rKhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/cZBodso2ML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/eyISl2VjtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/uFeypm5lHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/xY24RZNVx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/Z6b5q3ceEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/szp7pPZC4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/sevlw7NEFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/zNyuAd8fYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/adXMjIeCRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/7R4Oh0Pn70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/pVVqZ1y8Du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/bymdzIOtnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/FkNI6NoVpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/qUOVdh2YXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/wbigVbKYeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/6iofVUEfpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has great marketing, among the best PR and marketing in the world. - Ron Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/jWLew62MbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/QODCYAJFi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/1crjTXq0YJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/ukyYRhKxyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the Cecil B. DeMille of science fiction. - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/lLcpnrPjAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/kLExSrPjbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/sHc0WtnPKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/QGwY3FIstL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/uQdsdtrnYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/AxtmLUXLaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/9AtMKY2yd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/bMyMef5Dwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/KIOm2Edr7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/jomy60jj3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/ft767PYUYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/YS0Psx6YPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/FgpcgNYJ9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/UsQUm666JI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/WqDqkFeT2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/pMxgtzzPJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/ZCXosaUoN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/DfldFllK7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>