<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/4mImq5jZPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/i1glAYWpvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/ZpwpdeVcqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/Pnnd521zZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget how fast you did a job - but they remember how well you did it. - Howard Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/0bjPsAN8ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/HCJUWo5L5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/VP7bW2ll10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/mpkOdRneGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/eq3e3Z3ApS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/hf9hJ2iaYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/diMvoMeoDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/nxMNzouO9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/GibPOzCHhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/jvKO6PZ7ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/dZaXlvQGI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/h2KYmYlZZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/gTH03unw1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/T8IXR2Z25q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/5rnmnYiDdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/jJuGBCMW66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/WpMKunp73U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/nrHS8STW5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/kCBbvbmhcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Out why Facebook is great for Your Business  http://t.co/7jkxfy9tQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/TuThskzAGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/7om32u07wB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/K03xoAZ56v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/yA7v1IAnf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/hYMdca3Iev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/kDp10KCiuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/SHc22DFLrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/nbrqNL6Yl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/QJLs7wHIt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/ltPOphwMjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/ZfUpI5hZGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/hN6WTp259T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/tnXkvEqmZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/ilfHuDufVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/SbB5LbF90Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/YMoDtztWqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/hTBNXj6z3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/GRZuMJcdx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/O9GWPl7O9R]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>