<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 6b. is more important than spending time with them. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 6a. For some parents, being able to get their children what they want for Christmas ...#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 5. "Don't tell me you are working for me when you don't even know what bothers me." #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 4. A young lad responded, "who cares about those gifts when they are never accessible?"#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 3.A young girl said,"Christmas is almost here, mum has 2 work extra hours to be able to get us our Christmas presents"#Ch…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up! by Chidi and Victor AKunna: Consistent Honour: We… https://t.co/EwAViY58Gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up! by Chidi and Victor AKunna: Consistent Honour: We… https://t.co/aPZLNt0J0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up!

Consistent Honour: We have been doing a series on this question 
"how... https://t.co/N0Hir5S95D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode: “My 11 year old wants to have a boyfriend”: #Competence: As a follow-up on… https://t.co/TiNwE5IQ09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode: “My 11 year old wants to have a boyfriend”: Competence: As a follow-up on… https://t.co/Bf9hjeivVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up!

Someone once asked me, "how do I get my man to open up?". As I... https://t.co/CFQABfDGuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up! By Victor Akunna: Someone once asked me, “how do… https://t.co/RmkQobSy8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IntimacyCode: Getting him/her to open up! By Victor Akunna: Someone once asked me, “how do… https://t.co/TumyGL7wif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover The Red Spot And Spice Up Your Romance – By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “I love him so… https://t.co/P0xUqVppSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover The Red Spot And Spice Up Your #Romance – By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “I #love him… https://t.co/AKQkPKh08u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the Honeymoon Have to End? By Sandi Greene: One night during our engagement, my fiancé… https://t.co/iFyrrku6kI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the Honeymoon Have to End? By Sandi Greene: One night during our engagement, my fiancé… https://t.co/psDoezkCik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our latest articles on love, relationships and romance: https://t.co/ZWDJk6NY4f https://t.co/diA283aIgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected #Divorce: Why Some People Abandon Their #Marriage By Chidi Akunna: It had been a… https://t.co/9ezCmksYPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected Divorce: Why Some People Abandon Their Marriage By Chidi Akunna

It had been a long week for Fred and... https://t.co/ZXsjOn6ZsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected Divorce: Why Some People Abandon Their Marriage By Chidi Akunna: It had been a… https://t.co/3XG0VQRqEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/wIEkQ7qwcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode

"True intimacy requires active presence" ~Victor Akunna https://t.co/XjkCjcXg1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode

"True intimacy requires active presence" ~Victor Akunna https://t.co/0Y07ZqC9GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is like a living organism, it must be nurtured daily to blossom." Victor Akunna https://t.co/Cvsm5nghrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Pornography Impacts Marriage By Greg Smalley: “So, what secret did you share?” I’m… https://t.co/hHBWoDTeR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Pornography Impacts Marriage By Greg Smalley: “So, what secret did you share?” I’m… https://t.co/QS974u3865]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimacyCode

"There is no intimacy without constant forgiveness" ~Victor Akunna https://t.co/mGqLNbTMuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Top Tips for Planning Your Wedding by Hitched: Planning Your Dress: Don’t Start in… https://t.co/q6rYJYhs1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Top Tips for Planning Your Wedding by Hitched: Planning Your Dress: Don’t Start in… https://t.co/2Qrb85ZuKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Romance Story – By Lanre and Olusola Ogundare: FFA: Please introduce yourselves. My… https://t.co/bl1sqARxVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #Romance Story – By Lanre and Olusola Ogundare: FFA: Please introduce yourselves. My… https://t.co/4rNuiqLJ0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @modupelanre: Strong drink = Hangover
Holy Spirit = Makeover

And be not drunk with wine, wherein is excess; but be filled with the Spir…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Thesowerschoice: @FamilyAffairs05 just gave the vote of thanks...on Entrepreneurs Connect. I'm Taofik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/d4clv3Yble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication and Friendship – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: One of the things we have observed in… https://t.co/QigBJKQYND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication and #Friendship – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: One of the things we have observed… https://t.co/un7RGCgJyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the things we have observed in marriage is that it matters who you spend time with. Couples often learn... https://t.co/MWbOqgp6MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. ...because we may keep projecting our pain in every relationship.#PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. Until we deal with past hurt, we cannot experience true intimacy in our relationships. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. They say, "hurting people hurt others", make up your mind to be a source of pleasure, not pain. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. Then come up with a plan to help others in a similar situation. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. Acknowledge that and appreciate God for the experience. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20. For example, making you more sensitive to people's pain and more determined to be successful. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Run your mind through the experience &amp; try to see the positive side,how it made U a better person. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @arihilam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. It is hard to pray for someone and hold resentment against him/her at the same time. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @arihilam @excelength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. Pray for the individual that hurt you. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @excelength  @ChrisInspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. Ask God to help you, if you are finding it difficult. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15.To deal with past hurt,acknowledge that U are hurt. Nothing is as bad as covering a wound, it only gets worse. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. When past hurts are not dealt with, there would be a reoccurring pattern of pain in our relationships. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13.This is why it is important for your spouse to be able to express him/herself at any point,without feeling odd. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. If you are not happy about something your spouse has done, express how you feel. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11b. It also prevents you from accessing depths in your union. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11.It could make U build a wall in your heart that would prevent you from being truly vulnerable to your spouse. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. Holding on to past hurt can deprive you of the chance of getting the best from your relationship. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9b. ...snapping at your spouse over what you think he/she is saying, which may not be. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. You may find yourself reacting unnecessarily due to past hurt;... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. This is why past hurts need to be addressed, else they will present themselves in 'explosive' ways. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7b. ...you'd be fencing out good people that can bring good opportunities and the most rewarding experiences. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. You'd end up feeling more hurt because in a bid to protect yourself from being hurt,... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6b. ...there are relationships that this cannot be applicable to. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. Initially, I built a wall. That seemed to work with some people, but... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. I have had to learn different ways of managing them. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. The same can be said of my most painful experiences. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Personally speaking, some of my best experiences so far have come from interacting with people. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. If you interact with people daily, there is bound to be a clash of values, unmet expectations, rejection,... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Very few people can say they have not experienced hurt at different times in the past. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @homebuildersng: Is love enough?  #marriage #staymarried @Grace_Festus @theiaministries @olawunmiesan @FamilyAffairs05 https://t.co/eQxY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aushamaki: Do you text or glance at your screen while driving? Let this be an eye opener. I hope we all make a conscious effort to be m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NikeAdeyemi: This #weekend, spend some quality time with your spouse. Talk, laugh, plan, #pray &amp; cultivate deeper #intimacy. #qualityti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and #control – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: We have been on a series on sustaining healthy… https://t.co/6qQZaTtjZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and control – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: We have been on a series on sustaining healthy… https://t.co/oy0ra7e7Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 37. Marriage is beautiful, do not let a limiting mindset steal a wonderful experience from you. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 36. If you are married, are the mindsets you have about marriage serving you? #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 35. If you are yet to be married, do you think your mindset about marriage will serve you in marriage? #mindsets #iConnec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 34b. ...from those who have the kind of result you desire. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 34. If they are not serving you, make effort to adopt a positive mindset and ideas... #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 33b. ...you can consider what you believe about it by reviewing your mindset and guiding principles. #mindsets #iConnectH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 33. If there is an aspect of your marriage you are yet to get results in, e.g. your finances, ...  #mindsets #iConnectHea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 29. Of what use is your money if it cannot be used for the interest of the family? #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 28. A spouse may decide to 'gather' and not disclose, even when there is a need to be sorted in the family. #mindsets #iC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 27. However, the challenge with this advice is that it encourages selfishness. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26b. ...it is likely that his/her spending habit may lead the family into debt or affect their creditworthiness. #mindset…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26. One of such is if one of the spouses is extravagant and ... #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 24. The last mindset I will consider is "be 'sharp' with your money". #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 22b. ...you may need to cultivate friendship with your husband. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 22.If you find the company of your friends to be interesting and that of your husband to be boring, ... #mindsets #iConne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20. Now that you are married, the right order of things is that your spouse comes before your friends. #mindsets #iConnec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17b. ...but the men should deal with their wives with affection. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17. This is not to in any way empower women inordinately, women ought to respect their husbands,... #mindsets #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16. A woman ought not to feel oppressed in her marital home;... #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 15. The command is for men to love their wives, not to suppress them. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14. This sounds like asking a man to get ready to be tough and exert force where necessary. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. Another mindset is "you have to assert your authority as a man as quickly as possible". #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 11. Rather than buy into such mindset, it is important to query it and expect to have a better experience. #mindsets #iCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10b. ...because of this mindset, you'd hear, "I knew it, Aunty said it,..." #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10. Sadly, if after two weeks, there is a disagreement that should be talked over,... #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9b. ...putting in no effort towards the success of the marriage. #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9. Some people sell this mindset to young people and unfortunately, they settle for this,... #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8. One of them is that "honeymoon stage will last only two weeks". #mindsets #iConnectHearts]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>