<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/3W11XxI6Qj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/lCEoH3WIQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/yc3jmVYveM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/cZ8QJRtLes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/iUzxBMfHJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/bsgPl28b7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/P6ELOMcNaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/qvhXVZv0Sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/XE0aLEkUhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/biap3DVft3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/m3Gi8oMLrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/RGrhZfRPmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/AaDpytXJzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spencer Davis Group  http://t.co/JEcB2UXPLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/X7I1mzmuqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/5vdaYbaTO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/CfdH88XBbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/DVhfFvs3p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/1eJmAcn3jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/AhnkV0H5In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/ug7fdqGGyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/eSmWpnYjQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/s2UrGBKcoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/ViORJr72Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/MOPXneVyPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/7bg5GprEEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/TaJhZLgFje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/83dXWjkgSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/YSVuIz751r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/0S1bCHpvJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/f35m12896A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/2JRgsA4cd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/w8Wf95iirZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/k8COT2RuZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/ZyFAPPH6Sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/se3Qeo7Eo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/5Nq5ZGOlJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/K6WrjQkOcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/YvLghCk3lQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/KulzAKbWpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/ICcyoNcj9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/5chYqL78p6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/6wRJGnhLZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/TrLEdbnhlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/CYTu88OEmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/x2kynn9GaW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>