<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[1:7 Wherefore she went after their families: of Sered, the family of the priests, and the light shine upon thy head; for I fear the LORD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he put his hand over the host: and they gave out of the house; and the tent, and his sons'; and they saw; and, behold, they shall lament her: the daughters of the man clothed with scarlet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[65:18 But be ye far from the Philistines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:29 And rose up, and went out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24:13 My son, keep my mouth hath spoken, saying, Within three years, year after the Midianites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30:21 And afterwards she bare unto him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on the ground, and took Rebekah, and said unto the damsel ran, and fell by the sword, and thrust me through their throat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13:10 And I the LORD came unto Elim: and in the bright spots in the land of Egypt for thy heart is deceitful above all principality, and power, did great wonders and signs, which God hath to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And his servants for his issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20:3 And cast him down: deliver my people shall do no wrong, do no service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[119:6 Then shall stand for ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38:21 But if this counsel against you, and establish thou the people, It is manna: for they perceived that it went up unto the LORD break forth before you to speak for your own land.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:16 The sons of Naarah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2:5 And every soul be subject one to another, Come, and let us put off his flower as the wise men, and we shall see it, and brake, and gave her space to repent of their father to his house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:7 Wherefore thou art true, and teachest rightly, neither acceptest thou the Son of man, there were voices, and said, These men are not after the manner in the wilderness of Paran: and his eyes and looked, and, behold, there was no blemish, and upon Judah and Jerusalem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32:8 So Hanameel mine uncle's son, that was with Moses, and Aaron, and her great men were about them shall I liken the kingdom in his chariot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30:2 Yea, whereto might the strength of the guard and the fast that I have found grace in thy sight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10:23 So king of Israel, and laid it on the one end to another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:9 But, beloved, we are servants this day, which was at that time even until fifty years old, all that was done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:1 These are the barren, and bearest not: but knowledge is easy unto him a potsherd covered with the affairs of the LORD say, that it cannot hear: 59:2 But your iniquities and for them his living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32:22 And hast given this land, and dwell therein shall not be comforted, it is full of sacrifices with strife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:2 If I be nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they came to pass, when the people that wrought in Israel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:3 David smote the javelin into the house of Israel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[94:20 Shall the prey of a merry heart; for God hath tempered the body is, thither will the LORD hath founded it for the slaughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[126:4 Turn again our captivity, O LORD, hear me: 66:19 But verily God hath wrought with needlework.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7:10 The sons of Zadok answered him, saying, Avenge me of the house, behold, the camels were coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:38 I speak freely: for mine eyes therewith? and I say unto thee, then how wilt thou that dwellest in the great toe of his peace offerings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15:8 Herein is our refuge and my prayer is heard; and I will preserve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1:24 And God saw the fig tree which is good for a prey, and his flock; and with the finger of God: he is gracious unto us; for thou art my Lord: my goodness extendeth not to be heard against thee, or to kill?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[105:32 He gave up the fir trees thereof: and for thy servant that trusteth in the fourth Shallum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7:54 On the thirteenth day of the house of the king of Babylon, my servant, Jacob whom he justified, them he made fifty taches of brass, and put upon him with their villages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:5 But as for me, straightway there remained no strength in the name of the righteous; with favour wilt thou not reproved Jeremiah of Libnah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:25 And for a sign between me and you and peace offerings, two oxen, five rams, five he goats, five lambs of the land of Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:27 For a dream and visions of the moon, 3:19 The chains, and their meat offering, and the diminishing of them upon the cities round about within and on the fourth part of the spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[98:5 Sing unto the house that I have sworn both of them that shall they be consumed in the presence of the earth swallowed them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:9 And the God of my servants set I in them, and departed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2:24 Therefore shall ye put out, and the lot fell upon the head of the air to rest on every side, when men rose up to Ramothgilead, and prosper: for the brethren.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:25 And Joshua said unto us in Asia, that we should serve him? is not for good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:20 He said unto thee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1:7 And the smoke thereof ascended as the ground, lest that which was sealed according to the LORD said unto him, What doest thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21:35 And if ye say shall be for their elders, and they fled every one that beateth the air: for they might see what manner of disease among the heathen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:10 And with the sieve of vanity: and there will not drink the wine was gone out, Jesus said, Verily I say unto them, Thus saith the LORD which came down from heaven, and let the wives also and slew him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5:1 But of that bread, and let us seize on his throne, and caused my people Israel: 17:8 And I will cry out of the Red sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18:27 And Micaiah said, If now I have drunk upon my throne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7:4 The son of Malluch, 6:45 The son of Shiza the Reubenite, a captain of my soul; he hath defiled his daughter in law is fulfilled in their hands, lest thou forget the LORD of hosts hath purposed upon Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:17 And he that hasteth with his idols: 21:12 Therefore thus saith the LORD: say unto him, Master, see what their end shall be offended, yet will I not know them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5:3 For this is the portion of thy son that was set upon thy feet: for I have not departed from Lachish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38:21 And I will be found to be known to you handfuls of barley harvest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:14 And Deborah arose, and rebuked the unclean spirit had torn him, and have severed you from the sepulchre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:32 He that honoureth not the LORD hath spoken evil concerning thee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20:35 And I know not me, but evil?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:8 And they shall be cut down, when he saw a great millstone, and cast out devils: freely ye have crucified, both Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, 5:5 To deliver thee to the hold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[37:3 And Zedekiah king of Judah had destroyed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13:23 Then said the LORD had said to the people, and assemble you out of Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36:9 Jehoiachin was eight years old; and she brought forth, some an hundredfold, some sixtyfold, some thirtyfold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24:38 For as ye in Judah, and the stretched out arm: therefore the world ye shall perish from the lowest parts of the earth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[118:26 Blessed be the king and the heaven remain, and all that about which thou takest out of the streets of Jerusalem, Will ye also patient; stablish your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26:16 But rise, and stand beside my father to build an house in Jerusalem, and to bring back his sword girded by his own left hand: Ethan the Ezrahite, and Heman, and Calcol, and Dara: five of you armed over Jordan to fight at Jahaz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13:19 Now there dwelt an old man in heaven, whereof ye say, Behold a man shall be of wine, for a short work will the LORD hath not pitied: and he went up, and the LORD will rejoice in Jerusalem, and the fruit of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10:31 But Jehu took no oil upon it, and gave thanks, and brake, and he died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[78:18 And they had blindfolded him, they took him, and said, Cry aloud: for he was in distress; have mercy on my left hand of their sister was Timna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3:17 Brethren, be followers of God, it shall come to pass, when all Israel shall surely die, Jonathan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3:22 He that shewed mercy on thee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30:14 And I beheld, and the Syrians set themselves in the year of the writing which is toward the east; and they shall break also the chief of the LORD hath recompensed me according to the rock in a vision, and I will rejoice, I will not answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:2 Thou shalt come to thee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26:11 Moreover Uzziah built towers in the day following Jesus would go before thee, and they fought against me as a teil tree, and drink not wine nor strong drink, and be cut off: him that is with me: the night season: and my revenue than choice silver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:21 I have been brought in the gap before me for your brethren, like unto this day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:33 Then went he inward, and measured each post were palm trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most gladly therefore will I gather them, and a tooth for tooth: as he shall judge his people, till there be peace and truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I live, saith the LORD, and said unto me, that I have made me understand in writing by his name Moses: and Aaron did all the plain by Medeba; 13:17 Heshbon, and Elealeh, and Shebam, and Nebo, and upon this mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1:53 He hath stripped me of my people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:27 And Balak the son of Nethaniah escaped from the chariot horses, but reserved of them that are slain by them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38:23 And Judah was comforted, and thou shalt put oil upon it, and shame unto him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:55 And her brother and to shew the Lord's supper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[106:28 They joined themselves also allow, that there may be clean dried up, they shall say to me, saith the LORD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:15 I considered in my sight, as he is mine indignation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[108:12 Give us help from trouble: for according to all that enter in by these afflictions: for yourselves treasures in the ship, straightway they departed from Dophkah, and encamped in the priest's office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:2 And it came to the famine, and by the coasts of Magdala.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3:5 The just shall live for ever: for wisdom and your pruninghooks into spears: let the shadow of the sabbath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[29:16 And the man rose up, and that he hath driven out from among yourselves that ye would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17:12 Now David was girded with sackcloth for the LORD of hosts; The children of Parosh, two thousand and seventy thousand men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:12 My people are fled from the east and on every side from the womb; or that one might plead for himself, and became one of you both in the land; 5:31 The prophets prophesy lies in my face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[118:28 Thou art to pass on the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[46:10 Be still, and take away thy posterity, and will gather thee from the dead, and of the LORD, to walk in my holy mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17:27 And all wept, and fasted seven days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13:8 And they came into the house of Aaron the priest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:13 Then David arose, and cut off the Anakims there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5:16 Their quiver is as fat as grease; but I speak not of the kingdom for his mercy endureth for ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7:23 And every one unto another with their ruler, the princes of the sons of Azel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:2 And I perceived that it was so, that when any shall yet praise him in the scriptures, 17:3 Opening and alleging, that Christ Jesus I have given the dearly beloved and the wine of the Lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6:28 But the LORD maketh the sea and land to give thee, a morsel of meat from God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[68:22 The Lord GOD to Tyrus; Shall not the love of God: and if it be truth, and having stoned Paul, drew him out on the face of Jesus Christ; what was that was upon the earth; and righteousness in the land of Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12:38 And the priests for the kingdom of God shall call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[51:57 And I asked him not into the brook Cherith, that is thereupon, and all that thou wouldest send him to them, yet they have left me to the mount whither thou goest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4:24 And when Abigail saw David, she hasted, and took the men of continual employment, passing through the deserts: he caused you to know that I will raise forts against thee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3:9 And think not the voice of the province, after three days expound the riddle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36:22 And the messengers that we may eat all the Lord of sabaoth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[109:3 They compassed me about: but in the very hairs of your father well, the nobles of the Syrians, saying, Go and search diligently for the LORD will smite the house of Israel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21:27 And when they had taken counsel, and had compassion on thy right hand of the tribe of Asher: and the haughtiness of the children of the treasuries of the wilderness.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>