<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10371 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Hi, Please find the below job description and if you are interested kindly share me you updated resume along with good time to connect Role: Scrum Master Location: Atlanta GA… https://t.co/wXAD9uHvNj https://t.co/BUXFn5w1Rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR775) Job: Date: Mar 15, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR775) (Job Number:434149) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/ZU9b5SZzn0 https://t.co/fE5dttyALB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media Group Search… https://t.co/OCLNta1KRQ https://t.co/WqrnnsD7UU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master / Website Development Project Manager: Other agencies may call this job Project Manager or Account Manager, but we don’t like using the M-word. Rather, we do our web design and software development work in 5-person teams, with each member of… https://t.co/9n9egB0Byi https://t.co/4OPgBpAKVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-00576 Location: Boston, Massachusetts Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/27/2018 Qualifications: Candidates should have 5+ year’s experience as a Scrum Master in a large scale professional environment supporting… https://t.co/wDe45Vit7K https://t.co/InNE01paFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency traders use old gold in drive to draw Islamic investors: DUBAI/SYDNEY (Reuters) - In Dubai's decades-old Gold Souk, customers from around the world haggle over bangles and necklaces. Elsewhere in the emirate, the region's top center for… https://t.co/9JprDxb1fp https://t.co/9bu65SaFOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst/Developer: Available Jobs | JANUS Research Group – About – Overview – Vision, Mission, Values – Leadership – John Dewey – J. Scott Martin – David Sales – James Griffith – Rob Elich – Jeremy Wagoner – Shawn Rodier – Joseph Bailey –… https://t.co/qAPrOQQCAr https://t.co/B1QHhJNJqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/EQdvJgalVK https://t.co/ujBRQGRO0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MOBILE SCRUM MASTER: MOBILE SCRUM MASTER ADDISON, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/20/18, Posted Date – 03/20/18 Primary SkillsScrum masterTax TermsC2COverview Phone – Skype Visa – H1 [Preferred] Only from Trusted Source, EAD is Fine. 5 Year… https://t.co/gURR1PKkCY https://t.co/MouXKcwCUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fullscreen – Senior Ruby Engineer: The Senior Ruby on Rails Software Developer within Fullscreen Engineering team supports the architecture, design, development, and deployment of applications, API services, and client integrations for Fullscreens Brands… https://t.co/40Lm4L637e https://t.co/bgF8xtrUpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer/Cloud Engineer: 7+ years engineering experience with Agile/Scrum methodologies. Solid understanding of algorithm complexity, parallel/distributed systems, advanced data structures, computer networking, operating systems and cloud… https://t.co/Q2oGG3Ntd7 https://t.co/G7FjIz99rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst – Multiple Locations: We seek for a Business System Analyst with Agile testing and automation background to join our organization.   This is a rewarding opportunity for the right candidate to make good use of his/her analysis,… https://t.co/QkQJEenMcz https://t.co/rnfQnt51Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai cryptocurrency firm denies Alibaba trademark infringement: DUBAI (Reuters) - A Dubai-based cryptocurrency company called Alibabacoin Foundation has rebuffed allegations of trademark infringement brought against it by the giant Chinese online… https://t.co/kpe3Ok8tAh https://t.co/kcB0eac0YQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing development of the team within… https://t.co/0l9h2WjTVc https://t.co/WRZ3i8kK4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/KwwCDmPCej https://t.co/gwG7dLmnsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test I: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/keAPsjjQQF https://t.co/aKyS2szQme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst: FULL-TIME DIRECT HIRE ROLE (MUST BE US CITIZEN OR GC HOLDER) EXCELLENT SALARY, BENEFITS AND RELOCATION PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES Analyze requirements and transform them into manual and automated test scripts. Create and maintain… https://t.co/diyWCpSeTS https://t.co/LpRmsZAE1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Developer: Overview Software Developer IV (SDIV) will be part of a team of some of the best and brightest in the industry who are focused on developing scalable web and responsive applications that touch our growing customer base every… https://t.co/PNoviAPR3X https://t.co/UwFabHUwxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican senator says Facebook scandals may be 'too big' for company to fix alone: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A Republican U.S. senator warned on Sunday that Facebook Inc may need to be regulated to address concerns about the company's privacy and foreign… https://t.co/fxrn93KtpZ https://t.co/UpKbrIKBRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – Exton, PA: Do you enjoy working with highly-skilled, self-motivated colleagues? Do you also have a passion for helping customers be successful? Are you passionate about Lean and Agile practices? If so, Guidewire has an opportunity for you.… https://t.co/96w2gy6zYW https://t.co/FIvq4y2Fz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Product Manager – Eden Prairie, MN: Optum is the industry leader delivering health services dedicated to one goal: making the health system work better for everyone. For those who need care, provide care and pay for care, we deliver integrated,… https://t.co/R1x2fhucaS https://t.co/ONPM3VZJbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA Engineer: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to make that a… https://t.co/nUelSJCnRq https://t.co/AaBxeDcP5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DCGS-SOF Project Manager – 15507: DCGS-SOF Project Manager Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company) Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants for… https://t.co/Zj806gZSNh https://t.co/gQD4uyuNyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer (JavaScript / Angular / React / Node): _Logikos was built on the idea that a software company that focuses on excellent engineers working in collaboration will produce better software for its clients. _ We are looking for a… https://t.co/YjNryaY0cM https://t.co/ZKLO0YY6DY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IS Senior Project Manager/Business Analyst: Why Join Altec? If you’re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there’s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the customer first, and view people as our… https://t.co/t6y6UXM2MV https://t.co/KUTyOgO6xJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California proposes new rules for self-driving cars to pick up passengers: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - California's public utility regulator on Friday signaled it would allow self-driving car companies to transport passengers without a backup driver in the… https://t.co/mylefLlRQu https://t.co/mXjPsdr8J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer (2018): RSDCGroup, LLC (RSDC) is a Veteran Owned Small Business (VOSB) with a presence in the Washington, DC Metropolitan area headquartered in Arlington, Virginia with offices nationwide. We deliver results for our customers through… https://t.co/ah5ZCEEtro https://t.co/cTulcQis77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/PM: IT Careers – About Us – Our Culture – In the Community – Leadership – Our Services – Enterprise Strategies – IT Planning – Enterprise Portfolio Management – Process Quality Assessment – Managed Solutions – Project Based Services –… https://t.co/fTI3bmof3z https://t.co/M5A2z82nVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Scrum Master, App Dev: Client Reference Code: 216153JOB SUMMARYThis role is process management focused, working with the Charter XG (Experience Group)’s web and mobile applications development teams, development architect, development testers,… https://t.co/LN4JO4aP4n https://t.co/qsjhK7FQQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: * Hands-on design and development of highly concurrent, scalable, distributed transactional systems using TDD (Test driven development) and (DDD) Domain driven design models. * Accountable for Unit, Automation tests,… https://t.co/e07i9ksIu1 https://t.co/U6ex9H1Zp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Information Systems Security Officer :18-00501 Ref No.: 18-00501 Location: Melbourne, Florida Primary Skills: ISSO, JSIG, NISPOM Ch8, ICD 503, and/or NIST 800-53, Linux, UNIX, Solaris and Windows, RMF, Must have a Top Secret… https://t.co/9jIQF75S0W https://t.co/dn6TA0WPJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager (Scrum Master): Project manager (Scrum Master) Ref No.: 18-00610 Location: Mount laurel, New Jersey Start Date / End Date: 04/01/2018 to 04/01/2019 Technical/Functional Skills – Knowledge of agile methodology and frameworks like Scrum,… https://t.co/IJVww91GSD https://t.co/5n8SJhYJrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook suspends Canadian firm AggregateIQ over data scandal: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Friday that it had suspended Canadian political consultancy AggregateIQ from its platform after reports that the data firm may have improperly had access to… https://t.co/BiFbH2Jx2v https://t.co/0Y1MjEeFV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/tYR6myPIQI https://t.co/KLnCQUN9fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Application Developer: * Design, Develop, and Test Software applications built with *******, C#, MS SQL SERVER and front end frameworks such as Knockout JS or Angular JS. * Production Support for Software applications built with *******, C#,… https://t.co/Tx2tIZtgji https://t.co/xadLewulqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst(Scrum): Business Analyst Alpharetta, GA Full Time Position Job Description: Strong experience in working as a product owner and senior business analyst. Prior Experience in working on projects using Scrum and SAfe framework is a… https://t.co/F0qcjL6F1u https://t.co/ecsPD1jKxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/bv0fmPKI1w https://t.co/bYh1zI56Gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR800) Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR800) (Job Number:435230) Description: Job Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/VS9qW0ppG8 https://t.co/bPX5gtKmvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines regulator orders pushback in Uber's shutdown amid ongoing review: MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippines' anti-trust agency said on Saturday it has ordered Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] to continue domestic operations as it reviews the ride… https://t.co/MY3OvPtjgy https://t.co/k2HLX0yYIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Release Train Engineer: Description:Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIns 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   We are seeking a talented… https://t.co/m04Q2kWgW7 https://t.co/5MBS6A0V37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DCGS-SOF Project Manager – 15507: DCGS-SOF Project Manager Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company) Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants for… https://t.co/xJrgJgIz5e https://t.co/I6KtTP4SSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/y9OFl9eW6p https://t.co/m3TYIcvo5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master role in Murrysville, PA: SCRUM MASTER ROLE LOCATION: MURRYSVILLE, PA 15668 OVERVIEW: * Serve the role of Scrum Master as defined in the Scrum Guide * Guide the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values * Assess the… https://t.co/w3lHh6EnJ8 https://t.co/1fxFGh4d1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/LACu0HqbKu https://t.co/D8GuhLjXJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/671MknduR0 https://t.co/YD8LwKmOQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activist fund says Toshiba chip unit worth as much as $40 billion: TOKYO (Reuters) - A Hong Kong-based activist investment fund said Toshiba Corp's chip unit was worth as much as $40 billion, double the sale price agreed with a Bain-led consortium, as it… https://t.co/qSObyLCNqS https://t.co/wP7sWXfYXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/PM: IT Careers – About Us – Our Culture – In the Community – Leadership – Our Services – Enterprise Strategies – IT Planning – Enterprise Portfolio Management – Process Quality Assessment – Managed Solutions – Project Based Services –… https://t.co/vSPYVZEdL2 https://t.co/Juio994INA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test Specialist: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/pGM91G5lAH https://t.co/aldMyQA3lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX/UI Designer: As one of the nations leading pediatric health care systems, Nemours is committed to providing all children with their best chance to grow up healthy. We offer integrated, family-centered care to more than 300,000 children each… https://t.co/HIDRa5850V https://t.co/hmepZWtnXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Acquisitions Team: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/KY7UcCyw8e https://t.co/EzOekGlb6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director – IT Project Management: DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT FULL TIME PERMANENT POSITION – No H1B LOCATION: ATLANTA, GA SALARY: up to $110k/yr DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT SUMMARY This position is responsible for leading cross functional teams… https://t.co/9t0N8zU08B https://t.co/ce1B3S3ksH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/qdwVMxOFNV https://t.co/fl2TinIHjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics tips record first quarter profit as chip boom winds down: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics Co Ltd tipped a surprise record first-quarter profit on Friday but market reaction was muted due to growing concerns that the… https://t.co/39knAswlfm https://t.co/2AgWspe0Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect (Java): Technical Architect (Java) – Vacancies – Values – A Xebian – Culture – Contact – Vacancies – Our Values – People First – Quality without Comprise – Sharing Knowledge – Customer Intimacy – A Xebian – Culture – Innovation Day –… https://t.co/n8nN1FSTkH https://t.co/UfSA15zYmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Are you: * Are you interested in working in an exciting fast pace Internet of Things company? * Do you enjoy learning and growing within an innovative company? * Do you like working in an environment that encourages collaboration and… https://t.co/lbRw86YuoH https://t.co/PgEQ7uVv53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US IT Scrum Master: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/LPsUSsKseA https://t.co/Om5xyzF2IR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Interface Designer (EFT Analytics): Learn more by visiting our website here! EFT Analytics, ****** looking for anUser Interface Designer to join our team in New York City! TheUser Interface Designer would be part of a fast-growing technology… https://t.co/wATsoaeeGn https://t.co/2buIaxuyq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – System Analysis and Program – III: Ericsson Order Care (Aka ConceptWave) Order Management and Catalog experience * Experience in modules such as Order Care, code tables, APIs, Taxing Model, Versioning, Buy-Flow, Order negotiation,… https://t.co/khecjoN8Gn https://t.co/ioYCBCHhdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple says repeal of EPA carbon plan would threaten investments: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Apple Inc said on Friday it opposes any repeal by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency of the Clean Power Plan, which is a priority of the agency's Administrator… https://t.co/A4htjWVz58 https://t.co/W05fGSvRYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xamarin Developer: Xamarin Developer The Xamarin Developer will develop, build, and support system enhancements and applications using multiple technologies. The successful candidate will have both technical depth and breadth and will have experience… https://t.co/jf933088CX https://t.co/FvQGoRhp9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer, Marketing Technology: Job Posting Title: Sr. Software Engineer, Marketing Technology Job Description: Ever wonder what happens to the data collected on you that serves up sometimes relevant ads as you browse the web? Ever felt… https://t.co/Pp9RDSv3DZ https://t.co/yJ5PujwbWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Developer: Overview Software Developer IV (SDIV) will be part of a team of some of the best and brightest in the industry who are focused on developing scalable web and responsive applications that touch our growing customer base every… https://t.co/HFLU7ZrYjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1804 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position Description:… https://t.co/uil7WlUOUU https://t.co/0r1yWBjMPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level – Scientific Computing Software Developer: Description: Leidos is seeking Scientific Computing Software Developers to support a variety of sophisticated acoustic training and simulation systems. Position provides opportunity to travel to… https://t.co/AVnogYsCgy https://t.co/bRkMVhBsJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Engineer III: Client Reference Code: 216084 Job Scope: We’re looking for a highly motivated individual to join the Video Operations Automation and Tools team. The successful candidate will be part of a group responsible for engineering… https://t.co/PW0eyiSn8j https://t.co/OJyEuKmCOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook backs political ad bill, sets limits on 'issue ads': SAN FRANCISCO/WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Facebook Inc backed for the first time on Friday proposed legislation requiring social media sites to disclose the identities of buyers of online political… https://t.co/nxkoQMSKQZ https://t.co/uNG4GFaEft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10518 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Pittsburg, PA //… https://t.co/4TItN5M8Mt https://t.co/7rb8UFbqWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer Job Location Cambridge, MA Req Number 2018-0140 Department Business Systems Apply Now Overview: Foundation Medicine is a molecular information company focused on fundamentally changing the way in which… https://t.co/uwmUZMfsgb https://t.co/ulO3lje1k6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software-Systems Solution Architect: Description: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Leidos currently has an opening for a Software/Systems Solutions Architect to work in Dayton, OH. Interested in being a leader that is responsible for driving the… https://t.co/Z8B8beVkgX https://t.co/M8dBIAx7xS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Team Lead: DevOps Team Lead Responsibilities: Develop, Implement, maintain, and improve Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery/Deployment environments Provide technical leadership, guidance and technical team management Participate in… https://t.co/S1trGXJJgE https://t.co/suvGKxVaj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Position Overview: The Sr Project Manager is responsible for managing key projects as it relates to Operations, Vendor Implementations, New Product Development and major software enhancements. Additionally, the Sr. Project Manager… https://t.co/2vrZSGmy9G https://t.co/DTVp06aw0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer groups to approach FTC over Facebook's facial recognition: (Reuters) - A civil rights group and some consumer groups said on Friday they would file a complaint with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) alleging that Facebook Inc's use of… https://t.co/rIQMc8Hkoi https://t.co/aTi69JzXJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer, Web Service API: Experian is the leading global information services company, providing data and analytical tools to clients in more than 65 countries around the world. The company helps organizations to manage credit risk, prevent fraud,… https://t.co/CwDIA0GjDJ https://t.co/E1xMQpOuRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Shutterfly’s Lab Engineering team is seeking to add a key contributor who would be instrumental in the design and development of order fulfillment software, APIs, and features. This role will require a strong technical… https://t.co/CEUMdZbs42 https://t.co/QbQOwnA8Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US IT .Net Developer: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/0LVkSf3g3G https://t.co/Fq8qH0ldAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Corporate – St. Louis, MO: Role Overview: We are seeking an Angular developer with a C# .NET background to join our team in St. Louis, MO. You will have the opportunity to utilize a wide range of new development technologies while… https://t.co/GIAPGH0Poc https://t.co/p046xxoaPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Data Analyst: Permanent position open in the Rockville area for Health Data Analyst. Primary Responsibilities: * Converting business requirements into technical specification for data integration and reports * Configuring the front-end and… https://t.co/K61Y0gYLlz https://t.co/wzpKUfut4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer – Node.js – REMOTE: SemanticBits is seeking a Backend Software Engineer to implement a wide range of REST services in Node.js and databases. You will work in a closely knit Scrum team to solve complex backend problems, such as… https://t.co/YuC3xN4Qcn https://t.co/4Sv0yv5uix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab's Uber deal still has some obstacles to navigate: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Regulatory scrutiny could complicate ride-hailing company Grab's takeover of Uber Technologies' Southeast Asian business, but there is little the authorities can do to stop Uber… https://t.co/pEwYbYXnQU https://t.co/Sr03uI2y1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst(Scrum): Business Analyst Alpharetta, GA Full Time Position Job Description: Strong experience in working as a product owner and senior business analyst. Prior Experience in working on projects using Scrum and SAfe framework is a… https://t.co/6nqp0qKGoX https://t.co/yCh97fnb9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER: Job TitleFULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER – ID:30696 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER LocationNew Jersey, NJ Date Posted01/04/2018 FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER Location: New Jersey, NJ 07059 Duration:… https://t.co/5bzuAP2lda https://t.co/qDtzcyS4s9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI LEAD: UI LEAD Ref No.: 18-10468 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Hello My name is Akshay and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc.I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available for a project. This role… https://t.co/MiA6e2jT2R https://t.co/K2qgphfMoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPE Cloud Volumes Software Engineer (QA): HPE Cloud Volumes Software Engineer (QA) at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program – Students &amp;… https://t.co/prquHsxHVp https://t.co/P1xB00GDrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Job Title: Senior Scrum Master Location: Chicago, IL Duration- 6 Months Roles &amp; Responsibility Guiding the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values to delight customers – Guiding the team on how to get the… https://t.co/RKwZeJF1Xq https://t.co/73ZK6xlOEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump taking 'serious look' at policy options on Amazon: Aboard Air Force One (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he would take a serious look at policies to address what he says are the unfair business advantages of online retailer… https://t.co/rkSghHRXG9 https://t.co/KK6fnmIL8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: LOCATION: PITTSBURGH, PA/MURRYSVILLE, PA REQUIRED SKILLS: * Scrum Master in Agile * Ability to coach and influence Agile concepts to people that are new to the Agile Methodology. * Scrum Master Certification required * Version 1 or JIRA is… https://t.co/e813AT2W5n https://t.co/LXoHoS1joP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Position Overview: The Sr Project Manager is responsible for managing key projects as it relates to Operations, Vendor Implementations, New Product Development and major software enhancements. Additionally, the Sr. Project Manager… https://t.co/3jUIsTwdQF https://t.co/7st172A2TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer: Description:Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   We are seeking a talented Java… https://t.co/wAS6zX0uDD https://t.co/LkmXrr5GFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey applications and custom… https://t.co/R18JAJLaaq https://t.co/5kagDhVXL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/LemD3zhSti https://t.co/8iqJwL36vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineering: Description: Job Description This position is a Systems Engineer on the Exploitation Services (program), working hand-in-hand with the ACE, Chief Architect (CA), Chief Engineer (CE) and the Program Management Leadership team… https://t.co/gHabYItrdE https://t.co/VEUwJ7oAmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta takes down water department website two weeks after cyber attack: (Reuters) - Atlanta took down its water department website indefinitely on Thursday, two weeks after a ransomware cyber attack tore through the city's computer systems in one of… https://t.co/gPPW0Mnqmh https://t.co/k95EiQCCWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/REFRU6mYS1 https://t.co/JtvHKgyYW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer, Principal: Req ID 91987BR Business Title CNO Developer, Principal Group MCIS Location USA COLORADO Aurora Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is looking for a Principal CNO Developer to join… https://t.co/HqQBleHqs9 https://t.co/ZyX3Ce6sjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Intralot Inc: INTRALOT is engaged in the supply of integrated gaming and transaction processing systems, innovative game content and value added services to state licensed gaming organizations. Based on its extensive know how, advanced… https://t.co/tg2kHlDexo https://t.co/pnlcK79r5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: About the role Our business is undergoing an explosive transformation: positioning our product as an industry leader in a powerful, new emerging market: the Digital Experience Platform arena, for this reason we are looking for… https://t.co/i6dpkmKWdE https://t.co/GpNQ7Zkohd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Ruby on Rails Developer: THE OPPORTUNITY KleerMail is looking for a experienced and talented Full-Stack Ruby on Rails developer to contribute to the implementation of our Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) product offerings. Your primary focus will… https://t.co/hTP37OBQix https://t.co/8laIHcYUmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify shares attract all ages, not just Millennials: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The buzzy debut of Spotify Technology SA on the New York Stock Exchange on Tuesday drew retail investors across generations, not just the Millennials who make up the largest… https://t.co/Wt60WjaDcj https://t.co/iONKQMHKGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner: Description: The Leidos Health Products &amp; Service Group has an opening for an Agile Product Owner with experience in the commercial healthcare or related industry to support the design, integration, testing and delivery of the Leidos… https://t.co/R2P0U8GJ8F https://t.co/SijstbUPyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Security Engineer: At Northwestern Mutual, we believe relationships are built on trust. That our lives and our work matter. These beliefs launched our company nearly 160 years ago. Today, they’re just a few of the reasons why people choose to… https://t.co/Dv9AvkAhtO https://t.co/D1cZrAexDV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>