<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great moments in cinematic history.  #BretEastonEllis #AmericanPsycho... https://t.co/hOMFwCMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're not how much money you've got in the bank. You're not your job. You're not your family, and you're not who you tell yourself." -F.C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most guys will fight to know you. Some will deny you're a real person, and some will just ignore you. The zealot. The atheist. The agnostic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Everyone still alive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With everyone's imagination atrophied, no one will ever be a threat to the world." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am Jack's bloody face... #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/jgL89yKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe God's hate is better than his indifference." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great 2009 interview with Chuck Palahniuk in Time...  http://t.co/7PaOYr5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're all such products." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Have been accused by someone that my Twitter rant last night about the movie version of "Les Miserables" was possib ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant art... #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/d71aPrv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your handwriting. The way you walk. Everything you do shows your hand. Everything is a self portrait. Everything is a diary." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all those asking me, Chuck's last name is pronounced like the names Paula &amp; Nick: Paula-Nick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You only ask people about themselves so you can tell them about yourself." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougCoupland: Why do drug dealers always look like drug dealers regardless of the drug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A copy of a copy of a copy... #FightClub #Insomnia #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/F1Ml0mxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just because you have stopped sinking doesn't mean you're not still underwater." - Amy Hempel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's another longest day of the year. Again." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Birds ate my face." - Invisible Monsters...  #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/6w8yrahL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe the point is not to forget the rest of yourself if one little part might go bad." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All women have to do is get naked, and we give them all our money. I mean, why are we such slaves?" - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want out of the labels. I don't want my whole life crammed into a single word." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just don't want to die without a few scars." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't want their lives fixed. Nobody wants their problems solved. Because what would they have left? Just the big scary unknown."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: You're an evil person. You're a person who pretends to love people so you can control them. But you don't care abou ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you can just crumble it up and throw your past in the trashcan, then we'll figure out who you're going to be." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just want one person I can rescue and I want one person who needs me. Who can't live without me. I want to be a hero." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The truth doesn't glitter and shine." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not like you anymore. I don't need to brag about my pain." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This quote from Diary seemed apropos today. #ChuckPalahniuk... http://t.co/3OuxWfwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The whole world is a disaster waiting to happen." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is nothing special in the world. Nothing magic. Just physics." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FightClub Zombies. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/Ry1QJ58r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every person is obsessed with himself. You are your own favorite hobby." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is like a ticking bomb." - Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Recycling and speed limits are bullshit. They're like someone who quits smoking on his deathbed." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters fan art. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/l47a053j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Almost all the time, you tell yourself you're loving somebody when you're just using them. This only looks like love." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, she still loves you. She wouldn't bother to torture you if she didn't." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sorry Mom, Sorry God." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pretend to be a vampire. I don't really need to pretend, because it's who I am, an emotional vampire." -Bret Ellis, The Rules of Attraction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're such a flake. You love me. You ignore me. You save my life, then you cook my mother into soap." - Marla Singer, Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fan art from Guts... #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/fozHtxUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have endless ways you can commit suicide without 'dying' dying." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's that fallen heart feeling that you rushed right through the moments where you should've been paying attention." -Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Misty wants to wave good-bye with her middle finger to this whole fucking island of genteel lunatics." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: The next book will indeed be DOOMED (the sequel to DAMNED).  Will be released in October 2013.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is short, death is forever." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Worker bees can leave. Even drones can fly away. The Queen is their slave." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Folks build a reputation by attacking while you're alive -- or praising you after you ain't." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Good to see even the stars of Gossip Girl like a little guts-y literature every now and then. http://t.co/npaWBsXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to waste your life is by taking notes. The easiest way to avoid living is to just watch. Don't participate." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If death meant just leaving the stage long enough to change costume and come back as a new character, would you slow down? Or speed up?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Demon or angel or evil spirit, I just need something to show itself. Ghoulie or ghosty or long-legged beastie, I just want my hand held."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "I am an invisible monster, and I am incapable of loving anybody. You don't know which is worse." - Chuck Palahniuk ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more things you own, the more they own you." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/AtQarv9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Leonardo's Mona Lisa is just a thousand smears of paint. We're all of us a million bits put together the right way." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a hundred years removed from anything original, but the truth is aren't we all?" - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can only die in the future, I thought; right now we are always alive." - Amy Hempel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're training a new employee to take over your boring old job. When you raise a child." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe sex and affection aren't mutually exclusive." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is partly soused with occasional bursts of despair and irritation." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For this moment, nothing matters. Look up into the stars and you're gone." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "Nothing is static. Even the Mona Lisa is falling apart." - Chuck Palahniuk http://t.co/T0vdDAuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most boring thing in the entire world is nudity. The second most boring thing, is honesty." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Amphetamines are the most American drug. You get so much done. You look terrific, and your middle name is Accomplishment." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Finally found. The uncut suicide scene that got slapped with a US NC-17 in 2002: The Rules Of Attraction: http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What you don't understand you can make mean anything." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe self-improvement isn't the answer, maybe self-destruction is the answer." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I disconnect the telephone to keep the outside world in it's correct place." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The bigger the mistake looks, the better chance I'll have to break out and live a real life. Our real discoveries come from chaos." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Psycho, Bret Easton Ellis... http://t.co/HHFRYJTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're all of us immortal. We couldn't die if we wanted to." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am not loved. I am not a beautiful soul. I am not a good-natured, giving person. I am not anybody's savior." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: This is cool. @WelshIrvine, @DougCoupland, @JackKetchum @StephenGJones72  share their favorite books of 2012 - http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Two lips and a tongue can promise you anything." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe you don't go to hell for the things you do. Maybe you go to hell for the things you don't do. The things you don't finish." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant Artwork... #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/3U6JYP8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To everybody, everybody else is a liar." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find value in what we've been taught is worthless. Find good in what the world says is evil. " - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "We're all of us, haunted and haunting." - Chuck Palahniuk http://t.co/Ze01bQKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At the time, my life just seemed too complete, and maybe we have to break everything to make something better out of ourselves." Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have your adventures, make your mistakes, and choose your friends poorly-- all these make for great stories."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougCoupland: 2013 is a terrible name for a year. I hereby rename it 'Tammy.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WelshIrvine: There is waaay too much snow in Miami tonite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WelshIrvine: Big love to every single cunt on planet earth! 10 mins till the bells!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/mBPuUvKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything is important, every detail. We just don't know why yet." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We'll never be as young as we are tonight." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every time you don't throw yourself down the stairs, that's a choice. Every time you don't crash your car, you re-enlist." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all live pretty much the same life." - Guts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters quote... #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/eNCBrOsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It can only take a moment to waste the rest of your life." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to kill all the fish I couldn't afford to eat and smother the French beaches I'd never see. I wanted the whole world to hit bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are times when the wolves are silent; there are times when the moon howls." - Amy Hempel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel my heart ache, but I've forgotten what that feeling means." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you could be either God's worst enemy or nothing, which would you choose?" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's the best revenge of all: happiness. Nothing drives people crazier than seeing someone having a good fucking life."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: And yep, financing finally came through for the HAUNTED movie adaptation.  Stay tuned for more details.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>