<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who fondly remember "Animaniacs", here's a transcription of the show's pitch meeting: https://t.co/of19keDuDw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medical question: can a brain tumour lead to too much cellphone use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmkritter Agreed! I don't like "Arrow", "Supergirl", "Vixen", or "Legends of Tomorrow"; "The Flash" is the only DC show I watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brenopolis: For every minute you watch a film, you age a minute. But, for every minute you watch a Terrence Malick film, you age 5 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because my other cat is totally baked and keeps talking about how pretty the ceiling is. https://t.co/X2EjlkHfNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistershrewd That sounds very hip -- almost tragically so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because the darkness deep inside his soul makes it impossible for him to enjoy summer as other cats do https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck I think you'll be more comfortable writing if you climb out of the vacuum and sit at a desk or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he is finding out what a cold and unforgiving place the modern music industry can be. https://t.co/ZFcT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck And how do you feel about that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adw1661: John Cleese &amp; Graham Chapman - behind the scenes of "Monty Python &amp; the Holy Grail" (1975). https://t.co/9ttoqFvrko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord, just look at her! She used to be a human female. https://t.co/KkyiYGEYqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Fred Astaire's dance moves, 1936. https://t.co/KBANI0xi7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tarakjpratt: Phew. Clarke's arm must be tired. #DadJoke https://t.co/aikYE4zv5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Iain_McDougall: 1975 “Monty Python &amp; The Holy Grail” released in UK #OnThisDay Graham Chapman, John Cleese &amp; @EricIdle @IMDb https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because I just told him a screening of an obscure French film he was excited about has been cancelled. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he wants to write an epic novel about being a cat but struggles a lot with writer's block. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if they will preserve the overt racism that characterized the show's Fox run. https://t.co/NDNbnKTaPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prof_elemental: Have taken up cooking. Actual food this time. Not like when I brewed all that horse brandy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt "Zero Dark Thirty" the pro-torture propaganda piece?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Early on, have your protagonist do something less nice than the audience would do. It makes them think, "Oh, I like her!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck My laptop kept spontaneously playing "Someone Like You". Then I realized -- it's a Dell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Why did Adele cross the road? To say hello from the other side!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Wheeler: Dear Hollywood, please cast Idris Elba's actual face in some movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wilw: R2 and 3PO should have just flown the Eagles to Arrakis to defeat the MCP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMFlint: 149 years ago today the Zoetrope, the forerunner to the motion picture, was patented, 1867.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StatsBritain: 97% of Britons miss David Tennant and Billie Piper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Are they the nanny-cam bears with the hidden video camera? Then I have an explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw a post: "Can someone please find Henry Rollins and keep him safe? I don't trust 2016 any more."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Do mean that drinking is better than worrying about solving computer problems? That sounds like something I could support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarelGeis Is it true he was in a band before "Wings"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynneux @stevecavers It seemed kind of like a celebration -- "This could be the last 4/20 Day under prohibition!" Then music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevecavers: "If you see packages in the meat drawer labeled 'Steve', that's who it belongs to and not what it contains."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sinKEVitch: I KNEW it.  https://t.co/eNSocFnHzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he's seen things you people wouldn't believe, attack ships on fire off the shoulder of Orion. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Filmkritter: Fawlty Twin Towers 
#MakeTVShowsEvil @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCFerrys: Att'n passenger: Please smoke whatever you're smoking in designated areas only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistershrewd If he thinks the crowds are there for him, he must be high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: The spine: what your characters wants by the end of the play. The vertebrae: each scene that gets her closer to (or fart…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avram Ah, but Dave's regressed about 1,400 years since then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: John Cassavetes &amp; Gena Rowlands, photographed by Peter Falk. https://t.co/nlsanq6CTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AshleyEsqueda: We need to run this person out of the universe https://t.co/Spv8Cmu5bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Considering how they ended it -- oh, and also most of the middle -- I don't think "good idea" is something they recognized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheUnNovelist: Step by step. #amwriting #writing https://t.co/tJnW7intnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmcconville @ItsAdamCanuck Maybe it wasn't 78 dead spiders. Maybe it was one growing spider sloughing off 78 old exoskeletons. Better?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley I think they couldn't afford seat belts after paying all that money to the Exploding Console Manufacturing Co.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Thanks! Woo hoo! Oh baby, I am gonna shred so hard --!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Which one? I need a new shredder, in case I ever get divorced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCFerrys: Hey cheechakos, welcome aboard the MV Hyas Klootchman Tyee of Oak Bay. Enjoy the view of the skookumchuk from the klahanie de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dam3ian: President Trump on the front page of "The Boston Globe" for April 9, 2017: https://t.co/MAhx1eSJrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @debcha: For those who were asking… https://t.co/ZXvhTS0M2t https://t.co/FPylIxpNNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LtlFreeLibrary: "The only thing you absolutely have to know is the location of the library." - Albert Einstein https://t.co/J72eDidftk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeyface: It’s on now, Warner Bros Entertainment Lasso. You fucked with the wrong babysitter. https://t.co/wzMoYwZlo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Yeah, I think Florida is up to the 1950s these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheUnNovelist: Don't do nothing when you can do something. #amwriting #writing #writingtip https://t.co/mS9FhmRLMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people say that I'm ignorant and apathetic. Well, I don't know, and I don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Hmm ... I must have been absent that day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Fidomobile, how do I cancel my fucking account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck No, if you shoot the control panel of a closed door, that locks it. Shows you that I know more than a seven-year-old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Dave Sim and Colleen Doran wrote about restoring B&amp;W artwork for the digital age. Have you any tips of your own to share?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Given your track record with "Nelvana" and "Brok", have you any interest in producing a history of the "Canadian whites"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people say I use big words to sound smart, but I am not cognizant of any polysyllabic propensity as a simulacrum of intelligence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jondaly I don't understand how you can golf and swim at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Publicity photo of Laurel and Hardy, 1932. https://t.co/b9jbempfnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about writing counts as time spent writing, right? https://t.co/h9w2KSTKAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: As a playwright, you primary responsibility is to not bore your audience. It's not to improve them. This is already an a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nooMcinaP Listened! Funny (you liarfaces)! (And if your gear ever goes down again, I'll record you; call me.) Panic Mooniverse rules!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt My girlfriend when I read her your Tweet: "We all deserve a Tom Hiddleston. That's not in question here."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: boring. https://t.co/S5uyajXJmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colebrax: On the set of 'One-Eyed Jacks' (1961) Marlon Brando receives a visit from Jacques Tati: https://t.co/BssOfhaeL4 https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scammerhead: Watch for the Scammerhead to show up at the @MariettaFilmFes Aug 7 https://t.co/zx4QYYs7hY #Indiefilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I have the issue myself, and can scan it for you if that would be helpful, but I don't want to add to your clutter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Sorry; the actual download there seems to be dead. It's a good article on the 8-bit hand-colouring sent to Sparta Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Possible source material: "How to Colour Comics the Marvel Way" from "Marvel Age" (1984): https://t.co/axI1uL16Qn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MizCaramelVixen: Hey!!! I need a black comic artist for the #BlackComicsMonth anthology for @80Grey! It's a paying gig AND a chance to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdofEV: Useless cat. https://t.co/5P6dY5eENf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Sure, everyone wants to go back in time and kill Hitler, but nobody does anything about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because I have just told him and some friends about modern America's uneven distribution of wealth. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Oo la la!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Like this: https://t.co/D7rXdQ8TEK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck (The coat, I mean, not the maid's tool.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Or a duster!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Or Gary Groth's "Black &amp; White &amp; Dead All Over" contemporaneous look at the '80s b&amp;w boom and bust: https://t.co/IAxG4Vq9fP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Your primary goal as a playwright is to keep the audience member from ever pondering which armrest is hers. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I wonder if you've seen "Failed Universe", a sophomoric but amusing parody of Marvel's New Universe from the b&amp;w '80s boom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Do as I say, not as I do"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @FidoSolutions admitted they didn't need my birthdate after all. That means they could have helped me all along, and just chose not to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vashikoo: The Raven Bar matte painting from #Raiders of the Lost Ark #filmmaking #LostArt https://t.co/orRkTHT4fA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. @FidoSolutions can't figure out why I can't log in to the Fido website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FidoSolutions You won't tell me why you want this information. You cannot need it to verify me if you have nothing to verify it against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FidoSolutions You did. Not usefully, though. Why do you need new personal information that I have never before provided to "verify" me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FidoSolutions You cannot validate my identity with this information, as you have nothing to validate against. I have never provided it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does @FidoSolutions want new personal information from me to help with my old account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now @FidoSolutions wants my birthdate, which I have never provided. To ID me? How many people with my name *and phone number* are on file?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To solve my problem of being unable to log in to their website, @FidoSolutions wants me to log in to their website and fill out a form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAtwood "Better Far is Woad!" https://t.co/S00cbzl7pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern The late, great George Carlin talks about that right at the start here: https://t.co/N9R0z9Gfoq.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Fidomobile! Once again I can't access your systems because of their poor setup. Can I please have a phone number to speak to a person?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evanjstern: Dating someone new is mostly just trying to figure out if it's worth watching each other's favourite movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Do they still make "Crystal Pepsi", or is this leftover stock from the early 1990s? Y'know, like Twinkies?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>