<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriBerman: .@staceyabrams never said she wants undocumented immigrants to vote &amp; clearly doesn't. This is BS Republicans use to justify…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinMKruse: Chrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrriiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiissssssssssssttttt. 
https://t.co/a54q4uL7bz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenSpeakUpBiz: @DavidAFrench David French: I'll find the silliest take on this whole thing! Watch me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepSwalwell: Leaders are measured by where they stood on questions of morality. General Lee sided with slavery. Lincoln sided with free…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: One thing I have learned watching the elections in 2017 + 2018 is how wrong the pundits’ narratives and polls have been fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @janekleeb: Great @PodSaveAmerica segment on climate change. More leaders need to say “We are going to get to zero carbon pollution...”…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PRRIpoll: “Just 20 percent of young Americans made it to the polls in the last midterm election, and we’re seeing some cynicism among y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: So therefore I provided a decisive vote to seat #kavanaugh who has given every indication he will vote on #scotus to blo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: The idea that climate policies would "destroy our economy" is disinformation spread by fossil-fuel interests and right-win…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: Is this “the mob” GOP??????
Pro-Trump, MAGA hat wearing “Proud Boys” *actually* beat people up and the NYPD did nothing?…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimmykimmel: A great teacher from Texas came all the way to LA for a special performance of her viral hit #AScaryTime... @MercedesLynz…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrianKarem: From pool reports: Neither hurricanes nor suffering Floridians can keep POTUS from his Sunday golfing rounds. ⁦@realDonaldT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Morfeld: A bunch of state senators who have opposed Medicaid Expansion for the last seven years are writing opinion pieces stating…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennThrush: I wish the follow-up question would have been: ‘why did your press shop lie about it?’ https://t.co/e5mFsChqoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Harvard: New and old spots at Harvard encourage pause and reflection, for religious and mindful communities alike https://t.co/99oPJYyl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNBC: Trump suggests Defense Secretary Mattis may depart Pentagon, calls him 'sort of a Democrat' https://t.co/2PCSQoaBqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnJHarwood: new ABC/WashPost poll

control of Congress:

women 59% D, 37% R
men 46% D, 48% R

it’s urgent to vote:

women 70%
men 62%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: “I think he's sort of a Democrat, if you want to know the truth," Trump said when asked if Mattis could depart the admi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaegerExclaims: Hear that #Nebraska? Ben Sasse thinks you should fire Deb Fischer. I agree. https://t.co/ZA5WrvYjWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinMKruse: “The government of the United States is not, in any sense, founded on the Christian religion.” — The Treaty of Tripoli, 17…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Morfeld: That could all be very true, but the bigger issue is elected officials who lack political courage to create laws that pro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelMParsons: @BenSasse Awesome! I love being told about how tribalism is killing our country by one of Donald Trump's chief enabler…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kendra_alayne: @BenSasse Politics are at the center of my life because every time I turn around, you numb nuts are trying to remove pro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dabeard: Like father, like son: Jared Kushner's dad went to prison after his conviction for tax evasion and other charges in 2005. Here…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BenSasse is either incapable of self reflection or he is cynically trolling with his high-minded rhetoric and his do nothing politics. https://t.co/Ji5Nl6jecO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbg1: Seems that the First Lady is more of a Trump, and less some silenced secret dissenter, than many anti-Trumpers imagined. So much…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrantleyGasaway: When “America First” was part of a campaign to attract immigrants: a 1915 poster from the National Americanization Com…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KyleMunson: Killer graf: “In his almost 16 yrs in Congress, King has passed exactly 1 bill as primary sponsor, redesignating a post off…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BucarLiz @PaulRingel @MRaucher @ESweenyBlock @DFozardWeaver @kecia_ali @ProfIRMF @mpgPhD @krw18 (Monday is our "fall break")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BucarLiz @PaulRingel @MRaucher @ESweenyBlock @DFozardWeaver @kecia_ali @ProfIRMF @mpgPhD @krw18 I'd love to start, starting next Tuesday...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elizabeth_Calo So do I...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sullivanamy Horror is what is happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamilSmith: The 53,000+ Georgia residents with “pending” voter applications should go to their polling places, if they can. They still…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricHolthaus: Yep, there's a hurricane headed toward Portugal. In centuries of record keeping, there's never been a hurricane landfall…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kgrandia: After @SenatorCollins helped vote in Brett #Kavanaugh she received a "six figure" donation from Judicial Crisis Watch, a dark…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @roblee4: My response to @realDonaldTrump and his comments last night about my collateral ancestor, Robert E. Lee. https://t.co/ISw6nMsp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilmoreGlenda: Enslaved people built and sustained UNC. At long last, Folt apologizes. Hope she realizes there is no place on campus fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottBlake: VOTE
Raybould @JaneRaybould
Eastman @KaraForCongress
Krist @BobKristNE
Danner @DannerForNE
Skinner @JaneForAuditor
Battiato…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RVAwonk: "It was a really fun night, and overall I cannot recommend violence enough. It is a really effective way to solve problems.” -…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdKrassen: In the aftermath of Hurricane Michael, Trump spent the day meeting with Kanye West.

Meanwhile @AndrewGillum, who is running…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: "I can't emphasize enough how important this is right now! If the outrage is clear and swift and public now it could shift…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AshleeMPreston: Welp...it’s official...Kim Kardashian finally decided to divorce Kanye West... https://t.co/C2p25mxWJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MsPackyetti: The government: if you’re a tribal resident, you get a PO Box, not a street address. 

Also the government: you can only v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriBerman: "Approximately 80.15% of pending applications were submitted by African-American, Latino and Asian-American applicants. Only…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ccjones13: This is a big deal. Democrat @BenMcAdams has overtaken Mia Love in the polls out of #UT04 for the first time. A congressiona…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: @DavidAFrench Any discussion about civility in politics right now that does not place Trump's *deliberate* and *concerte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatzOnEarth: @DavidAFrench Hey bright guy https://t.co/HbVmE9zSxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanchait: @DavidAFrench You're saying a tiny handful of street protesters is *worse* than the president of the United States calli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kfabnews: NOW: Leader of the @NebraskaDems @janekleeb joins @CBakerShow to talk about the upcoming midterms, civility in politics, and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickqmason @CGUnews Thanks, Patrick, for the invitation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BRepairers: #VoterSuppression happening at the hands of the candidate in Georgia gubernatorial race! We will not be silent anymore!! #P…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @werehist: #OnThisDay 20 years ago, Univ. of Wyoming student Matthew Shepard died 6 days after being brutally beaten, tied to a fence po…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @forgive_luv: @mmurraypolitics @NatefromUSA VOTE BLUE! https://t.co/ZrOXarhLWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewNebraska: .@SenatorFischer's approval rating is well below 50% and nearing a net negative. Nebraskans don't want a Senator who perso…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: .@BrianKempGA you need to recuse yourself or step down as Secretary of State.  Stop suppressing the vote!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Stacey Abrams' campaign is calling on Brian Kemp to resign.
https://t.co/WuuwrRsA6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: Good, albeit infuriating, @paulwaldman1 look at how Republican voter suppression efforts under way now in Georgia are a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoyAnnReid: One more thing: as the polar energy behind Democratic votes shifts back to the South post-Alabama and Virginia, expect vote…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JRubinBlogger: This is why VRA needs to be amended to fix sections 4 and 5. Roberts told Congress it could. This is shameful https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmusic: You don't silence women, ever.

I talk about #generalconference with the wonderfully astute @patrickqmason on the newest @morm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @trinaboice: A touching movie that illustrates the sisterhood and friendship between two women of faith during many struggles.  Opens in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lmower3: .@AndrewGillum and his chief of staff have been using chainsaws to clear this street for the last 45 minutes or so. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come see me talk "Race and the Making of the Mormon People" tonight @CGUnews! https://t.co/yh2Gq74rop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @myrna_perez_: Lots of people are concerned about Georgia right now.  They should be.  @ktnmorris and I (@myrna_perez_ ) reported recent…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @asu_csrc: On religion and politics: A relevant read on Kavanaugh, Mormonism, and women via Religion and Politics/@CtrRelPol https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only am I reading @rtraister’s book, I’m teaching in my American Prophets class. https://t.co/73dfBJFb5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennThrush: Critics aren't charging. Reality is. https://t.co/5agT0D1hIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a few (hundred thousand) in GA and FL who could use all our help! https://t.co/zcmqjLXdci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SRuhle: THIS STORY MATTERS https://t.co/ImtwgbzHfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to @CGUnews for this talk! I'll be also talking with the Miller-Eccles Study Group tomorrow and Saturday! https://t.co/4TN5KHpih3 https://t.co/ijnC1IYFUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Denver airport on my way to https://t.co/ijnC1IYFUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Robillard: NEW: Two days after she cast the vote that could both define and end her political career, Heidi Heitkamp was back home in N…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PolitiFact: .@MarshaBlackburn says Democrats have advocated for open borders. Trump said Democrats had an open border bill. Not at all…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UnionSeminary: "To deny someone the right to vote is to suggest that they're not human." - @RevDrBarber #PoorPeoplesCampaign https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNews: President Trump directly accused Hillary Clinton of engaging in a conspiracy with Russia to affect the 2016 election during a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maddow: "Kemp’s office has cancelled over 1.4m voter registrations since 2012. Nearly 670k registrations were cancelled in 2017 alone..…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: NEW:  Ethics complaints filed against Justice Brett Kavanaugh in the weeks leading up to his confirmation are still live.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: "According to the AP, fully 70 percent of the voter applications that are being held up by Kemp’s office are from black p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lily_gladstone: Disenfranchised voters in ND - PLEASE read! https://t.co/69tCvvUCTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thecrisismag: BREAKING  @AP: 53,000 Georgians' voter registrations (nearly 70% of them African-American) are being held up by @BrianKem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has always been clear. But don't you still think he'd vote to convict if there was clear evidence (and clear politics)? https://t.co/4fPodHkHkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheExponent: The #SocialMediaFast happens to coincide with the opening of this film about Jane Manning James and Emma Smith. Don't let…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet due to gerrymandering, Dems need to win at least 6+ to flip the House. That’s not democracy. https://t.co/hw6yU2pCi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytopinion: A persistent refrain in the fall of 2016 was “I can’t wait till this thing is over already.” Making Americans want the elec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @goldengateblond: I need the @DNC to hire the people behind @Fire_Ted_Cruz to make ALL the political ads because holy hell this is balle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: He literally offered to pay the legal fees of supporters that beat the crap out of people. https://t.co/rW0P2fvqzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SikhProf: Or the racist who killed Indian immigrant Srinivas Kuchibhotla in Kansas?

Or the white supremacist who massacred Sikhs in Wi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricHolder: Outrageous/Unjust. R’s in North Dakota make it harder for Native Americans to vote. Requiring street address when many of t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HamillHimself: Read every word of this message from @taylorswift13 If even a fraction of her 83.5M followers go to https://t.co/sbOmiO5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, but their wages of whiteness have never been higher! https://t.co/FBrUQ4OBGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markfollman: So now it’s “lock her up” for ANY female political opponent of Trump, including one of the longest-serving US senators in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Newsweek: 61 percent of Trump's twitter followers are not real, according to new analysis https://t.co/rwW2qIWhOn https://t.co/uSNl2L2H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @saladinahmed: abducted not adopted
abducted not adopted
abducted not adopted https://t.co/USLmOY6eo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFPfaff: In 1997, Susan Collins was afraid to get in a Senators-only elevator with Strom Thurmond because he was likely to sexually…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @benepstein55: If you live in Illinois (and many other states) today is the deadline to register to vote. https://t.co/kX0ZNVjQXb is a g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @richardhine: BREAKING: UN Ambassador Nikki Haley resigns, declaring that the rest of the world couldn't possibly have more respect for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please ask him what percentage of the Americans he has sworn and oath to serve are "evil." https://t.co/7MNzWxCx9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DennisPCrawford: @DonJBacon Bacon is too extreme for #NE02.  He voted to take away insurance from 23 million people and to gut pre-exis…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RuthHHopkins: North Dakota Native voters who do not have a residential address: here are instructions so you can vote in the midterms.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @questlove: spread the word. https://t.co/6KPRo7SV7M]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>