<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: What defines us is how well we rise after falling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone else is happy with less than you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that you enjoy are never a waste of time, everything else is suspect. https://t.co/IlVw6BVtAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give people a piece of your heart rather than your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is never too late to be what you might have been. -George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Golden retriever owners will understand! ;D

Get this t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/WFMYk9Naak https://t.co/HYPzKcmD72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to expect things of yourself before you can do them. -Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so lucky.  Do you agree? https://t.co/5jNL1bxuzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All great achievements require time. - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is but a canvas to the imagination. -Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Sometimes the thing we can't change end up changing us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake friends believe in rumors. Real friends believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep looking UP :) https://t.co/TUK4u5Gf2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't follow your dreams - chase them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to believe in yourself when no one else does that makes you a winner right there. -Venus Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By leaving behind ur old self &amp; taking a leap of faith into the unknown, u find out what u are truly capable of becoming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @coffee_lst: Yours truly and faithfully. https://t.co/0cMwszffm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope is the only thing stronger then fear. https://t.co/uKNoxS8JpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be selective in your battles. Sometimes peace is better than being right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are hardest to love need it the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change begins at the end of your comfort zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to feel rich, just count all the gifts you have that money can't buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do everything in love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you'll not settle for anything less than your best, you will be amazed at what you can accomplish in your lives. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you figured it all out today, what would be the point of tomorrow? ENJOY the process of being a work in progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_HQ: Never give up!

Get your motivational t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/3ymJ4O86S2 https://t.co/mSyW7OCnZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:) https://t.co/ZDYSvU9BCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Sometimes you have to get knocked down lower than you've ever been, to stand up taller than you than you ever were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/PrP0sJ7Mw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: To be honest... :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/TFXlB06038 https://t.co/kvLxNEnAiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge is knowing what to say. Wisdom is knowing whether or not to say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work like you don't need money, love like you've never been hurt, and dance like no one's watching. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thing to remember. https://t.co/w4LH3eDlRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_moxy: ✔ Awake
✔ Blessed
✔ Grateful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn your wounds into wisdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something today that your future self will thank you for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real friendship is like fluorescence, it shines better when everything has darken. -Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: God didn't promise days without pain, sun without rain, but He did promise strength for the day and light for the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not regret growing older; it is a privilege denied to many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the unloved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream your dreams with your eyes closed, but live your dreams with your eyes open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness will come to you when it comes from you. Success will be yours when you choose to take responsibility for making it so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the possibilities. https://t.co/kbjEMrH39V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes God doesn't change your situation because He's trying to change your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seek respect, not attention. It lasts longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to walk away from what you want to find what you deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice. https://t.co/fjY4zJyLmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you. -Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end, we only regret the chances we didn't take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Sweet dreams! :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/LpbzchsTGm https://t.co/9tNLmjFg4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovLikeJesus: Everytime you forgive you disappoint the devil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true. https://t.co/YxC46GZidV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Million dollar ideas are a dime a dozen. The determination to see the idea through is what's priceless. -Robert Dieffenbach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great spirits have always faced violent opposition from mediocre minds. - Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: Knowing This Saves Lives. 
Please Watch And RT.

https://t.co/x88zEzwopG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: It's perfectly acceptable to stay in our pajamas and read books all day, right? :)

Get your t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smallest deed is better than the greatest intention. -John Burroughs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give it your all. https://t.co/LoRHpZ9z0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've accepted your flaws no one can use them against you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you stop chasing the wrong things you give the right things a chance to catch you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @catscofffee: I wanna play. not fight https://t.co/Co7bbvTWRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only two ways to live life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God will wreck your plans when He sees that your plans are about to wreck you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your actions and your words should always agree with each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_grit: If you don't want to be the best, then there's no reason going out and trying to accomplish anything. -Joe Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for the good in each day. https://t.co/BRgC73bH1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everything that is faced can be changed, but nothing can be changed until it is faced. -Lucille Ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only disability in life is a bad attitude. -Scott Hamilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If God is the DJ, then Life is the dance floor; Love is the rhythm, &amp; You are the music -unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past cannot be changed, forgotten, edited or erased; it can only be accepted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way I see it, if you want the rainbow, you gotta put up with the rain. - Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Saintly_Life: Everyone should see this no matter what their beliefs!  Its' Eye Opening! https://t.co/1Rl6WmdggQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great things never came from comfort zones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be faithful in small things because it is in them that your strength lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing which you think you cannot do. -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my new favorite quote. https://t.co/YquHAN8Cuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I let go of what's not meant to be, I clear a path for good stuff to find me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @catscofffee: Cuteness is my middle name https://t.co/fNOGZDN83c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You live longer once you realize that any time spent being unhappy is wasted. - Ruth E. Renkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/bw9oJxFtEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love fearlessly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is ever wrong. We learn from every step we take. Whatever you did today was the way it was meant to be. Be proud of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you give up is the moment you let someone else win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a good one. https://t.co/wcxL6NugbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty is about living your life &amp; being happy with yourself inside &amp; out &amp; not worrying about what people think of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: I choose to be happy today. https://t.co/GFqCBrz0JD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life isn't about finding yourself, it's about creating yourself. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect the BEST. Prepare for the WORST. Forget what others THINK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true, everyone should be reminded of this. https://t.co/BoM337clmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness doesn't result from what we get, but from what we give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be more concerned with your character than your reputation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: Our experiences shape us.  Appreciate them, for you wouldn't be the person you are without them. https://t.co/KoCxVtmuKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God doesn't give you the people you want, he gives you the people you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no mistakes in life, just lessons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Lord! https://t.co/ve5NvAawPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love like there's no tomorrow, and if tomorrow comes, love again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you win, say nothing, when you lose, say less. -Paul Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you're on the right track, you'll get run over if you just sit there. -Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A happy person is not a person in a certain set of circumstances, but rather a person with a certain set of attitudes.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>