<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/rTzXvynGAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/0dQ367sVtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/pJFEpRoSrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/l3k3v3LdnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/pJmviM5c6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/Tw0YuJi8wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/Yto0hURbj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/TbqQv1MRPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/SrMOVFeG9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/BHnR60qwiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/6D3A5JGTqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/0zPuOskOY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/DW4ZtFNxyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/NWDPYvYj6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/w8i5jyutgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/g633fbzqpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/mrKy4qFOHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/ZLfNlJKwqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/1eJtiWw0yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/rZGyy4c3V1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/jfVdJRosx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/LxfqyhnhIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/RohgDwl1gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/DKawOOOPex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/RLwWV3WdjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/NwnCUPjMdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/Ta5Ki91rBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/khJc48TeHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/9PHMk7HZk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/Fj6q4BUqby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/nBkmSktE7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/qWSh13u5Wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/nUAkLzYOZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/SQV4UCUi0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/cxElYHWXnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/sAqRHjrPfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/RLwWV3WdjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/btNtVGC7YO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/VQI7aJ4Hk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/jVzbmxSBql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/HSVQ8mhzQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/6D3A5JGTqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/WTjZOYWJsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/cBIh6GAaq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/ezqpCT5Cil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/7t5lARsXKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/Yto0hURbj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/KwJZPdK4hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/w8i9x6F84O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/cqNI8QA7Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/8H9SO9Xzc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/TFQycO6WxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/ANcXNekg2r]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>