<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/hLf2AFWkBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/4pEQBdNlqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/cDtQqDnKBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/PdZ54Evaw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/54uDStBKQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/erhJMinJst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/yfmkOfgVU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/hyyXJ8u4IY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/nAVClb6ayA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/TAPmNdsOGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/av2VJQadFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/xdY9sFlhxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/0FZYY1VOeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/EMGqQynpkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/bJ9b3aOxr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/rfa3aZuexR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/sLNmgZETZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/TLUuiEqyT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/NGmmFiLwXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/BfuGxtsMY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/j1tIlr8XON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/n3HoM5CKHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/K2UTG3433y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/IjGgwF1Rnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/Rvg08l8mmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/yGmLV1vFUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/Fmm4OX4ASA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/wnhcNGwWUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/aCxKDFeKbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/HUPa8ZQ58d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/mqAhlpgGJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/N1AGO7LO5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/KALovzuVeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire character. Train skill. - Peter Schutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/akCPtc1X7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/s34uokOqN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/1a5cqiGPN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/uBMmmpNcEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/9REwa3juMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>