<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/8UfLqg64aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/uFyBtuBUu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/mBNlZFqJZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/ZKfTQxnAXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/KxFv33eKPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/biilWwlkqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/lY7eEqNsxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/fQGVrGVXe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/g5hraLiWgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/EzlFSTuK4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/ZZVBPZ5jsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/meZc0qygvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/Z8lTXP1slI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/NRdacZR5Hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/BLjgUF04Rz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/8cOt5Hn957]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/KyCZVnAQOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/Zi1CyqviLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/1Y3N0QESIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/7ruqOeoWZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/3El52AnqZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/BCCZ2hH3xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/7h7XrU0sTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/XPNXARMGmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/QVuFTAdISC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/B0iZNv1AGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/CHWuWCyAr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/meZc0qygvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/qPWvdhW9l9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/VoobKd2WAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/7saXrLdNcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/i6WuOJdirF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/79SNwuuiaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/O1p76dOqsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/6ho3V1wUXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/t2070TH5iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/BxQi5UtEpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/uFyBtuBUu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/uOz424oUZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/svQtcI9wkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/peMhV2hwUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/STVixiuSiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/XPNXARMGmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/MYut1ynsFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/lAOLIaXLj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/YCEBUAblKw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>