<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Ways to Pick the Perfect Wedding Bands By Jessica Zaleski: PHOTO BY TREVOR DIXON 1… https://t.co/hhZDqyySZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Ways to Pick the Perfect Wedding Bands By Jessica Zaleski: PHOTO BY TREVOR DIXON 1… https://t.co/yil7YKxM8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Don’t Know Why This Happens – By Victor Akunna: Over 15 years ago, I took responsibility… https://t.co/0J3arsdEss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Don’t Know Why This Happens – By Victor Akunna: Over 15 years ago, I took responsibility… https://t.co/DFVyzYroLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40. I fall within about 3 or 4 spheres of influence, but the core one for me is the FAMILY. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27. Charity begins at home, not in the public square. As a philanthropist, don't show affection to your neighbour... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13. This is the foundation of any thing you will be doing in your society. Doing this shaped and directed our passion... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26. Hence, to positively influence your society, "be the change you want to see in the world" - Mahatma Gandhi. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. The Foundation of the American, Canadian, British, Nigerian families,... are built on the families within them. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. ...are often carried out by individuals from broken and dysfunctional families. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23b. ...costing tax payers billion of dollars monthly...  #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. Statistics show that most of the societal ills, such as drugs abuse, violence, rape, etc...  #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. People from families with strong role models often impact their communities positively and vice versa. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. as leaders, we must influence our families first. Our lives behind close doors must be congruent with our public personas. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20.that aspect of me nobody sees i.e. who we are when we are by ourselves.This is the person our family is often modelled after#24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19b. I have a philosophy which drives me to focus more on building my character,... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19a. Hence, our first duty is to build a family which would influence society from within,... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18b...."breaking a strand of boom stick is easy, but breaking a bunch is difficult". #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. There is power in a unified front. There is an African proverb that goes thus ...#24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. ...what Maxwell J. terms Family cohesion, 'emotional bonding that family members have toward one another'. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. When you clarify your purpose and values, it would help you, among many other things, to achieve... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15. Two are better than one, only when they leverage on their strengths. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. ...and energies as a family, thereby increasing our results through the power of synergy. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[39b. ... we can explore in order to transform our societies. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[39a. These spheres of influence carry within them opportunities and challenges... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[37b. ... or spheres of influence which include a. Religion b. Family. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[37a. ...developed a strategy to influence the society. These are also called 7 mountains or... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36. In 1975, Bill Bright, founder of Campus Crusade and Loren Cunningham, founder of Youth With a Mission(YWAM),...  #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35b... is that it enables you to know the aspect of society to influence. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35a. On the other hand, beyond family cohesion, another value of clarifying your family purpose... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34b... the family purpose of transforming your society, when they truly feel a sense of connection. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34a. More so, this strengthens the sense of commitment of members of your family towards... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33b. . This is so critical because there is no lasting success without successors. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33a. ...in discovering their personal purpose and how it fits into the overall family purpose. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32. In addition to clarifying your family purpose and values, it is important that you support your spouse and children... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31b...you stand the risk of being crushed by either pressure or fame. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31a. Without solid character and a sense of personal identity drawn from your purpose and who you are ... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30. UR first responsibility is to build your own character and that of your family before venturing into building your society #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28. ...when your wife and children receive only meanness and rudeness from you. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @24karatslife: Thank you @jabulaniapeh, @Grace_Festus, @Jennychisomblog, @livimart and @FamilyAffairs05 for making today happen. We love…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @24karatslife: Thank you very much for sharing your thoughts @FamilyAffairs05 . If only we know that family is the foundation of society…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38. c. Education d. Government e. Media f. Arts and entertainment g. Business. These are key aspects.  #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50b. my brother, Chris Chukwuyere! God bless you and your great wife, Shola. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50. Happy birthday to one of the great voices in the family life industry. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49. We cannot 'legislate' a good family, it must be built one value at a time, one family at a time.  #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[48. To build a family that influences society, every stakeholder must join hand in playing a role. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[47. Governments spend so much of tax payers' money, without positive results becos these children ve been 'messed' up at home. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[46. These things are good, but they can't address the root/remote cause of the menace. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45.by building better schools, hiring psychologists in schools, setting up juvenile correctn facilities bcos they are clueless #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44b. The painful part is that most governments are busy throwing money at the leaves of the problems... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44a. pornography, drugs, gangsterism are tearing down our youths. ... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[43. divorce rate has quadrupled, juvenile delinquency has risen over the years,... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[42. Right now, the meaning of marriage is being redefined in many cultures,... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[41b. ... which is to have godly seeds and enlarge His kingdom. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[41a. This sphere has been under intense and prolonged series of attack which are aimed at destabilising God's plan.. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. ...you must sit down with your spouse-to-be to prayerfully clarify the purpose of your family. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. Hence, to build a family that influences society, we must clarify why our families exist and if you are yet to form yours..#24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. Purpose is so critical to marriage because "when it is not known, abuse is inevitable"- Myles Monroe. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. The purpose behind wanting to get married determines what we expect, who we attract and what we put into it. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7b. However, that set me on a personal quest to explore deeper motives for wanting to get married. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7a. To my amazement, my response was too selfish for me to express. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. He asked me a simple question, why do you want to get married? #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. Many years ago, as a single man, I had a discussion with a senior colleague about my plans to get married. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4b... is about establishing a family that leads and sets the pace within your society. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4a. In other words, 'Building a family that influences society'.... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3b. This is what John maxwell calls leadership. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. ...force on or produce effects on the actions, behavior, opinions, etc., of others", https://t.co/b8QAJlUQ2A. #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2b. ...while the word 'influence' means "capacity or power of persons or things to be a compelling... #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2a. The word 'build' means, among many things, "to establish",...#24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends, you can join Victor Akunna on Twitter @familyaffairs05 from 7pm to 8pm (GMT + 1) as he examines... https://t.co/MhzxhJtXPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1b. ...it within the context of the illustrious theme - "the life that count"#24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1a. There are many interesting ways to look at the topic, but I would be considering #24KaratsLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends, you can join me as I examine 'Building a family that influences society'. #24karatsLife https://t.co/MkDLA5Wf0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @24karatslife: Thanks to our facilitators, @careerwiseng, @Grace_Festus, @iamemekanobis, @IsiomaOleleh, @FamilyAffairs05, @Jennychisombl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: Jesus is the reason for this season! Merry Christmas!

Thanks for joining us tonight, we appreciate you! 
https://t.co/fl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: May your home experience true joy this season! #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 21. Interestingly, we can never be too full of the excitement his birth brings. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20b. ..of His birth? Have they experienced the joy of his birth? #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20a. Do your children know the reason for the celebration? Do they know who Jesus is and the purpose....#ChristmasAndYour…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 19. The excitement should be built around the joy the birth of Christ brought to the world.#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18b. ... Christmas is beyond the gifts, the lovely meals and the frenzy. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18a. Let them know and understand the reason for the season...#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17b...but make the most of the season to deposit some values into your children. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17a. Of course, Christmas time is not the only time to infuse good character in your children...#ChristmasAndYourChild #i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16c. ...Life. They would produce better and stronger men and women." #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16b. into their children when they are young as in sacrificing to give them a good education later in #ChristmasAndYourCh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16a. According to Tim Lahaye, "if parents were as conscientious about infusing good character into.. #ChristmasAndYourChi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 15. The more time we spend with our children, the more opportunities we have to pass on values.#ChristmasAndYourChild #iC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14b. for their children, but spend less time with the children. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14a. Sometimes, parents labour so much, trying to provide the best...#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. I am not trying to condemn this, but to encourage prioritisation. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12b. so as to be paid double for the day's work.#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12a. Some parents in the western world wouldn't mind working on Christmas Day....#ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 11. Sadly, they still spend less time with their children over Christmas. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10. Some parents spend so much time at work, trying to meet up with the heavy demand of Christmas. #ChristmasAndYourChild…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9. Oops! They mustn't hear me say that.😀 #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8b. have been conditioned to expect special gifts at Christmas. #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8a. Thinking about it, I am beginning to wonder if it is just that children...#ChristmasWithYourFamily #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 7b...will not get the things they want" #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 7a. In the words of a parent, "if I don't work, they will not be happy because they... #ChristmasAndYourChild #iConnectHe…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>