<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker discovers a tiny glass sphere that lets her have sexual intercourse with eunuchs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A busboy owns a map which shows the location of every realtor in India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lizard made of carrots is born in Varanasi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A circus performer discovers that the stars are secretly being manipulated by a caliph living in a glass pyramid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Australian dictator declares war on childhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Afghan empress listens to a Stradivarius violin that plays the sounds of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polar bear appears next to Alexander the Great. It says: "Beware of moons."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Welsh tsar invents a new moral philosophy based on the movement of Stradivarius violins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dutch philosopher writes a sonnet that is made out of Tori Amos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A railway station is haunted by the ghost of a Trojan necromancer. She was murdered by a ghost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cook makes a pie. Inside is love at first sight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, a hairdresser in St Louis turns into a supernova during her lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fraternity of philosophers devise an alternate universe where everything is videocassettes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drunk nurse hears of an Olympic stadium located inside a moonstone, and starts looking for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archbishop builds a gigantic cathedral and fills it with razor blades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duke decides to have sexual intercourse with every tea kettle in Las Vegas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archduke buys a tiny crystal which lets him see every unicorn on earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman owns a fireplace that allows her to kill everyone in Reno at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university professor writes a PhD thesis about every storm that has taken place in the Roman Empire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bureaucrat in Nashville writes a book on how to write a poem about infinity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baroness causes anyone who sees her to think they are a meerkat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A historian is writing a list of people who will be saved: A bank manager, a sex worker and a soldier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New Zealand there is a firefly which is trapped inside a labyrinth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Assyrian archangel tells the story of an owl with supermarkets instead of eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a snowstorm in Seville. It snows monkeys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A parallelogram made of intelligence appears in Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A depressed president plays a game of tic-tac-toe with a moon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spice merchant buys a spell from a witch. It causes her to grow an extra brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Bangkok there is a dictionary that is made of scorpions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer programming is currently out of the office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seventy-seven nuns imagine a cinnamon roll into existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful man with scarlet eyes is hiding in a labyrinth. He is thinking about sycamore trees. A sea serpent is dancing behind him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tsarina owns an ice sculpture which depicts every crime in human history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pirate ship is elected mayor of Glasgow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a strip club in Delhi where books take their clothes off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mermaid hears of a church made of fine bone china, and wishes to smash it with sledgehammers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen falls into a pool filled with hearts. A porn star jumps in to save her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 11 o'clock miniature foxes roam the streets of Sydney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beauty therapist is climbing up the side of an enormous lily. But he will never get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By thinking of a copper coin, a cold-hearted baron is able to turn into a turtle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a clockwork wheat field there is a platinum motel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bald eagle lays an egg. Irony hatches from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Swiss king decrees that everyone must start brushing his teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are standing in a glass jungle. You can hear the faint sound of a flute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Portuguese nurse has set up a clinic for treating greed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Scientologist is crying. His tears are praying mantiss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rocket ship floats in front of you. Then a witch appears and says: "That rocket ship is my husband."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mongolian veterinarian sees a cloud in the shape of a ham sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At twilight Canada is flooded with soy milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sex worker proposes marriage to a crystal diamond ring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine eels are on a secret mission. Their aim is to steal a gigantic pearl from a zombie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chestnut tree appears before Emmeline Pankhurst. It says: "I really like enjoy masturbating."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A golden rollercoaster whispers to a professor of English literature: "I feel so gay."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A showgirl searches for a giant machine made of marble which allows her to destroy philosophy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ghost of an HR manager is roaming the streets of a small town in Colorado. It has come to swallow everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clerk is found dead in a locked room. Next to her is a whale and an evil zombie. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A necromancer finds a tiny crystal which lets him see every act of procrastination happening around the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A solicitor in Ohio flies to Tokyo on her lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An illustrious cook makes a smoothie out of mulberries, pears and ancient Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Iraqi queen is building a swimming pool that is filled with twilight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A solicitor is pruning a rose bush. Suddenly, the rose bush turns into a lasagne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Italian archivist spends eleven months writing a book about geese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Japanese math teacher writes a PhD thesis that is made out of molecular gastronomy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Moroccan congressman secretly leaves his palace at midnight to have sexual intercourse with psychoanalysis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pharmacist is checking Facebook inside a rainbow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nun finds an essay by Wittgenstein on the subject of slurpees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archangel hears of a maple tree that grows books and yearns to read them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen starts to build a replica of the Mall of America out of sexual fantasies, but runs out of sexual fantasies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By concentrating very hard on an ash tree, a Burmese congresswoman is able to create self-awareness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astrologer is murdered. The murderer is revealed to be Charlotte Bronte's Jane Eyre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess aims to write a poem about every wooden leg in Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Russian yacht sails across a lake of stained glass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A five-star hotel floats above Bengal. A viceroy looks up at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tsar marries the Sun. They have one child: A daughter who is made of clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astronaut invents a new kind of astrology based on the movement of mosquitoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A field marshal is writing a shopping list. It has four items: A pianist, a beehive, a sunflower and Princess Diana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Babylonian hacker sees a constellation in the shape of a beehive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A learned society of children devise a world where everything is acrobats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brazilian judge sentences an assassin to be devoured by a wizard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker in Quebec is famous for taking a photograph of dolphins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 15-year-old South African butler owns a telescope that lets him sense the presence of symmetry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By touching a bonsai tree, you can reach a parallel universe. It is made of the New York Times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An alchemist finds a 16th century book containing instructions for building a cathedral out of armies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Ukrainian mother hears an oboe that sounds like sorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An economist is poisoning Madonna's "Ray of Light" album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nihilistic sculptor falls into a lake filled with gerontophilia. Nobody notices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ancient Chinese peasant appears in an outlet mall in Ohio. She starts to cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A parallel universe made of thousands of years appears in Silicon Valley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 21-year-old screenwriter falls in love with irritable bowel syndrome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baroness owns a prism that allows her to have sexual intercourse with everyone in San Francisco at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clairvoyant turns over a tarot card with a willow pattern plate on it. 'Beware of player pianos,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duke owns a stained-glass window which depicts every magic trick since the dawn of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A child starts a company which sells memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You find out that you are a chocolate-covered cherry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kenyan physician hears of a temple located inside a planet, and becomes obsessed with finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight you will dream about telephones, business suits and an ice cube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Parisian scholar spends all his time writing an opera about dragons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an empress in Switzerland with a sea shell instead of a testicle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl finds out that a mattress is controlling America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Tibet there is an oak tree which is in love with a gold mine.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>