<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved today. Sunday’s are the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much at stake tomorrow at Restoration City.  Continuing our Sacred Trust series with a talk that could be a game changer for our city!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to face the day! https://t.co/u5SCRpA9YF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know what your prayers are saying about your heart? https://t.co/2xYtBsuhtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hey, that guy is so sarcastic and critical on Twitter that I would love to go to his church!”  #thingsnobodysays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religion condemns. Jesus frees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gossip is clearest way of announcing your bitterness and insecurity to others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we realize God’s never given up on us, it makes it hard to give up on others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_mcgee can't wait to have you @RCChurchDC in August!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: Defending your priorities and making everyone happy are mutually exclusive goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your calendar to defend your priorities, not to cater to everyone else's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Membership at Restoration City?  Join us for lunch this Sunday: https://t.co/YbsdvQpvmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith is willing to take the first step without knowing the second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church: A Community On Mission https://t.co/d8mNPYkBfV https://t.co/NEhyc4PdOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for tomorrow at Restoration City! Welcoming Maggie Konstanski from @WorldRelief! Great day to invite a friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders! These guys carry so much so well.  Love them! @ Lake Anna, Virginia https://t.co/XkM7Hoob8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“He himself bore our sins in his body on the tree, that we might die to sin and live to righteousness.” -1 Peter 2:24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending the next 36 hours with our Community Group &amp; Team Leaders. Can't wait! Love this team!!… https://t.co/QtDxXB0ekC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking Syrian Refugee Crisis This Sunday At Restoration City https://t.co/jY4J0lzROn https://t.co/1PULKBVfBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgiveness is the path to freedom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus calls and empowers us for a life of joyful service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can learn a lot about #leadership from the current turmoil @wmata: https://t.co/lX9dsnCSJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some places just make it easier to hear from God. @ Great Falls, Virginia https://t.co/p753wg3olB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents, are you teaching your kids a love for God's Word? https://t.co/u41bOnUcAx https://t.co/Pp92P74lid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constantly amazed by the ways God uses this girl! Genuine, loving and gracious...oh, and she did… https://t.co/Jp6ffT3AD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heroes! Sunday's wouldn't happen without this crew and their willingness to come early, stay… https://t.co/4oKZQUdJRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A godly Mom is a daily display of the sacrificial love of Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RCC is meeting in the Crystal City Marriott this morning - park where you normally do &amp; our Connect Team will help you from there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good! https://t.co/eBZ8dHLdpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A heartfelt “Jesus, help me” is one of the most effective prayers possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storms come. Jesus sustains. https://t.co/2vmNDLVNkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't have the joy of intimacy without the risk of vulnerability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We show grace in proportion to how much we understand the grace we've been shown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @welcomerefugee: Watch this compelling new short film from@WorldRelief - "Syria: The Search for Refuge."  https://t.co/SHDefdEjaf #World…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stellar day at Restoration City in so many ways!  Fired up by everything God is doing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer I'm a dad, the more I appreciate my father.  Thanks for setting the pace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You two. I love being your Dad! https://t.co/HZsLe9wUIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Community Group is hosting a huge yard sale this morning to benefit the Nicaragua team.… https://t.co/3TQ9RcDE1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn’t mater how well a vision is cast of its poorly executed! Get to work!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @jdgreear and the leadership, wisdom and humility he has shown at #SBC16.  He exemplifies unity and grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College Community Group. Tonight. 7.30PM. Greenberry's. 1805 E Street. https://t.co/Z4w7ObZGdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your Savior, not your circumstances, dictate your attitude today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_mcgee feel the same way about all God is doing through you in Brooklyn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for a hike with this crew! @ Great Falls, Virginia https://t.co/0xQAg6mNZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, July 10th, Restoration City will start gathering at Gunston Middle School! https://t.co/BPRA3pzke5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to have my friend @AllanMcC joining our team as a church planting resident starting July 1: https://t.co/9lLmdRUSpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City will be gathering in a new location and launching a church planting residency this summer: https://t.co/sXXj8Q6gy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Jesus, heal the brokenness of fear and hate with the power of Your love and grace. #PrayForOrlando]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT DIRECTIONS FOR GETTING TO RESTORATION CITY THIS MORNING!!! https://t.co/tTbnHRSbK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great (and hot!!) summer afternoon with RCC volunteers at Nats Park! Thanks for all you do to… https://t.co/8UNblWlwsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've gotta find a way to get to Restoration City this Sunday! It's just that simple! https://t.co/d84nHdMGqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel compels us to live for the glory of the King who died for us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you feel the need to tell others that  you are the leader is the moment you realize you aren't. #Leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for every Jesus follower shaping culture through politics, media, the arts and science.  Your work has value and God is for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For I, the Lord your God, hold your right hand; it is I who say to you, 'Fear not, I am the One who helps you.'" (Is. 41:13)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision inspires.  Vision + execution transforms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the gospel advances, all of society flourishes! @ Washington National Cathedral https://t.co/qajFONiOZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing room only at an RCCKids team meeting! Love this crew and their dedication to the next… https://t.co/jbPJ7U0Jlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the idea of a life defined by discipleship but not sure how to do it? Join us tomorrow at Restoration City!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started the day with a simple reminder of how grateful Laura &amp; I are that Restoration City is… https://t.co/TQRHDHp8Kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being against things is easy. It’s being for things that requires vision and courage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind of loving #snapchat.  Follow my story at johngmcgowan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty amazing collection of leaders for #Passion2017. https://t.co/slSuXlvw4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calendar issues are heart issues in disguise.  Clear heart = clear vision = clear priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup! https://t.co/nr7mFLQ7kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living for everyone's approval is an excellent way to end up with no one's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America needs the church far more than the church needs America: https://t.co/Z7GY1VcdAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad we devoted this morning at Restoration City to processing issues of race, justice and love.  Listen here: https://t.co/eTnxLSX1qH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headed to GUNSTON!! Huge day ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also loving the number of college students who gave up a Saturday to serve our partners at… https://t.co/4UChsiN3DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about #AltonSterling #PhilandroCastile &amp; #Dallas tomorrow at Restoration City.  Some convos are too complex for social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys have been serving our church all morning. So grateful for all they did to make our… https://t.co/BO1Uy0f04m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is talking about #AltonSterling #PhilandoCastile and #Dallas.  The church should as well: https://t.co/vhlA4glXW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I'm speaking on Dallas, Falcon Heights, Baton Rouge &amp; Romans 12 this Sunday at Restoration City: https://t.co/BwNFewCyoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!  Speak up &amp; Seek God. https://t.co/M3P4vwpQdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy doesn’t guarantee productive. Focus on what matters and move the ball forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian, the world desperately needs the hope you're afraid to share. https://t.co/U7iYb2v2lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask for President Kanyatta to bring justice for Willie, Josephat and Joseph and #JusticeinKenya https://t.co/guujb8pZ5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If ye loved Christ better ye would love all Christ’s church, and all Christ’s people. - Spurgeon. #sameteam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I pray that the church in these days may have a more loving spirit towards herself.” -Spurgeon. Disunity dishonors Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Grace alone is the way into the Christian life and the way forward in the Christian life." -@jamesmarshallg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City, we all have a role to play in welcoming our 1st church planting resident, Allan &amp; Kim McCullough. https://t.co/AUGQzKQIUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No better way to end our time at the Synetic than seeing people cross from death to life! Thank you, Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Sunday gathering in the Synetic. Going out with a bang!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronbrum @drmoore if he's wrong, it's because of exegesis, not philosophy.  But I happen to agree with his handling of the text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful post from @drmoore on applying 2 Chronicles 7:14 correctly: https://t.co/8ePX3616a6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're 18-25, don't miss #Passion2017.  Can't say enough about how God uses these gatherings. Register today: https://t.co/lQqzmDtjTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for @IJM friends mourning the loss of colleagues in Kenya. May God give comfort, resolve and peace. https://t.co/dDFDj2GHrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's calling is accompanied by God's power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, @louiegiglio.  So grateful for your life, friendship and leadership!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT @KenyaembassyDC: @IJM lawyer &amp; two others abducted in Nairobi. Please help us find them. https://t.co/IJS09aLrnt #JusticeinKenya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came out of our room wearing a suit:

Laura, “Jack, doesn’t daddy look good?”

Jack, “Wow! You look just like a penguin!”
#needtodressupmore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunston's a great facility.  Asking God to do great things through us as we start gathering there on July 10th. https://t.co/8SmrAlxe9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about being impressive.  Faithful and helpful will get you much further.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer in the city! @ Georgetown Waterfront Park https://t.co/yi1kYIvqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scripture never lies to you. Emotions frequently do. Trust God’s Word over your feelings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really believe tomorrow at Restoration City will be a roadmap not just for a new location but… https://t.co/bIQjRIuMeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willing to help us as we move to Gunston on July 10th? Would love to have you serve with us: https://t.co/nAEA2QwNwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half-hearted living comes from half-hearted devotion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Jesus Christ is the same yesterday and today and forever."(Heb.13:8).  Increasingly good news in our chaotic world.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>