<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 325: INTENSIVE FARMING IS THE GREATEST CAUSE OF SUFFERING ON EARTH – DISCUSS  http://t.co/a3457XSb0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 323: DOES VEGETARIANISM MATTER? SOME VAGUELY INSULTING Q&amp;A HERE: http://t.co/aw6WBvR4zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 319: HOW DO I SAVE FARM ANIMALS? THOUGHTS PLEASE! http://t.co/emNrBV0w6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 321: ON A MARCH AGAIN - who would have thought - with @ciwf. read more here http://t.co/iJKJbJjp4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myLaurenHansen thanks lauren! let me know if the week might be interested in a story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseWills3 thats great. so glad you like it. woof woof from moose!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmSanctuary Hi. I'm writing a blog about saving animals, currently looking into farms. any advice? http://t.co/ONjiVQb7EK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just off to hang out with happy pigs on small farm- want to see what real cared-for pigs are like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LouiseWills3: @MartinUsborne Just bought 'My Name is Moose' - Love it! Adorable!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 316: WILD ANIMALS IN A SILENT ROOM – PHOTOS OF ILLEGAL CONTRABAND  More here - http://t.co/j5XQ4Gihnz http://t.co/hiGzmIe7fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just contributed to this great video project on stray dogs http://t.co/Hyf52a0Cay #indiegogo via @indiegogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please watch this video and check out the lost dogs project on crowdfunding website @Indiegogo http://t.co/ehRl7g5FAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 315: HOW I ACCIDENTALLY GAVE MONEY TO A CRIMINAL TAXIDERMIST more here: http://t.co/U2pWKNXf1e http://t.co/3PRUV0Nc3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 313: DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH IVORY COMES THROUGH LONDON? I VISIT A SECRET POLICE HAUL IN LONDON http://t.co/HRp2QLrJvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SHADOWWABBITS8 the grey one!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 311: I CHAT TO ONE OF THE WORLD’S PANGOLIN EXPERTS – WHERE DO WE GO FROM HERE? http://t.co/MokrkC2ZTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two not-so-wild animals. Moose and bug sleep on each other’s faces. Nice to be back with the … http://t.co/1pgYdFDoeR http://t.co/9L5bP1eIDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 308: BACK IN THE UK AND FOX WALKS INTO OUR HOUSE http://t.co/1pgYdFDoeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithHayley woof woof!!! Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just going to pick up Mango - the dog who was rescued from Philippines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: new website is officially live!! first person to place order gets a prize - a secret one but promise it will be good! …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegentleauthor 24 hrs left to kickstart @hoxtonminipress: collectable east London books http://t.co/cLzgdETQQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance copies of the East London books look gorgeous http://t.co/gfiObMeYfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 hours left to pledge! Artist books about East London http://t.co/cLzgdETQQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thepongobongo: #welovecrowdfunding Londres a través de los ojos de un anciano de 86 años http://t.co/g5vhpE3WlA   @MartinUsborne @kicks…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch a man watching the film 'earthlings' http://t.co/1QPU3FDksw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHoughton8 thanks Max!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @small_epic: Can’t wait to receive the first books from @martinusborne’s publishing project, Hoxton Mini Press: http://t.co/2qSrKKcw97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeanP thank you, not easy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As my year to help ends I'm starting a small art publishing company about East London. 5 days left to buy a book! http://t.co/cLzgdETQQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: Only 12 days left in our #kickstarter campaign. http://t.co/ftYpoAPREk Pledge while you still can! #eastlondon #hackne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 368 – DARK NIGHTS HUNTING BADGER HUNTERS http://t.co/adE7VZ7VC5 #stopthecull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Usborne Photography - Spring 2013 news - http://t.co/5VqBZIvtLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 362: VIDEO: STRANGE FEELINGS ON EXITING A SLAUGHTERHOUSE http://t.co/16MrMVpkVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciwf Going undercover in a spanish slaughterhouse (part 2). Still no photos! http://t.co/UafSyeQvm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 361: UNDERCOVER IN A SPANISH SLAUGHTERHOUSE (part 2) Still no photos! http://t.co/UafSyeQvm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ciwf: Excellent work @martinusborne – thank you for raising awareness for #animalwelfare and #pigs especially in #Spain #factoryfarming…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StyleTails: INTERVIEW | We get some serious advice on following your passions from @MartinUsborne - photographer &amp; animal lover http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LumleyNews Hi, I took your portrait for CIWF. Just made a video going undercover in spanish pig farms. Please RT, http://t.co/07yn6TBIbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops @ciwf I went undercover into a spanish pig farm....watch me here http://t.co/07yn6TBIbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 351: A CLOSE CALL AT PSYCHO FARM http://t.co/kAg8keYlJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: woohoo! thanks @kickstarter for making us project of the day!! http://t.co/CxTkWXYCKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: The sun is shining in east london and our #kickstarter has launched!! http://t.co/ftYpoAPREk #mondaysaintsobad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bimal_tailor Hi. Thanks for getting in touch and buying a book! Which one did you buy? have printed different books in several places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: excited to launch @kickstarter campaign tomorrow!!! Anyone seen a flower mkt shopper today? #columbiaroad http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick1974 you write about such rubbish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelstaffcom off to Spain to do a book on hunting dogs and started a photo publishing company.. Can I DM? Question..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriSethCohen: @MartinUsborne can't wait to purchase your book on Joseph Markovitch !
#advancedstyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenePiroltPhoto thanks so much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannynorthphoto thanks for the thumbs up! Have you checked out our new photo book publishing company? @hoxtonminipress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelstaffcom great to hear from you! How are dogs on heath?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: #FreeBookFriday! RT &amp; send us pic of a real life character from Adam Dant's 50 People of #EastLondon book for chance t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CornwallsVoice thank you so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccauleyphotos yes, totally fine, thanks so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertElms Glad you mentioned the old man in East London book. Very happy to come in to the show to discuss! He's one of a kind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CornwallsVoice: @MartinUsborne Sharing your blog far and wide = with huge thanks for all that you are doing in this year to help !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriSethCohen thanks!!! Saw your order from @HoxtonMiniPress come through today. Will get that out to you on Monday. Hope you enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Burrows1984 @thegentleauthor thanks for the kind words!!! Pls follow @HoxtonMiniPress as well for info on our upcoming titles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccauleyphotos yes. Thanks for checking!! Great to hear you like the story. Pls follow @HoxtonMiniPress as well for info on our next books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eyefarrell thanks! You can get a copy of the book here: http://t.co/QQKn2Fw4Un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: Use my Uber promo code, bfjwx, and get £20 off your first Uber ride. Redeem it at http://t.co/Sy54KyN1bK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This touching picture just emerged. Joseph markovitch aged 16, in 1943 http://t.co/InNuxtaegU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: Which title do you prefer for our next photography book? Suggestions please!! http://t.co/oaxJilQLeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbneighbourhood: this book always seems to put a smile on my face. @HoxtonMiniPress http://t.co/uJ0z0NkJzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: excited to see photographer Madeleine Waller today to go over final image selection &amp; layout of our next book! http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleB315 working on some new projects this year and hope to exhibit dogs in cars in Europe as well - details to come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @fionaalcampbell ! Happy new year. How are things?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edebonneval @hackneycitizen thanks for the great article on @HoxtonMiniPress !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edebonneval: I’ve lived in East London for 86 1/2 Years– interview with author @MartinUsborne http://t.co/yIR7qF6o70 via @hackneycitize…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegentleauthor Joseph Markovitch has passed away. Thank you to all who read his wonderful words. http://t.co/RG71DOLMta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph Markovitch, Jan 1st 1927 - Dec 26th 2013. A dear friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeleVdb sorry for delay. Will reply by email now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed copies of 'The Silence of Dogs in Cars' and other titles available again for purchase on http://t.co/WJ9UDhoQt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: On the hunt for pics of our books on display in central london shops. First person to send us one gets free book! Pls …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: Christmas offers just added to our website. http://t.co/qQh961jv6W spread the word! http://t.co/3uWCpsnp66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: Hoxton Mini Press is now on facebook. Please like us here! https://t.co/ZTfy36DKbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcreedy I'm sure!! It's only that we've never lived there! We have to start with what we know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales in NYC going great. Thanks Lee Marks. Love being back here http://t.co/909KKNbsSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to NYC to try and sell some photos at AIPAD. Those bagels are expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My book about the old man of East London now back in stock! http://t.co/mma2vwju8V #hoxtonminipress http://t.co/v9XtcwOPju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlotteReed glad you like book. Thanks for mention. Working on new book about abandoned Spanish hunting dogs #galgos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: If you missed @MartinUsborne on the @RobertElms show you can listen to it here http://t.co/NbIUBgTliY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheHoxtonHotel: Meet The Photographer We catch some words with photographer @MartinUsborne ahead of the @HoxtonMiniPress event http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just flew across london in this air ambulance chopper. For a shoot not accident. Smoggy views http://t.co/RgQqixohOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solo show opening in Paris tonight. Hoping it's well hung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New solo show being hung in Paris . Opening tomorrow #tagomagogallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Usborne Photography - Spring 2013 news - http://t.co/v40XZHo8B7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solo show opens in Paris tomorrw 1 April. NOT A JOKE. 6pm TagoMago gallery, 4 Villa Ballu Paris. Till 30th May http://t.co/FPswVhgaXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eastlondonlines: Great to hear @HoxtonMiniPress on @BBCRadio1 this morning! Read our interview with @MartinUsborne here: http://t.co/TX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikewaldvogel thank you Michael! Glad you heard it and see you in the summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luisaturquoise thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got on train to Paris and the mag has 5 page spread on our new swimmers book! @HoxtonMiniPress http://t.co/bn6Sxzk8e5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on BBC radio on @RobertElms talking about my photobook with @HoxtonMiniPress 94.9fm 11.40am - 11:55am http://t.co/gZqzRwwUQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: listen out for @MartinUsborne on @BBCLondon949 with @RobertElms tomorrow 11:40am talking #josephmarkovitch &amp; #hoxtonmi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ravcyp so sorry about that. We've had loads of problems with the site but it should be all fixed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xu_liz hi can you email us please? Studio @ martinusborne . Com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @storasade: This book is so heartbreakingly beautiful! Can't recommend it enough. &lt;3 @HoxtonMiniPress @MartinUsborne http://t.co/3a2fEBP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Galgo rescued from hanging. Will make full recovery #thisdogshitreallygettingmedown http://t.co/OihhlLCVmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Spanish hotel food for veggies http://t.co/VNelipX026]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>