<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MCRSanta Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maaddieclaark Hi Maddie, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinnyBlazin Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your video. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldRowSwig Hi, I'm a journalist an @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with the person who shot the clip. Can you help? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chewedxup Hi Marcus, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM pls? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BartoshSmith Hi Ashley, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch with you. Could you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoggieDoc83 Hi Andy, I'd like to contact you about your wonder Woman vid. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_brookethegreat @Jaelthegreat Hi Brooke, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnPittem @fcrugbytown Hi John, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasminnie98 @JohnStamos Hi Jasmine, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlestar1208 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks and stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vdalovda Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks and stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kellykavanaghxo @spin1038 Hi Kelly, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixBelle_ @MetEireann Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@balihaaree @AlJazeera @unitedsikhs Hi Balpreet, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crayhargrave Hi Chris, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your clay pigeon golf shot.Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitness_mua @TheEllenShow Hi Emily, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAStoinev @andylassner @TheEllenShow Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dj_Odyssey_ @JordanPeele Hi Jay, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alber_toar ¡Hola! Soy periodista a @newsflare. ¿Este es tu video? ¿Podemos utilizarlo en nuestra plataforma para nuestros clientes internacionales? https://t.co/5qdxkucp6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDanLevy @deadmau5 @rebel_toronto @RickandMorty Hi Dan, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phamd89 @deadmau5 @rebel_toronto Hi David, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanpowerlifts @deadmau5 Hi Shan, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hartmand45 Hi Daniel, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can DM? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawkirsten Hi Kirsten, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackesnombre @WKRG Hi Jack, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseGracerys Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ptvlinds Hi Lindsay, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BehindTheLine24 Hi. I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hdowsett @Rock_City_Notts @NeckDeepUK Hi Hannah, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM pls? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lidiaxanna @NeckDeepUK Hi Lidia, I'm a journalist at @newsflare. Can you follow me so I can send a DM about your video please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burningphoenixr Hi Sofia, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSukkarieh @TheMoscowSlip Hi Sarina, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_sarinas Hi Sarina, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YasminVal_ @LoyleCarner Hi Yasmin, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_samuelnelson @LoyleCarner Hi Nelson, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HebbJack Hi Jack, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM pls?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clodeineee Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use your footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline and https://t.co/oyvj3TkiX8 video player, apps and social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our terms here: https://t.co/MvsGrpeRLy and reply to confirm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarthsWays Hi, do you happen to have any video footage of the snow rollers? I'm with @MailOnline Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arnoutvos @MailOnline Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arnoutvos Hi Arnout, I work @MailOnline Can we use your footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our terms in the attached image and reply to confirm. https://t.co/UYVMBI56ZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wifibananas Ok, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wifibananas I work at the Mail Online and we'd like to speak with the person who shot the video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wifibananas Hi, did you film this video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaGato4boys Hi Kerry, I hope your son was ok! I work for @mailonline and I'd like to have a chat about the clip. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FotograafPeter Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use your footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our terms in the attached image and reply to confirm. https://t.co/lawTtWjNG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garydoc777 @MailOnline Thanks Gary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garydoc777 Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use your footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our terms in the attached image and reply to confirm. https://t.co/8TwoAZDyAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronHJones Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use the footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our T&amp;C’s here: https://t.co/TNK4U2wIlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ajohns2130 @MailOnline Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@praizekirkwood Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use the footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our T&amp;C’s here: https://t.co/TNK4U2wIlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ajohns2130 Hi, I work @MailOnline Can we use the footage &amp; screen grabs in the MailOnline video player on the MailOnline website, apps and MailOnline social accounts? We will fully credit back to this video. Please find our T&amp;C’s here: https://t.co/TNK4U2wIlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam28691 Hi Adam, I work at Newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@averyarmour @hqtrivia @ScottRogowsky @L_M_A_Y @megmk Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Just_Becs @Target Hi Becky, I work at Newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincebarber87 @TheEllenShow Adorabe! Hi Vince, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with your video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gsinclair28 @chalmersalloa Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MkhizeThando @Radio702 @eNCA Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinyue_ Hi, I work at @Newsflare and I;d like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Drunken_Gamer Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@violetgonda @easyJet Hi Violet, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with the video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJRosaOfficial @Ryanair Hi JJ, I'm with @newsflare and we're interested in working with your footage. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatDontIGot Hi Nicola, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbeykrysiak1 @weatherchannel Hi Abbey, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuisBrooo Hi Luis, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your Travis Scott video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben_RA Hi Ben, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with your video. Can you follow me so I can send you a direct message please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireHastings1 Hi Claire, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpenPatel Hi Akshay, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bast_shiva Hola, estoy periodista a @newsflare y quiero que hablar contigo acerca de este video. Puedes seguir me para que puedo enviar un mensaje? Gracias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_niks Hi Nix, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbywomackhbf @amazon @MariahCarey @wafanasieff Hi Bobby, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielap526 Hi Daniela, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben_RA Hi Ben, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about the video of your grandmother you posted on YouTube. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slukas Hi Steve, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimRichardson9 @skigrahambell @skieurope1 @TheSkiClub @BBCNews @BBCWiltshire Hi Tim, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shanawashere1 Hi Shana, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liz_VanMeter Adorable! I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philmackie @DaveThroupEA @dharford79 Hi Phil, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cameo Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your package thief video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizmurdock Hi Liz, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with your video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LachlanVe Hi Lachlan, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your videos of the Melbourne incident. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonydandrea1 @Newsflare @andrealebowski @CavanThomas Where am I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rosstugcapt @JudithRalston @SeanBattySTV @Newsflare I can't send a direct message until you follow me or send me a Dm yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rosstugcapt @JudithRalston @SeanBattySTV Hi Ross, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scrilla100 @AmericanAir Hi Scott, I work for @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonydandrea1 That's not a very good score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan_pintor @SCVSignal Hi I work for @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heres_happyness Hi I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amollenbeckKFI Hi, I work at @newsflareand I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fijean @Newsflare D'accord. Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fijean Bonjour, je travaille chez @newsflare et ns aimerions contacter la personne qui a filmé cette vidéo. La connaissez-vous? Avez-vous filmé la scène? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntonioKuilan Hi Antonio, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about one of the videos you uploaded to YouTube. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkepticalZack Hi Zach, I work at @newsflare and I'm trying to contact you about one of your videos. Can you follow me so I can send DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sessionar08 @TWOweather @GavinPartridge Hi Lee, I'm with @newsflare and we'd like to work with your video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uhlisssuhh Hi Aly, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with your video. can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eskzul Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malloriesullivn Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about video. Can we talk via DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Teeduma Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattJ777 Hi Matt, I'm with @mailonline, do you happen to have video footage of the moose watching the Olympics by any chance? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@b1g5te @zabbajojo @MailOnline Great, thank you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>