<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: .@POTUS on Donald Trump: "This guy's gonna be your champion? He wasn't going to let you on his golf course." https://t.co/lAA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshMarvine: "The iPhone doesn't have a headphone jack but the Galaxy literally explodes" is a perfect metaphor for this election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Surveys https://t.co/ZnS3vlw4yZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to listen to family and friends opinions on your designs... https://t.co/c9VsIi5dkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinkaGuides Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalwinaWisniews Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrbasagoiti Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickMotown: Weather forecasters. Stop editorialising rain as "horrible" and unbearably hot weather as "lovely". Just relay the data and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guide to understanding how to use website page data such as page views, bounce rate, and average time on page.  https://t.co/ycXkKlEEf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarlowNYC: Here's the disgusting audio of Trump on 9/11 bragging about how his building is now the tallest in Lower Manhattan: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ratmiley: The music industry will head into a very dark place if points like the ones made here are not addressed. https://t.co/iN3ThBB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoneEmett Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Attention Ratio? Landing Pages 101 https://t.co/NEafPC8Ar4 (useful rule)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheUXList: How To Design Ecommerce Sites https://t.co/SeyalP1LJE #UX #TheUXList]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly just wanted to be a world leader. Not the dull work of actually representing constituents. https://t.co/0y9hss4M3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charlesarthur: Interesting thread. https://t.co/gRX0Qnx3md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New Rules of Form Design https://t.co/9OB0TMo96J – handy guidelines/advice https://t.co/MWtxZJAMwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BenedictEvans: Self-Driving Cars Can Learn a Lot by Playing Grand Theft Auto &lt;- I can't imagine how this could go wrong  https://t.co/l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interface looks interesting, would have loved to play with it... The First Virtual Reality Store Launched by eBay https://t.co/44rp2q8qDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealTrumpatine: During a campaign on Endor, Princess Leia completely collapsed! Why does biased media not discuss her health/stamina ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theuxcrunch Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidschneider: NHS on verge of collapse? Luckily it's going to get £350m a week like it said on that bus. Oh. https://t.co/NC9BsqzIzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BritLGBTAwards Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperBettingBro Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validate and Launch a Brand New 5-Figure Infoproduct https://t.co/aUiSBtyDip (good mailing list launching tips)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Users Want the Same E-Com Experiences as Their Western Counterparts https://t.co/1ehWVRHFdG https://t.co/hIdeZJcl0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrendanNyhan: .@michael_hendrix on humans vs. algorithms https://t.co/JVziFU5x34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always enjoy @BBCTrustMe – taking popular food/health trends and testing how valid or nonsense they are. Great use of the BBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neebone @alushtom A now they can own the priciest wireless Beats by Apple pair too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SEMinds Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neebone Yep, that's the real thing they should be fixing. Every time you hear leaking tunes the person is wearing white earphones...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketeeringIM Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cool that they're wireless but have Apple made earphones that don't leak sound to the rest of the bus/train?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mcgourty22N: Lady just asked me what "mansplaining" is. I think it's a trap. We've been staring at each other in silence for half an ho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BenedictEvans: IPhone 7+ camera: depth. 3D capture. Object capture. VR. Possibly live VR streaming. 

Non-trivial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water resistance basically means you've run out of meaningful features doesn't it? #AppleEvent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth considering if you need 'Price Per Unit' on your ecommerce site https://t.co/NfPAXm1PcT https://t.co/XMQRi4ZnTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GA_London: Learn how to use analytical tools to make data driven design decisions @ishmatt &gt;&gt; https://t.co/7WDZKFRhxa https://t.co/nnKi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's legit btw, from an actual site I'm registered with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting tactic. So smoothly done too. https://t.co/zCl3JA3wSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done. Alternative on Dean Saunders and Brian Clough – a story that went viral but doesn’t finish there https://t.co/EQLBqu3cdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edbott: This is a poster child for false-equivalence "journalism." https://t.co/uDHn42kR7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting, on the success of subscription retail and the move to receiving monthly boxes https://t.co/vZe0osbDNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomorrowLab Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveavery Thanks for signing up! And good spot with the typo, have just fixed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book on the way... How To Design Ecommerce Sites https://t.co/2MYJfpiJWS #ux https://t.co/cL6l383Lpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workdotlife Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How it feels to be given an Olympic gold medal ... nine years later at a Burger King https://t.co/mS20Imqqfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCurrencyBlog Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoachimDeVos Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @astroehlein: I know facts don't matter anymore, but still, for nostalgia's sake... https://t.co/81ErGEItpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, the Internet Has Not Killed the Printed Book. Most People Still Prefer Them. https://t.co/VxasS5a9RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several worthwhile tips in here... The 31 Worst Ecommerce Mistakes You Can Commit https://t.co/41ywvNAq8x https://t.co/3FER8emGcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBistronomy Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to record user visits to your website, to watch back later https://t.co/kwc2JCRk8W https://t.co/RlYQhyPIhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingTomorrow Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gatosg: “We’re F*cked, It’s Over. Or Is It?” by @michalis_gk https://t.co/rKDC2UCn4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raselkhantaj Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing for interfaces. Keep it short: https://t.co/Lb32fYih4k https://t.co/ECvSfcyAST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uxdxconf Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephenkb: Fascinating thread. https://t.co/O6h1OS5N7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Practices in Virtual Reality (some useful thinking) https://t.co/6PVUGRZ0EP https://t.co/RqRWNuFMEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveavery @danbarker I guess you'd have to consider that with the placement of them! But wonder if repeated presses are ignored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveavery Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May is more popular [than Corbyn] in every age category.  Even with the youngest 18-24 group. https://t.co/oi1O8PUKYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @annadahlstrom: "75% of users make judgments about a company’s credibility based on the visual design of its website" https://t.co/azz75…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheMediaTweets: "It's happening Maureen! It's happening! Get into the panic room. Bring the Royal Doulton with you!" https://t.co/vHa4T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great history on the dinosaurs of Crystal Palace, one of my fave things in London https://t.co/dry8VloTgX https://t.co/tumDn6B55w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GA_London: Learn about the core rules &amp; best practices of UX design for ecommerce sites w @ishmatt &gt;&gt; https://t.co/ISkqDbF1XA https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understand data from your webpages with The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide https://t.co/HjMDFLZP5r https://t.co/wTKSbylULw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Birbiglia’s 6 Tips for Making It Small in Hollywood. Or Anywhere. https://t.co/gAMG6sMXqx this is nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream big Britain, dream big. https://t.co/4Sxx4bFNlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charlesarthur: Corbyn’s digital proposals are nonsense - either here already, or impossible, or beyond public sector scope. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstonShaw Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alushtom Ha – dropdown fields for everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danbarker: Amazon Dash buttons have officially launched in the UK. They're available here: https://t.co/kl4BHuSshj https://t.co/atk6KUH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WPOneClick Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@union_building Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obvious but worth remembering: Minimize Design Risk by Focusing on Outcomes not Features https://t.co/dmtemQhkY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HypeMarketingHQ Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@socialkash Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dunmoreorless: SKY SPORTS HAVE JUST INCLUDED 'BRAVERY' AS A STAT TO COMPARE WILSHERE TO RAMSEY. THIS IS NOT A DRILL. https://t.co/Tivyy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reductress Became the Most Brutally Truthful Comedy Site Out There https://t.co/htCpN7xLTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danbarker: "Under pressure":
278,630 shops in the UK.
2 per week = 18 enquiries since EU ref.
= 0.0065% of shops. https://t.co/X8iK8PXf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Detectives Who Never Forget a Face https://t.co/NPEdnTNp1i (or when people beat machines)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched @louistheroux's Scientology Movie and Q&amp;A. Very funny and Louis deals with their responses perfectly. Black Mirror-esque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalphCapocci Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson Yeah it nails it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BargibleApp Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slashmyfees Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret life of (the other type of) startup employee: it’s like being a firefighter led by an arsonist  https://t.co/L4QtSzTo7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamuelMarcLowe: This point on transparency by @DavidAllenGreen is key. 'We can't show them our hand' is nothing more than a smokescreen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Sense of Modern Pornography https://t.co/ozA6ws4GHX (and why no one can say if it's 'good' or 'bad' for us)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Otto_English: Modern politics summed up in a tweet. https://t.co/M1MicqcQCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StigAbell: Love lift us up where we belong.
Where the eagles cry
On a mountain high. https://t.co/lWmuzngw9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New E-Commerce Checkout Research – Why 68% of Users Abandon Their Cart https://t.co/ODvNQOVoEH https://t.co/NOkqg5LQEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_lefleur Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to pretend you’re a great designer (aka the traps many designers fall into) https://t.co/RV8f2RHbUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulmasonnews: "Government bans foreign _________" fill in the space and that's Conservative politics from now until 2020. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers Confront an Epidemic of Loneliness https://t.co/0hW5ABPU7r &lt; Good stuff on how the UK is tackling it in old age https://t.co/Q0goKrYqfx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>