<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/ZwaXt3y5lG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/6zI5QiWTG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/T6bCQXL4fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/3xgOmITLBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/yLZcmIjWme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/MRSYPEj3Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/BCCwVWsw05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/i22eI7uNxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/aPtK95LN9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/QFsHcVKYtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/NH5bDeoByZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/jlX0QZAD8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/2bhYZU40Jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/A1yB4SANsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/rcuVxUFso0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/9pnX60a7jZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/BlYXmP6yzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/pcYANydnz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/30foLONlpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/6CWZHrFGxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/tAIeOP17Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/7SQvqi65lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/YQhl5MPAbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/g3n6s5AL7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/4Fo3XXxiYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/Px9RyD697p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/HHI3PRJce8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/CDLisRiUvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/vb6BHS9QvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/xCB3T9RCp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/ZegABqKxry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/30lLn2CHDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/H0IhzDCrRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/NFjJ6n0zTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/x9eZgSCXoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/OFc5iEmXOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/1RTFlizRjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/3td4b9ABBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/GXZxodyTyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/01rFj6sN8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/8gZ0QHaAPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/IW8edLhnIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/Emv5LZ3Dyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/ELfzdG4I0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/Q7lmqJiwo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/BMfu2riekW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/WFt1IdJ344]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/9wsEBha2wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>