<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/SbCL8BX0iF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/AOBCytu5GI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got rock 'n' roll in my blood. - William Shatner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/Im0Dc4o7sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/Axe8WrnFJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/E0pg6D4DgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/3l1z6oqvsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/VHRXNBLdrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/vDAIpsEP74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/NXmSbv6GEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/S36LeBcDSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/dNADhU3o0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to http://t.co/QQVYKF0GLM  http://t.co/6KhnlFkmQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/GysSNwVTS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/EJh6TmlPP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/s7j6LOiz4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/Sudi6jfDqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/RFZXZEMUvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/MG6hOPgoOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/r8dYsaZ95T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/rJYJ02zCor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/z3671JfMmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/JguBAt0fso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/UQvzmwPcn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/vbacsNAIfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/Ep78dMxoqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/Jtg7kEmqxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/U6oF0CCiYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/RpMe6mL7my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/ZWiZz9Gacr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/79OKUuXTeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/udwq39ZIx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/ZOVo97bjEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/SmaH9aVF5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/GjxJgBlDM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/FLyeDRuFcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/NH6ufdj3qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/I6qPip3sHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/wxuaEbpuxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/QUazw4AoEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/li3GfcTCL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/G0gSfVdFYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/xkZo3iidpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/aSyLvCCVjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/DLE2PTjpVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/t5b5XkUdra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/29aKdlDF82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/RGi4z9aZaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/2eOqmaoq8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/O8D0aEAa8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/QaeJxjYodu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/0S4Ow7469Q]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>