<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Connolly shooting from that line ball with 2 minutes to go is a joke why not let your free taker take it if your gona shoot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne that's not even me in that pic who's that your with ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne can't remember bud what was that night again ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne yeah right your nannys do be straight into the pockets ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne I thought you could cook no ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne I'll say what I want you ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love them people on snapchat and insta that are always eating healthy and training makes it that little bit easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See that fucking beans ad where they're slapping the can are they winding me up if I done that I be left with 3 and half fingers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to starting training with someone next week all you can do is focus on yourself the rest will look after itself ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 the year your not allowed go on a debs without a fake Hermes belt on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkI35E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gaymore11: When my ma comes of age theres no even debate, she's going into a  home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interviews for JD must be like.. 
"So tell us about yourself"
"Well gaz from Geordie shore is my idol" 
"So when can you start"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne fuck off will you ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lee_steacy fucking crazy it is ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ we be better off going up to SBG and throwing cash at John Kavanagh like everyone else ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lee_steacy stop pal fella is from D12 mixing it with the likes of drake and ronaldo it's a joke ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McGregor is gona look back on all these great pics in a few year and say "why the fuck did I wear them poxy glasses" https://t.co/7MOUhWe92p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No good coming from not being able to sleep head is all over the place ðŸ’­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United fans the worst people in the world to watch a game with you haven't played since you were u13 for the Bosco give it a rest mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday ðŸŽ‰ @EricaMorgan__]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been to the gym every day this week. There's no better feeling than being motivated ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dundalk ðŸ‘ðŸ½ðŸ‘ðŸ½ðŸ‘ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSlattery7 very funny aren't you  ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rowemance96 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSlattery7 fuck off your winding me up ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSlattery7 don't think they'd be open now tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorfoley18 ah fuck sake thought you were gona tell us somewhere around sold them ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorfoley18 haven't seen them ones anywhere where you pick them up ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/fCx7MxXzZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyG_ how would you know what social media is like ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeNorton95 thanks ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please tell me where sells the new fulfil bars that's open now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyG_ lethal they are ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne @_fllwrs who ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Them new mint chocolate fulfil bars ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ they might aswell just get rid of all the other flavours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can just imagine this fella sitting at home texting himself off his ma's phone with his number saved as Wayne Rooney https://t.co/2Q4n1kBHx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne only means one thing, home alone is on in Jim's gaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@figow11 @Jamie__Dunne @PhillyG_ https://t.co/F1xiexGA4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@figow11 @Jamie__Dunne @PhillyG_ ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday mate hope you have good one ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½ @PhilKavanagh_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GantleyMannix deadly pic bro ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell Bellew he's not in the UFC ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acampbell68 @Edwina_Currie @Thatcherite4 @SeanyLawson @_Lar11_ ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyTaaffe say nothing lad it'll be a surprise hashtag sly insta pic ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here lads can we just skip Halloween and lash the Christmas lights up in grafton street ðŸŽ…ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @GZambra_92 @Owen85Weston2 @_Lar11_ ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoastMySeIfie @SeanyLawson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How crazy is it that our own thoughts can do the most damage to us #WorldMentalHealthDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyTaaffe @Jamie__Dunne ðŸ˜»ðŸ˜»ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["O'Dowda coming on for Ireland" https://t.co/X2YW3SuRqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @_Lar11_ @Owen85Weston2 @GZambra_92 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne roll on Father's Day bro ðŸº]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say Five Guys is decent and all but why does it look like someone sits on the burgers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day in Ibiza smashed uppppp what a trip ðŸ˜ˆ https://t.co/dlHdSrOSDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The little bro ðŸ» https://t.co/W37PzzZ47H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has just made my day seeing this what a bloke ðŸ‘ðŸ½ https://t.co/zW7R3I4fjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobCourtney3 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ like watching the CCTV footage on crimecall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking hell snapchat videos on Samsung are that slow I just clicked onto someone's story and the World Cup final 2014 was on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekRyan80 nice one mate I'll have a look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know any good websites or shops to get decent protein?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ tell me about chief break your heart it would]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday and I'm not in the humour of a Dominos talk about having a bad day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaffeLeanne your a bit late bud could of done with that a bit earlier ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tyson_Fury: #Tysonmontana https://t.co/ccaTHpVuRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samcaswell33 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ it's all about winning ball who has most possessions on the Dublin team? we'll say no more https://t.co/8wS5ygXuBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samcaswell33 Dublins best player all year and your giving him shite Ye haven't a clue ðŸ‘‹ðŸ½ðŸ‘‹ðŸ½ðŸ‘‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person in Dublin not out tonight right here. Championship 1/4 final tomorrow tho ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmangan991: Match of the day haha https://t.co/yyCfNSovUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ "that's me done for a while now" yeah mate to save up to buy your next outfit to wear in 8 weeks ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ couldn't of said it better. Look great on a night out but your sittin in watching the X factor with ur owlone for the next 3 weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick of Instagram people act like they've more money and more exciting lives than they actually have. They only post what they want u to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthy eating? Nah mate haven't heard that saying in years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The double champ does what the fuck he wants" must of watched that video about 100 times today McGregor is the ðŸ end of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criscyborg @kayleigh_787 @ShannonSharpe @CWayneBull @RealSkipBayless @arielhelwani @Jamie__Dunne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing Paddy Pimblett can scrap cause he would defo be bullied with a wig like that if he couldn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still not over that John Lewis ad after breaking me heart waiting around all year for that shite ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GantleyMannix ðŸ’™ðŸ’™ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to this legend @GantleyMannix enjoy your day bro ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½ https://t.co/lVqkm1t1mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSlattery7 do you ever stop ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't be arsed tbh not coming back on here for the day ðŸ‘‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing nothing but bad news lately but they're the things that make us realise how lucky we are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ @ballsdotie chief @samcaswell33 makes this pass to me on the regular and he is shite they'd wanna give it a rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rowemance96 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the angel card done it for me, straight into the box with that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rowemance96: @LeeColeman3 add that one to it aswell will ye https://t.co/FBkkgHAmzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dunphygraham123 @_Lar11_ @DubGAAOfficial ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the two boys like messi and Iniesta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ @DubGAAOfficial he will work harder than anyone on that panel can't wait to see him play next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ @DubGAAOfficial definitely better than most, hopefully gets the chances he deserves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just throw that one in here mate https://t.co/b5jiPIFiOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night last night that's me in till Christmas now ðŸŽ…ðŸ½ https://t.co/NdJj4B4QJ5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>