<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@3littleseedling Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about the vid of your son in the puddle. Can we talk on DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judegatt51 @FrankIero Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about the video;. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoJoF30 Hi jo, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about your geese video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellaespo3 @TheEllenShow Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gvilleredhed Hi Mandy, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat with you about your video of ZoZo. Can you follow me so I can DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanMefford21 Hi jordan, I'd like to contact you about your homecoming video for @newsflare. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraciLloyd Hi Traci, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about you video of Max dancing. Can we talk on DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinmartin311 Hi Erin, I work at @newsflare can we talk on DM about the video of your daughter seeing Luke Bryan for the first time? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHVuyovich Hi Cindi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your baby video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcBurdiss Hi Marc, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your #Monsoon2017 video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaBabyyy Hi Georgia, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch with you about your dad's vid. Can you follow me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccar795 @NWSPhoenix @FOX10Phoenix Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me back so I can DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Chappers Hi Kenneth, I'm with @newsflare. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM about this video? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hajira_amla Hi Hajira, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about your rat video. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@00and1 @PAROOKAVILLE Hi Andreas, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonUlrich11 @fcunion @QPRFC Hi Ron, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyFratelli Hi Joey, I'm trying to contact you about your latest video on behalf of @Newsflare Can you follow me so I can send a DM?Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesaucem Hi, I hope you're ok. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kill_Lem_all Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your video. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM please?Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karmabertelsen @TravisPastrana @NitroCircus Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dangerous_afc @Newsflare Ok, thanks for letting me know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millah25 Hi Christopher, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotspur2012 Hi Terry, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dangerous_afc Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torangmirsh Hi Torang, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delanie_hunter @ThomasRhett Hi Lanie, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieValley Hi Jackie, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chantellord @Monarch Hi Chantel, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samraeGO @SFBART @SFBARTalert Hi I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRITgrlINDOfood Hi Aisyah, I hope you're safe. I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maddyoconnorr @RobertorRobby @PostMalone Hi Maddy, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomdragon Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCTTC1 @jeremycorbyn Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefaley Hi Mike, I work at @Newsflare and I'd like to contact you about the vid of your gf crying. Can you follow me so I can DM please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiec10 @TheCBSO Hi Eddie, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdhaanB @Newsflare Hi, thanks for getting back to me. Could you put me in touch with them please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaureguispeanut @Newsflare Ok, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaureguispeanut Hi, I hope you're safe. I work at a @Newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdhaanB Hi Adhaan, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parish__hilton Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Douglas_Gallant Bonjour Douglas, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette video. Peut-on parler par DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rsma_guadeloupe Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette video. Peut-on parler par DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DianeAsselin Bjr Diane, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette video. Peut-on parler par DM? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geembailey Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can we talk on DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomesecuestres Hi Rafael, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgios_kon Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can we talk on DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lobillo_feroz Hola, estoy periodista a @newsflare y quiero que contactarte acerca de tus videos. Podemos hablar por DM por favor? Gracias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Posh1 Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @Newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRTJr Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @Newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Osalta21 @SSFFrance Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @Newsflare et je souhaiterais vs contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tracylafferty Hi Tracy, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBeauvarlet Bonjour, je suis journaliste chez @newsflare et je souhaiterais vous contacter au sujet de cette vidéo. Peut-on parler par DM svp? Merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanWalkley Hi Dan, I work at @newsflareand I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bleacherbum54 @Cubs Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@satherax Hi Sath, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send an email? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callummaguire96 Hi Callum, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frazier_uk Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your Ibiza video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattbrady775 @YouTube Hi Matthew, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RunManyMyles @wmata @nbcwashington Hi Myles, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagloud Hi Ruth, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with your brother about his Tortola video. Can we talk on DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkneebone Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your Tortola video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KDBraddy Hi Kevin, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your Aileen video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJ_DaveFrumTarn Hi Dave, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joyturingan @CNN Hi Joy, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianBush904 @RAMJacksonville Hi Brian, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2605Nicky Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uappala Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your videos of the flood. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@festivalflyer Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about your Bestival videos. Can we talk on DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonStormRider Hi Simon, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your Irma vids. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatkinsHiago Hi Hiago, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicek3591 Hi Alice, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your catfish video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM pls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maurg1 Hola Mau, trabajo a @newsflare y quiero que contactarte acerca de este video. Puedes seguirme para que te envio un mensaje? Gracias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ackernans @NTelevisa_com Hola Kath, trabajo a @newsflare y quiero que contactarte acerca de este video. Puedes seguirme para que te envio un mensaje? Gracias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lalocedeno Hola, trabajo a @newsflare y quiero que contactarte acerca de este video. Puedes seguirme para que te envio un mensaje? Gracias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moy_etito Hola, trabajo a @newsflare y quiero que contactarte acerca de este video. Puedes seguirme para que te envio un mensaje? Gracias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deniselaguardia Hi I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please, can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarioG2681 @WPLGLocal10 Hi Mario, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindsayBCR Hi Lindsay, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coach_pick Hi there, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarrarNeil Hi Neil, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about the video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iucoleman Hi, I hope you're safe. I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimvanaalst Hi, I work at @Newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your Irma videos. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkCornerPoet Hi, I work at @Newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cams_hungry2 Hi Cam, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can we talk via DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@German6212 @TheEllenOffice @TheEllenShow Hi, I work at @newsflare, one of the largest viral media companies in the world and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluejaylover49 @DinaPugliese @KevinFrankish @CityMelanie @WinstonSih @AdamWylde @TheEllenShow @ellentube @jimmyfallon Hi Lorraine, did you shoot this video? I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with it. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franco_713 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naptural_mae Hi Amanda, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReitzGriffin @fairfaxcounty @fox5dc Hi Griffin, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaveFranco @ABC7 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keatonpine Hi, I work at @newsflare and we are interested in working with this video. Did you film it yourself? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyalMavin Hi, I'm a journalist at @n ewsflare and I would like to contact you about the videos of the Kasukuwere raid you posted. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caarlymcneil Hi Carly, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about your Glasgow street party video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM Please? Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELB_ayano Hi, did you film this video? I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to talk to you about it. Can you follow me so I can send a direct message? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ricocantrell @acosmov @azcentral Hi I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shitlondon Hi Patrick, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about your Southern Rail hack. Can we talk via DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenwls @BridgendCBC Hi Darren, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danna003evo6 Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to talk to you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a direct message please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0start18 Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to talk to you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a direct message please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenranger555 Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to talk to you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a direct message please]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>