<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Global warming will ruin beer, scientists warn https://t.co/I98pfngJcA https://t.co/h8vNfU08qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Just spoke with the Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia who totally denied ... https://t.co/I9JkSf5Kp5 https://t.co/5jpR2w0k2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Opinion: Elizabeth Warren demonstrates the folly of identity politics https://t.co/Cwx6LPBUhK https://t.co/cWeqtOk6Uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Photo of the Day: A United States flag provides a backdrop to the last few ... https://t.co/v5sInpLqmC https://t.co/l4vKdBEfly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Susan Collins' honorary degree should be rescinded, nearly 1,500 St. ... https://t.co/xN8zGeOukD https://t.co/zDJYGvEH4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Stand together, Britain's May calls for unity on Brexit https://t.co/nTb9KS33Ut https://t.co/wMysbqQCs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: “Op-Ed praises Trump Administrations efforts at the Border.” ... https://t.co/LcXX35WCCD https://t.co/hJ871nrjU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Meghan Markle wore a dress and it broke the internet in Australia https://t.co/9pKPju2Y9H https://t.co/ifIGJbCb9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Walmart is cutting its earnings targets given the impact of its purchase of a ... https://t.co/qEjw9V9xcj https://t.co/OvkoDZhQWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: RT @ReutersIndia: Tanushree Dutta, who helped trigger India's #MeToo ... https://t.co/fph5J2kx7W https://t.co/p5Y21hbphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Iranian media say militants have abducted 14 members of a border ... https://t.co/UnbGgm1V6a https://t.co/nsJz3Bldvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Female employees described “frequent sexual innuendos, lewd comments or ... https://t.co/nzkL7yCdWW https://t.co/z9ZvtT1l19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: "It's time to fight back that's what Huey said. Two shots in the dark, ... https://t.co/7HvZrnA52h https://t.co/qLAilIu0dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: “Angela Merkel has governed for an extraordinarily long time and with ... https://t.co/PcXboLquju https://t.co/DrNo7QM5dW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: “This shows that we are part of this community,” said the president of ... https://t.co/unztnmAVtc https://t.co/D6FA4sU7wm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Two Koreas, U.N. Command hold first talks on disarming border https://t.co/az5j6DCsRS https://t.co/vdL1mklhbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Trump surveys Michael's wrath, rescuers search for bodies https://t.co/IAIvk0MU5R https://t.co/HiFqXiac1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: New York City restaurant lets customers catch their own meal. https://t.co/5qHV7m5F8X https://t.co/jH2anLYnXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: RT @APWestRegion: Paul Allen, who died more than 4 decades after co-founding Microsoft with his ... https://t.co/IwHCpTquZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: The NYPD is looking to charge at least nine members of the far-right ... https://t.co/6StIZzlTuj https://t.co/vuZTMroK1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Britain's Prince Harry and his wife Meghan are expecting their first child. ... https://t.co/dXHyYrNV8F https://t.co/q2Ty9xP99D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Women poised to make history with the 2018 midterm elections. https://t.co/YOBLzM7lxP https://t.co/yyrwQ3GbDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: These powerful pictures capture the trauma of sexual assault
https://t.co/Y0kUvCVe9F https://t.co/0QbqMs0R5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: "I'm trying what’s called a reverse Marcel Marceau, where I imagine myself not ... https://t.co/YyCI9ct75U https://t.co/9MwjITUgqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@FLGovScott: "Everything I have asked the president for, FEMA has come ... https://t.co/Q85FEs4tCi https://t.co/IuDaTyHnxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@RepRooney: “We have to uphold the same principles against Saudi Arabia ... https://t.co/odX8U7e1GD https://t.co/wHbVPLO6cU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Stuart Varney on @foxandfriends: “Political violence has no place in America.” https://t.co/lgY6OS3wu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: What title will Prince Harry and Meghan Markle's baby get? And will they ever be ... https://t.co/gr0AjXUrBW https://t.co/a7H0HN7F5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: RT @ReutersUK: Ireland's #Brexit backstop, and why it matters https://t.co/9iuNds8hPe https://t.co/j6inRbSUDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Attorney General Jeff Sessions and Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein ... https://t.co/1BNiGcDeTA https://t.co/9O6UwCRRQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: “I had my own gods in the forest but I cannot go back to the forest ... https://t.co/7CVWDRHINl https://t.co/fKxddRGmUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman of Saudi Arabia has had only praise ... https://t.co/q5jbusYKwK https://t.co/FwK4Ne4Mga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Seeing isn’t believing anymore—why computer-generated video fakes are getting ... https://t.co/nVC7nnPVfH https://t.co/yvQCPp39gC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Meghan Markle, Prince Harry expecting first baby https://t.co/1ZKzeLI4D3 https://t.co/e0kcjKFU8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cnnbrk: JUST IN: Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, and Prince Harry are expecting their ... https://t.co/MsKAK8D9Cx https://t.co/ebLN7eSipw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Ireland demands May keep promise on Brexit border https://t.co/v0g1eWbn4P https://t.co/urbtqglZqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Reversing a decades-long position, the Diocese of Vermont has announced ... https://t.co/ZOLtGu8IfO https://t.co/9QprhLdMNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: FEMA chief calls destruction left by Hurricane Michael some of the worst he's ... https://t.co/AYLwWEFfLT https://t.co/UijzO0cQKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Ariana Grande and Pete Davidson reportedly call off their engagement, end ... https://t.co/GN7CBGd1Kl https://t.co/REdC1NK8MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: “We have a responsibility to protect your information," Mark Zuckerberg ... https://t.co/Aq2HQ8fnH6 https://t.co/TdTlO7Jflv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Suspicions about the disappearance of the Saudi dissident Jamal ... https://t.co/XLtzkrjUh4 https://t.co/4obcW38RjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: More dead expected in destroyed Florida Panhandle towns after Michael https://t.co/3jvHt7gBGB https://t.co/O0ZtCqd0P5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@POTUS: 'I think I know more about' NATO than Mattis does https://t.co/M5G1xqyfPY https://t.co/IaItoufGGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: From “I’mma let you finish...” to Make America Great Again: We tracked ... https://t.co/A6VxPp6DG6 https://t.co/jwEEvMKMBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: M. J. Akbar, who founded and edited several newspapers and magazines ... https://t.co/ATjBFLH5ch https://t.co/Tj3XhxyC4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Would-be looter in Hurricane Michael-ravaged Florida shot, killed after ... https://t.co/WmGwAnQE8Z https://t.co/AYRXIfiylc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Thanking your significant other isn’t just polite, says a growing body of ... https://t.co/MdzVkgvxNR https://t.co/znj2oQGxCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: “The abusive, racist and threatening language used in the letters has ... https://t.co/RBMGEbRU0O https://t.co/gxJh5VOVFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: In a rare honor, Matthew Shepard will be laid to rest at DC's National ... https://t.co/JKJMN4ZK00 https://t.co/S93E0rJnoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Jordan and Syria say border to reopen on Monday https://t.co/AAcLgMteNR https://t.co/3ItuaYOq3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: A princess of her Orang Rimba tribe, her noble lineage meant she could ... https://t.co/XoZrtn7UeZ https://t.co/wkExzlMoNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: President @realDonaldTrump rallies this month https://t.co/ycFSzXMXtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: M. J. Akbar made his first public response to multiple allegations of a ... https://t.co/rVcy0L9zLE https://t.co/OaKlWPQ9HA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: On @foxandfriends, @robertjeffress commented on Andrew Brunson, the American ... https://t.co/6qquuFzs60 https://t.co/Fn73A4VCdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@robertjeffress: "This is a country that is founded on faith, it's a country that is founded on ... https://t.co/35QajMFBQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: WATCH: Twin pandas Qinqin and Aiai are now able to live independently of their mother https://t.co/QiCTe0QKQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Here's the official pictures of Princess Eugenie's wedding https://t.co/D8Vw63WBCf https://t.co/v4XQcx7AiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: John Kelly called Elizabeth Warren 'impolite arrogant woman' after ... https://t.co/fX6uCML9Eb https://t.co/nRGrwAdelB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Old internet accounts are like digital ghosts—they can come back to haunt you. ... https://t.co/0Dd3T7LhMU https://t.co/A1RoIfDaTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@SenatorLankford on Brunson release: “If they're gonna be a member of NATO, ... https://t.co/qocy2FsgeG https://t.co/z7xgTS7xnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: One of Britain's most distinctive artists prepares to debut seven large-scale ... https://t.co/Bs4Rxgxsz7 https://t.co/FlxR5R42O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Martyr priest, now Saint Romero, challenged power in El Salvador https://t.co/iFQpICVtdG https://t.co/f7Wpn2m81I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Rent the Runway co-founder Jenny Fleiss on ignoring the naysayers and starting ... https://t.co/pFPGHmpZqJ https://t.co/eXfndjbLE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: "Today, I’m calling on de Blasio and the NYPD to release the names of ... https://t.co/3O5MYckhJQ https://t.co/54kbEuRy37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: The Humboldt Forum is a new Berlin museum that cost nearly $700 ... https://t.co/bCcwvBH4Tg https://t.co/IQ96yOyq4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: OPINION: President @realDonaldTrump freed me from prison – I’m glad he wants ... https://t.co/Rv4mRg79jn https://t.co/CpLk5b63BA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Stars like Taylor Swift don’t make a difference when pushing their politics: ... https://t.co/DWPTMLirt8 https://t.co/t9NVy9yRLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Holiday entertaining? No problem. Here's the one (incredibly easy) dish you need https://t.co/1g7uFoxPbX https://t.co/jZxwbsntLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: New York Attorney General Barbara Underwood said the Proud Boys ... https://t.co/2fHiseETYg https://t.co/Z9sMRCN36M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Mexico Beach, Florida is picking up the pieces after it was devastated by ... https://t.co/2gXaF6i2gw https://t.co/a7saWZH0Fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@SteveDoocy: The greatest meal of my life (but not the happiest) https://t.co/ZNVHfsLE0T https://t.co/Dc3PmnKszP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman stands out as the youthful face of a ... https://t.co/OdFTM5qiT8 https://t.co/biIdRiCvPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Pastor Andrew Brunson, who was detained for two years in Turkey after ... https://t.co/fX3YjJfHpd https://t.co/scRMncWFgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Hundreds of survivors found but toll from Michael seen rising https://t.co/J8IYjPmunV https://t.co/Xz6IRWuLir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@Franklin_Graham: “We are very grateful to President Trump and Vice ... https://t.co/qhs1P4tWNj https://t.co/XXgMP7khIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: ICYMI: Jacksonville Zoo and Gardens welcomes a newborn baby gorilla https://t.co/D5391rvtBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Colombia’s peace deal was supposed to mean a chance to practice ... https://t.co/c8N6EKg3E1 https://t.co/fvFX7bzI9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Happy 243rd Birthday to our GREAT @USNavy! #243NavyBday https://t.co/uQHlGGBUy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: $87M worth of cocaine seized by U.S. Coast Guard: reports https://t.co/CxikgQ9kLc https://t.co/SsjEXDJCUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Colombia’s activists and community leaders are being slaughtered. Many ... https://t.co/qPKeljYQEX https://t.co/ANpQqkhxRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Driver, 74, says he meant no harm, just wanted to get away from 'angry mob' https://t.co/FN16sExaRh https://t.co/QRxFcEqFA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@RepMarkWalker: “Early evidence is showing there has been some foul play ... https://t.co/vdPHkCv6zn https://t.co/cRgkm92MB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Thousands compete in Catalonia’s human tower competition. https://t.co/iey731Jm4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: The Latest: Palestinians in the northern West Bank say a woman has been killed ... https://t.co/IsMSCLp4xZ https://t.co/PwjTjIiehf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Outgoing U.N. Ambassador @nikkihaley Haley criticized the UN Friday after ... https://t.co/dk6DyKEjak https://t.co/NatkGVSaJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: President @realDonaldTrump on disappearance of Jamal Khashoggi: "It is ... https://t.co/1sb1lnbFlJ https://t.co/p1SaCYPWAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: ICYMI: Breakdancing makes its debut at the Youth Olympic Games in Buenos Aires https://t.co/Z60JG9w578]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Rescuers find first body in town worst hit by hurricane Michael https://t.co/H5HJdqV7Qa https://t.co/gGKJY3OgEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Pastor Andrew Brunson freed amid Saudi-Turk crisis @FoxNewsNight https://t.co/lYhFTXtLIm https://t.co/9YUrHKza4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@MarshaBlackburn up 14% despite @taylorswift13's plea for opponent ... https://t.co/MqfSfHu0uT https://t.co/0IiUErx8Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: U.S. courts of appeals wield a lot of power. They often have the final word ... https://t.co/TU1x0F5Pge https://t.co/AQDnDnwuSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Hurricane death toll rises to 17 as search goes on in Florida https://t.co/um8EWZaIzX https://t.co/OsJvHcAFPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@JordanSekulow, Brunson family spokesperson: "Tonight is a night for the ... https://t.co/yruBeiJ82p https://t.co/QqW0XYg4ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: A look inside Princess Eugenie's royal wedding https://t.co/I1EIEhywh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: How a quiet spot for walking in the U.K. became a famous landmark for ... https://t.co/Nq7kdIJHAx https://t.co/Ant7BN63Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Facebook purged a lot of partisan political pages on Thursday. Here's ... https://t.co/9Ib9fiGIbN https://t.co/4iqrMNnPIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Anjas Firmansyah watched his house wash down into the earth. His wife ... https://t.co/71t5YYLkJy https://t.co/Xf8BjaSs3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Danielle Spencer, who played the tattletale little sister Dee Thomas on the 1970s ... https://t.co/sd234K5W77 https://t.co/J3Q5GdRaTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: @visualsandra: "As I dropped off one 18-year-old at college, I ... https://t.co/qa0iE1CFC2 https://t.co/Pt6HOxLF7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Dave Chappelle defends Kanye West's Donald Trump meeting: 'I support him' https://t.co/hBFkNKLnnJ https://t.co/ZvuVEGddfS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>