<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[One day you'll find someone who doesn't care about your past because they want to be your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you're in a relationship, doesn't mean you have to post a status about that person every minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when you close your eyes, and he's all you see, and when you open them, he's all you want to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How would you know if he really loves you? It's when you cry, he hugs you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who has truly loved you is the only one who has the strength to accept your mistakes and forgive you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God puts people in your life for a reason, and removes them from your life for a better reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no mistakes on life, only lessons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not give hope to someone, if in the end you gave up on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u try to change people, they usually remain the same. But when you don't try to change people, they change in the most beautiful way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I remove my brain to stop thinking about you? Or should I remove my heart so I can stop loving you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to have a fairy tale story to get your 'happily-ever-after.' You just need to be happy with the life you lead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter the distance, no matter the time, I will be there by your side. Even when the world may be ending, I shall be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If one day you into my heart, you'll cry, because there is full of you. If one day I went into your (cont) http://t.co/GAXEyFyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna be the only girl you love all your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful woman wouldn't compare herself with others. She's proud &amp; happy being herself, &amp; that makes her incomparable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am someone else when I am with you, someone more like myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe that God wants us to meet a few wrong people, so that when we finally meet the right one, we will know to be grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love actually is all around us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't always be super nice to someone. Sometimes you have to show your bad side to know who can accept you at your worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the happiest things on the earth is when you know you are in love with someone who loves you more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's biggest mistake is giving another man the opportunity to make his woman smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just couldn't live in a world where you don't exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm alone, music is the perfect best friend to be with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm afraid I'm not good enough for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to have a bad day every once in a while. Otherwise, you'll never know what a good day feels like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's easier to pretend you don't care than to admit that it's killing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be yourself. There's no one better at it in the entire world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't love someone because they're great. Love someone because they make you feel great &amp; you two are great together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, I want to thank you from the bottom of my heart for never leaving me, and always being here for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes all you need in the end is someone who will hold you and say everything is alright...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love isn't enough to keep the relationship going. It takes a lot of effort and patience to make the commitment stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always remember that, no matter how useless you feel, you're someone's reason to smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretending to be happy when you're in pain is just an example of how strong you are as a person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone sticks by your side through your bad times, they deserve to be with you through your good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm blasting my music so I won't hear my thoughts, but the lyrics just remind me of what I'm trying to forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is something which can't be expressed in words, but can be felt by anyone in the universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God speaks to those who take time to listen and God listens to those who take time to pray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What ever God does, is not for us to understand, but to accept and believe that His way is always for the BEST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand why destiny allowed some people to meet, when there's no way for them to be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on love. Love is unpredictable and you'll be surprised how much love can make you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, I wonder why I love you, just trying to find it out and then the next day I see you... how love doesn't need a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the good things I've learned to be a thankful person. From the trials I've learned to be a strong person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A love like ours isn't common, we treat each other with respect and we remain loyal because we only want to be with each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you look into someone's eyes and you feel something indescribable, that's when you know it's real. And you shouldn't let it go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never be good enough for everybody. But I am best for someone who really appreciates me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to be perfect, you just need to be yourself, because I love you for who you are, just the way you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TipsToHappyLife Accept the things u cant change, move on and let go of anything that's holding u down, and always thank God for everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a gentlemen won't get you all the women, but if you're a true gentlemen, you only want one woman anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't imagine how much I miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't silence your enemies with words, but you can silence them with actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't completely control your life, but you can still make the right choice to make it easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a guy is away from his girl, all he wants is her trust. But on the girl's part, all she needs is his loyalty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A negative thinker makes everything worse, heavier, &amp; harder. A positive thinker makes everything better, lighter, &amp; easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss you, not the "I haven't seen you in a while" kind of miss you, but the "I wish you were here at this very moment" kind of miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up just because of what someone said. Use that as motivation push harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jangan ragu untuk berdoa, bahkan ketika kamu tak menemukan kata untuk dipanjatkan, karena Tuhan selalu mengerti doamu. God is Awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AstrologySecret: 1000 followers（Ｔ▽Ｔ）。 (≧≦) 谢谢大家!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you more today than yesterday, but not as much as tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What hurts you today, makes you stronger tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't marry a man unless you'd be proud to have a son exactly like him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two people are connected at heart, it doesn't matter what you do, there are no boundaries or barriers if they are destined to be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If God gives u a "tomorrow", thank Him, because every tomorrow is a new chance to make a difference &amp; turn things around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing like your best friends! Keep your circle small and cherish your friends forever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most difficult phase of life is not when no one understands you, it is when you don't understand yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let a bad day make you feel like you have a bad life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I first met you, I honestly don't plan on falling in love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart beats a little faster whenever I see you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't always look for happiness, sometimes you may just have to create it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think life is too hard, remind yourself that it won't last forever. After all, life's only temporary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I think of you, I get the biggest smile on my face and you still don't understand how much you mean to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please follow my other accounts in Chinese @aiqingfenxiang &amp; @AstrologySecret. Thank you (^-^)ノ~~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would stay up all night just to talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will always talk about you, especially when they envy you and the life you live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you not because of who you are, but because of who I am when I am with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest thing ever is watching the person you love loving someone else &amp; then trying to act happy, even though you're dying inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how hard things may seem, there is always something good coming around the corner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, I've tried my best, but if today I lose my hope, please tell me that Ur plans are better than my dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it may seem like the hardest thing to do, but you have to forget about the boy who forgot about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be with someone who knows exactly what they have when they have you. Not someone who realizes it after they've lost you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the best I have ever have. I can't tell you how much you have change the way I view about life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up just because of what people said. Use that as your motivation to push harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You knew me better than I knew myself. You loved me like nobody else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our small, stupid conversations mean so much more to me than you'll ever know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's things in life you have to let go of no matter how much it hurts because, you know it's for the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is perfect, but with the right person... you've got a perfect match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no one busy in this world, it's always about priorities. You will always find time for the things you feel important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl is in love, you can see it in her smile. When a guy is in love, you can see it in his eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing in God doesn't mean I will never fall, it just means I trust that He will catch me when I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I end up being the one walking away, I want you to know that it wasn't because I stopped loving you, but because you stopped loving me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is all I need, He is always there, He is my everything, He is GOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still like you, I'm just tired of trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate that feeling. The feeling when you're sad and you have no idea why, but you just are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing someone is your heart's way of reminding you that you love them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can go back and start a new beginning, but anyone can start today and make a new ending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's turn our mistakes into lessons, and our fears into hopes. We should have faith in God and be strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F.R.I.E.N.D.S: (F)ight for you. (R)espect you. (I)nvolve you. (E)ncourage you. (N)eed you. (D)eserve you. (S)ave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who really LOVES u sees what a mess u can be, how moody u can get, how hard u are to handle, but still wants u in their life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't need to be perfect. It just needs to be true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it ironic? We ignore the ones that adore us. Adore the ones who ignore us. Love the ones who hurt us. Hurt the ones that love us.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>