<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Doc Fix: 
	The agreement reached in Congress yesterday is an important step that will prevent a tax hike on ... http://t.co/1ZxP6D36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Continuing to Strengthen American Manufacturing: 
	President Obama describes a series of steps t... http://t.co/geoBboIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: What $40 Means: 

	A quick look at what happened this week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	National ... http://t.co/fTDvVDiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Plouffe: "You helped to extend the payroll tax cut": 
	This afternoon, David Plouffe, Senior Advisor to Pr... http://t.co/IPepdE3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Preview of the 2012 Economic Report of the President: 
	The Economic Report of the President has been prepared... http://t.co/RvZx3X8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: Exporting the Boeing Dreamliner: 

	Today, President Obama visited the Boeing assembly facility i... http://t.co/faUFV1bI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing BusinessUSA: 
	Today, as part of the Administration’s ongoing effort to support and strengthen Ameri... http://t.co/XZqSJzEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: First Lady Michelle Obama Surprises White House Visitors: 
	Yesterday, First Lady Michelle Obama surpris... http://t.co/3CQ9Y5Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 2/17/12 or "Go Big!": 
	This week, the President made a major announcement on preventive care, u... http://t.co/NOaiGLUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Surprises White House Visitors: 
	This morning, First Lady Michelle Obama surprised a ... http://t.co/eUe9mOzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$40 Less Would Be a Colder House: 
	On Tuesday, President Obama asked Americans to tell him what losing $40 per ... http://t.co/OczAI4DE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Year, 54 Million Americans Received Free Preventive Services Thanks to Health Care Reform: 

	Each day, m... http://t.co/zbmB77tK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Payroll Tax Cut Helps to Fuel the Economic Recovery: 
	In December, Brian Deese, the Deputy Director of ... http://t.co/ALNbz9b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chart of the Day: Another Milestone in the Resurgence of the American Auto Industry: 
	Today, we learned that ea... http://t.co/BiD4m4Ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expanding the Healthcare Tax Credit for Small Businesses: 
	Ed. Note: This was originally posted on Open for Bus... http://t.co/UHcLFBxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 86 Million: 

	In 2011, the Affordable Care Act provided approximately 54 million Americans wi... http://t.co/ZsMi7r3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An America Built to Last: Strengthening Economic Security in Retirement: 
	In his State of the Union message las... http://t.co/NQSOHkJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses Insourcing at Master Lock: 

  President Barack Obama tours Master Lock Company with... http://t.co/mYlLylPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden’s Turn to Host Vice President Xi of China in the U.S.: 
	Yesterday, at the invitation of Vi... http://t.co/tLEOA75G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady and Dr. Biden Urge State Action to Support Military Spouses with State Licenses: 

  From left, Def... http://t.co/RnnMBS4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady and Dr. Biden Urge State Action to Support Military Spouses with State Licenses: 
	Earlier today, I h... http://t.co/Cd5bSiys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$40.00 Means an Inhaler for My Little Girl: 
	President Obama yesterday asked Americans to share their stories, ... http://t.co/QEnitCvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Your Voice Matters: 
	Yesterday, we had the good fortune to host a group of individuals who answered the Pre... http://t.co/r4PYhDE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans Tell President Obama What $40 Means: 
	President Obama today asked Americans to share their stories, a... http://t.co/qwuROjVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2013 Energy Budget: What It Means for You: 

  Secretary Chu details President Barack Obama's $27.2 billion fi... http://t.co/teDdgOmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Pushes Congress to Extend the Payroll Tax Cut Through 2012: 

  President Barack Obama deliver... http://t.co/pnmADK6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Administration’s Unprecedented Fraud Fighting Pays Off: 
	More than most seniors, Jacqueline Jefferson of ... http://t.co/dBONwG1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Plouffe: "Here we go again": 
	This morning, David Plouffe, Senior Advisor to President Obama, sent the me... http://t.co/eOX4jftN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$40 Means Being Able to Afford My Daughter's Medications: 
	At the end of this month, a two-month extension of t... http://t.co/7qqPpFlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$40 Could Be the Difference Between Eating and Not Eating: 
	At the end of this month, a two-month extension of ... http://t.co/90WDYf2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$40 Means No Extras for My Students: 
	At the end of this month, a two-month extension of the payroll tax cut wi... http://t.co/BbcsmmQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Congress Must Extend the Payroll Tax Cut Through 2012: 

	Today, President Obama has invited a group of Am... http://t.co/L7xO8I3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2013 Education Budget: What it Means For You: 
	Ed note: this post originally appeared on Homeroom, the U.S. Dep... http://t.co/hM6B88XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's 2013 Budget is a Blueprint for an America Built to Last: 

  President Barack Obama delivers... http://t.co/MWXLzIxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President’s Budget Request Reflects Strong Commitment on Global AIDS: 

	Ed note: this post originally appeare... http://t.co/rdzXsBuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Awards the 2011 National Medals of Arts and Humanities at the White House: 

  President Barac... http://t.co/W8BnBf71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's Plan to Train 2 Million Workers for Jobs in High-Demand Industries: 

	Today, President Obam... http://t.co/dtdWXoAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2013 Budget: 
	Ed. Note: This has been cross-posted from the OMB blog

	Earlier today, the President sent to... http://t.co/zpv7gobW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2013 Budget: 
	Earlier today, the President sent to Congress his budget for the 2013 fiscal year. This year’... http://t.co/eSRNuaCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama: Changing the Conversation on Healthy Eating: 

  First Lady Michelle Obama holds a roundtable ... http://t.co/C9pvOxI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What They Are Saying: Preventive Health Care and Religious Institutions: 
	On Friday, President Obama announced ... http://t.co/7P04FPtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Extending the Payroll Tax Cut for the Middle Class: 
	President Obama urges Congress to extend t... http://t.co/c7n3Gx0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs Rep. Gabby Giffords' Final Bill: 

  President Obama signs H.R. 3801, the Ultralight Air... http://t.co/1j11tEXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: The Next Generation of Scientists, Engineers and Inventors: 

	A quick look at what happened thi... http://t.co/frF6JtdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Independent Report Review Confirms Energy Loan Portfolio is Expected to Perform Well: 
	On October 28, 2011, the... http://t.co/vOmdKaIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the 2012 White House Science Fair Participants: 
	You've already met Joey Hudy. He's the 14 year old from A... http://t.co/XqVaLdKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Entrepreneurs at the White House Science Fair: 

  Hayley Hoverter met President Obama on Tuesday at the... http://t.co/3bl7uJke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Black Women in American Culture and History: 

	Last week, President Obama signed a proclamation, ... http://t.co/E05oD69b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 2/10/12 or "Don't Be Bored...Make Something": 
	This week, the President happily kicked off the ... http://t.co/auxKI3Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Is on the Road with Let's Move: 
	Ed note: this has been cross-posted from Let's Move!... http://t.co/vQoPWhyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know: Waivers, Flexibility, and Reforming No Child Left Behind: 
	Explaining that our kid... http://t.co/YLHeTYzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Bo After Blizzard: 
	In early February of 2010, back to back blizzards hit the Northeast, and... http://t.co/UZKmWvbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Missed: Open for Questions on Innovation for Global Development: 

	Yesterday, the White House hosted... http://t.co/72Sulqnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait: Taking Action on Alzheimer’s Disease: 
	Alzheimer’s disease, which today afflicts as many as 5.1 ... http://t.co/O8VM09Y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Highlights New College Affordability Proposals at Florida State: 

  Vice President Joe Biden s... http://t.co/sPxdiiht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's Move: Two Years of Healthy Changes for our Nation's Kids: 

  First Lady Michelle Obama joins local stud... http://t.co/19HjVKDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Mess With Texas … Science Students: 

  President Barack Obama hosts the second White House Science Fair... http://t.co/yKwheYmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harnessing Science, Technology & Innovation to Promote Global Development: 
	Today at the White House, senior Ad... http://t.co/KtHDxXg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting Tax Payer Dollars by Strengthing SNAP: 
	Ed note: This was originally posted on the USDA blog.

	Whil... http://t.co/xXDW6I9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Launches a Marshmallow Cannon: 

	Who says science can’t be fun?

	At today’s White House Scie... http://t.co/OH2AXvHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Hosts the White House Science Fair: 

  President Barack Obama hosts the second White House Sc... http://t.co/lNruhD6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICE Names Its First Public Advocate: 
	Cross posted from The Blog @ Homeland Security. 

	Today, I am honored to... http://t.co/cdYhzoYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Science Fair: Recognizing the Importance of Scientists, Engineers, and Inventors: 
	[Editor’s note: ... http://t.co/i1giWiwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commemorating National Black HIV/AIDS Awareness Day: 
	On this, the 12th annual National Black HIV/AIDS Awarenes... http://t.co/EQbHAiuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How You Can Join the White House Science Fair (Virtually): 
	On Tuesday, February 7, over 100 students from over... http://t.co/4VgKKFDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open for Questions: Innovation for Global Development: 
	On Wednesday, February 8 at 9am, the White House will h... http://t.co/ZrYP3TIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Seeing the Savings from the Affordable Care Act: 
	Last week, several announcements from the Department ... http://t.co/W96n8NCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Let's Move! Anniversary with Sam Kass: 
	Today, we’re holding a special session of Whi... http://t.co/KLSWa3xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: It’s Time for Congress to Act to Help Responsible Homeowners: 
	President Obama continues his ca... http://t.co/idmIMry1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Hanging Out with America: 

	A quick look at this week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	Talking Tuition... http://t.co/GCkYYw4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Startup America White Board: 
	This week, we celebrated the 1-year anniversary of Startup Ame... http://t.co/17b2kK3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating a Veterans Job Corps: 

  President Barack Obama delivers remarks on the Veterans Job Corp and the ec... http://t.co/9bLhNwYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: The Tuskegee Airmen Visit the White House: 

	President Obama and First Lady Michelle Obama invited... http://t.co/kXfLY9LZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in January: 
	Today’s employment report provides further evidence that the economy is c... http://t.co/fJBKpLd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 2/3/2012 or Riding the Advanced Technology Superhighway: 
	This week, the President made history... http://t.co/HfpJKnUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Conversation with "We the People" about Immigration Policy: 

  Felicia Escobar, Senior Policy Advisor in th... http://t.co/xur2uCRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama at the 2012 National Prayer Breakfast: 

  Click here to see the video. 

	This morning ... http://t.co/JW49pszS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Roundup – Helping Responsible Homeowners: 
	Last week in his State of the Union Address, the President ... http://t.co/pOvdm7FJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors are Saving Money Today and Tomorrow, Thanks to Health Care Law: 
	Ed note: This has been cross-posted fr... http://t.co/Knb59Vrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama Talks About Being a Mentor: 

   First Lady Michelle Obama drops by the Girls Mentoring Novembe... http://t.co/RLOm0dGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An America Built to Last: Strengthening Economic Security in Retirement: 
	In his State of the Union message las... http://t.co/G03k1tgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Talks About Ways to Help Homeowners: 

  Housing and Urban Development Secretary Shaun Donovan... http://t.co/7r0ASyRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Reform, Preventive Services, and Religious Institutions: 
	Thanks to the Affordable Care Act, most health... http://t.co/XLGXiRFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Look Back at Joplin: United We Succeed: 
	Eight months ago, one of the deadliest tornados in U.S. history touc... http://t.co/lo8pElOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Hangout: Startup America: 
	On Thursday, February 2nd at 5:30 p.m. EST, Gene Sperling, Steve Case an... http://t.co/jXheljlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFPB Director Richard Cordray's Response to Administration Housing Announcement: 
	In response to press inquirie... http://t.co/6yy3rViw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choice in Medicare is Stronger than Ever in 2012: 
	At the time the Affordable Care Act was passed, Republicans ... http://t.co/Jo8iATEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooting Out the Corrosive Influence of Money in Politics: 
	In last week’s State of the Union Address, the Presi... http://t.co/BtTIdzFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Showroom of the Washington Auto Show: 

  President Barack Obama is shown the American Pride Chevrolet ... http://t.co/p52TqE4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cabinet Meeting Focused on Small Business: 

  President Barack Obama holds a Cabinet meeting in the Cabinet... http://t.co/Lx8TQMoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup America Policy Challenge: Universities Respond: 
	Today, President Obama recognized the one-year anniver... http://t.co/xszKvnxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Startups in the State of the Union: 
	Ed note: In honor of the one year anniversary of Startup Ameri... http://t.co/tqXRK65X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Hangs Out With America: 

  President Barack Obama participates in an interview with YouTube a... http://t.co/DiV0MhUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes Georgian President Mikheil Saakashvili: 

  President Barack Obama and President Mikh... http://t.co/LG6T8prG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulatory Reform Progress: 
	To promote economic growth and job creation, we need cost-justified, evidence-base... http://t.co/QXjF9bTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: Two Years: 

	Today’s jobs report shows that private sector employers added 233,000 jobs to th... http://t.co/jKC7d39a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Todd Park Named New U.S. Chief Technology Officer: 
	I’m very excited that President Obama today is appointing T... http://t.co/cuotnNAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Year of Safer Products: 
	Ed note: this post was originally published at On Safety, the Consumer Product Saf... http://t.co/ith7Wlax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in February: 
	Today’s employment report provides further evidence that the economy is ... http://t.co/uOPdfzFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/8/2012 or "Speak Softly; Carry a Big Stick": 

	This week, President Obama addressed both the ... http://t.co/5zb6ipMa]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>