<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/JYlRw3wZ6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/eN4nPxCZZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/SXHmWkSNRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/j6iiCoWIMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/ckrWxNHFkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/8BmMzY9vZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/X6rCcvW0O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/b1oSj2BBR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/vyC55mGATi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/30lLn2CHDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kIumbjf7F0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/9UqvdC7cX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/VtXGggp4xW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/slCe01eGuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/mfOL3jkFYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/txHLZcyJaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/FSqnqAbuVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/roshfTnknG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/WbYCEFIf7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VPHVMl03Fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/SR4O6R9ioO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/qNWdJhkdJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/XIk3EnYUBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/hRgvqpYAp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/t08T636bVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/wXm78GYr7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/1YVDFF6sXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/AFObH5J6fr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/pv9096Wxqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/pv9096Wxqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/EK7k4ymeVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/QxDXHv0p24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/n8PeADKATI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/vxGG89D0F9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/fET6oRAhH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/2oxn5Tir6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/vvII7NDStQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/aGlgS5VOOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/ELfzdG4I0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/lxTWrlTT6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/BcNn3G2W8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/slCe01eGuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/9waP2BhEEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/ZmuQplxDPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/LmUnqdpD71]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>