<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/1BP0Jlt9Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/U2iJwMynbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/W4pQmojQ6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/fZlotlVvrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/drY2kBcMRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/XvMosfPmq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAR TREK ENTERPRISE - Brake Light Vinyl Decal - ENGAGE!  --&gt; http://t.co/DsqP5Srq9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/8U2Y06Yncp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/ydaY5PASTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/NgtYY5mSEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/PgPwgAweIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/ttFoM8ajd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/k0KC8uvWXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/u9Jva2o16O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/LieDWb30fE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/Qxp890zL4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/osWwwWhzs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/TPWOclQosy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/yuEutOgTbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/tS6qv6i0ZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/K8cp7PTix8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/YEV6bm1843]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/8K4Eq5urOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/5jSHnaf2Az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/bEIDXMzVzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/oo80gdD7Q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winner ain't the one with the fastest car, it's the one who refuses to lose. - Dale Earnhardt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/ITPx135uBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/vuh73gURSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/xvo7cQRctF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/xnJ4CwhMSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/KlcNCEQC9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/IrbAvnjFmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 12 - And so it begins...  http://t.co/qDrSq209sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/O85N3ZOu2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/Egl7M7luJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/6iG9lEpUcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/c0TZnEnLYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/NXPzzYFvUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/Y05s0RVxgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/f2tx6PZtPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/2AldDow538]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/Zh8tpI9u8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/udeYEPnjOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/GF51uldsCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/00lFBnyG7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/HSVPHb20rq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/SFy7VjPcUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/Xy8jtqLFg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/4YZGECQaUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/AAKxj18uCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/xGC6BR8DBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/r9Gt7DfZZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/lzPJuyf6gZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>