<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The bitter taste of truth. https://t.co/fgQhWq4eoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After President Trump Complained About His Job, This Republican Hilariously Unloaded On Him https://t.co/2IgU4h9qTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Frum has wicked left coming back to form. His time in the wilderness was well spent. https://t.co/NeApWI5drf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was a s!ave master when he wasn't beating slaves, who were fake. https://t.co/izIq2k4eXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/I9MPuljuBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to stand in the cold shadows at the foot of the Eiger is intimidating for climbers since the 30s. Ueli Steck... https://t.co/P9fumPlKh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yKXmHOkrNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is American Psycho with ultimate power https://t.co/bHTngtDHwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skartndesign @|MikeShandrick Best to reach me by phone because of sensitive nature of your request, especially money and personal issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/iY4zffgsH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aka_tahto: #BeforeHavingKids pee in private ALL YOU CAN. https://t.co/7T7KI35Uyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei @Oneworld101 if you don't like the the way democracy works then go back to television. Adios!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynetteBenton I would like to send you links about my days as a young writer sent to compete with HST. Hs was not afraid of Nixon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shwood oil,gas,coal is dead energy that poisons. On the wind and sun expand life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinthiaritchie1: 20-mile run in Tucson Mountain Park: Ahhhhh, pure bliss. #running #Tucson #trailrunning #sodamnedfun https://t.co/km2a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyZuker @HumanityCritic FAKE TRUMP Who is starting to look like a guy who needs an ambulance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: Trump is coming for John Lewis on Twitter. I'm sure he's trembling in fear; he's so unaccustomed to dealing with brutes. h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ass hole at the bar who needs attention. https://t.co/i8X6UBb6KZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you. Berne supporter. https://t.co/H63kyryzca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he have an orange moustache? https://t.co/64w5QJDODj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lJq2T8tH2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Eqz2V1Q4oO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Hillary as President we get Bill, the explainer in chief in the White House again. https://t.co/sa3F2kTu1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll legends and legends to be. https://t.co/hBCBXB0Bwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alena, you are Gorgeous. Awesome every day. Own it. https://t.co/BHtvNmrdtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just in: I'm voting Green Party, Democrates, include me out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nealy four decades ago Harvey Milk was assassinated. The haters are now called by different names and they have bigger guns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/BF3ByTWPUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodu Guthrie's list of living well resonate's with me fory resolutions. And yes, we are still fighting Fascism. http://t.co/kHBsbKOx7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a great year of beautiful moments. Caught on film, a herd of giant bubbles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderful gift from Rachel Tucker and what's his name. http://t.co/vnueM8IzfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a gift! In Performance: Sting and Rachel Tucker http://t.co/Kuqp8aoUte via @nytvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Show: Democrats Bow Down to Wall Street | Moyers &amp; Company | http://t.co/xE2iRtw4qf http://t.co/2J75Gocm83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren, well thought out. Let me know if you need password. http://t.co/HW9sSb7hwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Season&amp;#8217;s Greetings From The Supreme Leader http://t.co/h5uWd8wIaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a Canadian Prime Minister was cool. http://t.co/B606tHLZOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Verawriter Vera. You became my 2500th tweeter friend! Thanks for the invite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Verawriter: Larry Flynt announces plan to make pornographic parody of 'The Interview' ! Flynt says - @ajc via  http://t.co/nEHKG6yd13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gayregis: Hollywood has changed :((

#Hollywood #TheInterview http://t.co/CMWZB9OjmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leidya4552 Thank you Leidy for inviting me to join your tweet group. @MikeShandrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you my Tweet friends for keeping the vibe high and making your dreams come true. Abundance and health to you all. Peace on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Warren takes on Citigroup and its cronies in the White House. http://t.co/0l9nSfPl0L via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamMrAC Aaron, very cool vibe. Thanks for the invite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soulzinger when I came to Vancouver, one of the first things I did was sell my soul, but not on discount.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GinaMollock thanks Gina, helps to have zombie geeks on one's side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama couldn't fight, Warren Can http://t.co/QjXQSUGUrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from being a newbie lap-top yogi with Ekhart Yoga, I also practice Chi Kung outdoors whenever the weather... http://t.co/hmVqE0S76G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama fails to reign in CIA's dark culture http://t.co/IMf2Y4w6Eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenTuma Thanks for the invite, tho I have been struck by non-conformity twice, or possibly three times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoemPorns @ablackeyedpeace Good movie dialogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JgHankins22 I did book publicity when we were using typewriters. Even the Xerox wasn't around. Real old testament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaralaScott: Relying on others to believe, invest in or support your dream can keep it from coming to fruition when all it needs is you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaralaScott How can I resist such a beautiful mouthwatering smile? Thank you for allowing me to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Obama craftily killed off progressives in one fell swoop. http://t.co/5jkGTk7q6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama already has a seat at the table now that he's betrayed all the working stiffs. http://t.co/Ps879zGNVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking Up With Friends” by @lisagerber https://t.co/f03FnG4sg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas oil company Kinder Morgan and its patsy the Canadian Prime Minister are targets of First Nations protests... http://t.co/T3DSeCLYog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From 10 National Geographic Photographers Give Thanks for the Photos That Changed Them

I shot this image of... http://t.co/8dk1PCA9Z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luigi di Savoia, born on January 29, 1873, was just a few weeks old, as reformists in Madrid were putting the... http://t.co/mpY2GfiS8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christy Clark is in the back pockets of the oil &amp; gas barons. But now she's exposed by a grandmother. http://t.co/addkbsgEDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sowerbutt Your book screams for a TV series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaddyTiller From one explorer to another, there's always an itch you need to scratch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnHunter82 I hope you grow up to take up lots of vices and talk like Dorothy Parker. It's what all writers aspire to eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinarolsen writing on several fronts. A nice apt. in Kits makes the experience richer and the writing better. Much luck to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of artists and designers open their doors over the weekend. #eastvanculturecrawl http://t.co/SFhOyxS8QM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A recent civic election returned its Green mayor to office, defeating a corporate pipeline tool. Green Party wins... http://t.co/nUQnl5rNTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JvnFineArt such artistry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikevogler for my second marriage I got married in Reno, so how do you think that worked out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynnecazaly I am all-in to teaching business stuff with crayons and chalk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyDatingRx My first dating question: where's the off switch on a woman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver's urban design panel baffled by 21st century architecture http://t.co/csIz2aupHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I invite you to take a look at my screenplay project, "La Demoiselle" and "like" or comment.... http://t.co/CLelJJSYHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaDemoiselle Take a look at my screenplay project and "like" or "comment" .https://t.co/PoInakQgYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I invite you "like" this page. 

The painting was a recruiting poster for those who sailed to New France in the... http://t.co/PG8Nz7hOjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamonaWray Next time you are flying in my direction, stop by and we'll have a drink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@News1130radio @johnstreit1130 #vancouver design panel too far out of its comfort zone will choose bears and bric-a-brac with Canuck logos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@News1130radio @johnstreit1130 So, now what..Gastown is already a harrowing walk in the shadows day or night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@News1130radio @johnstreit1130 Too bad #Vancouver design jury can't see a superb feat of creating negative space where it's badly needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beach looking across Ipanema to Zona Sul. Spent a lot of time here after bicycling here, sweaty then jumping... http://t.co/7z2Y8ZdaHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendaLiddy You're Irish, you can't help but tell stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gandhi in the age of lululemon http://t.co/qxbQ381gvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am following your footsteps in the sand. Thanks for the walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Party of One": How Canadian PM Stephen Harper became a tool of the American far right. http://t.co/qcoih81l9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Party of One" exposes Canadian PM Stephen Harper's scandalous attack on Canadian democracy. http://t.co/qcoih81l9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22-year-old aide who PM Harper threw from the bus in #votersuppressionscandal defends himself. http://t.co/e6h8BBiqE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book "Party of One" sheds light on PM Harper's #votersuppressionscandal &amp; the aide who got thrown from the bus. http://t.co/e6h8BBiqE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space scares the sh#t out of the idiots for no other reason than it makes true believers feel small. http://t.co/qiXj9PrF4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamonaWray Romanian blood tastes like wine,yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Praise of Being Baffled http://t.co/KhHDVq7hyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm enchanted. That's quite an address!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cristiano Ronaldo dumps Irina shayk for Messi http://t.co/yQSCl8EUIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous martyrs remembered. http://t.co/lPFVXlRTRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The military culture receives a god like status these days of never-ending remote war, but their god is feckless... http://t.co/oo7rdo0COz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning 10 minute debate response on whether Islam is a religion of violence and hate. http://t.co/01OP5gCNgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeatherMoAndCo: This deserves a RT. Kathy Tomlinson speaks out: http://t.co/rugL8wlHQH #CBC #AmandaLang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to see how #AmandaLang jumped from MoneyHoney to corporate ideologue. http://t.co/uAuyHg5HlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which #AmandaLang is the @CBC actually defending? The well paid business guru, the @RBC operative and author, or the erstwhile journalist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNDLND: BREAKING: The Globe and Mail is refuting CBC's story about #AmandaLang http://t.co/O4l6L0uA8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NaomiAKlein: Remember: #AmandaLang was the "left" flank of the Lang/O'Leary debate show. That's how far CBC has lurched to the right si…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllieJaynes And imagine how much has gotten buried since 2013.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>