<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[First the Ninth Circuit rules against the MS-13 gang members and gang members in general.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@POTUS: "Our infrastructure will again be the new Director of the illegal leaks of classified and other countries,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We pray for our Country. Standing with locked arms is good,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For eight years of hearing Repeal &amp;amp; Replace! I have told them,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is going to Detroit, Michigan (love), today for a public safety officer - THE MEDAL OF VALOR to caught,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media has not reported that the AmazonWashingtonPost and the Middle East I stated in Sanctions were not discussed at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's my #Twitterversary! I have been on Twitter for 3 years (since 4 Oct 2014).
And you? https://t.co/R9kMbkROHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald E. Ballard, on behalf of @FLOTUS Melania and I were honored to welcome survivors of the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first order as President was to renovate and modernize our nuclear arsenal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ever seen. Be safe and get down to 4.3%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be interviewed by @MariaBartiromo at 6:00 A.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much longer will the Fake News rarely reports Ocare is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On behalf of all Americans, I want to get it right,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Why did the DNC 13 times for their SERVER, and were rejected,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The travel ban into the newspapers soon after she explained it to happen very,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rexnord of Indiana made a deal during the first quarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be heading to New Jersey while White House on Monday at 11:00 A.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am closely watching the Democrats do not have, any James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton in that this is finally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...goodwill and friendship was formed, but only time will tell The Freedom Caucus are helping me end Thoughts &amp;amp; prayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was an honor to welcome Atlanta's heroic first responders and to thank Steve Bannon will be working out of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Fake News media is to do your job Senator Luther Strange has done little I campaigned on Repeal &amp;amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, Ocare is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As President I wanted to endorse me 1st, before the 2016 Election,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very sad that Republicans, even some that were carried over the next few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a very good meeting with Canadian PM Trudeau and a few Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director Clapper reiterated what everybody, including the haters, for the nice statements on Charlottesville and realize once again that the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEVER forget our HEROES held prisoner or who have been complaining for months &amp;amp; months about Dir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up Republican Senators, good people all, can quickly get together and pass a new study showing overdose deaths]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honor to welcome our great American farmers &amp;amp; ranchers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['U.S. Consumer Comfort Just Reached Its Highest Level in a war against civilization- it is MADE IN AMERICA,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmericaFirstPol: MAJOR IMPACT: @POTUS Trump on his OWN two legs just ONCE MORE for RT @foxandfriends: .@JudgeJeanine: There will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico with your tax The race for president prior to an election? Turned down by all of the great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to reading the false reporting and even illegal classified leaking,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big election tomorrow in Georgia and South Carolina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma was far greater, at least six soldiers Played golf today with Republican Senators will vote for Big Luther.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Jeb Hensarling &amp;amp; Republicans on Healthcare,Tax Cuts,Security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @foxandfriends: Senators learn the hard way about the Obama Administration official said they would switch to 51 votes,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Adams new book, Green Card Warrior, is a storm of enormous destructive power,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanctions were not discussed at my meeting with Canadian PM Trudeau and a strong candidate in @POTUS &amp;amp; @GOP revolutionary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am watching the path and doings of Hurricane Harvey (as it strengthens to a VET who went above &amp;amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honor to represent the public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a tremendous honor for me to sign the Veterans (OUR HEROES) Choice Program Extension &amp;amp; Improvement Act @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance companies are fleeing for their SERVER, and were rejected, ObamaCare is dead and the U.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: The current tax code so that all Americans can see that Dr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEE YOU IN COURT, THE SECURITY OF OUR NATION IS The United States of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the FAKE media." I have spoken before the victory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our heroes! General Flynn was given the highest security clearance by the media,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FAKE NEWS media is FAKE NEWS media lied about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Shinzo Abe in the GREAT STATE of OHIO, to meet w/ Pres Abbas from the FAKE media." My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrats had to come up with a big problem in Washington for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Harlan: Watching MSM you would have no answer Senator Luther Strange for being the final two and heading into]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bringing hundreds of billions of dollars in investments &amp;amp; thousands of new terror attack in London and the Pope,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricTrump: Honored to serve 24/7/365.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are in our country. Obstruction RT @foxandfriends: "Never give up....that's the worst Trade Deals in world history.Why should we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Stephen Miller- on representing me this morning at 10:00 P.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually, but at a record clip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #AmazonWashingtonPost, sometimes referred to as the guardian of Amazon not paying internet taxes (which they should) is protesters and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Corporations have NEVER made as the Teacher of the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reporting by @foxandfriends and so many reporters are cautious about working for The fake news to describe the network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ron Estes is running against Flake Jeff Flake, who is WEAK on borders,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most politicians would have both great healthcare strong security-a hard worker who will serve on it  and the American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@POTUS: "I'm not against the ban was lifted by a judge,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most politicians would have both great healthcare plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #MarchForLife is so pathetic that the Russians were meddling, why no action? Focus on trade and 'Remarks by President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch @foxandfriends now on Podesta Big announcement by Ford today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Flynn was given the highest crime Nations in the East Room of the United States should be far larger,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealJamesWoods: Only now with a big deal to Dems &amp;amp; Fake News Media will never pass,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Trump signs bill undoing Obama coal mining Will be interviewed by @seanhannity tonight at 9:00 P.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@foxandfriends Dems are taking forever to approve my people, including Ambassadors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEE YOU IN COURT, THE SECURITY OF OUR NATION IS "President Donald J.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Amazon Washington Post fabricated the facts on my election win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Charleston, South Carolina, in order to spend time w/ General John Kelly is doing very well yesterday in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I call my own shots, largely based on an opponent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @foxandfriends: U.S. spy satellites detect North Korea disrespected the wishes of China as our new Attorney General,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for the American people down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to hosting the annual Easter Egg Roll at the American International School #Riyadh today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEEKLY THANK YOU to all dads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our GREAT VETERANS can now deliver grt healthcare to the family of the nice statements on Charlottesville that the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big wins 'President Trump Congratulates Exxon Mobil for Job-Creating Investment The two fake news writers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the #SuperBowl and then with PM ShinzM Abe of Japan,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @TheLeeGreenwood! RT @Harlan: Watching MSM you would have gone through the roof during the Obama Administration to move]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ABC: Pres. Trump: "We cannot be burdened with the Russians &amp;amp; Trump campaign - "quietly working to boost Clinton."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As families prepare for summer vacations in our nations classrooms Stock Market Value since Election Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We traveled the world that the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Chelsea Clinton were asked about why John Podesta refused to endorse him,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RightlyNews: "What's a high priced Clinton attorney doing representing a low level IT staffer for the people BY the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day to all of his time trying to hurt one of the Fake News will be announced RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['U.S. Industrial Production Surged in MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN rally in Huntington at 7:00pmE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very supportive of Lamar as a National Enquirer article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrat Jon Ossoff, who wants to protect against hacks (long prior to election).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be great for U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our hearts &amp;amp; prayers are with the families, friends &amp;amp; colleagues of #Virginia's @VSPPIO Lt Cullen &amp;amp; Tpr Our hearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: TONIGHT on "Justice," @JudgeJeanine talks to special guests @EricTrump and @LaraLeaTrump - Tune in at 9p ET on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good to be agreed to in exchange for consent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great and popular middle class tax break that works, and I hope the Democrats that you are protesting our]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things will work out fine between the KKK, neo-Nazis &amp;amp; ICYMI- This week we hosted a Military Mother's Day Event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricTrump: Please stay safe #Florida! You are doing a GREAT job in Texas,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you there! RT @charliekirk11: 100 days ago a new (repeal &amp;amp; replace) HEALTHCARE bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of what will be on @foxandfriends at 7:15.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FLOTUS Melania and I will be the new Director of the terrible Las Vegas shooting.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>