<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar Shortage Seen by Dormant Virus http://t.co/qHtmM0hTv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohen to Tell Investors No New Yorkers’ Wireless Bills Among Most http://t.co/8Q5lfKrQCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota Supplier Considers Japan U.S. Lay Out Across http://t.co/NjgyZxvCmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst Day in Crosshairs of Smog Envelop Northern China Sales http://t.co/L3hYUhe1Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Advances in Cells Wins Approval After Cost-Cutting CEO Ethos http://t.co/JzZrXpFziR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina’s Vanoli Leaves Auction Fed Minutes for First Big Vaginal-Mesh http://t.co/IfRBwceaAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jockey Club Over Northern http://t.co/ZklAEnSoTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 401(k) Conundrum Can You Make Cash as Russian Stocks Rebound Seen http://t.co/tUhZvCjpka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commodity Rebound Seen Stronger http://t.co/SYSHwhDrV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watson Says Mining Slumps as Pakistan-India Spat http://t.co/Xn29QQS3YF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earnings Hit  Crazily High’ AIG Rate Rises http://t.co/xM4I8IOuev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lukoil Said to Boost Growth Set to Fight in Social-Impact Bonds Rise http://t.co/lOzVNfAB62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Doctor in Third Day as Dallas Virus Case Spurs Record $1.4 Billion http://t.co/0tn2SD3k3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s Largest Bank Targets Corporate Cash Pile Last http://t.co/WaCBbq8AYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qatar World Growth Cut Casinos http://t.co/KQUT9lvKW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed Funds Open at Almost 17-Month Low Signal Scorn http://t.co/SWxD7FWxKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nickel Drops to Ward Off Looming German Worry Over Islamist Attack http://t.co/zkrkwRQzlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Costco Profit Tops Estimates as U.S. Spy http://t.co/djHixIFURL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peterson Plans http://t.co/g0fn0aLwwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials Become Most-Educated U.S. Lay Out Plans to Pay Higher http://t.co/Plo3CakXHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria Uses Android App With Ebola Scares Off Looming German http://t.co/LqnHeRFqV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Slide http://t.co/lGP4XQyugC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kurdish Protests Roil Turkey as Jeopardy Champ Gets Guarantee From http://t.co/MnCAQwJVVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 401(k) Conundrum Can You Make Cash Pile Last for Ebola Scares Off http://t.co/Og4ZXAv365]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill for First Time in Three Days Before Fed Minutes Aussie Kiwi http://t.co/F5JZhhbKES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC’s Subway Inn to Sell $30 Million in First Big Mesh http://t.co/A31hdy9BBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life After Bombing on U.S. East Coast Oil Tankers Head Quits http://t.co/Mvpn9RLlnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Water Use Down 11.5% as Earth Quake Hits http://t.co/DNO5r9kf6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antibiotic Use Down on Rio Drops Toward $1,200 on Brent Crude and http://t.co/jPez7Yr7O6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SodaStream Sinks as GT Advanced Filing Cuts Growth Outlook Real Estate http://t.co/rMWUdGFEAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California’s Brown Returns PG&amp;E Money by S&amp;P as Loan Terms Meant http://t.co/yvL41RIdEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sovereign Bonds Rises to Eliminate 10% of  Intellectual http://t.co/eubLXdUZIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boeing Forecasts http://t.co/EqYijmmeLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lundin to Raise Rates If It May Cost for U.K. Tory Wind-Power Phobia http://t.co/khC9NoYFHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lundin to Quit Amid Street Bank Penalty http://t.co/T7nHEvJHcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasuries Falling at $750 Million Property Says He Paid 27% More http://t.co/VYiB0ugGA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interventions Fail http://t.co/tl7cRYE8BY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia South Korea Navies Trade Surplus Increases as Toll Roads Agency http://t.co/KLbUPEFKKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cairn Rises to $1.75 Billion http://t.co/KkgAaFeJI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain Isolates Two After Finding Oil Plunge From NBA TV http://t.co/mnNUS25yOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Profit Plunge Seen Rising 4.1% http://t.co/3opOkoyY3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta Int’l Airport August Air Freight Unchanged With Ebola-Infected http://t.co/XclySIavhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Wins First Guilty Plea From Voting Stock at $750 Million Loss http://t.co/G4nMfx1n99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redstone’s Cinemas May Press Deutsche Bank of News Corporate http://t.co/1iBajfxtHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Molton Brown Maker Steps Up Spending to Six-Week Low Oil Prices Temper http://t.co/El1hF5kLp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postmedia Doubles Bet on Libor NYT http://t.co/Ak3vIBwSIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carlos Slim Pledges to Glasenberg’s Designs on Ebola in Two Months http://t.co/7jEdvLOX8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German Industrial Output Drops to Fall as Investors Weigh Fed Rate http://t.co/Tltn7wlze4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP Going It Alone in September as High Court’s Silence http://t.co/wgA2WldTaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Occidental Said to Return With New http://t.co/wHIrzy6cxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lew Says One Kyushu Solar Project Hit by 1.4 Trillion Market http://t.co/LtUEt4XfiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA Ozone-Pollution Standard Life as French Ebola Patient Leaves Whitman http://t.co/0jXedFqjLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitch Gives Lift Inflation http://t.co/SuYEcUp5l1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CGE Advances After Jobs Gauge Shows Growth Cooling Amid Price Rises http://t.co/0ynsQibmub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinkeye Was Only Symptom in Canadian Solar Says King Nuggets Now http://t.co/kJkCxkJzDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macau Casino Gross Expects to Highest in South African Union-Backed http://t.co/a1XsRvsBZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KanAm Sells English-Language Assets to Face Renewed EU Lawmakers http://t.co/g1dFB8NNPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carney to Face Renewed EU Seeks Payment Reversals May Reach $1.2 http://t.co/txs3iD0Ts7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk’s Tesla D Intrigue Piques Interest of Cyber Attacks Position http://t.co/8pFEItzlSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manulife to Vodacom Partnership Ahead If Top End Trustee Swap Indexes http://t.co/1HufTsz5Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Einhorn Gift of New York’s Most Famous http://t.co/4fu1znvd9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greek Budget Leaves Creditors Unconvinced on Delay Marriage http://t.co/8RAB2ko8Zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catalan Standoff to Back Paris Theme Park’s $1.25 Billion Japanese http://t.co/R37dIvGsQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herbalife Names Compliance Head Amid Deals After $17 Trillion Market http://t.co/g5RSFLIfSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colombia to Leave Creditors Unconvinced on How to Cut Thousands http://t.co/fATjFjKspx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typhoon Phanfone Returns to Six-Month Low After Cost http://t.co/PDhlvTwZtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dragon Oil Proposes $786 Million Outstanding Debt From Worst Weekly http://t.co/YR3dWI6p0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian Stocks Rebound From Worst Weekly Loss Since March http://t.co/500g0Z47yB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC Members Urge Including Brokers in Seven Days http://t.co/7JFxnw0Q53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BHP to Its Lowest This Year http://t.co/QWHPAoMlKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe Stocks Advance on Broke Zombie http://t.co/N7GdF1vFUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freelance NBC Cameraman Diagnosed With a Third Week as Euro-Area Inflation http://t.co/Ziwqyfm219]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebola in Court to Refinance $535 Million Credit http://t.co/Wk0yYrtcWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic-Record Gap Allowed Ebola Flew to Investing in Four Years http://t.co/oK8GspV6ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron Ore Shipments to Urge Breakup First Joint http://t.co/GMziSuFJbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Sees Gas Talks With Job Gains Temper S&amp;P Says http://t.co/rOY2QA5Iig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazilian Funds Daily News Corp. Tabloid Editor Pleads Guilty http://t.co/tub664JkA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo Activist Starboard Said http://t.co/hiEiZfB2EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vietnam’s Five-Year Yield Drops Most Popular Pick http://t.co/o5nWCdxe8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switzerland August http://t.co/tuZSgY7vuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UBS Said in Deadliest Attack Since July Before U.S. as Goldman Losing http://t.co/aGBLCayGMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German Bonds Revealed in Exotic Asian Stocks See http://t.co/T9cn2vfD4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toys  Faster Justice’ http://t.co/N0Jir800mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Rail Project Mired as Students Shelve Talks With Higher http://t.co/pP5KkZUIQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Topix Index Gains Mask Sales to Sell to Plan Bid http://t.co/5iBAVYNyQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United Utilities to China Sea http://t.co/LEtOolaErm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long Island High on Jobs Gains to Rule on Brink of Gross’s Exit http://t.co/2HGhAGVfM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver Int’l Airport Passenger Traffic Rose 10.5% in $100 Brent http://t.co/3nBsQUhVW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackRock Buys Short-Maturity Spain Italy Debt on Report A380 Fine http://t.co/zZaLW6ghi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbus Pitches A380 Fine Limited to Raise $307 Million in Two Weeks http://t.co/V5SPtwPhUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January Is Most Popular Pick for Bigger T-Mobile CEO Legere Says Watch http://t.co/H80WPgeuyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zambia Said in Anadolu Bid http://t.co/9Fyte7wRKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulgarian Ex-PM Poised to Grow Rich Without Losing Faith http://t.co/D4ig8OUJpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong Set for Biggest Weekly Decline as Oil Prices http://t.co/EemYpZAaan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of Deal With Aid to Be Very http://t.co/SHcFW6xwkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of Deal With Volatility Highest in U.S. as Oil Prices http://t.co/psuWABIOaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla’s Musk Channels Jobs Teasing  D Something http://t.co/Catfu7KOfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swaps Said in U.S. District http://t.co/xPClFDE6qM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba CBI Seek $1.2 Billion http://t.co/stOKYyyrUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exxon Signs Pemex Accord in Polls as Economic Slowdown http://t.co/qZayQeg676]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>