<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@whitemoosecafe Amy chance of starting a political party? The Stensonite Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg Bord Gais Energy Theater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan @leinsterrugby @Saracens What's your seat Anne? Very unhappy with our spot at Exeter game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocker that a rugby agent thinks this way.... https://t.co/vl81ypI53s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never seemed to fulfill his potential. https://t.co/JWPaiZgqeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbucsfan Shtap! Fantasy lock pairing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure he got a bollicking for the pat on the head. Otherwise he's been excellent. https://t.co/ADkJ9BABEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are they accepting them? :) https://t.co/XKn2Wx5V08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 Give Kockott a big cheer for me! Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throw in! Have Castres any decent hurlers? https://t.co/ZlL5O55g6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Colliniho Sorry I was being vague! Brive vs Worcester was played later than scheduled yesterday. That's an option if weather improves etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Colliniho Normally they play within 24 hours if there's a postponment. See Brive vs Worcester yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Colliniho Holy moley. That pic is something.
Normally they try to replay within 24 hrs if a match is postponed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh that's sloppy indeed. https://t.co/sG0hW9I0PB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never want to hear a CHEAT chant at a rugby match in Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad He kicked the ball out on the French tryline when England needed another score to win the Championship on points difference. He was smiling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster fans going to TP tomorrow: Please cheer Rory Kockott when his name is announced. Never Forget: France vs England 2015.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot stand that shower but let's see the other side do it first if it's not been done. No lobby group should be allowed to hide. https://t.co/Q9VwsOgHeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Influencer" has got to be the most pretentious term in 2018.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus how is this happening.

You didn't name her. She chose to come forward. https://t.co/9ijeCVhu7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulVStenson: I see we’ve made the news in both America and Australia today. This is good. Seems my approach was a lot more effective t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper I am in a DELIGHTFUL state of mind after your WONDERFUL Global Balding episode....yessssssssss....cheers! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There have been some legitimate points raised and a lot more lazy bandwagoning. https://t.co/hxR8arHaE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Owenins Yeah....I'm not getting into this again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanBuckl3y @JFitzpatrick92 @threeredkings Who goes in instead Ian? Sweetnam hasn't been playing. Wootton is still pretty raw. I understand the decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper @WrestlingSoup @JoeNumbas 1. Thoughts on Dolores O'Riordan &amp; Cranberries
2. How on earth have WWE managed to ruin Woken Matt.
3. NFL predictions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lennyabrahamson: Nothing to do with the rights and wrongs of the issues being discussed, but does anyone else find a certain ex-cyclist…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it with E*an in Brazil too: If you must mention someone use an asterisk. https://t.co/SLKAgOqVEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop feeding K*mmage. He is making €€€ from your mentions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Ah thanks for clarifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a conflict of interest here Simon? WRU bidding against other regions? https://t.co/aLwypAgTvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whitemoosecafe You've just sold Saturday lunch. I look forward to it. Keep up the fight for common sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotel rooms do cost a thing. @whitemoosecafe https://t.co/H9eGxzROcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't name anyone. So nah, not bullying. https://t.co/84It1rTY5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper DubyaCDubya 2000 couldn't even have wrecked Broken Matt. Embarrassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @lemonsrbitter Maybe it's just me but his conditioning looks a bit different. Perhaps he had bulked up too much 2-3 years ago. He looks much quicker on his feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper @WrestlingSoup @JoeNumbas Yeah it's big news here. Very iconic like Sinead O'Connor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TommyBowe14: I’ve spent most of my career in Belfast,
At first George said I wasn’t very fast,
I eventually found my gears,
Had some in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were you Cranberries fans? @WrestlingSoup  @JoeNumbas @iamjondraper https://t.co/cJN0z5Ys7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is really sad news. Incredible singer. RIP Dolores O'Riordan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful tweet. https://t.co/BJhfagPV9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Vikings: WHAT ON THE WORLD JUST HAPPENED??!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words. #NOvsMIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @ColmODonoghue No worries. I was responding to your "squad".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @ColmODonoghue I said squad too. :)
I really like Dillane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @ColmODonoghue Both of them is debatable. One? Sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmODonoghue @phog6189 Yeah I think that's an excellent set of options.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 There's definitely a change in policy of Kindly Feck Off Then once you sign abroad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 That is harsh yet we are stacked in the back three. I agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 In that case you've left Ireland for two years but are only ineligible to play for Ireland for one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 There's a good reason why Beirne gets ignored now. Say you sign a two year deal and intend to re-sign with Province X during Year 2, then it encourages others to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 Should they? Ireland is stacked at lock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a bit disappointed, yet at the same time respect, Grobler's decision to deny an interview request. It would be interesting to hear his side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW I don't think two years for knowingly taking substances to cheat is enough. However, meanwhile in the US the NFL doesn't give a fack as it only bans for 4 games on the first offence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop feeding P*ul K*mmage too. A man who has made his fortune because of doping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas But Aaron Rodgers is a BAAAAAAAD MAAAAAAAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 Do they bring him into the 23 next week I wonder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Earls is superb to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huwscarlet Money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter @timoconnorbl @epcrugby In short Glenn....yikes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I laughed out loud at thus. https://t.co/bow9XXFOzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbyrichmond Very good win today for Saints. Now let's hope Sarseholes lose and get knocked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robby Soup! @WrestlingSoup https://t.co/Vjwb8NzKSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That "cheat" chant is the worst. https://t.co/qarUXKszWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverNorgrove Abbayé Saint-Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissKeelyD I wouldn't waste your time on E*en.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a shit eating grin. https://t.co/jPbd9srzx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop feeding E*an McK*nna. Stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gramiq: Genius. Until today, if you Googled “Trump” and “shithole” all you got were hotel reviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnORafferty That museum is incredible. The cafe near the open square....that ceiling. Ridic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariaflan @phog6189 Keep up the good work Marie. Give it to the insecure craturs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveparkstaz Oh I agree this subject is very late. Perhaps I misunderstood your point. My bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She obviously hasn't THANKING GOD enough for good grammar. https://t.co/UIsv9yu97q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see that as looking for clicks like RugbyL*D or J*E. He mentions the player and references the quote. https://t.co/3Db9JTAL8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The conveyor belt from college football is so great that a rugby player would have to be incredibly talented to get a look in. https://t.co/rmjUtFOQjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloyjh @John_McGahon @WilliamsDuncan Cllr, if I called your office to say you're the worst councillor in Ireland is that criticism or abuse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_McGahon @molloyjh @WilliamsDuncan The only person that benefits is you in your little world.

Would you send an abusive letter to him? This is no different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_McGahon @molloyjh @WilliamsDuncan So why do you need to "at" him. Why does he need to read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_McGahon @molloyjh @WilliamsDuncan @ing someone is the online equivalent of sending an abusive letter. Do you do this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_McGahon @EimzT @WilliamsDuncan @Twitter So you have to inform someone directly that they are the worst professional scrum-half? Does that make you feel better? Do they have to read it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_McGahon @WilliamsDuncan Why do you feel the need to @ him? Dick move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 What on earth happened in the first half? I missed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath What happened to you in the second half?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell @MRSCDublin Cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell @MRSCDublin All ok Michelle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath @AnnLeinsterFan :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan @Vicki_McGrath NO BETS doesn't play for Leinster though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan @Vicki_McGrath Which Leinster player should I back for tryscorer tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @Colliniho Jeremy Loughman on short term deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath Excellent movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbyRichmond This is a great meme idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick, somebody ask the oppressed John W*ters what he thinks. https://t.co/y4RUxuLcBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyMick Horse had bolted Mick. Too many guns out there already. I don't think there's anything that can be done. Incredibly awful situation that is too far gone to properly fix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RVAwonk: daaaaaamn @NYDailyNews. https://t.co/Yhv2JN4j7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colliniho @MajorTomSavage Unfortunately the horse has bolted. An Australian buy-back style isn't practical. Can you imagine anyone turning up to homes trying to take guns away from some of the gun-nuts? There would be anarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colliniho @MajorTomSavage Yup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @merrionstreet No big exit. A bit anticlimactic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @merrionstreet Thanks Mike! Big entourage outside main entrance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's staying in the Shelbourne Hotel this evening? Gardai escort and taxis/buses outside.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>