<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ikea founder Ingvar Kamprad dies at 91 - BBC News https://t.co/DnN6Y3LYlT https://t.co/XQQQxsof1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could soon be a crime to blame Poland for Nazi atrocities, and Israel is appalled - Washington Post https://t.co/2xdP2EsTsU https://t.co/Z1K37tqi3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio fires chief of staff after allegations of 'improper conduct' - Washington Post https://t.co/9b5ZO1epdP https://t.co/JXaVNyT8pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 rescued in the Pacific after ferry sinking leaves them adrift for four days - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/mGiSGhtwU4 https://t.co/kf0gzQkjfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan foreign minister hopes for improved ties with China - ABC News https://t.co/8VDXdaWk9S https://t.co/wKRkUs9McZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US and South Korea to resume military exercises after Olympics https://t.co/xjtspHkM30 https://t.co/4ULMhEwEDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koch network to spend $20M selling GOP tax overhaul ahead of midterm elections - USA TODAY https://t.co/A8J9AS5a5q https://t.co/j57R38ZpAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was the Saturday Night Massacre? https://t.co/TwmGJkP1ak https://t.co/BbQ4DF0vXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity's Twitter Account Was 'Briefly Compromised,' Social Media Platform Says - TheWrap https://t.co/oGtJxgq1n1 https://t.co/Ro2crWFvgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employees claim reassignments are political retribution. Democrats say they're at least a waste of money. https://t.co/clzNVssdgi https://t.co/c2rdByu7vB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After feeling injustices by the administration, these people of color took action. They're running for office. https://t.co/hj2nq2oxsx https://t.co/cz0Ctwjbnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body found in pond believed to be missing 4-year-old boy, FBI says - CBS News https://t.co/yP7GiNhLSl https://t.co/jo1pr4RTBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Hundreds of employees leave EPA https://t.co/lFqX2FshOc https://t.co/9XaIkmIlUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body found in pond believed to be missing 4-year-old boy, FBI says - CBS News https://t.co/iz0DDtlzfW https://t.co/u8Zr8M3GJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property investor: Turpins' Texas home uninhabitable https://t.co/fPrfwtCx2c https://t.co/06as3m6Yvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump's favorability trends upward despite scandal-seeking news coverage - Washington Times https://t.co/bfPa3OQQBr https://t.co/oiyzVE7VgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casino mogul Steve Wynn resigns as RNC finance chair amid sexual assault allegations - USA TODAY https://t.co/s6H0ZiOP1F https://t.co/DT9GtrUKxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynn spoke at Mar-a-Lago last week https://t.co/P1RpD9h3gy https://t.co/fFcOC3CA4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holocaust survivor: The deniers are winning https://t.co/PD84l4kWsg https://t.co/IKh0lUvMFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calley: MSU should put aside '100s of millions' for Nassar victims; stop fighting lawsuits - Detroit Free Press https://t.co/R1y4B50Qxy https://t.co/HFNmv3d1HD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casino mogul and Republican National Committee finance chairman faces sexual misconduct allegations https://t.co/apgkH5uNrq https://t.co/F5sXyNTK3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University that employed Nassar to be scoured for abuse https://t.co/5GLlF2ApR4 https://t.co/F1RVqoEONs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton praises 'activist b----es supporting b----es' in online video - Fox News https://t.co/WpfHtNVlKQ https://t.co/2wVe4c8FWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN anchor reads emotional letter from classmate https://t.co/g4GPFZVXJk https://t.co/zNpuYWaWjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton 'dismayed' by harassment complaint involving ex-aide - News1130 https://t.co/5zzh2DYpbB https://t.co/4iT8ahgKBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear Trump thank Steve Wynn last week https://t.co/nRDOqK4X05 https://t.co/WbOhQA6jjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite terminal cancer, couple has a wedding to plan - https://t.co/W9TXaAfhTV https://t.co/rrgHIaWAlG https://t.co/R3bBHSeTB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pays tribute to International Holocaust Remembrance Day: 'Our nation is indebted to the Holocaust's survivors' - ABC News https://t.co/sg5Ha0s27p https://t.co/MyH9CemUS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caroline Wozniacki holds off Simona Halep for Australian Open title - USA TODAY https://t.co/3K6WKKAuae https://t.co/gTFtmPW40E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caroline Wozniacki wins Australian Open https://t.co/OeAlBSjfGd https://t.co/ExziZnFqup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: 40 dead, 140 wounded in Afghan car bombing - Washington Post https://t.co/zrpS7bVOYQ https://t.co/poR3WbdlJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US's Mattis: Diplomacy should impose reason on North Korea's Kim - Reuters https://t.co/II5Qi8Bq21 https://t.co/G9tKoeOQuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porn star's friend speaks out on Trump https://t.co/g58PEDs4vt https://t.co/6hQqEdXUcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detained Saudi billionaire Alwaleed predicts his troubles will end soon - CNBC https://t.co/Yw7K2OfjV9 https://t.co/X2tT5iSCvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las Vegas mogul calls allegations 'preposterous' https://t.co/CBwKMx6HDC https://t.co/PFla3ekmfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems slam Border Patrol targeting bus in Florida as 'arbitrary' and 'disruptive' - The Hill https://t.co/EuWv9stwq1 https://t.co/yvL8dOJlTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nutella discount sparks chaos in France https://t.co/pIGy1PUdLi https://t.co/zNbwJHS2j2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beaumont inmate nabbed with booze, snacks charged with escape - Beaumont Enterprise https://t.co/VyRS99hTvP https://t.co/YJUnC5COBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 500K in jail without a conviction https://t.co/u5ElhFS986 https://t.co/GtdnwyFetc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jury finds man guilty of manslaughter in death of ex-NFL player Joe McKnight - ESPN https://t.co/L8CfXWG8eN https://t.co/yjvbNHUSm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual harassment bill promises transparency but cuts watchdog https://t.co/ekTWb2ZsI3 https://t.co/PFU15ul1Ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Force One's new refrigerators cost $24 million - CNN https://t.co/yIZfly8jLG https://t.co/hU7tpB8VUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire couple's deaths were homicides, police say https://t.co/OCq5zGfcAd https://t.co/j6rlT6yq2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President is still fuming over the Russia probe and has the deputy attorney general in his crosshairs https://t.co/sy5R3sLe5v https://t.co/8nd3WS6znW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New refrigerators for Air Force One will cost you $24 million https://t.co/Fu7OiW5zsH https://t.co/Wzswrf0AdT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weekend of prayer and grieving after deadly school shooting https://t.co/SpXueXY6Sk https://t.co/xKizCVNSj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steps Trump has taken during the Russia investigation that could be troublesome https://t.co/Wte64zFXXi https://t.co/noB9FwQUPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kabul blast kills at least 40 and injures 140 https://t.co/08s14qjzvE https://t.co/PRrX3ZZz2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Tillerson's tense relationship https://t.co/kyUoZGKeg4 https://t.co/CJAbWWWU14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson's staff prints out the President's tweets for him to read https://t.co/ozNq53KFon https://t.co/H2dWBmxd70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bombardier ruling: Q&amp;A - BBC News https://t.co/sepl7vDSs3 https://t.co/A7EJIAmHXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Even a giant tax cut can't buy Trump the love of the billionaires https://t.co/AgnUhhxf2Y https://t.co/a14nbY7fpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The billionaires were found dead in their mansion. Now police say they were murdered. - Washington Post https://t.co/ihPwBHRjF5 https://t.co/moAv8BiTw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump's troubled Mideast peace bid https://t.co/X2BwQjBW5y https://t.co/gRsvMwizau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. James Kauffman, awaiting trial in wife's murder, found dead in jail - https://t.co/XVMLgkBGtM https://t.co/fYToYONcCh https://t.co/BRj6uEYpuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State Department employees hire attorneys, charging 'political retribution' https://t.co/lFu4pNR6gc https://t.co/VkXAE8gIfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grassley: Trump should let Mueller work https://t.co/vvvTsqGDid https://t.co/DSVIYTkCB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynn shares tumble 6% after reports of 'decades-long pattern of sexual misconduct' by CEO Steve Wynn - CNBC https://t.co/ZMFLhDIpZx https://t.co/aA51jCAptl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As hospitalizations increase nationwide, the CDC warns the fierce flu season may not have peaked yet https://t.co/9T3LXC1CPz https://t.co/1E0sj15k4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Chose to Shield a Top Adviser Accused of Harassment in 2008 - New York Times https://t.co/0tevtpnxoA https://t.co/Uj4V74CHab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI agent fatally shot kidnapping victim during botched raid in Houston - https://t.co/B3KTN0TMxD https://t.co/5tErZdfOhk https://t.co/VktqybuJWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannity flip flops on critique of Trump report https://t.co/F22QIAPuBG https://t.co/uzeFaZUKcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputies interrupt inmate's escape to pick up booze, food - Fox News https://t.co/u4drOIwG2S https://t.co/hPrfRFyG1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeers heard as Trump calls media 'fake' https://t.co/tqVYIGDEQN https://t.co/TImFqwJrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: America is open for business https://t.co/AxDCxTohHn https://t.co/cye1ofA1ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dutch Spied on Russian Group Tied to 2016 US Election Hack - Bloomberg https://t.co/pBJgkd9skc https://t.co/hRR5rnW8E6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump set to speak at Davos forum https://t.co/4QdBoEhkXA https://t.co/BuMZYQh7pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey's Erdogan vows to fight Kurdish forces as far as Iraq - BBC News https://t.co/ZBVD02k2zc https://t.co/oo83Fis88F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems tab a Kennedy to deliver State of the Union response - New York Post https://t.co/IkfGwlvoGX https://t.co/ozXuKC16OL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 times the WH denied Trump was considering firing Mueller https://t.co/8Bh20tzB2r https://t.co/Vvu6Nt8SwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wins over global elites at Davos. All it took was a $1.5 trillion tax cut. - Washington Post https://t.co/A7NHy3DXJw https://t.co/5dn0TpxaLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump takes salesman pitch to Davos https://t.co/zUxZaDaiKU https://t.co/NjAPzgNjlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump apologizes for retweeting anti-Muslim videos from far right British group - Washington Post https://t.co/jq9m0TlLBi https://t.co/zreACo713j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASEAN leaders watch India's national day parade - Washington Post https://t.co/6XdSAxTK4q https://t.co/2z3S9CHZRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump rolls out plan for path to citizenship for 1.8 million 'Dreamers' - Reuters https://t.co/MmRnLz5DoQ https://t.co/ya4NBr7SJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Kennedy will deliver Democratic response to Trump's State of the Union speech - Washington Post https://t.co/59Er6XJ8AH https://t.co/DVttaZdESl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump swaggers into Davos ready to take on the world https://t.co/3zpJO69zQV https://t.co/w21gCZUhpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got so many theories and suspicions about the All-Star draft - ESPN https://t.co/M2wDMVhCdZ https://t.co/TvpZ27Yf79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican lawmaker: If true, Mueller news is concerning https://t.co/4wTRUVXwfk https://t.co/CjRjuAHCVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russians got tens of thousands of Americans to RSVP for their phony political events on Facebook - Washington Post https://t.co/vN0XPOAbYS https://t.co/bMuCzRazyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lawyer says a president can't 'obstruct justice.' True? https://t.co/Y7fjltAekr https://t.co/z0eLzS95f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Pat Meehan will not seek reelection after sexual harassment furor - https://t.co/XVMLgkBGtM https://t.co/XkETS9H19T https://t.co/CuPLapj2ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In August, Trump said he hadn't thought of firing Mueller https://t.co/dmfwA3hy1I https://t.co/Q7S7f4Wj2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at odds with Kelly as a familiar pattern unfolds https://t.co/avIYr2GCsS https://t.co/zjKVZ3UaNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House jumps back into Dreamer battle with citizenship offer - Politico https://t.co/cbpOxgrWwJ https://t.co/hjkUtNxno0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employee Who Sent False Hawaii Missile Alert Is Refusing to Cooperate With FCC Investigation - TIME https://t.co/b00iNntXCu https://t.co/39cVvwN3uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adviser's history of fighting immigration https://t.co/PdAYpbWMuC https://t.co/MxYY818ZqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's citizenship comments could complicate things for GOP https://t.co/tdKtnLf9wv https://t.co/oDkvBY1110]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump supports path to citizenship for up to 1.8 million 'dreamers' in new White House proposal - Washington Post https://t.co/IoCKAZixre https://t.co/zYrvpcpXDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Economy Grew at 2.6% Rate in Fourth Quarter - New York Times https://t.co/52uhXqaDu4 https://t.co/1Xj8L1Z44H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade war could hit US industries in China https://t.co/85ZpBHMktZ https://t.co/n0eOFSb3zN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a North Korean Missile? Call the Cairo Embassy - New York Times https://t.co/PR86nAzU3r https://t.co/N6afUsn86i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump official defends tariff with can of soup https://t.co/4gLAaSF9sQ https://t.co/vXNrucCxEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Moore asks for money for legal expenses https://t.co/VGzx8wBwjN https://t.co/hPxi2AA5RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avalanche strikes crowded Mammoth Mountain: 'Essentially, the top of the mountain came loose' - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/PRHZiP6IB3 https://t.co/SeX5wIVfCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student used dad's gun to kill parents https://t.co/ujVyT8yohB https://t.co/HmdnJGQaIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Flake: GOP is in a 'bad place' https://t.co/ks0ofNCUaC https://t.co/Y3LDvr9fm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow-moving nor'easter hammers East Coast, kills at least eight - https://t.co/B3KTN0TMxD https://t.co/FrVA2GL2vK https://t.co/qDK5mTX5a8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First lady Melania to attend Gridiron dinner with Trump https://t.co/HaUEVUJVgG https://t.co/cvDx5y22KR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Homes underwater,' 900000 without power as deadly storm pushes out - CNN https://t.co/wKdncZn7hI https://t.co/rauZ3AN8Y9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>