<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/3SEQGtMhv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/s6vSrNUwhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/zeFK5Vn0yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/D8lwdXtTRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/5eTi6iUuRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two-party political parties in the US consists of the appointed and the disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/ad0NnyvUVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/B5SeMDC3Wa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/c9pyi89EOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/Ho4rTykGMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/GXwJRYFa1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/MAnkhgpp48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/5AiXcXEIos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/J19sjPX48b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/Ja32Zn0QLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/zxkJE81qMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/Jz46somJa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/MPyEZzt0g8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/zZycDdmNKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/UVPEDMIcFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/2NxI8odxrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/uNWSVCugi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/xVFSQOD079]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/zgRfE1VT7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/j9wHkZZMUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/uGygLY4WTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/hSfxZJZXdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/CPlfnTkal9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/EHr3XabJKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/Du6wXJ1Rzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/46fK13vSls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/z06Y4YgZYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/axHf1MKPg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/GXRUGNrRyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/1Wu9yMSAW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/DoxrCak49k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/7NOKVxhbD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/vm8LeoAZuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/S0SK6n3YD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/Y6PzJkrRge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/1bX7zqYs2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/JfZ8wtVMOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/JNT8mKQQy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/CqeFkeTzN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/SZjdXrjLa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/M7TNc4gMXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/8bAQWJKS19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/rxhGSChtW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/zdIVHtn83p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/54icLIDdE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/IPW9LKoCIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/205MQxiLk8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>