<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an empty tomb to remind us that nothing is hopeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had so many conversations this week that reminded me of how much I love the people of Restoration City!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions about marriage, divorce, remarriage and dating?  I'm jumping on Periscope tonight at 8 to answer them live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't imagine where I would be without a local church. Don't just attend one, connect deeply with one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbross319 ahead of schedule!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking over the talk for tomorrow at Restoration City and getting so fired up!  Hard passage, amazing truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying, longing and loving well in the aftermath of #Paris. [new post] https://t.co/zCPeqfbErj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel assures us that, given enough time, every act of evil will become a self-defeating proposition. #PrayForParis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst flourishes of fear and hate give rise to the greatest expressions of love and peace. #PrayForParis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus, draw near to #Paris and draw Paris near to You. #Pray4Paris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humility opens more doors than pride can ever break down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus meets us in places of awe inspired surrender: https://t.co/PjtH0wKML4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to have @catalystleader in DC on Tuesday.  Still time to register! https://t.co/tQVhXJONzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally some good news on my screen! https://t.co/W54GrGB9jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Christians - don’t be afraid to celebrate #VeteransDay. [New Post] https://t.co/3LZvbSU1up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for the sacrifice, courage and service of our veterans. You defend our freedom and we don't say thank you often enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blessing of God can never be found outside the will of God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real passion doesn't wait for perfect conditions. Take the plunge today and pursue what you love! @… https://t.co/SW3eZekmj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ego is rarely accompanied by great ability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clear, helpful answer to a common question!  Thanks @jdgreear. https://t.co/KK9oyn105n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I look to myself, I have little to write or preach about.  When I look to Christ and His Word, I find a limitless sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrogance is insecurity’s favorite mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lack of obedience to Jesus indicates a lack of love for Jesus. (Jn. 14:24) Fight the cause, not the symptom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love for Jesus will flourish into obedience to Jesus.(Jn.14:23)  But if you start with obedience, it won’t flourish into love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when the storm builds, God is at work for good. https://t.co/KJ07zwCo7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that @passion268 is in my hometown of Syracuse tonight.  Never thought this day would come! https://t.co/tWequzZ50K #evensocome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the unexpected parts of this city. #DC doesn't conform to all the stereotypes! https://t.co/epKfdXR7CE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“These things I have spoken to you so that my My joy may be in you, and that your joy may be made full.” (Jn. 15:11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely cannot wait for #Passion2016. Jesus uses these days in the most unimaginable ways.… https://t.co/I6FhQVI70V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your success is predicated on someone else’s failure, you’ve already failed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your greatest contributions will never be made by imitating someone else. Find, trust and develop your own voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of my frustration with others is misplaced frustration with myself. Take responsibility before assigning blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most satisfying leaps of faith often come from illogical obedience to the still, small voice of God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing the work of Christ absent the power of Christ is impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So amazing!! https://t.co/J0iIHtJi9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Sports so true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurt, frustrated, angry? Pray it through before you tweet it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @donaldmiller: Keep your phone off in the morning until you've finished working on your most important project. Do this for a year and y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Marine Corps Marathon - one more reason to love #DC! https://t.co/fKu9uXmROa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roar!!  #MarineCorpsMarathon #servedcfall2015 https://t.co/hIJqVec1et]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Getting ready for the Marine Corps Marathon to roll through Crystal City! https://t.co/i8Uc3ysg3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today may just have been my favorite day yet with Restoration City Church! Loved seeing so many… https://t.co/aDZs65dfBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love being at Martha's Table for #ServeDC2015! https://t.co/LEbiF3wEUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a rush hour trip on metro to get me rethinking my position on purgatory. Might just be real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @AnnVoskamp and @JeffersonBethke for giving us something so good to think about: https://t.co/wuHOCKxci2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We free our souls to genuinely love when we stop weighing others down with expectations that only Jesus can fulfill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is beyond frustrating if you use Him as a means to an end &amp; beyond satisfying if you pursue Him as the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God wants intimacy with you more than activity from you. Revelation 3:20, "“Behold, I stand at… https://t.co/POZ4GSDz4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City! Don't forget - we're gathering in the Crystal City Marriott this morning! Right next to the Synetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's love for you is defined by the beauty of the cross, not the horror of your sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking off the Christmas season tomorrow at Restoration City.  So excited!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The extent of your leadership will be determined by the depth of your sacrifice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is doing amazing things through New Hope Initiative. So grateful for Karen &amp; Sandy Baird and… https://t.co/taifrmy0lI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person you're most nervous about inviting to church might just be the one who needs it most. #BeBold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being great at one thing requires being good at saying no to many other things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I promise your life will be more impacted by the books you read than the shows you watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physical intimacy should be a result of, not a substitute for, spiritual intimacy. [new blog]: https://t.co/4xHmTqGvDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been missing these two crazies and their gorgeous Mom. So glad we'll all be reunited today! I… https://t.co/Hya1Ojcrax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace makes vulnerability less terrifying and healing more attainable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cultivate faithfulness. God will cultivate influence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jamesmarshallg: "To be little with God is to be little for God." - E.M. Bounds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion2016 prices jump at midnight. Get registered now! These will be amazing, life shaping,… https://t.co/FXdDykNzXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying grateful in a fallen world requires a massive perspective shift. [new blog] https://t.co/3Cutn9wffU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing invigorates my faith like seeing someone else come to faith. Fresh life is a gift to the whole church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't understand the gospel and be indifferent to Jesus.  The gospel demands a response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge honor to gather here with Laura's family and baptize her brother, Greg. Love that my… https://t.co/uztuc1JIim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love watching you find your way, little man. https://t.co/AejYHFFlnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude is the evidence of a deep awareness of grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Happy Thanksgiving, Restoration City! https://t.co/HKfiF8I7Zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for a Savior who shines brightest when life is darkest. #HappyThanksgiving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good to be back in RDU - home away from home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus did not come to teach us versus them. He came to model us for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the gospel seriously frees us from having to take ourselves seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s terrifyingly possible to reject the prosperity gospel in your head while still embracing it in your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the church! Absolutely nothing else like it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look. They're becoming friends. https://t.co/mEO5X0v93j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swelchipedia those will definitely put you to the test!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear is never the Christian response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any hope for a miserable marriage? [new blog] https://t.co/O956V9CpkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May we always meet the cowardice of terror with the courage of compassion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for a great day @CatalystLeader. Loved having you in DC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCooP so true! Love you, bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you trust Jesus with your soul, you can also trust Him with your singleness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! Praying every gift, blessing, joy and moment of today guides your heart to… https://t.co/4pKD0oNlbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus didn’t come to do a victory lap with the conquerors. He came to dwell among those suffering in the darkness of shattered dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Restoration City! Take 2 minutes and pray with me that Jesus will be glorified in our 4pm gathering!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the A/C is running.  Experiencing complete holiday disorientation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won’t find the hope of Christmas in the hype. It’s in the Baby born to save the world. [new post]:https://t.co/FLRLuKSxaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one is more ready to communicate God's grace than someone who has faced his own desperate need for it." - @PaulTripp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relax. Knowing we have a perfect Christ takes the pressure off creating a perfect Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can try writing a Christmas Eve sermon without one of these but I wouldn't recommend it! @… https://t.co/yn0v5uqFbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Eve.
4PM.
Synetic Theater in Crystal City.
Love to have you with us! https://t.co/8f2kQ0LorZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning so much about wonder, joy and being in the moment from this guy! https://t.co/igtBOuecSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of those Sundays that leaves you thinking: Wow! Jesus, you are amazing!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved hanging out with this team at ICE! Love these guys! @ Gaylord National Resort &amp; Convention… https://t.co/OgsTXstj7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to bring school supplies and/or gift cards with you tomorrow, Restoration City!  #LiveForRestoration https://t.co/3rw2DV1pml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Sunday is a great chance to invite people to church with you. Don't miss it!! [new post]: https://t.co/ydji4fLXlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoiding conflict is impossible.  Ignoring it is deadly.  Resolving it is liberating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!  Loved the response last Sunday and can't wait to see even more this week!! https://t.co/QbBvCn6fSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sin breaks. God restores.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>