<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/FpMVW4vQOZ https://t.co/C8jT1XYKiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCabe's legal defense fund exceeds fundraising goal twice: The fundraising page for a legal defense fund for fired former FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe has managed to raise $500,000 in its first 48 hours. https://t.co/OKlnMqcgTs https://t.co/hUqtaIEe58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Campaign Developer: Job Description: Position Description We have an immediate need for an Adobe Campaign Manager (ACM) Developer to join our team to work in our Detroit, MI location. The ACM Developer uses technical expertise to ensure successful… https://t.co/C2WjPyxYfJ https://t.co/Hm8pIqzTxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/YKzK8YtNdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/g9zZBxnDRh https://t.co/tRDs6T1Y6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Consultant: Developer Consultant What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At the heart… https://t.co/X0DGvGVLfF https://t.co/GZdN01KkuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Data Architect Data Architect Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans Highest in Customer… https://t.co/lzAAnsMdPH https://t.co/soypHCyhoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Are you thrilled to work on the latest in in-dash navigation and services for cars? TomTom’s engineering teams are challenging, fast-paced environments where people are empowered to make the best decisions. As a member of a scrum team… https://t.co/BkescVAoBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain in memoir: Maybe I'll be gone before you hear this: The contentious relationship between Sen. John McCain (R-AZ) and President Trump remains, even as McCain continues with his cancer treatments. CNN's Polo Sandoval reports. https://t.co/bFiHez4MCb https://t.co/hPGJBr0GeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs a strong, proven… https://t.co/jSVZ42bA8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Service Analyst – Logging: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/hTzG8axxfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/7LpwosRepo https://t.co/xqPbwO6QLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer-Oakland County: SUMMARY Responsible to design, develop, document and deploy ASP .Net MVC applications and modules. Interact with other developers to collaborate for efficient and creative software development. Will maintain code… https://t.co/uKzSln5t04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/pecvpfmJjV https://t.co/BDDwu7ov81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy, Cohen and Trump: What you should know: Everything you need to know about the saga between Stormy Daniels, Michael Cohen and President Trump. https://t.co/ES6XGnsKP9 https://t.co/LCBVoco3kZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Sales Director: The Regional Sales Director position is a remote based sales management position. This position is directly responsible for supporting revenue goals for the company through managing and motivating a regional sales team of… https://t.co/g7x3R6HNlM https://t.co/8cm7USTwzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/tKivWzYwHd https://t.co/SXmmcVxGh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Researcher: Senior UX Researcher – Detroit, MI Our team achieves more. So can you. We value autonomy and responsibility. Our ambition is to craft future of navigation experience and make autonomous driving a reality. We expect of every team… https://t.co/AGyAYmiV3R https://t.co/wzpIwXj8Za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance Professionals Wanted: NATIONAL DIRECT OFFERS LICENSED LIFE INSURANCE AGENTS TOP COMPENSATION! WE ARE EXPANDING OUR REGIONS NATIONWIDE AND WE ARE LOOKING FOR AGENTS AND AGENCIES WHO ARE READY TO RECEIVE A RAISE! OUR MOTTO IS “WHY WORK FOR… https://t.co/QobYgh2Ndw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/OxxY85EMDk https://t.co/YUZbOMs27z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels makes cameo on 'SNL' to mock Trump: Adult film star Stormy Daniels appeared in "Saturday Night Live's" cold open alongside many other big names that surround President Donald Trump. https://t.co/qt9BCEnmY6 https://t.co/E8XKnCFBhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Engineer: IT Engineer Primary Skills LINUX,C++,SHELL SCRIPTING,C,CIFS,Electronic Data Interchange Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking IT Engineer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job… https://t.co/VA6YQ5vjG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Desktop Apps: Software Engineer – Desktop Apps Software Engineer – Desktop Apps Company Amrock Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re Amrock, the nation’s largest fintech provider of title insurance,… https://t.co/hJoxmaWPPo https://t.co/D73069HgQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge in Manafort case says Mueller's aim is to hurt Trump: A federal judge expressed deep skepticism Friday of special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation in the bank fraud case against former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort, at one point… https://t.co/PtsQDwabWU https://t.co/Mk39rz1rBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android| Detroit MI| 6 Months | Positions -3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/QP9g5Ad2mV https://t.co/UmugwsQqY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/DeKgqp3JKA https://t.co/pyfrxRNb9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Backend: Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Company Sift LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the… https://t.co/rvMAgUF6LI https://t.co/H8hwItzNHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Regulators Demand Cambridge Analytica Hand Over User Data: David Carroll, a professor at Parsons School of Design, might finally get to see everything Cambridge Analytica knows about him. https://t.co/i4o00cQUIh https://t.co/ON2E5Xxs0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (BPM): Software Engineer (BPM) Software Engineer (BPM) Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken… https://t.co/Aoh6b1nNFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows cop kicking suspect in head: A Miami police officer has been relieved of duty after a video showed him kicking a suspect in the head, as he was lying on the ground getting handcuffed. https://t.co/dqFpyy6APm https://t.co/ZOvrfm4gh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ArcGIS Developer: About Connected Ecosystem Integration (CEI): At CEI, we don’t design the transportation. We design the transportation experience. CEI Environment team employees manage the technology enabling a new generation of connected vehicles. This… https://t.co/slhOzrKAao https://t.co/vZ8rtjaSiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager Associate Project Manager Company Xenith, LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We are a team of designers and engineers, players and parents, dreamers and doers. We care about… https://t.co/hWjrrbNcWw https://t.co/hOCFr4pdOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Primary Skills SSIS,SSAS,Design,SSRS,T-SQL,coding Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking SQL Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client . Job Description: Engagement… https://t.co/RI5ycQl7yU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst: Senior Data Analyst Senior Data Analyst Company Rock Connections LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are Rock Connections is a growing strategic marketing company that helps clients increase their revenue from… https://t.co/UrSE7xx14Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/HXGXs5Byfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The initiation into 'Star Wars' for our kids: Assuming you already know why "Star Wars" is so important (which I detailed in a previous genuflecting column), I'll make the jump to light speed and get to a parenting question to which I have given a… https://t.co/m4ZVXsSVT8 https://t.co/Mt6swFyAyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-16108 Location: detroit, Michigan Hi, This is Shipra from Enterprise Solution Inc. I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Please send your updated resume if interested for this role. Role:… https://t.co/saH0aODjiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Insurance Sales: NATIONAL DIRECT OFFERS LICENSED LIFE INSURANCE AGENTS TOP COMPENSATION! WE ARE EXPANDING OUR REGIONS NATIONWIDE AND WE ARE LOOKING FOR AGENTS AND AGENCIES WHO ARE READY TO RECEIVE A RAISE! OUR MOTTO IS “WHY WORK FOR ANYTHING LESS… https://t.co/BMeU61O13e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst| Detroit MI| 1 Year | Position-1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES The primary responsibility is to be responsive to our monitoring/paging system and manning the Connected Consumers Innovation Lab (CCIL) Manages the resolution of… https://t.co/KB3wYFuKNM https://t.co/kcHBouzw6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A CNN review of the EPA chief's documentation from races in Oklahoma raises ethical and legal questions: A CNN analysis has found that embattled Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt paid himself nearly $65,000 in reimbursements from… https://t.co/7Jnr654fga https://t.co/ZCfdOJI3RG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/MpX9aLQ29s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Artificial Intelligence Can—and Can't—Fix Facebook: Facebook is counting on artificial intelligence to remedy problems including violent imagery, hate speech, and fake news. It's making progress, but big hurdles remain. https://t.co/GMn4yumHLD https://t.co/sc7w3aJROv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/0D3oBSaOzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance Professionals Wanted: NATIONAL DIRECT OFFERS LICENSED LIFE INSURANCE AGENTS TOP COMPENSATION! WE ARE EXPANDING OUR REGIONS NATIONWIDE AND WE ARE LOOKING FOR AGENTS AND AGENCIES WHO ARE READY TO RECEIVE A RAISE! OUR MOTTO IS “WHY WORK FOR… https://t.co/IaUoLjJUr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer, Identity: Application Developer, Identity Application Developer, Identity Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D… https://t.co/yF2wKpx5Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/0ogqMS4Bk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer Backend: Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Company Sift LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the… https://t.co/dZlJNsAWrf https://t.co/Gxpw5IzcBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Primary Skills SSIS,SSAS,Design,SSRS,T-SQL,coding Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking SQL Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client . Job Description: Engagement… https://t.co/5QtKTnWRfd https://t.co/crBgcPeKWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst: Senior Data Analyst Senior Data Analyst Company Rock Connections LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are Rock Connections is a growing strategic marketing company that helps clients increase their revenue from… https://t.co/WKmz2W3xvX https://t.co/U6U1mo7k5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final Expense Agent – Cash Bonuses Paid: NATIONAL DIRECT OFFERS LICENSED LIFE INSURANCE AGENTS TOP COMPENSATION! WE ARE EXPANDING OUR REGIONS NATIONWIDE AND WE ARE LOOKING FOR AGENTS AND AGENCIES WHO ARE READY TO RECEIVE A RAISE! OUR MOTTO IS “WHY WORK… https://t.co/HzPsBDH3zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Instagram #Dogs and #Cats Are Training Facebook's AI: Paying humans to label images can get expensive. So Facebook turned to 3.5 billion Instagram photos. https://t.co/F5VLpZsuu8 https://t.co/1p6Sre4Kup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Insurance Agent: NATIONAL DIRECT OFFERS LICENSED LIFE INSURANCE AGENTS TOP COMPENSATION! WE ARE EXPANDING OUR REGIONS NATIONWIDE AND WE ARE LOOKING FOR AGENTS AND AGENCIES WHO ARE READY TO RECEIVE A RAISE! OUR MOTTO IS “WHY WORK FOR ANYTHING LESS… https://t.co/HGD7CPpa2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Solution Architect Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans Highest in… https://t.co/XbC6ggIjXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/aAwgViNSSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Armour still under siege in the US https://t.co/Jb9eGdLE7v https://t.co/EDro9bKrHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A California Ruling Could Force Uber and Lyft to Change How They Operate: The California Supreme Court said more workers should be classified as employees, hurting companies such as Uber and Lyft that treat workers as contractors. https://t.co/5LJaWtWDwr https://t.co/5paBxXrOTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 7 months ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/yZOFGeLNwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/4frsBG57nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/RQQ0aQx288]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH says Trump's medical records were taken, but it wasn't a raid https://t.co/LnECJ93UBj https://t.co/lx413e9TjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/wFjI80OpYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg Says It Will Take 3 Years to Fix Facebook: In an exclusive in-person interview, Zuckerberg discusses F8 and Facebook's trust issues. https://t.co/1vmptIHWrd https://t.co/Y2xuIYUXRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Release Engineer for DTA Products: Detroit (Headquarters) Test Release Engineer for DTA Products As a successful family-owned company on a path to global growth, the Brose Group offers challenging responsibilities and exciting career opportunities… https://t.co/JrNxGHi6SM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Consultant: Developer Consultant What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At the heart… https://t.co/VAYpV9xODC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Silicon Valley Lawmaker Has a Plan to Regulate Tech: US Representative Ro Khanna wants tougher scrutiny on tech mergers and an "Internet Bill of Rights" for users. https://t.co/I20Ps0btaR https://t.co/FHB6VIRXvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/y0ZAw4vhfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Primary Skills SSIS,SSAS,Design,SSRS,T-SQL,coding Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking SQL Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client . Job Description: Engagement… https://t.co/NuDznc53Nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pandora Learns the Cost of Ads, and of Subscriptions: A 21-month study finds that as users are fed more ads, they listen less; some subscribe, but not enough to compensate for lost ad revenue. https://t.co/S3VgW4jnD4 https://t.co/hDhY6zAE00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Application Engineer: We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans “Highest in Customer Satisfaction in Primary Mortgage Origination” for the past eight consecutive years, 2010 – 2017.… https://t.co/1X0GlnEOTy https://t.co/SsuhF1IJv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (DBA): Job Description: Administers, maintains, develops and implements policies and procedures for ensuring the security and integrity of the company databases. Implements data models and database designs, data access and table… https://t.co/ymGKcUCiCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Description: Responsibilities: Develop web applications. Perform tasks that include technical design, code development, documentation, unit and integration tests, troubleshoot and bug fix and test plan generation. Work together with… https://t.co/d9bRR7Er8i https://t.co/w3VS65fdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Telecommunications: We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans “Highest in Customer Satisfaction in Primary Mortgage Origination” for the past eight consecutive years, 2010 –… https://t.co/iMmL4WZH1e https://t.co/ffzg9kM4VV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Integrator: Xenith is a team of designers and engineers, dreamers and doers. We care about athletes’ successes in sports and life, so we are uncompromising when it comes to our protective gear’s design, fit, feel and performance. Every helmet we… https://t.co/v27kxfBi1i https://t.co/Q9G8Zzfzaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Inspector: Construction Inspector Beam, Longest &amp; Neff, LLC (BLN), is a leading provider of engineering, construction and technical services for public agencies and private sector companies around the United States. The Company offers a… https://t.co/TNHfWPJsP9 https://t.co/Zxf2suCqa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans “Highest in Customer Satisfaction in Primary Mortgage Origination” for the past eight consecutive years, 2010 – 2017. The company… https://t.co/6gcVdOlRwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sprint/T-Mobile Merger Is Huge—But a Lot of Questions Remain: The massive deal still has to be approved by regulators, and that may not be as easy as it sounds. https://t.co/7b72oOucaM https://t.co/aI8Wiu18Ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (BPM): We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans “Highest in Customer Satisfaction in Primary Mortgage Origination” for the past eight consecutive years, 2010 – 2017. The… https://t.co/iOuAcEfqvN https://t.co/0NAt0pL5gY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Campaign Developer: Job Description: Position Description We have an immediate need for an Adobe Campaign Manager (ACM) Developer to join our team to work in our Detroit, MI location. The ACM Developer uses technical expertise to ensure successful… https://t.co/VGx8u0vH5E https://t.co/8Zb1iduE9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer, Identity: We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken Loans “Highest in Customer Satisfaction in Primary Mortgage Origination” for the past eight consecutive years, 2010 – 2017.… https://t.co/bQYXbP7hCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In court, Trump's fortunes are plummeting https://t.co/x5UNWZMB5X https://t.co/nHCG7W0JIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. NOC Technician: Sr. NOC Technician Sr. NOC Technician Company Rocket Fiber LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are Rocket Fiber is a Detroit-based fiber-optic Internet provider that’s bringing rocket-speed gigabit Internet and HDTV… https://t.co/Qk70vvdNBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Analyst for Infotainment| Detroit MI|10 Months| Positions- 2: THE CANDIDATE MUST HAVE THE FOLLOWING SKILLSET/ATTRIBUTES: Experience creating user experience artifacts such as USER STORIES, STORYBOARDS AND WIREFRAMES Problem solving… https://t.co/NSRXx5WtJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (DBA): Job Description: Administers, maintains, develops and implements policies and procedures for ensuring the security and integrity of the company databases. Implements data models and database designs, data access and table… https://t.co/sQz1s4yy0Z https://t.co/G0n0r0jxIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Senior iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for a Senior iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in downtown… https://t.co/vcqkSWuUo6 https://t.co/Sx8xrwvpa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Inspector: Construction Inspector Beam, Longest &amp; Neff, LLC (BLN), is a leading provider of engineering, construction and technical services for public agencies and private sector companies around the United States. The Company offers a… https://t.co/AzNwAJchj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yardi System Administrator: Yardi System Administrator Yardi System Administrator Company Bedrock Management Services LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are About Bedrock Detroit-based Bedrock is a full-service real estate firm… https://t.co/CAVEGxyJ0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/h2aS840tqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/Ltp3eE97ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Inspector: Construction Inspector Beam, Longest &amp; Neff, LLC (BLN), is a leading provider of engineering, construction and technical services for public agencies and private sector companies around the United States. The Company offers a… https://t.co/WzTyQ5I4oH https://t.co/F8NYnyc42o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See Kim's 12 guards run alongside limo: As Kim Jong Un drove away from the early session of his summit with South Korean President Moon Jae-in, 12 bodyguards were seen running beside the vehicle. https://t.co/Orm5kqAnyx https://t.co/gcRXHnz9OX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected Golden State Killer enters no plea at court appearance: Joseph James DeAngelo, who police believe is the Golden State Killer, appeared in a California court Friday, but did not enter a plea to the murder charges he faces in the 1978 deaths of… https://t.co/K9fN9JtgoH https://t.co/ltyk9NDvpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Cofounder Sergey Brin Warns of AI's Dark Side: Google cofounder calls advances in artificial intelligence "the most significant development in computing in my lifetime,” but warns of ethical concerns. https://t.co/fPn9BbqVA2 https://t.co/CZqigaBY60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Campaign Developer: Job Description: Position Description We have an immediate need for an Adobe Campaign Manager (ACM) Developer to join our team to work in our Detroit, MI location. The ACM Developer uses technical expertise to ensure successful… https://t.co/nECCQgKGAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Simple antibiotic reduced child deaths dramatically: Giving the antibiotic azithromycin twice a year to young children in sub-Saharan Africa reduced childhood deaths by 13.5%, a new study has shown. https://t.co/05wDS5ciW7 https://t.co/Wxsd8cRU2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Manager: Compuware is unlike any 40-year-old software company you’ve ever seen; we are nimble, fast and obsessed with technical excellence and continuous improvement. We empower the world’s largest companies to excel in the digital… https://t.co/ehTXGz5XCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems and Logging Senior Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/D9qN4Lfm0e https://t.co/bwZllWxtWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt shows America its problem: The federal government's top ethics official has asked the Environmental Protection Agency to take "appropriate actions to address any violations" rising from the behavior of the agency's administrator, Scott Pruitt. https://t.co/9stq53QXnW https://t.co/XXSsLliWS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry-level Mainframe Software Developer: As the world continues to rely on the unmatched stability and consistency of the mainframe to support business-critical applications, Compuware provides the software, experts and best practices to ensure those… https://t.co/hvvtAVzJG4 https://t.co/SwhdX7i4Vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Engineer – Detroit, MI: Revature has partnered with a Fortune 500 company to find and develop a strong team of 20 Entry Level Software Engineers to work on next gen software solutions. This is an excellent opportunity for an… https://t.co/j6WKleeoV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heated exchange between Comey and Cooper: Former FBI director James Comey defends his decision to share memos with the media as a "private citizen," at the CNN Town Hall with Anderson Cooper. https://t.co/b5nf33WDFi https://t.co/APjph5IJem]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>