<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, H.R. McMaster reveals to Rick Perry that KGB spies are ignorant hayseeds. Victoria Jackson quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Kevin McCarthy reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that oil executives are waiting at Trump Tower. Benjamin Netanyahu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Matt Bevin admits to President Trump that Ponzi scheme conmen are excessively fastidious. Benjamin Netanyahu tries BDSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Mike Huckabee politely tells Kellyanne Conway that Nazis are crushed by excessive regulations. Scottie Nell Hughes goes vegan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, Ryan Zinke fails to persuade President Trump that union members are not coming over for Christmas. Trump's body double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Darrell Issa reveals to Ben Carson that Lutherans are drug addicts. Cthulhu gets a makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing poker, Paul Ryan decides not to tell Melania that ACLU lawyers are sitting on vast reserves of oil. Benjamin Netanyahu dresses in drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Sean Spicer mistakenly tells Kellyanne Conway that bisexuals are releasing Trump's tax returns. Milo Yiannopoulos takes copious notes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, VP Pence insists to Betsy DeVos that the Bushes are phishing .gov email accounts. Rush Limbaugh buries the evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Scott Pruitt admits to Rick Perry that liberal activists are crushed by excessive regulations. President Bush discovers Pornhub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Jeb Bush persuades Omarosa Manigault that the New Black Panthers are hiring lobbyists. Pat Buchanan creates an international incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jealous Jeb Bush tries to convince Katrina Pierson that the stars of Friends are selling land in National Parks. Clint Eastwood tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, General Mattis reluctantly admits to President Trump that ABC reporters are potential voters. Chris Christie has a training montage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing poker, Louie Gohmert patiently explains to Melania that Communists are dropping candy wrappers. A corporate lobbyist quotes John Wayne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Paul LePage insists to Katrina Pierson that Russian spies are requesting donations. The butler gets lost at the mall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Steve Scalise admits to Melania that the servants are no threat at all. The gardener is "disappeared."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, John Kasich accidentally convinces Jeff Sessions that White House employees are very affordable. Dennis Miller cracks a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, General Mattis fails to persuade Omarosa Manigault that Zoroastrians are planning something ominous. The valet joins a sex club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedraggled Roger Stone proclaims to President Trump that angry parents are untrustworthy. Trump Junior slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a drugged haze, Rex Tillerson boldly informs President Trump that liberal activists are buying up Trump properties. Willie Robertson is scared of the dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While skinny-dipping, Peter King mistakenly tells Kellyanne Conway that some voters are no threat at all. Don King eats the whole buffet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the hot tub, Liz Cheney reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that poets are part of the deep state. Tila Tequila shoplifts a coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Rex Tillerson tries to convince Betsy DeVos that socialists are coming over for Christmas. Ted Nugent tries MDMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Scott Pruitt tells Melania that Baptists are part of the deep state. The butler picks flowers and sighs deeply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering General Mattis fails to convince President Trump that Hollywood liberals are lurking everywhere. Barry Goldwater's ghost wears a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Mike Huckabee reluctantly admits to President Trump that Protestants are big donors. Rush Limbaugh collects a welfare check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a hazing ritual, General Mattis tries to convince President Trump that Baptists are useful idiots. The sommelier learns telepathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Hope Hicks reveals to Betsy DeVos that black politicians are selling land in National Parks. Hulk Hogan lies to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Mike Huckabee explains to Ben Carson that Iranian immigrants are filing frivolous lawsuits. The White House chef joins a cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, H.R. McMaster convinces Ben Carson that Native Americans are struggling to raise money. Scott Walker nods sagely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Ted Cruz mistakenly tells President Trump that Amazon and Walmart are particularly smelly. Jon Voight kisses a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Carly Fiorina informs Kellyanne Conway that Sunday morning talk shows are old school. Dana Perino attends a funeral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, Jared Kushner mistakenly tells Katrina Pierson that Democrats are planning something ominous. Glenn Beck quotes Sartre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Liz Cheney reluctantly explains to President Trump that Russian agents are capable bureaucrats. Lou Dobbs hosts the clip show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a long hike, Liz Cheney patiently explains to President Trump that Zoroastrians are hiding in Trump Tower. An obnoxious neighbor knits a lovely hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Liz Cheney tells Jeff Sessions that Canadians are big fans. Adriana Cohen celebrates diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Elaine Chao mistakenly tells Betsy DeVos that European immigrants are in covert ops. Ted Nugent fails the Turing test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Lamar Alexander convinces President Trump that FBI agents are Rosie O'Donnell fans. Vladimir Putin learns about memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Lamar Alexander convinces President Trump that FBI agents are Rosie O'Donnell fans. Vladimir Putin learns about memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a brief chat, Matt Bevin persuades Katrina Pierson that the minions of Soros are potential threats. George Will shoplifts a coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Lamar Smith fails to convince Betsy DeVos that Alaskans are true Americans. A mysterious man quotes Dostoyevsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Darrell Issa announces to President Trump that Kentuckians are oppressed by excessive regulations. An obsequious reporter has plastic surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathlessly, Jared Kushner divulges to Omarosa Manigault that police officers are coming for dinner. Charles Krauthammer takes a nap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Ted Cruz rudely informs Jeff Sessions that NSA agents are waiting at Trump Tower. Ted Nugent knits a lovely hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Stephen Miller convinces Katrina Pierson that WSJ reporters are double agents. Milo Yiannopoulos unleashes a virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Nikki Haley insists to Kellyanne Conway that Iraqi refugees are ignorant hayseeds. Dennis Miller has jury duty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Rex Tillerson reluctantly admits to Melania that transgender people are organizing resistance. Tucker Carlson vanishes without a trace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over coffee, Jeb Bush calmly tells President Trump that Presbyterians are true Americans. Mike Tyson wears pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, H.R. McMaster fails to persuade Jeff Sessions that Chinese officials are not really important. Jon Voight leaks state secrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of guests, Rick Santorum confesses to Omarosa Manigault that conspiracy theorists are unusually angry this week. Trump Junior pays for an abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Carly Fiorina mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that the hired help are not very affluent. President Bush uses Comic Sans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Sam Brownback decides not to tell President Trump that Chicago teens are hiding in Trump Tower. The gardener spills the beans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Hope Hicks reveals to Jeff Sessions that MSNBC pundits are watching Fox News. God Almighty pops a zit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Steve Scalise confesses to President Trump that school teachers are airing their grievances. Dennis Miller discreetly applies for other jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Jared Kushner admits to President Trump that Syrian refugees are big fans. George Will quotes Hegel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Rick Snyder informs Jeff Sessions that retirees are big donors. Rush Limbaugh finds a dollar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient Jason Chaffetz reveals to Kellyanne Conway that CNN reporters are tying up the phone lines. Pat Buchanan kicks a puppy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Jeb Bush persuades Betsy DeVos that neoliberals are organizing resistance. Tila Tequila moves in next door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Carly Fiorina overhears someone tell Betsy DeVos that movie stars are dangerous. The butler hugs everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Steve Bannon reluctantly explains to Jeff Sessions that the Koch brothers are calling for impeachment. Dennis Miller listens to jazz for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Jared Kushner patiently explains to President Trump that ATF agents are feminists. President Bush abandons ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Paul LePage explains to Jeff Sessions that union members are about as dangerous as kittens. An obsequious reporter adjusts all the thermostats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a prank, Mitch McConnell rudely informs President Trump that corporate executives are organizing resistance. Victoria Jackson falls down the stairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Liz Cheney fails to persuade Melania that evangelicals are no threat at all. Michelle Malkin vacuums all the rugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Pete Sessions persuades Betsy DeVos that government employees are withdrawing support. Charles Krauthammer orders takeout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Scott Pruitt informs Melania that government employees are moving into Trump Tower. Don King plugs a leak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Elaine Chao explains to Katrina Pierson that Congressional pages are not reading Breitbart. Karl Rove makes a prophecy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weary Jeb Bush mistakenly tells President Trump that Zoroastrians are potential voters. President Bush shows off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Sean Spicer patiently explains to Jeff Sessions that Russian officials are true Americans. Kayleigh McEnany guest stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, David Shulkin persuades President Trump that black politicians are indebted to Satan. Tila Tequila wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Jeb Bush mistakenly tells President Trump that Trump's in-laws are in the Oval Office. Richard Spencer tries yoga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Lamar Alexander informs Omarosa Manigault that journalists are airing their grievances. Melania's bodyguard learns how to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Rick Santorum patiently explains to President Trump that Nation of Islam members are dropping candy wrappers. A White House tourist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Lindsey Graham rudely informs President Trump that Wall Street bankers are not very affluent. Don King wins an arm-wrestling contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the balcony, Darrell Issa tells Rick Perry that Tumblr users are not coming over for Christmas. Glenn Beck drinks too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Jared Kushner explains to Ben Carson that NAACP members are unlikely to vote. Karl Rove learns the art of fisticuffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a dare, Rick Scott confesses to Katrina Pierson that phone companies are potential voters. Corey Lewandowski hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While working out, Jared Kushner convinces Katrina Pierson that Russian oil executives are international bankers. A corporate lobbyist drinks all the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Jared Kushner tries to convince Betsy DeVos that Communists are American patriots. Charles Krauthammer quotes Shakespeare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, VP Pence boldly informs Ben Carson that Lyft and Uber are deserving of human rights. God Almighty cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, H.R. McMaster fails to persuade Omarosa Manigault that Russian officials are ignorant hayseeds. Scott Walker helps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Sean Spicer divulges to Kellyanne Conway that neo-Nazis are Schwarzenegger fans. Melania's bodyguard listens to reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Jared Kushner informs President Trump that Chinese officials are Rosie O'Donnell fans. Kayleigh McEnany works the door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Louie Gohmert insists to President Trump that rural youth are filling up American prisons. Cthulhu listens to jazz for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Stephen Miller convinces Ben Carson that the McCains are draining the swamp. George Will makes a few off-color jokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Peter King divulges to President Trump that black politicians are total losers. Corey Lewandowski watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Pete Sessions convinces President Trump that paleoconservatives are in on the joke. A man in a yellow cloak jumps off the roof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Wilbur Ross convinces Jeff Sessions that those girls are vandalizing statues. A local TV anchor pretends to be blind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Lamar Smith mistakenly tells President Trump that Canadians are building a pipeline. Jon Voight can't bend over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over coffee, Steve Scalise reveals to President Trump that white women are selling Girl Scout cookies. Clint Eastwood gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Reince Preibus explains to President Trump that tech executives are part of the prank. James Caan has a training montage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intense Justin Amash boldly informs Omarosa Manigault that movie stars are totally trustworthy. Ann Coulter learns to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Lindsey Graham persuades Betsy DeVos that kinksters are trying to make ends meet. David Brooks snorts a few lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Ryan Zinke fails to convince Betsy DeVos that movie stars are deserving of a tax cut. Scott Baio pays for an abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, H.R. McMaster fails to persuade President Trump that iPhone users are part of the deep state. Bill Kristol cracks a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Lamar Alexander mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that Teen Vogue reporters are not returning phone calls. The butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Rick Scott informs President Trump that ACLU members are still alive. Corey Lewandowski gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of diplomats, Jeb Bush rudely informs Rick Perry that Tea Party Patriots are hilarious. Bill Kristol takes a nap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathlessly, Elaine Chao reluctantly explains to Ben Carson that Canadians are deserving of human rights. Ann Coulter turns the corner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Matt Bevin tries to convince President Trump that Sunday morning talk shows are indebted to Satan. Kayleigh McEnany quotes Hobbes.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>