<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw the Forbidden Fruit lineup and it's as if Irish festival promoters are punishing me for moving abroad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before they made me look silly by dropping more points against WBA, wrote this in defence of Jurgen Klopp's rotation policy for @BetBright https://t.co/JcJNeGYnJc https://t.co/abVhOK3Anh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[King Krule was fucking incredible tonight. So happy I seen him in such an intimate venue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Was told that I should ignore tweets in the way girls ignore me by a fat, loud mouth Australian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holmesprice Link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl Oh, I'm sure there's a reason or two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFinal_Third: Dangerously British quote this. https://t.co/w9BtUKTCuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry But people are inherently fucked up everywhere. Having American cousins and having visited the country on multiple occasions, it's largely a brilliant place. Just has some awful politicians/people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry God, you really hate America, don't you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Replete_music @YouTube Quite possibly my favourite Bowie tune. That Berlin period with Eno is incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kvn_clmn Nah, America is a brilliant place. It just has terrible politicians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burnley are going to 1-0 their way to the Champions League]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning Haha top man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho's own personal Sean Spicer https://t.co/kmu6wz2zLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 It could be him tbf, just sounded American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just your standard American religious nut in Dublin city https://t.co/eg3XynBFd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TifoFootball_: Belgium are a tantalising prospect on paper but often struggle to find balance, in association with @BetBright ,@ConorPa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New podcast looking at the Manchester Derby and the Derby D'Italia. Also, @SebSB on whether Daniel Levy will ever fully back Mauricio Pochettino https://t.co/cH0AhWHgQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFinal_Third: NEW POD: We spoke to @SebSB about the state of Spurs and the relationship between Daniel Levy and Mauricio Pochettino.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TifoFootball_: Guns, fascism, and a Scudetto: @ConorPacKelly tells us the incredible story of Lazio's 1970s team who were victims of su…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning And also, City pulled out of the Sanchez deal as opposed to him turning City down in favour of United. He wanted to play for Pep again, but City didn't think the entire package was worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning That piece is a joke from someone well known for it. The implication that the media is somehow biased against United is an hilarious leap though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyGabriel Don't worry, it was just the usual confused, bitter take]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning @JonnyGabriel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewatching American Psycho and am convinced that Jared Leto has been frozen in time https://t.co/u6crnWapaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl In all seriousness though, Chelsea's current transfer business is at best a clusterfuck, at worst an utter embarrassment to all concerned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl It turns out Conte is a glorified Italian Big Sam/Pulis clone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJDeece @chaosinthecbd @babastiltz Baba in the basement will be something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 He needs a summer break and a proper pre-season so badly. Looks perpetually off the pace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen as my favourite player Ronaldinho is retiring, opportune time to repost a recent two-parter I did on the great man for @TifoFootball_ https://t.co/I2pIbOHWJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature He's a fucking g. So rational and reasonable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus, shocked. A haunting voice I'll always associate with my childhood https://t.co/M2OsOmc8Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presented without comment https://t.co/ELIBR26FQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteTudor123 Can see why Guardiola hasn't been convinced by Aguero. Wasn't in the game at all today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning I wouldn't be laughing. Liverpool are coming for United in second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnBrewin_: Karius or Mignolet: Sheeran or Mumford?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX Ah yeah, but they've achieved and earned so much it's understandable that they've changed. AM has great singles, but the middle borders on unlistenable. So bland. Still love the lads though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX I really like Humbug and Suck It &amp; See. AM is their worst album by a distance imo. And replicating their debut album is almost impossible, because they are much more accomplished/refined musicians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen @waynefarry Yeah, they made massive money on them. Also 70 million on Matic and Costa. And Liverpool have just bought two players for close to 150 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen @waynefarry But they've literally all just been replacements for players sold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry Unless there's a significant deterioration in form, I reckon he makes it to the summer and steps away. It's bizarre. The club seem to think that they can compete at the top level by signing second rate players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry Chelsea are averse to spending money now. Unless they sold Hazard, Sanchez wouldn't be recruited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning He's struggled, but largely because he's been played out of position and his knee is still not right. Go back and watch him for Monaco and you'll see a completely different player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning Yep. Just like your tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning Fortunately he's only 23 and should recover from the knee injury he was rushed back from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen @SebSB Wow, this is actually a possibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonny days @SebSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz Amazing what having friends in high places can do for one's career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMc_Sports Think it's more systematic tbh. Conte's insistence on playing a 3-5-1-1 is making them far too defensive and overly reliant on Hazard to do everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GegenDepress RT'ing your own tweet that no one else has retweeted. Nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteTudor123 @GerraDeegan If Alexis really wants to play for City, you'd think he'd reject United and wait until the summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMc_Sports Think Liverpool are being held to ransom there. Leipzig quite happy to get another lump of cash for a player who hasn't been arsed this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMc_Sports You reckon Liverpool will stump up another 17 million for a player they've already bought?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just passed a girl reading a book of Patrick Kavanagh poetry to her boyfriend outside Trinity, which might be the most Trinity thing I've ever seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TifoFootball_: NEW: If Dennis Irwin is under-appreciated on a wider level, that certainly isn’t the case among Manchester United suppor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BetBright: New - Here's @ConorPacKelly On The Understated Brilliance of Denis Irwin...

https://t.co/sf2dOeTcN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Rashford fucking knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horan_james @CianByNature Maybe it's years of cynicism, but I really don't trust the FAI to make the right appointment. Could see them hiring a populist choice like Neil Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Oh god, none of these candidates fill me with any optimism. Throw Dennis O'Brien's money at Michael O'Neill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Not Warburton. Wouldn't be opposed to Chrissy Hughton or giving Stephen Kenny a chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 @KevBeirne Loyle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took Jack Wilshere 6 games, but he's finally back to himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Billie_T HB you mad bastard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PhilCosta They've only used it for a couple of incidents though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tocfcws An absolutely pointless signing. Offers nothing that Chalobah couldn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@minoguepaul Crypto craic is exactly what I imagined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry @LaCasacaBlog It's cruelty. Just give us adi kits ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two years gone. Bowie's still the greatest https://t.co/ZgLypVxg4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Davis, techno legend https://t.co/5NftPj7AnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFinal_Third: Don't fret. We're back. It's the first episode of 2018. https://t.co/4JNnmkX4HM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Think that Sanchez is a replacement for Aguero. Would be surprised if he's at the club next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent tonight watching the latest episode of @dineensparish's @thisaintnodisc0 and it got me in the feels. Donal is a national treasure https://t.co/shZHLwWHy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMc_Sports Wenger contract renewal on the way so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mj_hale @TifoFootball_ Thanks my man. Think the main reason Guardiola pushed him out the door was due to his negative influence on Messi. Used to take him out partying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry @SteTudor123 I somehow knew you'd be an adi originals head Ste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aanuadeoye As a Roma fan, they are maddeningly frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aanuadeoye I've watched enough of Roma chokes to last me a lift time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyGabriel It's all in the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMcAleer1 @Ankaman616 They just aren't my style. #againstturtlenecks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMcAleer1 @Ankaman616 As much as it suits you Carl, I won't be. Can't get on board with the turtle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Ah, but South Park was always sharp and onto something. This lad lacks any grasp of empathy/reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMc_Sports Oblak is going to PSG. Doubt he'd join Liverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry Jaysus. Hopefully that's just something he's misused in a second language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry What did Conte say to spark this latest petulant outburst?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 It's funny, because some Liverpool fans don't seem to rate him. He'll be unreal in Serie A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 Going to be great for Juventus next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin From what I remember hearing, he rejected Chelsea because he wanted to join Spurs. That could be complete nonsense though, so I'm not sure what to believe haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin Spurs pulling out probably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new video series I'm doing for @Tifofootball_ with the help of my boy @JM_Devine. Check it out https://t.co/grdfYG8Ges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenWills I mean, Llorente and Carroll aren't even close in ability. There has to be a better option elsewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenWills Jesus. That's honestly one of the stupidest ideas I've ever heard. The chap regularly misses 6 months at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenWills Wait, what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX Or a separate faction headed by Cody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiejowe It's gas that Chelsea discarded both KDB and Salah, both of whom are now the best players at their respective clubs. Weird transfer policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiejowe Just makes no sense to me. Signing b-level players to compete with the elite isn't a sensible idea. Makes what Conte has achieved all the more remarkable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen @JamesHeydenrych Think it's just to fill up the quota of English players. Perhaps to stop Spurs getting him too, but it's bizarre imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea spending money on Ross Barkley when they have a better, academy produced player in the same mould - Ruben Loftus-Cheek - out on loan is fucking hilarious. It's as if they enjoy burning money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sherwood on Sky for Spurs-West Ham. Paging @bankruptspurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJDeece My dad was surprised to discover I knew this one when I got control of the iPod over Christmas.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>