<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: ICYMI: People’s lives, &amp; our society’s faith in the American justice system are at stake. - @RushHolt, Jed S. Rakoff https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, Robot? Understanding AI ethics https://t.co/fYa1G6Wy2t via @theregister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Join experts at AAAS HQ as they discuss issues at the nexus of science and human rights at the #shrcoalition meeting https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @neiltyson: Comedian Dick Gregory always told it like it is. Our laughter was fuel to fight for justice in an unjust world. RIP 1932-201…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @natematias: A reminder that those of us who work with data from vulnerable populations should protect that data from being used in unan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColMorrisDavis: I resigned as #Guantanamo Chief Prosecutor over torture that these guys made $81M for devising ... a little accountabil…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: Women around the world are working for sustainable peace. Just like all civilian peacebuilders, they are #NotATarget. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNAUSA: Today is #WorldHumanitarianDay. These solutions are helping to protect civilians and end crises: https://t.co/STR9dxRFs2 #NotAT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNinKuwait: In 2016, @P4HR documented 108 attacks on medical facilities in #Syria, depriving people of care when they needed it most. #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IntlWomen: Her body is #NotATarget. On #WorldHumanitarianDay, sign the petition to end sexual violence in conflict @UNOCHA https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WIREDScience: The conversations happening at CrisprCon were all the right ones. @MeganMolteni reports https://t.co/0V4AhTgNO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Kids share facts about Monday's #SolarEclipse You can see all three of their videos here: https://t.co/m2HTX9sgND https://t.co/o2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EIrvingNL: New #ICC arrest warrant 1st to be based on social media evidence- exciting development, but lots of Qs still open
https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @susannahsirkin: Huge victory for victims of US #torture program, ending impunity for psychologists Mitchell and Jessen https://t.co/YYo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Settlement Reached in C.I.A. Torture Case https://t.co/1mKBN0Lvem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HinaShamsi: BREAKING: on eve of trial, CIA torture psychologists agree to historic settlement in 3 victims' case, via @ACLU https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieRedford86: Attn:law students! Come intern at the @EarthRightsIntl Washington, D.C. office next spring! How to apply: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeo: Both seem to be linked to a key emotional trait: empathy https://t.co/gLJEkjmZ6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CAMeissner: "In this battle for human nature, behavioral scientists have a pivotal role to play." Kudos, Evan. https://t.co/lN4zqxMPFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhiBetaKappa: Congrats, @mathbabedotorg! Your book, WEAPONS OF MATH DESTRUCTION, is a #PBKBookAwards finalist! @CrownPublishing https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmericanAnthro: "Racial hatred need not exist." AAA Resources on Race following events in Charlottesville https://t.co/P1nwruuhK4 https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But also this guy https://t.co/tlLdET3FZX https://t.co/6HBVazMMQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DuncanRights: JOB: Human Rights Advocacy Officer with @HRInews - interested in promoting a human rights approach to drug policy? https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samdolnick: Big job alert. Narrative features writer for @nytimes Climate desk https://t.co/dquN8uvfkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sacnas: SACNAS President Dr. Lino Gonzalez responds to the racist violence in #Charlottesville. Read the full statement: https://t.co/E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BKCHarvard: 16 short essays about Harmful Speech Online from Internet researchers, activists, &amp; technologists https://t.co/7t69fR3ECP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: "For science to thrive, you must have free exchange of people and ideas" - AAAS CEO @RushHolt #Cuba #scidiplomacy  https://t.co/B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Includes resources for social science &amp; urban planning courses https://t.co/UEeFs8hmGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kathleen_rest: Science Group Condemns Racist Violence in Virginia | Union of Concerned Scientists https://t.co/C8yVxAyqrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @humanrightsprof: Wonderful profile of @derekcongram &amp; his work to change how mass graves are located. Off soon to share his talents w/@…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OJPNIJ: NEW: Research-based recommendations for a victim-centered approach in responding to sexual assault cases. https://t.co/tpSCaJ3G…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelpAge_USA: Older women are 2 1/2 times more likely to experience #GBV than men. Find out more about our study w/ @AAAS_SRHRL : https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @openRights_oD: @openRights_oD’s latest: The #world is marching towards—not away from—universal #humanrights https://t.co/c9dClRvdOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Right to #Science is enshrined in the Universal Declaration of #HumanRights adopted by the @UNHumanRights in 1948 https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GENetwork: JPO position in Human Rights (environmentally sound waste management) with @UNHumanRights in #GENeva https://t.co/a8xpTbKAxL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DigiDem: Want to design mobile tools for reporting oil spills in the Amazon with us? We’ve extended the deadline to Sunday. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmember: Join @AAAS_SRHRL tomorrow at 12pm EDT to update the 1975 AAAS report on Scientific Freedom and Responsibility  https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: BREAKING: Federal lawsuit against psychologists who designed and implemented CIA torture program is going to trial https://t.co/2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrishtiEthics: Calling listening a "soft" skill reflects technocentric bias. Real listening is hard &amp; rare in technical experts' intera…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProPublica: Question: What's environmental justice?

Answer: Watch this video. https://t.co/iSIYXs6usK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jilliancyork: The Bassel Khartabil Memorial Fund will support projects in the spirit of Bassel's work. Please donate if you can: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: EFF is honored to share the letters we received in 2015 from activist Bassel Khartabil, whose death in Syria was confirmed this we…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Could you describe your Ph.D. research through the art of dance? Send us your performance and you could win $1,000! https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mwfrick: New @aaas report presents findings from a global survey of scientists on the meaning of the human right to science https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for legal analysis of state laws that overturn local civil rights ordinances? Here's a good start - https://t.co/kSdqcTr40U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmember: Help @AAAS_SRHRL update the 1975 AAAS report on Scientific Freedom and Responsibility, 8/9 Webinar  https://t.co/n5M47bjUBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScholarsAtRisk: Happy Birthday to #JamesBaldwin, who reminded us "ignorance, allied with power, is the most ferocious enemy justice can…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UCSUSA Science Protection Project: confidentiality &amp; legal advice for reporting violations of scientific integrity https://t.co/KOShr4JWuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: The Internet mourns news of the execution of Bassel Khartabil, Syrian open source and free Internet advocate. https://t.co/eWyTH5p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tiffanylohwater: “Science cannot be an elitist or an exclusionary undertaking” @RushHolt at @sacnas leadership program @AAAS #LPSLI17 h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrishtiEthics: Insightful commentary on technological paternalism in engineering codes of ethics in 2004 @ASEE_DC Prism magazine. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EngnRoom: new tech-related job opportunity at @amnesty --&gt; https://t.co/SImQutDN5m https://t.co/55K7ggMLDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fsu_engineer Remember the G20? That was 3 weeks ago. THREE WEEKS. Like living in Dali's clocks painting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Trelliscience: From OSTP vacancies to marine sanctuaries, the AAAS Force for Science group on Trellis is the place for @AAASmember disc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: We join science society leaders in requesting meeting w/ @EPAScottPruitt to discuss #climate science - https://t.co/14zGcMgm3d ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theNASEM: Neurocognitive, psychosocial impacts of violence, trauma workshop begins 9am w/ keynote from @AdamDSwanson https://t.co/4BVZy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Hackers at a conference were able to successfully breach US voting machine software in minutes https://t.co/v1qcLvCyYw https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pwnallthethings: Every single e-vote machine at @Defcon got hacked in &lt; 2.5 days (some in minutes) to hackers without inside or domain-…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fogarty_NIH: New from @TheLancet: Closing the #NIH Fogarty Center threatens US &amp; #globalhealth &gt; https://t.co/RGjGdCe8kQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BKCHarvard: Applications are due Monday for our 2018 Assembly team focused on the challenges of AI &amp; ethics. Apply! https://t.co/UR7DVf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jdakwar: Breaking: Judge rules 2 psychologists who helped design and implement the CIA torture program can face trial https://t.co/yTYh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMancisidor1970: Presentando trabajo sobre Derecho Humano a la Ciencia #HR2S ante la comunidad científica norteamericana @AAAS_SRHRL ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @phbalancedfilms: To join us in Nepal at end of Oct for our inaugural session, apply by Friday: https://t.co/wThy53vx2O 
#WomenInFilm #F…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SRWatSan: In moments, presenting my report on service regulation and the #Humanrights to water and sanitation at #HRC36 @UNHumanRights…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And won't get paid again until their workplaces reopen. https://t.co/hQDit5z4i5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConnieSchultz: Networks, please stop cutting away when Florida governor is speaking in Spanish. In this crisis, the goal is to save liv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCPaulAdams: From my brother's Univision colleagues in downtown Miami https://t.co/ADJlO5R6tR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattdpearce: I've created a Twitter list for following Hurricane Irma, featuring local officials and on-the-ground journalists: https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SunSentinel: The view of #HurricaneIrma from space as it makes landfall in the Florida Keys https://t.co/0LEnleMpY5 https://t.co/Ywiv4O…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByKristenMClark: It's a question many have asked this week... Here's why state officials say they won't do it: https://t.co/9ZClVrHtYQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MiamiHerald: Here’s how to volunteer after Hurricane Irma https://t.co/0jsQu7jiwg https://t.co/G4KPWVT3FR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, to all my friends outside FL: Despite all jokes &amp; stereotypes there r good people there who will need your help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew pulled off my gm's roof. No water or electric for so long. This is going to be worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My beloved home state is about to change forever. After years of tracking storms on Publix bags, we all know this one is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NWSKeyWest: ***THIS IS AS REAL AS IT GETS***

***NOWHERE IN THE FLORIDA KEYS WILL BE SAFE***

***YOU STILL HAVE TIME TO EVACUATE***

Pl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveThirtyEight: Within Irma's cone of uncertainty, there are 11 nuclear power plants and hundreds of hospitals. https://t.co/UCGbUZSrt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @phbalancedfilms: Don't miss the latest in the next chapter of our story! Join the e-update list today:  https://t.co/c9Ue1d7V9K 

#Wome…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EngnRoom: Reconstructing the disappearance of 43 Mexican students using 3D modelling @CentroProdh @eaafoficial @ForensicArchi 
https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science in litigation, the third branch of U.S. climate policy https://t.co/PceSRMr4JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kathy_mulvey: New research led by @UCSUSA's @BrendaEkwurzel quantifies fossil fuel industry's climate responsibility https://t.co/lhN2E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SciDip: Immigration policies have profound implications for scientific – as well as humanitarian and economic – interests. #DACA #Dream…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: We urge Congress to craft legislation that provides long-term protection for #DREAMers -  AAAS CEO @RushHolt https://t.co/ROzw5YE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieESuess Some are, yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @phbalancedfilms: Know a woman in Nepal who'd like to use film/storytelling to advocate for social justice in her community? Share: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MiamiHerald: Florida almost certain to feel Irma’s fury, but where remains uncertain
https://t.co/innMdJmC0j https://t.co/CfAf0HJyHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AILANational: Do you or someone you know have #DACA? Here is what you need to know now: https://t.co/gD99lItp5H #AILAStandsWithDreamers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ortizvillacorta: Sharing Microsoft's position related to this important issue in the U.S. #DACA https://t.co/eFs0s7NOU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @em_underwood: #DACA wasn't just good for Dreamers, it helped their kids: https://t.co/dhtTbb5Qht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Hundreds of thousands submitted personal info to register for DACA. What happens to that data? https://t.co/dDSJ4WJGSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This map shows why it is so difficult to evacuate FL and why so much $ invested in shelter-in-place after Andrew. https://t.co/tM3YvgERli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piguanaSue @darth @dog_rates Mostly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cc @darth @dog_rates https://t.co/stYuSgeRqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJUSA: World’s largest pharmaceutical manufacturer wades into #deathpenalty debate: 'Don't use our drugs.' https://t.co/aHIRmzhVNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hormiga: Toolkit for Educators to Support Undocumented Students and Families https://t.co/VNbZgdcIIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sciencemagazine: Friday's the deadline for our latest #NextGenSci -- share your thoughts on scientific discovery and human rights: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthewfsmith: The horror continues. More villages in south Maungdaw razed today. I'm told 80 percent of villages in Maungdaw township…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zararah: Satellite imagery used by @hrw to show almost total destruction of a Rohingya village in Burma: https://t.co/PfZUZceF4A #human…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: Let me say: too many worry about what AI—as if some independent entity—will do to us. Too few people worry what *power* will do…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinokreutzer: Our latest #HHI-MONUSCO-UNDP poll data from Eastern #DRC: humanitarian aid seen as improving situation but only where acc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: A new study has found that children of legally protected immigrants are less likely to suffer from mental illness - https://t.co/…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>