<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers: SOFTWARE Elementum SCM, Inc. has multiple positions open in our Mountain View, CA office for the following: Software Engineer(s) all levels, including Senior Levels (Job #40 &amp; Job #80): Dsgn, dvlp, implmt &amp;/or test sw for a… https://t.co/v4AWy4E1fy https://t.co/z2wTo4SPNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. chip stocks sink after new trade measures aimed at tech: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - U.S. semiconductor stocks slumped on Monday, including deep losses in Intel, Micron Technology and Nvidia, as new measures targeting the technology sector in… https://t.co/QoljRewT4T https://t.co/myMRU89yGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Regulatory Affairs: ENGINEERING: Cardinal Health seeks Manager, Regulatory Affairs in Milpitas, CA to ensure that new products and changes to existing products are prepared and submitted in a timely manner to Global Regulatory Agencies in all… https://t.co/AwyQ4MHOQG https://t.co/90yRiO00lu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xerox says to lower dependency on Fujifilm, seek new vendors: (Reuters) - Xerox Corp said on Monday it would start sourcing products from new vendors to lower its dependency on Fujifilm Holdings Corp and may not renew its technology agreement with Fuji… https://t.co/ufKTmYbmnI https://t.co/gWuzeM95Y2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer-Embedded: Software Embedded Devloper Rockford, IL Job Summary: Software Development Engineer with a minimum of 5 years of experience in the area of embedded software development for a 2 year contract in Rockford, IL. He/She must have… https://t.co/QvTNpx4HNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Solutions Engineer/Architect Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Diego, CA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/12/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/WPAeNMT66o https://t.co/AnQJqoLSUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Designer, User Experience – T-Mobile HE: Job Description Job Description Layer3 TV’s creative team is looking for a high caliber Senior UI/UX designer with a passion for usability and emerging technologies. If you want to be part of creating the… https://t.co/12rR7eMecz https://t.co/oqu9o57ZI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meituan-Dianping files for Hong Kong IPO; aims to raise over $4 billion: sources: HONG KONG/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - China's Meituan-Dianping, an online food delivery-to-ticketing services platform, is bringing its sizable initial public offering (IPO) to… https://t.co/XYWs0Mlm0v https://t.co/E2i6BgxNoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Advanced Programs): San Diego California : California Job Summary: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical… https://t.co/BDBngmdknV https://t.co/64OVCDUI9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager (Land Development): Assistant Project Manager (Land Development) Assistant Project Manager (Land Development) ID 2017-2484 # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MA-Southborough Category Engineering More information about this job… https://t.co/H9HRPaEFaV https://t.co/8U40UNobFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber battles to keep London license in court appeal: LONDON (Reuters) - Uber [UBER.UL] goes to court on Monday to overturn a decision stripping it of its license in London after being ruled unfit to run a taxi service in its most important European market. https://t.co/LJFfhwnNPo https://t.co/9Xvyoknl8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Solutions Architect: We are looking for a Chief Solutions Architect to join our team in Reston, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Position Requirements Summary: – Experience leading enterprise architecture… https://t.co/MiexqgDNsH https://t.co/QwLmMjXlPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Description Tracking Code PRGVAB-10 Job Description We are looking for a software developer to work on projects to support customer solutions and deliver cutting edge designs in audio, video and visual display/processor… https://t.co/6SZI9C3vS9 https://t.co/hiUBfK1NMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Peter Thiel: big tech directors miss shareholder meetings: BOSTON (Reuters) - Some small investors who want to give a piece of their minds to big tech company directors are losing their only chance: many board members are skipping annual… https://t.co/11HI3CWCYY https://t.co/7BpUL4YGhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Quality Test Engineer: Are you passionate about software development, data and analytics? Are you innovative with broad development skills that you keep current? Are you a committed team player able to work with and support others as they support you?… https://t.co/GSE9cg1rzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Database Administrator (DBA) Ref No.: 18-23809 Location: Plano, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our… https://t.co/Xja6Hosd8y https://t.co/2YN55VttzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Associate – Business Intelligence: Job Location US-DC-Washington Job ID 10227 Job Location United States Category Finance/Accounting Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm which prides itself in… https://t.co/AnpFCrXWzJ https://t.co/isqRUAHCSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Software Engineer (Swift): Senior iOS Software Engineer (Swift) with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications –… https://t.co/4N3znjvN9d https://t.co/zfyqK7gJup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox spirits and demons: China's tech giants splash out in cartoon arms race: HANGZHOU, China (Reuters) - Growing up in the Chinese port city of Dalian in the 1990s, Zhang Hongchang spent hours immersed in Japanese cartoons like Dragon Ball and Naruto. https://t.co/nmzrJ66f8P https://t.co/pA5VkYYZlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Rockwell Collins is seeking experienced Java Software Engineers to join their team in Cedar Rapids, IA location for the Test and Training Instrumentation (T &amp; TI) Engineering Department. Relocation is being offered, for the right… https://t.co/3h6Z4xe9xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/J4bVC9lrZH https://t.co/vfDsAOSTY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Networks Developer – Remote: Cloud Networks Developer – Remote Location(s) US-TX-San Antonio | US-TX-Remote Req # 38473 Category Software Development Overview &amp; Responsibilities Are you a Software Engineer who is passionate about building out next… https://t.co/aUtt9vjY8V https://t.co/EYbJjl4tk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compensation Manager: CrowdStrike is a leading provider of next-generation endpoint protection, threat intelligence, and pre- and post incident response services. We are the fastest growing endpoint protection company, one of the World's Most 50… https://t.co/QRpCCHyirk https://t.co/xdzn0VY0QC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps (AWS) Engineer: Want to work at a fun, innovative startup? Want to help small business owners? Interested in FinTech? Join StreetShares. StreetShares is a small business financial marketplace bringing together business owners in search of… https://t.co/6H1BnAiyeg https://t.co/fyG8fx6VLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager (Federal Employee Program): Senior Technical Project Manager (Federal Employee Program) in Washington, DC – CareFirst Looking for Health Insurance? Visit ************* – Home – Jobs at CareFirst – Our Teams – Talent… https://t.co/Zk6YEbVke4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Norfolk, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 06/18/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview This is a 3 month contract to hire, please only submit USC or GC for conversion purposes. Must Haves:… https://t.co/drF2jkxeRW https://t.co/sxUJ82o6wm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Manager: What you’ll be doing. This role will be responsible for the management and delivery of software development projects which create new or improved customer experiences in our mission to reduce customer effort and friction,… https://t.co/jrYPfZ8ISI https://t.co/HubKOpISMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber driver was streaming Hulu show just before self-driving car crash: police report: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Police in Tempe, Arizona said evidence showed the "safety" driver behind the wheel of a self-driving Uber was distracted and streaming a… https://t.co/tpaM3Nb1Sh https://t.co/4vQsi3CJjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multi-Family Project Manager: Careers Center | Multi-Family Project ManagerPlease Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/JN6RKn5Jex https://t.co/g9GygifmxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer – Integration &amp; Test 3/4:   Job Description – Systems Engineer – Integration &amp; Test 3/4 (18002969) Systems Engineer – Integration &amp; Test 3/4 Requisition ID : 18002969 Location : United States-California-Woodland Hills US Citizenship… https://t.co/c9BDSEcxCt https://t.co/c0IYeeIF5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineer, Firmware Engineer: San Jose, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Principal Engineer, Firmware Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of:… https://t.co/iHGCVsNTQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube pushes memberships, merchandise as alternatives to ads: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - YouTube said on Thursday that video uploaders with more than 100,000 followers could start paid fan clubs on the service, one of several new features aimed at… https://t.co/vbcmlkuYrK https://t.co/Flo7bG9XNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel CEO resigns after probe of relationship with employee: (Reuters) - Intel Corp Chief Executive Brian Krzanich resigned on Thursday after a probe found a consensual relationship with an employee violated company policy. https://t.co/4dJ6bPWz55 https://t.co/JQ68qWdrJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Cadence Design Systems, Inc. has openings for the following positions (various levels/types/multiple positions) in San Jose, CA. Some positions may allow for telecommuting. To Apply: Send resume w/ Ref# to cadencejobs2@cadence.com.… https://t.co/mI6QxfQilM https://t.co/ukPmKmEZCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Design, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/24/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/l9fPMrxPMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP aims to double CRM business in two years: sales chief: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - SAP SE aims to double the size of its sales and marketing software business within two years, its top salesman told Reuters, throwing down the gauntlet against market leader… https://t.co/hIqe2eG6H3 https://t.co/LRFbjkmifF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA Machine Learning Team – Cambridge, MA: Job Description Senior Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA Machine Learning Team – Cambridge, MA Location: US-MA-Cambridge Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc.… https://t.co/w3c9Fuo19L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager, Technical: Job Description Job Description Sr Project Manager, Technical The Sr. Project Manager is responsible for leading all aspects of a project or multiple, small-scale projects. This includes project planning, execution, timing,… https://t.co/ilea39AgST https://t.co/uJSKn9beOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: We are seeking a highly motived, flexible, organized, and detail oriented mid-tier Systems Administrator to join the Infrastructure team at our corporate headquarters in downtown Chicago office. The qualified candidate will act as… https://t.co/3jJfKXBrv6 https://t.co/nC6XLlTNnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Post Date:06/04/18 Company:HD Supply Compensation: Contact: Job Type:Full Time Phone: Education:High School / GED Fax: Experience:6 months – 2 years Mailing Address: Travel:Negligible Reference:GAMt05czS1 Company Overview HD Supply… https://t.co/nuhA3BzeKY https://t.co/PxGkgaCGHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan's TSMC to invest $25 billion in 5 nanometer node technology: HSINCHU, Taiwan (Reuters) - Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd, a supplier to Apple Inc, said on Thursday it expects to invest $25 billion in 5 nanometer node technology. https://t.co/vvLZ8pP872 https://t.co/VjqzJLmGky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, U.S. lawmakers meet to discuss 'problematic' measure on China's ZTE: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump and a group of Republicans from the Senate and House of Representatives met at the White House on Wednesday to discuss their… https://t.co/3dYuJnK7wh https://t.co/gMAdFjAWrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon, Berkshire, JPMorgan name Atul Gawande CEO of healthcare venture: (Reuters) - Berkshire Hathaway Inc, https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc and JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co on Wednesday named Atul Gawande as the chief executive officer of their health venture. https://t.co/sF4UfjqPys https://t.co/3DnKcmLQvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tableau Developer I (ISO): Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers… https://t.co/c7z4Q8of9N https://t.co/YfitYhGj2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/NATyhz3Dn8 https://t.co/gTWi45nbK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Staff System Hardware Engineer: For Siemens Sr. Staff System Hardware Engineer job – Engineering – Issaquah, Washington Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – –… https://t.co/ZsnPGRhJDz https://t.co/LXFaWohCwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Xiaomi plans to raise up to $6.1 billion in Hong Kong IPO: sources: HONG KONG (Reuters/IFR) - Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi is planning to raise up to $6.1 billion from a Hong Kong initial public offering, sources with knowledge of the matter… https://t.co/WYCGWZz1Wr https://t.co/oqwsp970fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wireless Protocol Stack Software Engineer: Wireless Protocol Stack Software Engineer – Job ID #: 13354 – Job Category: Software Engineering – Employment Type: – Division: IoT Device IP – Department: IoT Device Engineering – Primary Country: USA – Primary… https://t.co/M6fMAq8d1h https://t.co/zBhq24dlJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security SME/Project Manager: Req ID 98133BR Business Title Cyber Security SME/Project Manager Group MCIS Location USA NEW JERSEY Jersey City Clearance Level Needed None Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a… https://t.co/aeO0DBMoZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb says hacked, $32 million in coins stolen: SEOUL (Reuters) - Seoul-based virtual currency exchange Bithumb has been hacked and 35 billion won ($31.51 million) worth of virtual currency held at the exchange… https://t.co/bM1wSXxv36 https://t.co/XdIYgiypyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Accounting Manager: Financial Accounting Manager Dio USA Corp in L.A. Prep/audit financial reports using US-GAAP &amp; K-IFRS (Korean International Financial Reporting Std). Requires: Bachelor of Arts in Accounting, Business Administration,… https://t.co/dTsfchQ9Uk https://t.co/f6KqueuxT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU copyright reforms draw fire from internet luminaries as key vote looms: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Europe's attempts to force Google, Microsoft and other tech giants to share revenues with publishers and bear liability for internet content have triggered… https://t.co/eBSLY7uErq https://t.co/9onXVgXbXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 'spider' ETF captures Facebook, AT&amp;T in its web: NEW YORK (Reuters) - State Street Global Advisors said on Tuesday that it had launched an exchange-traded fund (ETF) that will track the recently refreshed communication services sector, which includes… https://t.co/nHJHH5wltE https://t.co/S1T2cNm2mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Captiva Developer: Job Summary – Client seeking a Senior Captiva Developer to join our d Development Services team. – The ideal candidate will have experience with Captiva on both Windows and UNIX platforms as well as an in-depth knowledge of… https://t.co/wMfRSqkxxI https://t.co/zo79vO6apA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Voltage SecureData – Provo, UT: Software Engineer, Voltage SecureData – Provo, UT Tracking Code ******* Job Description Discover the new Micro Focus – now the world’s 7th largest pure-play software company. By combining HPE Software… https://t.co/KeSz6ySgrT https://t.co/bWQIzTIHzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst (swift Expert): Job TitleBusiness System Analyst (Swift Expert) – ID:31909 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsPayment Systems, Swift MT LocationExchange Place, NJ Date Posted06/12/2018 – Individual will have up to 8-10+… https://t.co/nnyWPsWa5Q https://t.co/wg8gm1isgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator Seattle, WA,: Job Title: Senior Systems Administrator – Seattle, WA, Location: Seattle, WA, West United States, USA Company: Wilbur-Ellis company Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Chemical, Pesticide and Fertilizer… https://t.co/VnemD8y93P https://t.co/R09jYbynUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… As a member of the Voice Maintenance Engineering Team, you will be responsible for Vendor Technical Management and Equipment Lifecycle Management in Verizon’s Voice/VoIP networks. Focusing on… https://t.co/9hR5PHpWQ6 https://t.co/ZSwgLCibrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump told Apple CEO iPhones will be spared from China tariffs: NYT: (Reuters) - President Donald Trump told Apple Inc Chief Executive Tim Cook that the U.S. government would not levy tariffs on iPhones assembled in China, the New York Times reported on… https://t.co/JZFIX9P431 https://t.co/gvpjJh608U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Accountant: Senior. Tax Accountant Asian Grocery Chain; Provide tax issues resolution &amp; conduct research inclu. sales &amp; use tax, income tax, bus. property tax credit &amp; exemption. Reqs: Bachelor’s in Acct/Taxation/Bus. Admin, or related, plus 2… https://t.co/xcTrVX0DeF https://t.co/Lee5AMz93u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Applications Specialist: The Office of the Chief Administrative Officer (CAO) provides operations support services and business solutions to the community of 10,000 House Members, Officers and staff. The CAO organization comprises more… https://t.co/ACS9oQIKlK https://t.co/M90AjJx29b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to invest $550 million in China e-commerce giant https://t.co/PlPvOWJ7GJ: (Reuters) - Google will invest $550 million in Chinese e-commerce powerhouse https://t.co/PlPvOWJ7GJ, part of the U.S. internet giant's efforts to expand its presence in… https://t.co/IjuSZXKw4P https://t.co/VXHqACihgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Staff Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Responsible for ensuring software components are expertly designed, tested, debugged and ready for integration into the product line. Build out new applications and features… https://t.co/sJP23NZp9r https://t.co/cheof4967U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PeopleSoft Technical Solutions Modeler/Developer: Manages the interface development, unit testing and deployment and integration of technical solutions for the IPPS-A project. Provides data models from business systems planning and data requirements… https://t.co/8wEjwY3sIF https://t.co/GXxt4qTbHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon to add over 1,000 jobs in Ireland in country's biggest staff boost this year: DUBLIN (Reuters) - Amazon will add more than 1,000 new jobs in Ireland over the next two years, the U.S. online retail giant said on Monday, taking its workforce to more… https://t.co/VKKpoNvnwH https://t.co/dopPNOuw8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect I: Application Architect I Lake Forest, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/05/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Greetings from Saxon Global Inc. We have an Immediate need for a talented… https://t.co/0Jh0t0lxVW https://t.co/Pps1LoLn86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Web Developer: What does it take to protect and maintain the most sensitive data for over 220 million people and 25 million businesses? What does it take to meet daunting challenges and shape solutions that pioneer industries and improve… https://t.co/ih6Ebv7pWH https://t.co/X9NJjumi5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Programmer/Analyst: Careers Center | Mainframe Programmer/Analyst Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/opAxXh8VpA https://t.co/FIeGf2dXrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software https://t.co/8CIET5Whnv – TS/SCI – Tampa, FL: Requisition ID 2018-37035 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Designs, develops, codes, tests, and debugs… https://t.co/IkCEjMegEB https://t.co/5N5EKugnjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer, Senior: Req ID 98178BR Business Title Test Engineer, Senior Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Public Trust Category Engineering &amp; Support Services Job Duties and Responsibilities · ManTech, a well-respected… https://t.co/olf0QVuvdD https://t.co/cnF6ZX4JYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Huawei goes on offensive as exclusion from Australia 5G deal looms: SYDNEY (Reuters) - Chinese telecommunications company Huawei Technologies Co Ltd [HWT.UL] has gone on the offensive against Australian claims it poses a security risk, issuing an… https://t.co/l8Bzv7e3vl https://t.co/XxFmUwrnHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook signs agreement with Washington state to end discriminatory ad targeting: Facebook Inc has signed an agreement with the state of Washington to stop third-party advertisers in the United States from excluding protected groups from seeing their… https://t.co/w4zfOgYrdD https://t.co/rS8qR2TV0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer Columbus, Ohio. Design, develop, &amp; maintain various MFTS platforms. Duties: Design, develop, and maintain various managed file transfer system (MFTS) platforms. Review platform architecture to align with… https://t.co/RjdwkFj2Cq https://t.co/8bbfrg4Ud1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In cyber, Germany needs to counter-attack, minister says: Germany is considering laws that would let it respond actively to foreign cyber-attacks, Interior Minister Horst Seehofer as he presented a domestic intelligence agency report showing Iran was the… https://t.co/erjV6kWEtT https://t.co/XB9JuHrESH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Web Application Developer Information Technology Davenport, Iowa Apply Description Position at Lee Enterprises Lee Enterprises, a leading media company in the US, seeks a talented Web Application Developer to join our corporate… https://t.co/j62vN2RgnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Automation Engineer: Job Description Candidates shall have a Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field and have at least eight years of demonstrable experience with integrating, installing, configuring, upgrading, compiling and… https://t.co/10hrXZUAeM https://t.co/0Lr0jxieTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst II – IVR: Business Systems Analyst II – IVR in Fort Worth, TX at National General Insurance Toggle Navigation – Home – About – Benefits – Training – Our Values – All Jobs Join Our Talent Network Search Our Jobs Keyword: Location:… https://t.co/CuURhb9zkD https://t.co/UE7pHOfWKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Developers: T-Mobile Location Bellevue, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category IT/Software Development Job status Full Time Posted on Jul 01, 2018 Job code N/A Print Senior Product Developers Bellevue, WA… https://t.co/r4RFRv2YKC https://t.co/AscAFu2Xsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real Estate Services Project Manager: Job Description Real Estate Services Project Manager (R) Real Estate Services Project Manager (R) (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While… https://t.co/DWaJ12h7Z3 https://t.co/TzZkTltpzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker AMS shrugs off second quarter loss with rise in new orders: Austrian chipmaker AMS said new orders for its sensors used in face recognition will lift growth in the second half of the year, sending its shares higher and brushing aside a widely… https://t.co/uI6XtemMhG https://t.co/5UB2WhAND4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Technical Lead – US: Role Product Technical Lead – US Auto req ID 33022BR Domain Other Domain Skillset Other Languages , Country USA State / Region / Province North Carolina Work Location Charlotte, NC Company ITL USA Job Description… https://t.co/Sy5oPXufq9 https://t.co/pL4XEM1FAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplier Quality Technician/Data Analyst: Job Description BAE Systems is looking for an experienced Supplier Quality Technician/Data Analyst who: Would be excited to join a leading top tier global aerospace &amp; defense enterprise Has a long standing… https://t.co/xhETMrMeeT https://t.co/EHhZEyZyWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Quality Assurance Analyst: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 1 month ago(6/19/2018 10:01 AM) Job ID 23728 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance Group. As one… https://t.co/SSnlJl5PKW https://t.co/y5nT21DoNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers penetrated networks of U.S. electric utilities: WSJ: Russian hackers gained access to the networks of U.S. electric utilities last year, which could have allowed them to cause blackouts, according to federal government officials, who said… https://t.co/D1ok7LsNsG https://t.co/ajuNmURTNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of England says payments system can serve blockchain users: A revamped Bank of England payments system should be able to hook up with fintech firms using distributed ledger technology (DLT), the central bank said on Monday in a boost to the… https://t.co/2Sdlb8VC8q https://t.co/UBMD6BkWxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Staff Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Design, develop, and evaluate software from concept to production. Lead Internet of Things (IoT) for electronics mobile solution development. Design and develop iOS and… https://t.co/17Xmle7gOt https://t.co/LmDFOELNHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the largest and most diversified television broadcasting… https://t.co/Zon0iyFnGN https://t.co/KhgkvBgNcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst (Geographic Information Systems): Job ID: ********-12009-CK Company Name: Wood Mackenzie Description: EMPLOYER: Wood Mackenzie, Inc. POSITION: Senior Data Analyst (Geographic Information Systems) WORKSITE: 5847 San Felipe, Suite 1000,… https://t.co/esYu2WIWdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-39774 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Applicant will provide one-on-one Tier 3 level technical support for resolution… https://t.co/ktJogjRn1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayU buys Israeli payment technology firm Zooz: Online payment company PayU, a subsidiary of Naspers , said on Monday it agreed to acquire Israeli payment technology provider Zooz to support its expansion in high-growth markets. https://t.co/p6jAfiyAMi https://t.co/ct6M2oCsSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9063 ETL Architect: Back to Jobs Location: New york, NY, United States Salary: Posted: Apr 13 ETL Architect Position Type (Permanent) At this point client is not willing to sponsor visas. 10+ years experience in ETL tools such as Informatica with 2+… https://t.co/FG4Hf1Jbds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CERAWeek Innovation Agora Program Manager: CERAWeek Innovation Agora Program Manager Responsibilities: Collaborate with the CERAWeek Program Leadership Team, IHS Markit experts and moderators to plan, direct and shape the Innovation Agora program… https://t.co/3ZZ5dPKAs4 https://t.co/S8XPi1nYxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer – TS/SCI with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-39674 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the design and… https://t.co/2sZwUmtSR1 https://t.co/F6dwLxvUZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager, Mechanical: Associate Project Manager, Mechanical (Hydraulic Systems) – Careers at Universal Orlando Menu ToggleMenu Hide Buy Tickets Book Hotels Book Packages Hot Deals Buy Merchandise My Account Login Sign Up Maps Annual Pass… https://t.co/u7Icf2dQe9 https://t.co/2HoR7EA986]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Software Developer: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 07/19/2018 Location Everett Washington United States Job Description IT Product Systems is currently seeking a Junior Software Developer in the BWS Platform Build team… https://t.co/sXoiQqns6n https://t.co/fSlMT0nvhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZTE's HK shares jump 3.8 percent as U.S. lawmakers cut measure from bill: Shares of China's ZTE Corp rose as much as 3.8 percent in Hong Kong on Monday after U.S. lawmakers cut measures from a defense bill that would have reinstated sanctions on the… https://t.co/OHeLPZtlSf https://t.co/0rAMKIZ7za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR Mainframe Programmer (COBOL / CICS): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity – Performance Ratings… https://t.co/Z9Y0kTEKYA https://t.co/KbUSLg3mVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Applications Developer – Junior: Job Description BAE is searching for an Application Developer for a program based in Dulles, VA. You will be expected to challenge and to be challenged, to create, and to innovate. In this role, you will deliver… https://t.co/84sgmYP2En https://t.co/OwzkvwNHvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's https://t.co/PlPvOWJ7GJ plans move into Europe: CEO tells German newspaper: Chinese e-commerce company https://t.co/PlPvOWJ7GJ plans to expand in Europe and aims to have finalised its strategy for entering the market by the end of the year, its… https://t.co/KPDULb8v8Q https://t.co/yL0bpfiUdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Leader – Platform Infrastructure: What are we building next? The next generation of NOS architecture – hardware and software that aligns with SDN, is highly modular and programmable, supports modern software principles and distributed system… https://t.co/0pCY8yMTfh https://t.co/PycWEoBOfu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>