<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/18fVW12Hfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/BGocG4K9f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/coIwcicsgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/IxYySN7sQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/Z0pwkOrRqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/bHgMIKQ41c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/UdZGDrrRw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/6p7Eo5Q2Nr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/bdScG26oyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/crPlgGs4or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/ZSxClCbpPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/QKYFDEu0yO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/POhMMNmUUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/QJrLQnNH1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/pd7AMtWCGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/PM0l9XdgzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/n5BHKDJ66t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/wUOs62g293]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/BG7WPfRY0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/3xWIDz63Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/zfQaYxwf4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/NLPSWlPGKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/jQC8OP8kwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/dWHtuoM6ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/wEqCVDfUL7  http://t.co/FZ5l5i6IS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/t5J4QHjU5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/3xWIDz63Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/RA1yp182SK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/ZSxClCbpPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/rEoTiVjLS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/k4NbBrSWuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/NDiP7gMPLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/dK29THyOQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/Ij3se4MLTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/nV0v79QAv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/DnraMHCaH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/2HqUmPip2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/zYftN6jNE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/Jw0lR9MhWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/OldDmIMbn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/wUOs62g293]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/XKo3sYw3dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/Rd5eYiWm3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/W6zQm6iQym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/wkW3moXvrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/e98kIhuf7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/CY3AREHa2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/zT6mIuBGDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/8vmnQFmH0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/7AepevhtDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/dyBsqafTSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/uAEbEEg5sf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>