<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Service Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Web Service Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Web Service Developer who is responsible for the web services design… https://t.co/fl7lEcslxG https://t.co/oymRxQT4Ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/CPbyEuBwLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatia eliminates Iceland, finishing flawless run https://t.co/eqoor34KiC https://t.co/Qwsty0eKHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core java: Core java Ref No.: 18-24229 Location: Woonsocket, Rhode Island Role Java Developer Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills – Expericne onf J2EE – Experience with Front End(HTML, Javascript), JSF, spring – Experience with Spring, Spring MVC,… https://t.co/fVMItajqUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java back-end developer: Java back-end developer Ref No.:18-09371 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/22/2018 Job Title- Java back-end developer Location- Charlotte, NC Duration- 6+Months Job Description:… https://t.co/0ecwzMVuPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Angular 2.0: Key Required Skills: Java, Angular, Spring/Springboot Position Description: Candidate will participate as needed in all phases of software development with emphasis on the planning, analysis, development, testing,… https://t.co/I22YAUypr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java dveloper: java dveloper Ref No.: 18-26771 Location: irving, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! We are currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java Developer with the client based in multiple locations . Please let me… https://t.co/S4nticR5qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Java – Client Account Info: Are you a master of Java interested in the coming frameworks, tools and techniques? Do you know how to solve challenging problems in elegant ways? We re looking for someone like that who can: develop… https://t.co/XAsPCFf3NI https://t.co/4zauDdQkkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchin gives McCaskill Heimlich maneuver after choking, she suffers broken rib: Democratic Sen. Claire McCaskill suffered a broken rib after choking at a Senate lunch Thursday, where her Senate colleague Joe Manchin, a West Virginia Democrat, performed… https://t.co/totovr77o0 https://t.co/7RMyOYTLvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Position Information Position Information Working TitleSenior Java Developer Role TitleInfo Technology Specialist III – 39113 Job Open Date06/01/2018 Job Close Date Open Until FilledYes Is this position funded in whole or in part… https://t.co/rRKtXHKPZB https://t.co/xH2qJyDc5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Assistant can speak Spanish on Home speakers: Today, Google announced that Assistant on its Home, Mini and Max products can now speak and understand Spanish. Additionally, consumers in Mexico will be able to find Google Home on store shelves… https://t.co/9mzwEBFdOO https://t.co/VeIOJFuRGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist UI Developer AngularJS Java: Sr. Specialist UI Developer AngularJS/Angular2, JavaScript, Java, SQL Asset service technology at BNY Mellon has an immediate need for web developer with Java application development background. We are looking… https://t.co/P3zGmTZQHa https://t.co/pLNzZM8uQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Senior Developer – Java/AngularJS/JavaScript (Federal Technology Consulting) – Secret Clearance – VA: Front End Senior Developer – Java/AngularJS/JavaScript (Federal Technology Consulting) – Secret Clearance – VA in Arlington, Virginia, United… https://t.co/xFB93ZRbuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a composite of diverse people who… https://t.co/n0EAn9kohJ https://t.co/1jwH875kQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API: Java API Ref No.: 18-24345 Location: Monterey Park, California Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 10 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Java API Programmer… https://t.co/Fu8yeBakuo https://t.co/eTKf04ZvGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Java Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/nhnksgNA05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entire police force of Mexico town detained after mayoral candidate's assassination: The entire police force of a Mexican town in the state of Michoacán is being questioned in the assassination of a mayoral candidate, the office of the state's attorney… https://t.co/llcA9urCRM https://t.co/oyMmCjiXiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java and ExtJS Tech Lead: Java and ExtJS Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-26399 Location: Tampa, Florida Position: Java and ExtJS Tech Lead Location: Tampa, FL Duration: Fulltime Permanent Role 8-10 Years of Experience. Very Strong in Java and J2EE Design Pattern,… https://t.co/voRbkLKnL3 https://t.co/M9ApTOlgQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Must have React, Angular Experience Technical Architect – 140k. Prefer Atlanta, but will relocate the right person. 10 years as an Architect 5 years Angular, Ember, React 5 years , Java, Node * A minimum of 8 -10 years software… https://t.co/rRRycLO8AV https://t.co/NVSa3AwkeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court allows most disputed maps in Texas, NC gerrymandering cases to be used: The Supreme Court on Monday wiped away a lower court opinion that had invalidated congressional maps in North Carolina as an unconstitutional partisan gerrymander and… https://t.co/0pyffKCcIF https://t.co/uPDH7m8q6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Full Stack Developer (Java, Javascript): The Alternate Investment Services ‘ Client-Portal Technology group’ is a collaborative development team with the goal of delivering a uniform, responsive user experience to clients. ‘ We are actively working… https://t.co/PMEdOtGFBf https://t.co/272afcTAeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Sr. Specialist Developer – Java: Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for data, workflow, logical processes,… https://t.co/l8rF0REfkN https://t.co/C03uaUHxYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Java Developer, Data Delivery: About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries and markets that drive global economies. Our company partners with clients… https://t.co/FBKYyAd0En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Microservices Developer: Java Microservices Developer in Irving, Texas, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers… https://t.co/nKaLeHo2fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect Technical Lead – Java: Looking for an Architect Technical Lead Looking for a candidate of the Financial Services Industry that has 10+ years Hands on Java JEE .NET Python Angular Spring WebServices REST API Messaging ETL XML JSON RDBMS NoSQL… https://t.co/qSz4spXyP9 https://t.co/Ecgcbmn4tn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI/Machine Learning Senior Engineer (Java &amp; Python): at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Twilio Understand is the brain of Twilio’s natural language understanding (NLU). Twilio Understand, powers Twilio's conversational AI platform that allows… https://t.co/4XC4aqQecV https://t.co/VmbpIBWd8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (ETL / Webservices): MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Developer (ETL / Webservices) Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Developer (Webservice / ETL) who will be responsible… https://t.co/cw8cjfSYDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Enterprise Solutions Delivery: Java Developer – Enterprise Solutions Delivery As part of Eagle’s Enterprise Solutions Delivery team this role will design, develop and test features and functionality which provides the critical shared… https://t.co/LPS24n1PSp https://t.co/xegnsXGK8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Integration Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Silver Spring, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/4/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/cB52jmHwiq https://t.co/Pf1TxJFMuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Settle in with these weekend reads: The first glimpse of a director's genius. The last hope for a species nearing extinction. Grab a cup of coffee and settle in. Here's what you might have missed during a busy news week. https://t.co/qxqMb2kQgE https://t.co/4YUFWELV6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer – Full Stack: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride… https://t.co/0zJLpzqAcF https://t.co/QngaRrKv11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Tech Lead: Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food retailing, with a growing base of loyal shoppers.… https://t.co/ELLD4VxqNx https://t.co/1XEwWOwf0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Performance Engineer: Project Description Project of a central authorization solution for a global investment bank, being delivered by Luxoft. The solution should be able to face actively growing number of consumer applications while… https://t.co/x3kXyv3m8n https://t.co/kR7DpCcp1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular JS/Java – Developer: Angular JS/Java – Developer Ref No.: 18-24235 Location: Chicago, Illinois Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills 1) Hands on experience in in Angular 2 and above 2) Experience in using Bootstrap framework for layout… https://t.co/q4A07sHSIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Java Development: PROJECT MANAGER, JAVA DEVELOPMENT RESPONSIBILITIES * Hands on development experience with Java and DevOps * Architect, design and develop systems * Hands on experience with TDD in Junit, FitNesse, Cucumber, etc. *… https://t.co/XqbOBNUeoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ JEE Developer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Java Developer to join our team in Kingstowne, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Responsibilities: – Design and implement… https://t.co/I7BybnvJ7t https://t.co/iBQaIGsZS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Developer – Global Risk Solutions NEXEN (AngularJS / Angular / JavaScript / TypeScript): Senior Specialist Developer’ -‘ Global Risk Solutions’ NEXEN’ (AngularJS / Angular / JavaScript / TypeScript) ‘ The Global Risk Solutions (GRS) IT… https://t.co/PWm3Sdb9qN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Technical Lead: Java/J2EE Technical Lead Ref No.: 18-26204 Location: syracuse, New York Hi, Hope you are doing great!! We are currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java/J2EE Technical Lead with the client based in… https://t.co/DKZOmSf25V https://t.co/Iq50zs43vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe holds its breath over Merkel: All of Europe is currently on hold -- and holding its breath. Business as usual is at a standstill, even though the EU is mired in its deepest crisis since its founding and other urgent matters, like a trade war with… https://t.co/3HLOQ5uiY1 https://t.co/O5950XQjCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Dev, Senior: SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER RESPONSIBILITIES: – Participate in Requirements Analysis; design Applications based on System Requirements and Architecture, prototype if necessary, develop, unit test and deploy applications – Champion efforts… https://t.co/GaHqwYU8mg https://t.co/Uvr335EtJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Google Cloud Engineer reqd in NYC NY/Hoboken NJ: Position: Java (Google Cloud) Engineer reqd in NYC NY/Hoboken NJ Location: NYC NY/Hoboken NJ Duration 6 months Start Date 4-6 weeks Job Description Expertise in Machine Learning, designing pipelines… https://t.co/2vsLA5k1aa https://t.co/Pllr9wXLuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Level Java Developer DoD: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service oriented Mid Level Java Developer to join our team at FT. Belvoir, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this role… https://t.co/n1upcwJJhV https://t.co/tZ9WhYsjZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET – Selenium, Java: SDET – Selenium, Java in Morrisville, North Carolina, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know… https://t.co/0DRvbzkoMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions, tears, finger-pointing: How the policy of separating immigrant families at the border unfolded: The week is ending the way it started -- with lots of confusion about the policy that resulted in separating immigrant children from their parents. https://t.co/BnjQ0Pv5qA https://t.co/teQJYGvcyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java DevOps Manager: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Java DevOps Manager. Candidate will be responsible for project management activities including planning, technical requirement gathering, communication and engagement with… https://t.co/T6tZbd3cCl https://t.co/IxxzcFRpKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer: TITLE: Application Developer – Java CLIENT: Federal Agency LOCATION: Bethesda, MD POSITION TYPE: Full-Time Position PLEASE NOTE: This position does not require any clearance. We can submit Green Card Holders as well. JOB… https://t.co/lk8Ps3e920 https://t.co/XjwNbbwdf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker plays audio of children crying on House floor: Democratic Rep. Ted Lieu (D-CA) played the audio recording of immigrant children crying after being separated from their families. https://t.co/0sTunE2rjG https://t.co/0eZffJ9N0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript: Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript Tracking Code ******* Job Description Please note that our internships run in perpetuity throughout a students degree program, therefore you must live within… https://t.co/C48qTc2eFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter calls out Neymar's massive dive https://t.co/ChzHWxp6ob https://t.co/IsBxfIhuVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level-Java-Developer DoD: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service orientedMid LevelJavaDeveloperto join our team atFT. Belvoir, VAto begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this role you will… https://t.co/bexOPfWHNK https://t.co/jMNrTiN0aL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children allege grave abuse at detention centers: A year before the Trump administration's "zero-tolerance" policy resulted in more than 2,300 children being separated from their families at the border in a mere five-week period, a ninth-grader in… https://t.co/8r79vKgoUd https://t.co/WqikpP8Oqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer – Junior: JAVA Developer – Junior ======================= Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an… https://t.co/qF7yWCMmj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Associate Java: Senior Associate – Java #71125 Date: May 16, 2018 Location: Tampa, FL, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now EmailStart Please wait. New York Life Insurance Company is… https://t.co/yOVSYiKo6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steam's Summer Sale offers discounts on 'Fallout,' 'Sonic' and more: Steam holds seasonal sales throughout the year, offering decent discounts during certain dates in Autumn, Winter and Summer. It's definitely time for the most recent sale, just a day… https://t.co/aQb9fp1MNN https://t.co/BPo5Vx9Tzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer: JAVA Developer Ref No.: 18-26236 Location: Denver, Colorado Technologies: Java/J2EE Spring, Hibernate Rest Web Services Kafka Cassandra Git Pentaho, ELK Requirements: Proficiency with JAVA application development and migration.… https://t.co/LZy0PBVzPB https://t.co/2CXXJLOPku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer with modernization: JAVA Developer with modernization Ref No.: 18-26465 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Role: JAVA Developer with modernization Location: Atlanta GA Type: Contract The modernization engineer is a hands-on technical role… https://t.co/N6cIWVtXYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Rourke: 'Racist element' to child detentions: Rep. Beto O'Rourke says that racism is a factor in the Trump administration's child detention practices at the border. https://t.co/HbnXw0tq9x https://t.co/VGasPf8NfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer (React, Node, Java): Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/dtv0didSE8 https://t.co/3vq6B08l78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers Overview… https://t.co/CcRkmWJoCW https://t.co/rRZtRrMipL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Suns do what everyone expected with No. 1 pick https://t.co/AYyc9juFTx https://t.co/QPJvtzhXOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Licensing Software Engineer- C++ and Java: For Siemens Licensing Software Engineer- C++ and Java job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/hcfNnKv8it https://t.co/fVMa8HTLND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Gupta: After all my years of reporting, this still haunts me: Most of the time when you hear me talking about food, I am talking about the food we eat. But a few years ago, I realized I needed to talk more about the food we DON'T eat. https://t.co/uzUAXhMmBF https://t.co/4fvPo5D7hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volvo’s new US-made S60 sedan will be available via subscription: Volvo's new S60 sedan marks a bit of a sea change for the automaker: It's its first of its vehicles not to have a diesel variant, the first manufactured in the United States and the third… https://t.co/Q0YhG5P091 https://t.co/wR4Uvxvsqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer JAVA: For American Express Senior Engineer – JAVA job – Digital Commerce, Technology – Sunrise, Florida Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation American Express – Life at American Express – Our Company – Career Areas – Student… https://t.co/G4lYGLELVr https://t.co/7B6p1vOETX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Description Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and… https://t.co/y31u3WvjLx https://t.co/s3QWCXz61I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Description As a Java Developer and member of the Serco software development team, you will share responsibility for the design, development, automated tests, builds, and deployment of application solutions and delivery of the company… https://t.co/ZVk2geUb4i https://t.co/1iCsPq0r7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java developer: java developer Ref No.: 18-22707 Location: Quincy, Maine Role: JAVA DEVELOPER Location:Richmond, VA Core Java. multi-threading Data Structures. Spring. 5+ years of experience in Java/J2EE technologies Hands on experience using spring… https://t.co/RaVyxmq7Xx https://t.co/pLDoC3QztR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump team's epic language fail: You know the United States is being run by a gang of idiots when they not only try to use language in nefariously Orwellian fashion, but can't even get that right. https://t.co/lkuwbVPOF8 https://t.co/8sRRmJyR4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java: Java Ref No.: 18-18944 Location: Jersey City, NJ, New Jersey Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 8 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Sr. Java Developer based in… https://t.co/hk45fgtZmp https://t.co/5nYNJsxbny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Cup beer supply in danger: The football World Cup usually means barbeques, beer, and big summer parties, but these plans could fall flat for many Europeans this year. https://t.co/9lQ9QO24YV https://t.co/La4YDzhpjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Summary/Company:Are you a Senior Java Developer looking for a mission critical new Federal Contracting Opportunity with unlimited potential for growth? Look no further, Sparks Group is partnered with a well known organization… https://t.co/PXf1X7vlVh https://t.co/M49DL0T6dv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-JEE-Developer Journeyman-: We are seeking motivated, career and customer orientedJava/JEE Developer, interested in joining our team in Kingstowne, VA,and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Duties and… https://t.co/mcrv4SktRm https://t.co/isk53eK7Qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US is leaving UN Human Rights Council: US Ambassador to the United Nations Nikki Haley announced the United States is withdrawing from the UN Human Rights Council Tuesday, accusing the body of bias against US ally Israel and a failure to hold human… https://t.co/NW7JntbZGN https://t.co/PV5lwbznm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Job in Plano, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA – Careers – / – Search Jobs – – IT Jobs – –… https://t.co/al1twBE69H https://t.co/DTvVVE2NUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Developer: HomeAdvisor is looking for a senior-level JavaScript Developer to join our Software Development team. In general, we are looking for someone who has experience working on public-facing web properties, and being part of a… https://t.co/bTjdvdUmP1 https://t.co/0I3Ccx5yE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Solutions Architect: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Java Solutions Architect. Candidate will be a leader and participate in the development and maintenance of application and information system architecture and conducts… https://t.co/H0kHU9TeWO https://t.co/lZAeKE8soa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Web Service Developer who is responsible for the web services design and architecture on… https://t.co/VDhpsFNPA9 https://t.co/iQuCaNAE91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java, Unix, Weblogic: Seeking a candidate with 5 years applications, JAVA, UNIX application development. * This is about upgrades, enhancements, code changes to new and existing application * We do not want Middleware Administrators with application… https://t.co/DmHY0d3XB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Holocaust comparisons, Sessions doesn't get it: Comparing anything to Nazism is usually a losing tactic. The Holocaust was so wholly, systematically, profoundly evil that even the suggestion that something is Nazi-like is easily met with scorn. It… https://t.co/3JAtNCtiDf https://t.co/YsXl58V6YC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Engineer | React or Angular: San Francisco, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today If you are a JavaScript Engineer with PROFESSIONAL WORK experience in React or Angular, please read on! Based in the Mission District in San Francisco, CA is a… https://t.co/GA6615sJ3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Domain Tech Lead: Req ID: 13842 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our ability… https://t.co/qOlJDNvhw2 https://t.co/XDHwmBheK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber, Waymo and others to study the 'human impact' of self-driving cars: A group of companies have just formed a new organization that will study the impact self-driving cars could have on humans, like the millions that stand to lose their jobs to… https://t.co/WV19bw1Kyf https://t.co/RU1zNFpG8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer: Core Java Developer San Leandro, California – United States Job Start Date – 05/28/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Internet Authentication and Fraud Development within DCT has an opportunity for a… https://t.co/G4QrFKqPGV https://t.co/ABAyjuxOMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In tech, patents are trophies -- and these companies are dominating https://t.co/vbpGq5V3LO https://t.co/SNydgsIN1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java AWS engineer: Java AWS engineer Ref No.: 18-23263 Location: San Jose, California Position: Java AWS engineer Location: San Jose , CA Duration: 6+ months Qualifications: Experience with current Java Frameworks(Spring, Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Spring… https://t.co/X1FwmZzQUR https://t.co/t5DnfT0zJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Software Engineer – Full Stack: Sr. Java Software Engineer – Full Stack – FirstPRO 360 Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Life Sciences – Medical Device Sales – Project Services – Supply… https://t.co/tVTvBNCIX0 https://t.co/nZ3Pghyan1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer – Cyber Security Computer Software Company: SENIOR JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER Austin, TX Currently seeking an Austin based Senior Software Engineer to work with a profitable computer software company specialized in IT security… https://t.co/dvJXUa8B6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump demands credit for getting along with Kim Jong Un: President Donald Trump continued to defend his budding relationship with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un on Monday, demanding credit for his role in making "initial steps toward a deal" by… https://t.co/qPwXgFEwIS https://t.co/74mYUPge4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ADF Java Software Engineer: General Dynamics IT has an opening for a Principal Oracle ADF Software Engineer along the Gulf Coast in New Orleans; LA. Successful candidate must be able to obtain and retain a government background investigation. Candidates… https://t.co/Rsw9vIKIqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Development Engineer – Senior Level: Java Development Engineer – Senior Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA –… https://t.co/zHGJwFt0ei https://t.co/cOrkdOXgK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch these cooler towers implode: Fifteen hundred pounds of dynamite was used to implode two cooler towers in Jacksonville, Florida. https://t.co/ed70oVwTbg https://t.co/9bWSOyjgPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance:   Job Description – Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance (18006409) Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance Requisition ID : 18006409 Location : United States-Virginia-Herndon US… https://t.co/msHxqIgRig https://t.co/HWrVRFkWM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer: Java developer Ref No.:18-03027 Location: Hoboken, New Jersey Position Type:Contract Start Date: 02/19/2018 Client is looking for a Java developer. Disclaimer: This web page contains privileged and confidential information intended only… https://t.co/vfkrDPUAWT https://t.co/XOTRc071fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer: Core Java/J2EE Developer Ref No.:18-09528 Location: McLean, Virginia Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/24/2018 Core Java/J2EE Developer Must Have Skills Total experience of 7+ Years with 4+ Years in Java/ J2EE… https://t.co/HUYNFANBMV https://t.co/W5615qQYAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Westworld' mobile game puts you in control June 21st: HBO and Warner Bros. have been teasing their Westworld mobile game for nigh-on half a year. Now, though, they finally have something to show. The Behaviour Interactive-built game is slated to arrive… https://t.co/665qVALf7T https://t.co/DwqUTYlwyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java: Core Java Ref No.: 18-23209 Location: Mclean, Virginia Title:- Core Java Developer Location:- Mclean VA Contract Role Must Have Skills Total experience of 7+ Years with 4+ Years in Java/ J2EE Development Strong in Java, J2EE Sr. Developers… https://t.co/pdtjk3is00 https://t.co/FAllOQsvho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: Sr Java Developer Ref No.: 18-23246 Location: McLean, Virginia Position: Sr Java Developer Location: McLean, VA MUST HAVE SKILLS – Solid Java and Spring framework knowledge – Expertise in producing and consuming message with JMS Topic… https://t.co/6VgZBUj5Vo https://t.co/GhKJvlD3Wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: ***ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply*** General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT), a leading provider of systems engineering, integration, IT service operations and support solutions, is… https://t.co/lbtbsFMr1q https://t.co/n48OKfwigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Java Developer (UI): Careers Center | Front End Java Developer (UI) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/qoZDYpPkdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin could bring internet to a halt, report warns https://t.co/CYMznCBPaJ https://t.co/xtvhE3ZOLy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>