<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/5nBycozVJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/5wqMRDzJPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/JkbMm5SA7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/DBOAZu7t19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/VvkPdBJrWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/iahoc4TKjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/FuDK1mdQxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/ty4obPIUuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/huld568UPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/HmuoNTO4fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/IMy2M0nyxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/4o9yH01y1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/ikpVIWzVPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/qPKsm0pY78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/QTvgJlPXg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/MfTE9BKZlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/2P0QbfIduJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/rX4sG2RgHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/SvmMKgpyVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/ArN5y7eOP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/S4Z3bzGadP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/ZCO0SddYLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/jrldVI5ILo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/ZK9stfNNiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/MwAvNI54cH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/tmfgcfHd4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/LlPEi8w1y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/o883VHCz7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/W4rykCGUhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/wURR6D5bTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/c6HmM76n8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/RDIjXD2wNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/lO1NIt2vUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1TIcgf4vXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/2u6LOyIXlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/XvR3xyXT9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/NSLewNzl9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/V9ghWTrhTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/UZI2jOUXRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/79njtSYn3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/lm55CpiEZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/z6xQhVS9MT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/nw2Svx7GxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/W65FGCxZAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/8TmXuBCjoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/RBnv2L2bzb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>