<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/JcFBUIiohk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/fWvV8OvrXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/o1zvSRPAnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/84dzytrKm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/CudHWiqjDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/K3cy59JYnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/ifWY34eVKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/rUu9vREDf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/vFG70te7Bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/JInvDLiwgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/QJG2LDTFpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/wDgf70l3Gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/kHgxa9B4xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/2wQX961WPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/0zPuOtbCmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/KuuBpz2DiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mets have found ways of losing that I never knew existed. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/PV6XUfoe0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/26scktrrY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/t7ewk5zun2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/Rolsf58kkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/PMfsZGys26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/6gj4L8Q5aY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/6e93aNn2Hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/9pvMR5FVzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/ZFx8iJygk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/zsAoP5TzOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/Zeqy13p1xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/zSaxqSHHb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/V0hWnsrwNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/lMQFk7Zqpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/rdNrd556NX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/PZxXPbBaLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/8dkuvJ1hmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/PDmKnV7FwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/QObhe8OyJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/v0v62IWiL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/84dzytrKm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/lM63wTtoH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Everyday Impact of Math  http://t.co/qXws1ayJ4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/fyOQ1OGYD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/G6fSAJKYBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/Wqp01MNYMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/DcOwpXUvjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/c78TuMwWOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/nm5lyQKMCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/bT9FIwdRP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/xnfsAQmI48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/Z3Em0WIyVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/elcqqxK3VA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/WxvjElWiHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/btNtVGTJ6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/DVtoYwVfbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/9nKka6kMO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/u3HwV4AdTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/9JLF0hFrTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>