<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweden's Northvolt lands BMW deal in boost before fund raising: Sweden's Northvolt has secured a partnership with German carmaker BMW and is seeking more funds from the European Investment Bank (EIB) to help its plans to build Europe's largest battery… https://t.co/2ybw09Dwff https://t.co/djcZJrGKXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Search by Keyword Search by Location Create Alert Please enable JavaScript to subscribe.Send me alerts every days alert frequency in every certain days this Job Software Engineer now Date: Sep 22, 2018 Location:… https://t.co/BzXmhf4sQX https://t.co/guV0x8Eg4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rivals ARM and Intel make peace to secure Internet of Things: Rival semiconductor giants ARM and Intel have agreed to work together to manage networks of connected devices from both firms, clearing a major stumbling block to market growth of the… https://t.co/VYSKImixp1 https://t.co/U8wyX167Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMW teams up with Sweden's Northvolt, Umicore for electric car batteries: German carmaker BMW has created a vehicle battery recycling venture with Belgian materials and recycling firm Umicore and Northvolt, which is building a battery factory in Sweden. https://t.co/rMgMNxY7ab https://t.co/28Iw4oIN0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Angular Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems. Primary languages include Java and Angular. The… https://t.co/nW40Cgmdmd https://t.co/W92SFHbkap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Web Developer – [ 2 one 5 ] Creative – Work – About – Contact – Blog – Work – About – Contact – Blog Web Developer Job Description [ 2 one 5 ] Creative, an award-winning digital branding agency located in Old City, Philadelphia, is seeking… https://t.co/gsUwdglEoP https://t.co/HMFBiVtS1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany says it is pushing for battery cell production in Germany: Germany is pushing for battery cell production to be set up in Europe's biggest economy, the German Economy Ministry said in a statement following a meeting of members of the European… https://t.co/ZIV9s3j10j https://t.co/AgvXt438As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As companies embrace AI, it's a job-seeker's market: Dozens of employers looking to hire the next generation of tech employees descended on the University of California, Berkeley in September to meet students at an electrical engineering and computer… https://t.co/L3Uuyx8VfE https://t.co/ZinTd4ZJKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMW, Northvolt and Umicore team up on battery sustainability: BMW is partnering with Swedish battery company Northvolt and Belgian materials and recycling group Umicore on a project to create a sustainable life cycle for batteries, the companies said on… https://t.co/0lJ21lm1kv https://t.co/O52hiARWJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba's Jack Ma says in talks with Indonesia on tech training institute: (This Oct. 13 story corrects to clarify training plan is under discussion, removes references to the number people to be trained and timeframe in paragraphs 1-2) https://t.co/qkZ30penjR https://t.co/AFiyHI9OoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – AWS/Big Data Analytics: The Data Analytics team searching for a senior developer for AWS / Big Data development. Employer is shifting our development to leaner, faster and more innovative solutions. Business and technical team are… https://t.co/qTAqKpJw9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/fo0e8gOqda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer Instructional Media Specialist: DrexelJobs @ Drexel University : Posting Details Skip to Main Content – Home – Search Postings – Create Job Interest Profile – Create Application – Login – Drexel Home – Drexel HR Home – How to Tutorial –… https://t.co/9hzt7NCNp7 https://t.co/bYNwGm4ACb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Search by Keyword Search by Location Create Alert Please enable JavaScript to subscribe.Send me alerts every days alert frequency in every certain days this Job Network Engineer now Date: Sep 22, 2018 Location: Network… https://t.co/g8GngRO6CN https://t.co/G7YrVN6uFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Full Stack Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new… https://t.co/KKu9LzAph5 https://t.co/MuqSJLOuEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – SAP Preferred Success Product Management [Newtown Square, PA] Job: Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Customer Service and Support Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Intern COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP started in… https://t.co/tMYC58nTsP https://t.co/qrdG7KVTij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SR Number ERS-/ERS-/2018/****** Designation Project Manager Location Pennsylvania Job Family Engg (Engg – S/W &amp; S/W Product Engg) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for conceptualising and delivering the solution/product to the… https://t.co/DjQYsohgAs https://t.co/xVlOHqhVro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer Job in US – PA – Jenkintown for Precision Castparts Corp. | Engineering Automation Engineer US – PA – Jenkintown Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 19150 Req. Id 235 Req. Code ******.9 Category… https://t.co/FJbF0ritDP https://t.co/qE1d7SpRl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASP. Net with Azure Cloud: ASP. Net with Azure Cloud Ref No.:18-03871 Location: Chester Brook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery… https://t.co/A7lUFsAXkj https://t.co/jLa70VbdfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer/Support CICS MQ, API, COBOL, JCL: Specialist Developer/Support ‘ CICS, DB2, MQ, API, COBOL, JCL The Global Institutional Accounting and Risk Solutions Information Technology team is seeking an experienced Specialist Developer. The… https://t.co/jODF3jrFE1 https://t.co/xtx8awcRM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevSecOps Technical Lead: Are you looking for a job that allows you to have a meaningful impact on the Development Teams and enable delivery of secure applications at a faster pace? If so, this job is for you! The Enterprise Security and Fraud department… https://t.co/0gz7b8if5l https://t.co/tpMlm35FAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer: Job ID : 73078BR_2 Location : US – Connecticut – Branford,US – Pennsylvania – Philadelphia, UK – Altrincham : Job Description Job Description Position Summary: The Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer is… https://t.co/R5FtOK7yMz https://t.co/AqGApD6zGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Engineer – Network Resilience Analyst: Job Information: Cybersecurity Engineer – Network Resilience Analyst – ******* Job Email Opening Title Cybersecurity Engineer – Network Resilience Analyst – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon… https://t.co/1BrG1IYiJp https://t.co/eZT9yepMJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager: Project manager Ref No.: 18-39684 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 07/16/2018 Job title : Project manager Duration Long term Location Philadelphia PA Job Description: Needs to be Technical PM with 10+ years exp,… https://t.co/ImLoC7OeJW https://t.co/OVPOG0TVlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Presales Solutions Architect: Apply on Company Website Cyber Security Presales Solutions Architect Unisys Malvern, PA Apply on Company Website Posted 1 hour ago Cyber Security PreSales Architect – Stealth Location: Baltimore, MD (as needed… https://t.co/XTXJDCrDXj https://t.co/t5bdeg8hiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator 1: THE POSITION The Information Technology Office is seeking a highly motivated and experienced professional to maintain the data network communications for the PA Liquor Control Board. If you have advanced understanding of… https://t.co/ufNCD51Nnq https://t.co/u9lPQiE0za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: U.S. senators urge India to soften data localization stance: Two U.S. senators have called on Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi to soften India's stance on data localization, warning that measures requiring it represent "key trade barriers"… https://t.co/o2GjfmySZl https://t.co/tWyXwHmEiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP – Order to Cash Lead: Apply on Company Website SAP – Order to Cash Lead Merck &amp; Co., Inc. West Point, PA Apply on Company Website Posted 1 hour ago Requisition ID: BUS****** Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United… https://t.co/YUdqmRPCxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba's Jack Ma to open institute for tech entrepreneurs in Indonesia: Jack Ma, executive chairman of China's Alibaba Group Holding, said on Saturday he plans to open an institute to train thousands of tech entrepreneurs in Indonesia, where he is… https://t.co/qhQFNQ3QvT https://t.co/ivVj3iaCbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Analytics Consultant BI Big Data Scrum Master: Job Location US-PA-Pittsburgh ID 2018-5729 Group Analytics Type Regular Full-Time Overview Sr. Analytics Consultant BI &amp; Big Data Scrum Master EXL (NASDAQ:EXLS) is a leading operations management and… https://t.co/OQt6Ux9UCb https://t.co/hFBqY2gIg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DataStage Developer: Company Description Must Have Skills (Top 3 technical skills only) * 1. stakeholder management 2. Technical discussions 3. technical oversigh Job Description Detailed Job Description: 1. Hands on in coding 2. Code Review 3. Technical… https://t.co/evd3NPt9j0 https://t.co/GX95edqaT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ST Engineering wins $5.5 million Singapore contract to test smart lamp-posts: Singapore Technologies Engineering has won a S$7.5 million ($5.5 million) contract for the trial of a smart lamp-post project in Singapore, which includes fitting sensors and… https://t.co/0rHZviqFlo https://t.co/nDI89o7AVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Associate Consultant: IT Technology Associate Consultant Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by… https://t.co/2SnC3B233O https://t.co/xbh9SwpFJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HRIS Analyst – Intermediate – PSH HR Information Systems: Penn State Health Shared Services Location: US:PA:Hershey Work Type: Full Time FTE: 1.0 Shift: Day Hours: 8:00a – 5:00p JOB SUMMARY: Responsible to analyze day-to-day information needs for various… https://t.co/CLy4DrCHtw https://t.co/iuA3FON1A5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook now says data breach affected 29 million users, details impact: Cyber attackers stole data from 29 million Facebook accounts using an automated program that moved from one friend to the next, Facebook Inc announced on Friday, as the social media… https://t.co/AN5oZqSOAN https://t.co/WakSTo9Lnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook now says data breach affected 29 mln users, details impact: Cyber attackers stole data from 29 million Facebook accounts using an automated program that moved from one friend to the next, Facebook Inc announced on Friday, as the social media… https://t.co/i6327FssS6 https://t.co/IImGx2dBmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom gets EU antitrust nod for CA Technologies deal: Chipmaker Broadcom Inc said on Friday it has obtained antitrust clearance from the European Union for its $19-billion deal to acquire software company CA Technologies Inc. https://t.co/N9wYT2VePI https://t.co/iJtnigbGgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook trims data breach to 29 million users as FBI probes: Cyber attackers stole data from 29 million Facebook accounts using an automated program that moved from one friend to the next, Facebook Inc said on Friday, as the social media company said… https://t.co/fMRVVaYdAL https://t.co/NycBxHwqX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google tells U.S. lawmakers it is mulling options on China services: Alphabet Inc's Google unit has told U.S. lawmakers it is considering "a variety of options" for offering additional services in China. https://t.co/JxOGWsqBum https://t.co/neYdKS4hLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers urge Canada to snub China's Huawei in telecoms: Two leading U.S. lawmakers, both sharp critics of China, urged Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau on Friday to consider dropping China's Huawei Technologies [HWT.UL] from helping to build… https://t.co/3TION6YSzk https://t.co/5Vg5e0r0dA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Job Summary Personnel in this position will design, develop, deploy, maintain, support, upgrade and troubleshoot a variety of computer software applications and systems used by clients, both internal and external to the… https://t.co/oudFfxdS9i https://t.co/dnkOXsRjAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers stole details of 29 million users in Facebook breach: Facebook Inc said on Friday attackers stole names and contact details of 29 million users in the mass security breach disclosed by the social media network late last month. https://t.co/Nbk5WrUn41 https://t.co/pcAAV0d7bM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon says India customer base surges during festive sale: U.S. online giant Amazon said its festive season sale in India had got off to a strong start, with three times the number of people signing up to shop in the first two days compared to last year. https://t.co/LnuZJDkiWT https://t.co/nyupuBUlvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy resisting EU push to impose sanctions over cyberattacks: Italy is resisting a European Union push to impose sanctions on states who carry out cyberattacks, a move that appears in line with Rome's calls to de-escalate tensions with Russia but that… https://t.co/EeEX1xzNLv https://t.co/TVD3Fw97L3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Careers Center | Java Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/e4WxS6YBUL https://t.co/68thBn7ZwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Key EU lawmaker's plan to rein in online marketplaces a threat to Amazon: Amazon could face a threat other than just EU antitrust scrutiny after a key EU lawmaker announced proposals aimed at curbing online marketplaces' use of merchants' data… https://t.co/5VkJXuYH7z https://t.co/7vIYhuA50I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. defends FCC's repeal of net neutrality rules: The Trump administration defended the Federal Communications Commission repeal of landmark open internet rules known as net neutrality, urging a federal appeals court to reject a challenge. https://t.co/GHXjayaK9j https://t.co/hwHFFjWd3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer: – Location: Wilkes Barre, Pennsylvania, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: September 19, 2018 – Position Title:Java Programmer – Company Name:Chubb – Entry Level:No About Chubb For more than 125 years, the Chubb Group of… https://t.co/G6jkBxQE3S https://t.co/40nN7QK89I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Huawei to invest 1 billion yuan in cloud business over 3 years: China's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd, the world's largest telecom-equipment maker, plans to invest 1 billion yuan ($145 million) over the next three year to develop artificial… https://t.co/ArQvKZ3QY3 https://t.co/rnl8ZfEu5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nokia chairman reopens old wounds with new book: Nokia's chairman has pointed the finger at his predecessor over the mobile phone maker's fall from grace in a book that has reopened old wounds in Finland, where the company remains a source of national… https://t.co/WnlYnlBjWl https://t.co/jJz57iqjWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer: ‘ Sr. Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer-&gt;&gt; Leads the design and development of highly complex application problems, system administration issues, or network concerns. Performs systems management and… https://t.co/QTVUVtWkOa https://t.co/1SxtJG5009]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange teams up with Google on Dunant transatlantic cable: Orange and Google have forged a partnership to work on the Dunant transatlantic submarine cable project connecting France and the United States, the French telecoms operator said on Friday. https://t.co/1FWgWB076R https://t.co/t5Y7mX4mTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank picks Nomura, Goldman, three others to lead mobile unit's IPO: source: SoftBank Group Corp has chosen five investment banks, including units of Nomura Holdings Inc and Goldman Sachs, as lead underwriters for the mammoth initial public offering… https://t.co/4uOAtUp5G6 https://t.co/llgJpxUVcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMG Desk Developer II: To provide intermediate level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems, under supervision of a more senior developer.… https://t.co/oU7rhD4kHy https://t.co/kBJy9HCvkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange teams up with Google on Dunant transatlantic cable project: French telecoms operator Orange said on Friday it was partnering with Google on the Dunant transatlantic submarine cable project connecting the United States and France. https://t.co/s6WBkI8RfB https://t.co/8ikPbrLZK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer – Senior AV Engineer: Job Description TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable,… https://t.co/yxERYwgcmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla says orders placed by Oct 15 eligible for full tax credit: Electric carmaker Tesla Inc said https://t.co/XfEtWIUgdx orders for cars placed by Oct. 15 will be eligible for a full federal tax credit of $7,500 and these customers will get their cars… https://t.co/lfhwPSKstx https://t.co/udKt1OuGGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhatsApp hits the road with skits to stamp out fake news in India: On a hot morning in India's tourist mecca of Jaipur, an open truck painted in the signature lime-green colors of Facebook's WhatsApp messaging service pulls into a dusty lane, where five… https://t.co/GorKEtytHT https://t.co/Cq3QVii9OT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel reduces stake in ASML to below 3 percent: Intel has reduced its stake in supplier ASML Holding to just below 3 percent, according to an update from the registry of the Netherlands' Authority for Financial Markets (AFM) on Friday. https://t.co/nvjhxRoS9q https://t.co/w2rBNqemsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[App Developer MECH: App Developer – MECH Ref No.:18-00589 Location: Mechanicsburg, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile environment.… https://t.co/NFlhIpzpOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK to cut hybrid car subsidies: Britain will cut the incentives available to those buying plug-in hybrid vehicles as it focuses on pure electric models, sparking anger from an industry trade body as carmakers already face declining sales in Europe's… https://t.co/11LeIVGxRd https://t.co/R2VVJFRf02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla says orders placed by October 15 eligible for full tax credit: Electric carmaker Tesla Inc said https://t.co/XfEtWIUgdx all orders for its vehicles placed by Oct. 15 are eligible for full federal tax credit of $7,500 and such customers will get… https://t.co/aafvnWbb0B https://t.co/ZE1gAU8ziZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criminal Justice System Specialist 1: THE POSITION The Pennsylvania Commission on Crime and Delinquency is looking for a detail-oriented individual to coordinate the administration of grants designed to assist victims of crime to cope with the physical,… https://t.co/aqpgpII10d https://t.co/TDXm9Xn7ZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent Music delays $2 billion U.S. IPO due to weak markets: sources: Tencent Music Entertainment has delayed its planned U.S. initial public offering (IPO) until at least November as the owner of China's most popular music apps prefers to wait for… https://t.co/YKvD9DIoDA https://t.co/mDksWeW5aY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst: To provide entry level telecommunications network services, including administering, monitoring, documenting, installing, and configuring basic network systems. To provide first level network problem determination services. Come join our… https://t.co/KymapanJKF https://t.co/c7CrfMGEpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer: Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Job Description Job Description Position Summary: The Senior Software Quality Engineer is responsible for performing Software Quality Assurance… https://t.co/MkvtMvs33k https://t.co/fAcytIc3ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer PL/SQL Java: For BNY Mellon Principal Developer – PL/SQL Java job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers –… https://t.co/1XCFb2l376 https://t.co/SqqOa065ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer 1: Applications Developer 1 Salary $25.09 Hourly Location Mansfield, PA Job Type Full time Department Campus Technologies Job Number A20-FT-2018 Closing 10/21/2018 11:59 PM Eastern DESCRIPTION BENEFITS Position Description Work… https://t.co/Xv5kruTYln https://t.co/w4XyBGjhw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QRiBeDesQB Developer: Careers Center | ****** Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/oUfEyNZTFl https://t.co/J5mGHbpppn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cognos Developer: Cognos Developer Ref No.: 18-42427 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Title : Cognos Developer Location : Malvern , PA Contract Role Job Description Experience with Cognos 10 Good understanding of Cognos Admin, and other tools in the… https://t.co/Ke6nBnJeoy https://t.co/1M1PXwPFgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's Flipkart confident of bumper sales season; says Amazon losing relevance: Indian online retailer Flipkart, owned by Walmart Inc, expects bumper sales during the annual festive season that just kicked off, as it boasts that U.S. rival Amazon Inc is… https://t.co/j9gijKgbvE https://t.co/aLopi5Hi6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us API Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 20464Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Malvern, PA 19355Security… https://t.co/wiGnCCq0HJ https://t.co/DNoXCoDS26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. senators asks Google to explain delay in disclosing vulnerability: Three influential Republican U.S. senators on Thursday asked Alphabet Inc's Google unit to explain why it delayed disclosing vulnerabilities with its Google+ social network. https://t.co/N6e634yF9L https://t.co/oTMn2SB2Tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook deletes Russian firm's accounts over alleged data scraping: Facebook has disabled dozens of accounts and profiles belonging to Russian database provider SocialDataHub for what it termed the unauthorized collection of user information, the social… https://t.co/qtqTmT7JAW https://t.co/T684FkxhJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer Electronic Communications: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG)’ ‘ is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/TGbDDowMbL https://t.co/TbkrE1N6I1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Job ID : 73154BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description As part of a global team, the IT Project Manager will be responsible for the successful delivery of critical IT enabled business change, whilst achieving the… https://t.co/RlHWnhXaT0 https://t.co/L6UDCc0aHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn's Sept revenue jumps, buoys hopes for solid sales at Apple: Taiwan's Foxconn, a key Apple Inc supplier, reported a 30 percent jump in September revenue on Thursday, boosting expectations for solid product sales for the American tech giant even as… https://t.co/Jdyqq8rDeS https://t.co/JA4pxtbMD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager – Treasury Services Technology: Sr. Principal Project/Program Manager-&gt;&gt; Leads and provides innovative direction and guidance for a wide array of activities associated with project planning and management to ensure that projects are… https://t.co/ihBZYOSfeL https://t.co/hT7nhF2SQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC, Tesla support approval of settlement: U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, Tesla Inc and Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk filed a submission late on Wednesday in support of the approval and resolution of civil matters, saying the terms were in… https://t.co/uRJtNl2phm https://t.co/2viSIrYC8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VW's Skoda deliveries drop 16 percent in September as WLTP rules start: Deliveries of Skoda Auto cars, part of the Volkswagen group, dropped 16 percent in September, largely in European markets due to conversions to conform to the Worldwide Harmonised… https://t.co/stknteEoHG https://t.co/6fAWt4PIld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Reverse gear - China car dealers push for tax cut as auto growth stalls: China's top auto dealers' association has asked the government to halve taxes on car purchases to revive faltering sales, sources said, as worries grow the country's auto… https://t.co/89fJ8fqTsh https://t.co/m3OjPwJTtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ubisoft shares rise to beat market sell-off after good sales for video game: Shares in French video games maker Ubisoft rose by around 1 percent on Thursday, making them one of the few stocks to rise despite a broader market sell-off, after Ubisoft… https://t.co/9MUqAkJLfI https://t.co/u1emo5Upd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Alipay says stolen Apple IDs behind thefts of users' money: Ant Financial's Alipay, the operator of one of China's top two mobile payment apps, said hackers have taken an unknown amount of money from accounts using stolen Apple Inc IDs and the… https://t.co/lP93AFW3of https://t.co/qcvVUr8rN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German coalition parties spat over diesel car fines: Ministers from Chancellor Angela Merkel's conservatives attacked on Thursday a proposal by the Social Democrats to fine carmakers who fail to offer diesel hardware retrofits, opening a new battle front… https://t.co/InHAAHyb4w https://t.co/TY5KdjDs01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German economy minister doubts constitutionality of diesel fines: German Economy Minister Peter Altmaier said on Thursday the government could run the risk of breaking the law if it imposed fines on carmakers who fail to offer diesel hardware retrofits. https://t.co/9w0ERvWZCn https://t.co/XZrI2HlwKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple to buy part of supplier Dialog's business in $600 million deal: Apple Inc has agreed to buy a portion of chip supplier Dialog Semiconductor Plc's business in a $600 million deal, the two companies said Thursday, expanding the iPhone maker's chip… https://t.co/hx9SSaVoUr https://t.co/ORvAxScWJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Developer Healthcare Big data: Job Description Careers Job Description – About Us – knowledge Hub – Careers – Contact – Partner Login – North AmericaEuropeMiddle EastWorldwide – – Markets – Medical Technology – Enable healthcare technology… https://t.co/6Hpz4mkdW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PDM Sr. System Administrator: Job ID : 73211BR Location : US – California – Carlsbad|US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description Sr. System Administrator – PDM Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. is the world leader in serving science, with revenues of… https://t.co/Zyfp9wn9kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Careers Center | Mainframe Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/VG9Jytjs6C https://t.co/oBpnMKNeQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QRiBeDesQB Developer: Careers Center | ****** Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/pw7J9Nj0VU https://t.co/aycgvuHxUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst IT Intern: Job/Internship Description COMPANY PROFILE The Access segment consists of the JLG and Jerr-Dan business units. At JLG, we are committed to being the provider of choice worldwide for access equipment. The Company’s diverse… https://t.co/iMu1Bq6ILa https://t.co/4xEU4LU5OM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency theft hits nearly $1 billion in first nine months: report: Theft of cryptocurrencies through hacking of exchanges and trading platforms soared to $927 million in the first nine months of the year, up nearly 250 percent from the level seen… https://t.co/AvwPJN9FMw https://t.co/Wm2z0QWrGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanzanian rangers harness new technology to fight poachers: In Tanzania's Grumeti Game Reserve, next to Serengeti National Park, elephants roam, rangers sleep more peacefully at night, and poachers have been put on notice, thanks to new technology… https://t.co/jipNqTAgNK https://t.co/fOzwfNJR53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Vietnam cyber law set for tough enforcement despite Google, Facebook pleas: Vietnam is preparing to strictly enforce a new cybersecurity law requiring global technology companies to set up local offices and store data locally despite pleas… https://t.co/PNZdX8YD6t https://t.co/JsExZiRIUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IKEA eyes partnership deals to boost Russian online business: IKEA Group is looking to sign strategic partnerships with Russian companies to boost its local online business, the furniture retailer's Russia country manager Pontus Erntell said on Wednesday. https://t.co/Jg47FpizyA https://t.co/lsTUXohLNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global regulators say crypto currencies need vigilant monitoring: Crypto assets do not pose a threat to financial stability but "vigilant" monitoring is needed along with possible action to protect consumers, the global Financial Stability Board said on… https://t.co/5cvVGkzPpG https://t.co/tZtid0aHME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhatsApp bug let hackers hijack accounts with a video call: reports: A bug in Facebook's WhatsApp messaging service allowed hackers to take over users' applications when they answered an incoming video call, technology websites ZDnet and The Register… https://t.co/PapceWJq4b https://t.co/jVPYyKnwUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-Leg Tech HARR: Programmer Analyst-Leg Tech – HARR Ref No.: 18-00673 Location: Camp Hill, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic… https://t.co/8NfB3nc2wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France's EDF aims to be market leader in electric vehicle charging: French state-controlled utility EDF wants to become a European market leader in electric vehicle charging, its chief executive said on Wednesday. https://t.co/mMTFIuXWLD https://t.co/mWRqXQCPB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei unveils new AI chips amid Chinese technology ambitions: China's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd [HWT.UL], the world's largest telecom-equipment maker, unveiled an AI chip on Wednesday that will power its servers, in a push to boost its nascent… https://t.co/CaGr3mBFsl https://t.co/pUOMQV26Ky]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>