<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Kites rise highest against the wind - not with it." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Talent develops in tranquillity, character in the full current of human life." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let freedom reign. The sun never set on so glorious a human achievement." - Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One of the greatest diseases is to be nobody to anybody." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is not started today is never finished tomorrow." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every adversity, every failure, every heartache carries with it the seed on an equal or greater benefit." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do what you can, with what you have, where you are." - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A great man shows his greatness by the way he treats little men." - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People are just about as happy as they make up their minds to be." - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we are together nothing is impossible. If we are divided all will fail." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every man is guilty of all the good he didn't do." - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Start by doing what is necessary, then do what is possible, and suddenly you are doing the impossible." - St. Francis of Assisi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Aerodynamically the bumblebee shouldn't be able to fly, but the bumblebee doesn't know that so it goes on flying anyway." - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All glory comes from daring to begin." - Eugene F. Ware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you think you can win, you can win. Faith is necessary to victory." - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Act the way you'd like to be and soon you'll be the way you act." - Leonard Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where your talents and the needs of the world cross lies your calling." - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How far that little candle throws his beams. So shines a good deed in a weary world." - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Knowledge is power." - Francis Bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man should make all he can, and give all he can." - Nelson Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Improve your spare moments and they will become the brightest gems in your life." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Give a man a fish and you feed him for a day. Teach him how to fish and you feed him for a lifetime." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is not measured by the number of breaths we take, but by the moments that take our breath away." -  Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can't believe that God put us on this earth to be ordinary." - Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A good head and a good heart are always a formidable combination." - Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Time is more value than money. You can get more money, but you cannot get more time." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Time sets the stage; fate writes the script; but only we may choose our character." - Liam Thomas Ryder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are the only person on earth who can use your ability." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will find the key to success under the alarm clock." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is the condiment that gives success its flavour." - Truman Capote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest thing in the world is to know how to be one's own self." - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Confidence is a plant of slow growth in an aged bosom: youth is the season of credulity." - William Pitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Willing is not enough; we must do." -  Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is predestined: The obstacles of your past can become the gateways that lead to  new beginnings." - Ralph Blum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not because things are difficult that we do not dare, it is because we do not dare that they are difficult." - Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failures are finger posts on the road to achievement." - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The quality, not the longevity, of one's life is what is important." - Martin Luther King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not bring me your successes; they weaken me. Bring me your problems; they strengthen me." - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To avoid criticism, do nothing, say nothing, and be nothing." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not look where you fell, but where you slipped." - African Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've experienced many terrible things in my life, a few of which actually happened." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If everything seems under control, you're just not going fast enough." - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What keeps me going is goals." - Mahummaad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to have confidence in your ability, and then be tough enough to follow through." - Rosalynn Carter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fortune favours the brave." - Publius Terence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want a quality, act as if you already had it." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you are not willing to risk the unusual, you will have to settle for the ordinary." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only you can control your future." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the hopes of reaching the moon men fail to see the flowers that blossom at their feet." -  Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Throw your heart over the fence and the rest will follow." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong." - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without a sense of urgency, desire loses its value." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability can take you to the top, but it takes character to keep you there." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hard work without talent is a shame, but talent without hard work is a tragedy." - Robert Half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A year from now you may wish you had started today." - Karen Lamb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Education is what remains after one has forgotten what one has learned in school." - Albert Einstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The full use of your powers along lines of excellence." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest danger in times of turbulence is not the turbulence; it is to act with yesterday's logic." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For success, attitude is equally as important as ability." - Harry F. Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Respond intelligently even to unintelligent treatment." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The real leader has no need to lead; he is content to point the way." - Henry Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We know accurately only when we know little, with knowledge doubt increases." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." - Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are what we think. With our thoughts we make our world." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Delay always breeds danger." - Miguel de Cervantes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To change one's life; Start immediately. Do it flamboyantly. No exceptions." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To create something you must be something." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of success is to know something nobody else knows." - Aristotle Onassis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must not only aim right, but draw the bow with all your might." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man with no imaginations has no wings." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All children are artists. The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up." - Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pursue worthy aims." - Anna Cummins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That some achieve great success, is proof to all that others can achieve it as well." - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more elaborate our means of communication, the less we communicate." - Joseph Priestley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't resist change. They resist being changed!" - Peter Senge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing, not even sheer ability, can make up for the dedication required for a successful business career." - Ray Eppert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Discovery consists of seeing what everybody has seen and thinking what nobody else has thought." - Jonathan Swift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we see men of a contrary character, we should turn inwards and examine ourselves." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A person can succeed at anything for which there is enthusiasm." - Charles M. Schwab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For a man to achieve all that is demanded of him he must regard himself as greater than he is." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to teach people is by telling a story." - Kenneth Blanchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're not sure where you are going, you're liable to end up someplace else." - Robert F. Mager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One important key to success is self-confidence. An important key to self-confidence is preparation. - Arthur Ashe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To get the full value of joy you must have someone to divide it with." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I look at the masses, I will never act. If I look at the one, I will." - Mother Theresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Persistence and determination alone are omnipotent." - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Champions aren't made in gyms. Champions are made from something they have deep inside them . A desire, a dream, a vision." - Muhammed Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great works are performed, not by strength, but by perseverance." - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of success is to be ready when your opportunity comes." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is particularly hard if you divide it into small jobs." - Henry Ford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is more damaging to you than to do something that you believe is wrong." - Abraham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what happens to you it's what you do about it that makes the difference." - Wilson Mitchell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want a place in the sun, you have to put up with a few blisters." - Abigail Van Buren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything has changed, except our way of thinking." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whenever you see a successful business, someone once made a courageous decision." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the End, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends." - Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can't solve problems by using the same kind of thinking we used when we created them." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star." William Clement Stone]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>