<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot push anyone up the ladder unless he is willing to climb. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you make others feel about themselves, says a lot about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_grit: The principle is competing against yourself. It's about self improvement, about being better than you were the day before.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone else's happiness is your happiness, that's love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your passion is priceless. Never stop the pursuit. https://t.co/XeSCwb2uHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you just have to create your own sunshine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person often meets his destiny on the road he took to avoid it. - Jean de La Fontaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is hard at first, messy in the middle and gorgeous at the end. https://t.co/Ihlnx1NsT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't stop dreaming and exploring because we grow old. We grow old because we stop dreaming and exploring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more powerful then someone who has faith and a mission. https://t.co/AwMCvRwCun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm strong because I know my weaknesses. I'm wise because I've been foolish. I laugh because I've known sadness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the End, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends. - Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_grit: Great words for any athlete. https://t.co/ltvb3Bm80l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give without remembering and always receive without forgetting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL https://t.co/uFdZlNt7mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be positive, patient and persistent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/zRiSBuUxcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to learn to laugh at ourselves, don't take life too seriously. - Geri Halliwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your eyes to see the needs, and use your talents to meet them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes there is!! https://t.co/GAy1OOLHGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never too late to be what you might have been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't base your life on other people's expectations. -Stevie Wonder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleHeadBigH: Sometimes you have to forget what's gone, appreciate what remains, and look forward to what's coming next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to predict the future is to create it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At one point in your life you either have the thing you want or the reasons why you don't -Andy Roddick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a man does his best, what else is there? -George Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: 3 great pieces of advice. https://t.co/aTx7CrwXBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith… https://t.co/DzmE0tFH6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always looking outside myself for strength and confidence but it comes from within. It was there all the time. - Anna Freud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success isn't something that just happens - success is learned, success is practiced and then it is shared. -Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to believe that prayer changes things, but now I know that prayer changes us and we change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn your cant's into cans and your dreams into plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear kills more dreams than failure ever will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not your voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you find yourself in the middle of nowhere, and sometimes in the middle of nowhere, you find yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your head up high. https://t.co/YeYfOjEaJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is how you treat those who can do nothing for you. #greatreminder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious. - Albert Einstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up. https://t.co/YnZ5Cxk9PP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomanDoItAll: We rise by lifting others. https://t.co/IJgtNGKvWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody really cares if you're miserable, so you might as well be happy. -Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/WnfHBJqlmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got this!! https://t.co/fnYaO1frNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @catscofffee: We hope you're on the right path ;D

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/mDwGFLyOPd https://t.co/2HlYl1IgwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finish each day &amp; be done with it. You have done what you could. Learn from it; tomorrow is a new day. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: The expert in anything was once a beginner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a voice, not an echo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all lying in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be silent or let thy words be worth more than silence. - Pythagoras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live bold. https://t.co/CQyOT6sYMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Does this vest make me look fat? https://t.co/MOtGysGR7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look back - you're not going that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to start over. It's a brand new opportunity to rebuild what you truly want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise men are not always silent, but they know when to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The strongest people are not those who show strength in front of us, but those who win battles we know nothing about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Priorities first! ;)

Shop this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/4uq2mWLdnc https://t.co/GG9aqrwAYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have intense and unfailing love for one another, for love covers a multitude of sins." -1 Peter 4:8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live simply. Love generously. Speak truthfully. Pray daily. Leave everything else to God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: You cannot find peace by avoiding life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever let anyone steal your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: Aww! This is so heart warming.
https://t.co/cH1xtdZVjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true!!! https://t.co/ZWMhfMna0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: Do it with passion or not at all. https://t.co/AwSLdLf4Bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once the game is over, the king &amp; the pawn go back in the same box. -Italian Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen. -Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let a hard lesson harden your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Speak up, don't hide your thoughts and feelings, especially when you can make a difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't dream your life, live your dreams. https://t.co/6mJP46UKQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I walk slowly, but I never walk backwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the rest of your life the best of your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are blessed. https://t.co/aDzXIHq7HX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness makes you smile; sorrow can crush you. - Proverbs 15:13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to remain silent &amp; be thought a fool that to speak &amp; remove all doubt. -English proverbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I trust God with my Life... after all He gave it to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many people spend money they haven't earned, to buy things they don't want, to impress people they don't like. -Will Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: "Selective participation" at its finest! :D

Shop this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/w6sUm4FJmh https://t.co/VO4eXAJSg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose to look on the bright side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleHeadBigH: What if you woke up today with only the things you thanked God for yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can easily judge the character of a man by how he treats those who can do nothing for him. - James D. Miles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't make excuses for why you can't get it done. Focus on all the reasons why you must make it happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/AfNYmiI42v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live more, complain less.
More smiles, less stress.
Less hate, more blessed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to say 'no' to the good so you can say 'yes' to the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from it. https://t.co/aQMoefNyBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one rule for being a good talker -- learn to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pure_guts_: You don't always get what you wish for, you get what you work for. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put the key to your happiness in someone else's pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good, better, best. Never let it rest. Until your good is better and your better is best. - Tim Duncan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wait until you're ready, you'll be waiting the rest of your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspireMeNow: Have faith the good is just around the corner. https://t.co/yeXvqyKDws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you will allow is what will continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never stop caring, but if you decide to push me away, I will go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never regret the times when put others before yourself. https://t.co/DYjvTP6uL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is the condiment that gives success its flavor. -Truman Capote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One important key to success is self-confidence. An important key to self-confidence is preparation. - Arthur Ashe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it ironic:
- We ignore the ones that adore us
- Adore the ones who ignore us
- Love the ones who hurt us
- Hurt the ones that love us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reminder. https://t.co/AikzuLLIQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is only possible to live happily ever after on a day-to-day basis. -Margaret Bonnano]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>