<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotels Data Specialist: The Company Hopper believes that planning travel should be easy and fun. We empower and inspire travelers by analyzing trillions of past and current trips and notifying travelers when to buy a flight ticket or rent a hotel room in… https://t.co/eq1j92onW0 https://t.co/sSjeDe6OHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: JOB : Data Scientist (Mountain View, CA) Analyze and build data solutions for Google Support. #1615.27329 Exp Incl: machine learning; stat analysis &amp; experimental dsgn; data mining; Python, SQL, or R; &amp; data manipulation. Product Lead… https://t.co/JNXoRY3NCv https://t.co/6AASJCb9if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Information Security Governance: Job Description The ISPO is responsible for the governance of the enterprise-wide Information Security Program, and is composed of three separate areas: ISPO Governance, ISPO Operations, and ISPO… https://t.co/bJnZ6So4kJ https://t.co/1WhT30ZdY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Technology Development Engineer IV: PRIMARY CHARACTERISTICS: * Principles: Supports and models the company’s principles that are identified in the Declaration of Belief and Direction Statement, in all areas of conduct and business. *… https://t.co/L0CjXlH2I9 https://t.co/JvFlbs2tQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Specialist: Requisition Number: 58881  At Insight, I am the solution. Insight is a technology solutions provider serving global and local clients in 191 countries on all continents. Today, thousands of clients, including more than 80… https://t.co/kjrRSUNnDD https://t.co/ySPOVUX8NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Systems Engineering: The General Dynamics Land Systems Intern Program provides an opportunity for students looking to start or continue the transition from academia into industry. Our three-month internship assignments provide compensation based… https://t.co/GpDkbZTe3O https://t.co/gpiQdcu6Zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Smart Earbuds for Travel: AirPods, Pixel Buds, Erato Verse: Super portability and easy access to AI assistants make these wireless headphones must-haves on your next trip. https://t.co/fbbsXZZS9W https://t.co/3idTldmqkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Engineer: Senior Software QA Engineer Job Number: 23056 Primary Location: Redwood City, California US Alternative Location(s): At Informatica, We DATA. We Do Good, Act As One Team, Think Customer First, and Aspire For The Future.… https://t.co/Gcc5Iry0uP https://t.co/NU5WMN5hgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst II: * *Overview** If you want an exciting job with one of the largest off-price retailers in the nation, join the Burlington Stores, Inc. team as an Application Development Analyst! Are you a detail-oriented technology… https://t.co/sXIaUYCC9i https://t.co/cKpTOEUPPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Human Factors (4): Overview: * The Space Launch System (SLS) program is NASAs next crewed vehicle launch system. Our team is supporting SLS with Human Factors Engineering support. The program is currently developing systems and human… https://t.co/7Jy5sCcUY1 https://t.co/w4FsxaP4pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Description QGenda is a fast growing Atlanta-based healthcare software company, with an amazing corporate culture, where we strive to be the best place to be a customer. Our software is used by thousands of hospital departments… https://t.co/oQd5Buuqgj https://t.co/TWSyC3jhLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Lead: I HAVE DEVOPS NEED WITH GCP(GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM) EXPERIENCE IN LOUISVILLE KY 6 MONTHS NEED TO HAVE HANDS ON EXPERIENCE WORKING WITH GCP(GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM) /JAVA/GKT. TWO POSITIONS DEVOPS LEAD DEVOPS ARCHITECT https://t.co/P7ZhWHMa6O https://t.co/sLaUo41WJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst (SQL): Careers | American Institutes for Research |Senior Data Analyst (SQL) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/cgd22d3ZzC https://t.co/M2Eun0BTak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revenue Modeling Data Scientist: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the… https://t.co/sjsIeu861I https://t.co/bRrIQaS5wO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 28840BR Domain Financial services Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Functional Testing , Country USA State / Region / Province Minnesota Work Location Minneapolis,… https://t.co/NoLHM3sgRZ https://t.co/0PkAs6cCJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby Developer: The Backend Developer’s mission is to build the APIs and user interfaces that thousands of developers use when they deploy their sites on Netlify. Our main office is located in the Dogpatch district in San Francisco, CA. Currently, were… https://t.co/XdlfKeSrA6 https://t.co/3QyonNLpoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design, develop, &amp; support trading &amp; risk management applications covering securitized products. Design &amp; develop application components using SDLC, C#, .NET,… https://t.co/OMfpNOER8T https://t.co/iYirBbFgLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Lead: Jpmorgan Chase &amp; Co is looking for Application Developer Lead in Columbus, Ohio. * Design and development of mission critical data warehousing using business intelligence and analytical solutions. * Collaborate with business… https://t.co/iPoB2UXu6Z https://t.co/8W4LDWAzEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram Announces You'll Soon See "Newer" Posts In Your Feed: What users really want is a chronological feed, but today's announcement is at least an acknowledgement that not everything about the algorithmic timeline is working. https://t.co/roKOUV9w5A https://t.co/n59OFaNclQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy Solutions Development Engineer II #ESDE-RVA: Engineering: Johnson Controls, Inc. is seeking Energy Solutions Development Engineer II for its Rockville, VA location to provide technical, process &amp;/or financial support during the design process;… https://t.co/4cQmYghjcf https://t.co/Z5BgCZRL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Cadence Design Systems, Inc. has openings for the following positions (various levels/types/multiple positions) in San Jose, CA. Some positions may allow for telecommuting. To Apply: Send resume w/ Ref# to cadencejobs2@cadence.com.… https://t.co/nhHiGbdC7N https://t.co/Z2Q1vZHRGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/W Dvlprs: S/W Dvlprs HGST, Inc. has opptys in Irvine, CA for Sr Engrs. Mail resume to Attn: HR, 951 SanDisk Dr, MS:HRGM, Milpitas, CA 95035, Ref #IRVSKO. Must be legally auth to work in the U.S. w/o spnsrshp. EOE recblid 0jsmfadii2bse5ztuo6ysb359tzndu https://t.co/PJqrSgnMbb https://t.co/siygYqqGzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Consultant: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Technology Consultant, Deloitte Digital in San Jose, California and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to function as integrator between business needs and… https://t.co/k9U20xJyZN https://t.co/dcVgbABuKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Google LLC,  job # below: Data Scientist (Mountain View, CA) Analyze and build data solutions for Google Support. #1615.27329 Exp Incl: machine learning; stat analysis &amp; experimental dsgn; data mining; Python, SQL, or R; &amp; data… https://t.co/BgInQiFFZj https://t.co/tZK5pZDu3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: The Orange Water and Sewer Authority (OWASA), a progressive water utility providing water, sewer and reclaimed water services to the Towns of Chapel Hill, Carrboro and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, seeks a… https://t.co/9Uih19CC6N https://t.co/YqkWnOVb6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager: A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082: Provide sophisticated technical program management for the build-out of massively scalable, robust,… https://t.co/97b5vDWGKX https://t.co/z8WLTbyQeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Software Engineers (Job code: SW318): Apply software development practices to design, implement, and support individual software projects. Senior… https://t.co/yrxIoJjpGT https://t.co/bGywUFFPcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Analyst: We are a member-owned electric cooperative committed to providing safe, reliable, and affordable electric service with uncompromised excellence in customer service to the citizens of Jones, Onslow, Pender, Duplin, Craven and Lenoir… https://t.co/VHerilyZ3J https://t.co/CWjd80997v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Application Developer The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL backend coding,… https://t.co/RIv0Ha9G27 https://t.co/ajwiCarLDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Information Technology: Organizational Description: Advocates for Youth is dedicated to creating programs and advocating for policies that help young people make informed and responsible decisions about their reproductive and sexual health.… https://t.co/QNtGKGCLur https://t.co/w4GWtujf2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Delivery Manager: Recognized by the city of Alexandria as a Gold Employer, State Department Federal Credit Union is committed to providing the very best in opportunity and professional development. Headquartered in Alexandria, Virginia with… https://t.co/8bdwvW5pMB https://t.co/skRUDc0sqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Alternative For Every Facebook Feature: If you're ready to quit Facebook, here's how to replace everything you might miss. https://t.co/yDbowXXlfl https://t.co/qtnJYrSX8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Qa Engineer: Software QA Engineer, AT SLEEP NUMBER CORPORATION, 111 W Saint John St Suite 1200 San Jose, California 95113, 8+ yrs exp software tester;Tech fld BS rqd;Exp design verification, reviewing specs/ test planning;Exp creating software… https://t.co/UOSa0uyo8I https://t.co/rf18G9Fwew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: IT Positions available at Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: SYSTEMS ANALYSTS: Analyze, design, develop &amp; test applications. Prepare test plans. Create &amp; automate test scripts. Perform risk analysis.… https://t.co/cnJpUypVZp https://t.co/nEeuj9531T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Interaction Designer #8BO0823, Principal Solutions Consultant #8BW2623: TIBCO Software Inc. has the following opportunities in Palo Alto, CA: &amp;nbsp; Associate Interaction Designer [Ref #8BO0823] * Define all aspects of the user experience for… https://t.co/awNsJdcHVQ https://t.co/GlR4zKW8bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy Civil Construction Project Manager: Gallagher CRS is seeking experienced Project Managers that are eager to join prominent contractors in the Richmond, VA area. This position will be responsible for planning construction projects and oversee their… https://t.co/PY5M5RRdLp https://t.co/ct8Sw4bFoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Developer: Category Manager Commodity Manager Supply Chain Victaulic Headquarters in Easton, PA Scope: The Category Manager (CM) will be the lead for negotiations and supplier management with the Victaulic supply base, driving the strategic… https://t.co/FhHfync1lr https://t.co/gAMsyYkOek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mainframe Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Baltimore, Maryland, United States Position ID: J0118-1738 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI Federal is… https://t.co/eY3xcW6jJv https://t.co/eGYpr4JtB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineer 3:   Job Description – Mechanical Engineer 3 (18003481) Mechanical Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18003481 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/2hck51dWcU https://t.co/9lpAzAzXQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: i3- Integration Innovation, Inc. | Job opportunities i3- Integration Innovation, Inc. About Us i3 is an AAP/EEO/VEVRRA equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate against otherwise qualified applicants on the basis of race,… https://t.co/tD7b9a29Ll https://t.co/y95gjqfaNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Hardware Engineer -Intermediate level: Electrical Hardware Engineer -Intermediate level at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program –… https://t.co/87YHdVVZS2 https://t.co/cNEYwmQ0w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineer #180022427: JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co is looking for Associate, Software Engineer in Columbus, Ohio. * Participate in &amp; coordinate application development engagements. * Engage application development teams to implement Extensible… https://t.co/ouGv7I4AFs https://t.co/e6U7Va4BVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Materials Program Manager: Management Position Sunnyvale,CA, Cupertino,CA, San Jose,CA &amp; Palo Alto, CA A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/SM3mBnaqOt Services, Inc. candidates for the following positions (multiple positions available for… https://t.co/ZfnotZXA6p https://t.co/O9NBYSWTHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delivery Drivers: Borden Dairy has openings for Delivery Drivers in the Statesboro, Georgia area. Must be at least 21, Class A or B CDL. $15.00 per hour 40+ hours a week. Benefits include health, dental, vision, paid holidays, vacation and 401k match.… https://t.co/BO4hJpO6By https://t.co/2voylD6gb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Travel Apps: Signal, Sitata, Haven, SaferVPN, Mobile Passport, FoneTrac: Floods. Thieves. Hackers. Tackle any situation abroad with these mobile assistants. https://t.co/crNBVblgMC https://t.co/3ufp0iP9Rz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. * Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work challenges. * Lead design research education to… https://t.co/pAUJ4lHmgu https://t.co/Phg6yJWxSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Corporate Consulting: EMC Corporation (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Senior Manager, Corporate Consulting at our Palo Alto, CA facility to advise senior executives on company’s most pressing business and management issues.… https://t.co/x2jbk9VmYy https://t.co/r5rgCIBEBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software applications. Master’s in Computer… https://t.co/A53A6QPZ5i https://t.co/zfoN3EemlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineerin #FSAP01: Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers and/or projects w/in Analytical Product… https://t.co/swq4SCa9Mi https://t.co/a7gY0XxL5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job Description: Parsley Energy Operations, LLC seeks Software Developer to work at its office in Austin, TX. Develop new software solutions, including responsibility for components of medium size and complexity and… https://t.co/DYTY4SQqcM https://t.co/XC33F2Hmdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Big Data Hadoop Developers: KSN Technologies, Inc. in Chesterton, IN is seeking Sr Big Data Hadoop Developers to maintain, administer &amp; develop custom apps on Hadoop &amp; its ecosystems. No travel; no telecommunication. Position is project-based at… https://t.co/ilASqvLo8X https://t.co/uKuBnBS4vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager II: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082: Provide sophisticated technical program management for the build-out of massively scalable, robust, best-in-class tools and large-scale global distributed or embedded systems… https://t.co/sS2dQ6MHlb https://t.co/dhPi583YhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/W Dvlprs: S/W Dvlprs HGST, Inc. has opptys in Irvine, CA for Sr Engrs. Mail resume to Attn: HR, 951 SanDisk Dr, MS:HRGM, Milpitas, CA 95035, Ref #IRVSKO. Must be legally auth to work in the U.S. w/o spnsrshp. EOE recblid 0jsmfadii2bse5ztuo6ysb359tzndu https://t.co/I2ee0ITqz5 https://t.co/0VMKb2lvgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Development #JSWM: Senior Manager of Development (https://t.co/ijRvoAgyhH, Inc., Midvale, UT) Multiple openings available. Lead multiple teams working on significant &amp; critical projects, provide tech &amp; team leadership &amp; mentorship. Work… https://t.co/psJW1mgra4 https://t.co/wQnkgN335A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Requisition ID R43297. Software Engineer position with Capital One Services II LLC in Chicago Metro Area, IL; Multiple positions available: -Perform technical design,… https://t.co/Jk3fRm0AtT 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/mLJBZuT7n6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, System Software: TECHNOLOGY Mountain View, CA Sr. Engineer, System Software Responsible for designing infrastructure and interfaces, developing integration software, coding quick scripts and… https://t.co/GJ1f5K5lEm 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/L25XmmxPXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the Bike Cyclist Lael Wilcox Uses to Ride 20,000 Miles a Year: Lael Wilcox pedals a distance nearly equal to a trip around the globe every 12 months. https://t.co/hRo7p8VpD7 https://t.co/67Fz47ORyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL… https://t.co/Eiq5BSdUS9 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/yBCGiaMp3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer: Technical Program Specialist (Mountain View, CA) Define feature sets to ensure that the technical aspects of Google programs satisfy the business needs of Google’s clients and users. #1615.19122 Exp Incl: data analysis, stat modeling,… https://t.co/cD7XxJfN3S https://t.co/HZF8LgEjAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Wealth Engineering #FSWE01: Software Engineering Manager, Wealth Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers or projects w/in Wealth Engineering depart. Minimum Requires:… https://t.co/5xJvV1hMBv https://t.co/i3hYHqVSY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Treeline Interactive is searching for an Android Developer who possesses a passion for pushing mobile technologies to the limits and will work with our team of talented engineers to design and build the next generation of our mobile… https://t.co/Edoysyu3do https://t.co/KJsaBTjw4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Data Services: The Software Engineer – Data Services will initially report to the VP of Engineering and be part of a team responsible for the development of our data services, as well as our analytics platform. You will help drive the… https://t.co/yGeYyCts8I https://t.co/G6VQsVR1KJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer, Vaccine Operations: Technical Support Engineer, Vaccine Operations – Language – English – French – Worldwide Careers Site – Sign in – Accessibility – Working at Merck – Why Merck? – Diversity at Merck – From Service to Science… https://t.co/yFQIBk3gBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mechanical Engineer/Manager: Jacksonville, FL Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Senior Mechanical Engineer/Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – HUGE Room for… https://t.co/AQKWNliiF6 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ZPzWTW7tIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Regional Marketing Director,SAP Ariba Job: Date: Mar 7, 2018 Location: Newtown Square, PA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Marketing Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Management Employment Type: Regular Full Time Career… https://t.co/69YUeZoe1F https://t.co/zpVwlxpscC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Hamilton Township, New Jersey, United States Position ID: J0318-1102 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: CGI, a leader in providing IT… https://t.co/TTzUZtHCUr https://t.co/S0zCf8wcZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082:… https://t.co/KFuDK5g0WV 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/p1qzAocrCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sap Otc Manager #0617RC: Sap Otc, Manager Sought by Ingram Micro, Inc., Irvine, CA: Lead &amp; provide strategic systems direction to the Business for all key design decisions &amp; principles related to the overall SCE… https://t.co/bSHvu6ftPq 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Zj8csfQ6A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Developer: Sr Application Developer for US Bank National Association in Denver, CO to perform &amp;/or lead tech design &amp; develop of complex app system. At U.S. Bank, we’re passionate about helping customers and the communities where we live… https://t.co/xPBZsYG1uK https://t.co/TJTPzzt0E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administrative Assistant/Data Encoder: We are seeking a full time and part time Administrative Assistant/Data Entry. You will perform clerical,administrative clerical support and personal assistant functions. Responsibilities: * Assist with accounts… https://t.co/nL6YM50sww https://t.co/egm2jQxLDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Development Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Engineer Applications (Req#ALN2DS) Rspnsble fr dvlping &amp; deplying SW apps. Software Development Engineer… https://t.co/CxdlJXLnTU 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/HtFaI9m25x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scm/Devops #MP6334: Senior Scm/DevOps Engineers (Calabasas, CA) Be part of team responsible for development &amp; support our continuous integration/ deployment infrastructure which consists of automated… https://t.co/vxgGibZet7 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/msUSPWUewW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data #SSE228SU: PeopleConnect, Inc. has an opening for a Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data (Ref# SSE228SU). Work Location:  1501 4th Ave. Suite 400, Seattle, WA  98101. Job Duties:  Build large-scale backend systems, develop… https://t.co/RuUAY3l4ti https://t.co/gvEKJlNg0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R42120: Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, Virginia is looking for Master Software Engineer. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer applications using existing &amp;… https://t.co/oKtENlHW6F https://t.co/wHKNhCj51p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Wealth Engineering #FSWE01: Software Engineering Manager, Wealth Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers or projects w/in Wealth Engineering depart. Minimum Requires:… https://t.co/OGeU938jgg https://t.co/4pQL5TDY0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineerin #FSAP01: Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers and/or projects w/in Analytical Product… https://t.co/dwACiA0bXT https://t.co/42GjCILr1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D Character Artist: Software development company seeking 3D Character Artist to translate concepts design into next-gen models of characters &amp; creatures. Requires: 4 years experience in job offered, or as a… https://t.co/tlEiYHzoJv 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/GCRFP7OEsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate-Technical Operations Analyst #180023559: Jpmorgan Chase &amp; Co is looking for Associate-Tech Ops Analyst in Columbus, Ohio. * Installation, configuration, support and administration of the Statistical Analysis System Enterprise software platform.… https://t.co/3HQgJ6Q1bL https://t.co/kvHiaqIsUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Software Engineering #R42826: Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA is looking for Manager, Software Engineering. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer applications using existing &amp;… https://t.co/oCY19TYkTe https://t.co/KWXMlFpcNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Specialist: Technical Program Specialist (Mountain View, CA) Define feature sets to ensure that the technical aspects of Google programs satisfy the business needs of Google’s clients and users. #1615.19122 Exp Incl: data analysis, stat… https://t.co/9QxAHW5NT4 https://t.co/yJQfdLiqjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Software Engineers (Job code: SW318): Apply software development practices to design, implement, and support… https://t.co/wCE3cRE5QK 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/NWED6evrKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leica CL: Snap Candids in Style With This Discreet New Camera: While potential photographic subjects would shy away from a DSLR-wielding tourist, barely a soul would notice a box as compact as Leica’s CL. https://t.co/T4vjvDTRKi #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/CDa5eR0ROt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geographic Information System Technology Specialist: Utility Data Contractors, Inc is looking for Geographic Information System Technology Specialist in Denver, Colorado. Manage full life cycle development of… https://t.co/S2FL5T0lgt 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/JfL40QvX0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple Information Technology Positions (Pontiac, Michigan): Oakalnd County Michigan, Oakland County’s Award Winning Information Technology Department is hiring! Information Technology Business Analyst- Geographic Information System * $60,298.94 –… https://t.co/RB4uaD4BHq https://t.co/Kv0MsjMeTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst DSS67529599 *Richmond, VA* The developer would be responsible for the design, development, testing, debugging, maintaining and documenting of .Net Web applications in accordance to Software Development Life Cycle… https://t.co/zQStTCW9s9 https://t.co/9pY9DzyJdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Java Developer: Description Are you a talented Junior Java Developer looking for the next step in your career ? Check out PSS! Position Description PSS, Inc. is actively seeking a Junior Java Developer to… https://t.co/GR2snD1Xob 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/JtFCnMplyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Estimator / Project Manager / Sales: Construction Estimator / Project Manager / Sales in Snohomish JobAlready d Location Snohomish, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category Construction / Trades,Sales Job… https://t.co/EhHO7N3sTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Cyber Spec II – ISSO: 112036BR Info Assurance Cyber Spec II – ISSO MA – Woburn Raytheon IDS Information Systems Security Officer (ISSO) -Woburn, MA Security This position is for an Information… https://t.co/WOY3dv5rzf 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design,… https://t.co/JwsYe67mWD 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Tabulation BA – Web App: Design Tabulation BA – Web App  DOT77529377 *Ames, IA* The Strategic Business Analyst skilled at to writing detailed specifications in Microsoft Word for a web application, œDesign… https://t.co/yrFq6M3DeI 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Kht6XRlLx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer: Java Programmer VDH87525762 *Richmond, VA* In need of an experienced Java Programmer/Application Developer to work collaboratively with the DDP Informatics team and software vendor to enhance the functionality of a Java EE application.… https://t.co/klxLgqn6F7 https://t.co/Cg0B7lyOY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Functional Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/1270LGZRdw 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/q7dVSeJOF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Block Calls and Texts on iPhone in iOS 11: Unwanted calls and messages arriving on your iPhone? Block 'em all with our guide. https://t.co/6rrqZNAcd9 #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/0bYz2l3HkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dev Ops Engineer I: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/RYCVmb5Dul https://t.co/tMewQsMYJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Service Imaging Engineer Level 3: Unit Description Headquartered in Brentwood, Tennessee, Sodexo Clinical Technology Management (CTM) is part of Sodexo Healthcare providing quality of life services in 4,300 hospitals, across 34 countries, utilizing… https://t.co/VjK6BZ5cuI https://t.co/Ib5FKuhtYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Consulting Engineer: Network Consulting Engineer RT00110013 *Fort Mead, MD* The Network Consulting Engineer is responsible for the support and delivery of Advanced Network Optimization, Security, and/or Unified Collaboration services to Tier 1… https://t.co/GRhBraqoEh https://t.co/IJB5PolBrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Architect: Cloud Security Architect  VITA64528951 *Chester, VA* This position reviews proposed changes &amp; projects associated with cloud and hosting services used by VITA and the executive branch… https://t.co/pOVjNyJvhQ 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Hx6wic6jj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Consulting Engineer: Network Consulting Engineer RT00110012 *Washington, DC* The Network Consulting Engineer is responsible for the support and delivery of Advanced Network Optimization, Security, and/or… https://t.co/HXZjiHwBMg 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/4EtEah7HdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation &amp; Technology Director of Software Engineering: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our… https://t.co/F80bR2QHGq 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/01GhcMglip]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>