<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're unhappy with a crew member's behavior, tell them straight out in private. Don't be passive aggressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: Follow the law's spirit first and its letter second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Respond to questions unambiguously and with authority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard sleeping tip: Before bed, sit in a quiet room and read from a book; a book made out of paper, that smells of ink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If a workaholic crew member pursues busywork on shore leave, insist that they stop and enjoy their free time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joeyalison: .@thorazos https://t.co/1a8w8u1FNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be willing to ask for help, even from people you dislike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take no notice of cleavage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The truth is that sometimes you just won't know the right thing to do. You still have to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Try your best to speak in a way the other person will understand, even when it seems nearly impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Always be ready to change course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: Being angry does not make you right. It also does not make you wrong. Question what you are fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: Space is big. Bigger than you think. No, bigger than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Start your log entries with the current stardate. It helps you keep track of what year it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: As soon as you find out that a person is truly toxic, get them the hell off your ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When leaving to go to the bathroom, there's no point in being specific. Just say you'll be in your "ready room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep track of the current date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't negotiate absurd schedules with engineers. Encourage truth telling and reasonable time estimates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Suppress your inner alarm. Be the calmest person in the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: No one can relax around Dr. Jekyll after they have met Mr. Hyde.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard ethics tip: Target their weapons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you want your lieutenants to become leaders, send them on away missions without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard prioritization tip: If you cannot figure out the lighting controls, call for an engineer's help before running your meeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard levity tip: Ask him, "What's this on your shirt?" Then touch his nose. https://t.co/WrIAduhPAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: Spend some time staring at the stars. It feeds the soul and revives the mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tell the crew where to go. Let them figure out how to get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard career tip: The grass may seem greener on the other side, but sometimes it's because of all the fertilizer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tell good stories. The right story can persuade, inspire, or illuminate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you succeed too much and become cocky, recognize it, admit it, and stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: No good ever comes from checking your first officer's search history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: After any stressful adventure, give yourself and your crew ample recovery time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The respect you show your crew is a major factor in determining how they feel about their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Make it so every subsystem can be found and repaired manually, even if you need to crawl to reach it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard style tip: If you don't have much on top, keep the back and sides short.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If anyone on your ship seems perfect, it means you aren't paying enough attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: Neither the sun, the moon, the stars, nor any asteroids revolve around you. You are a dust mote with ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Hire aliens. It's no big deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Pick your battles. Fight injustices before annoyances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it sound like you know what you're doing, even if you're just picking a direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard artistry tip: Lacking innate talent at a skill doesn't mean you should stop. On the contrary, it means you need to practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Polite crew members solve problems together. Rude crew members escalate problems all by themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your orders do not dictate your ideals. Your ideals determine how you interpret your orders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take your best crew members at their word, however surprising their claims may sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Avoid euphemisms. Call a thing what it really is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: You're going to meet some buffoons and scoundrels. Try to be the better person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Stirring up competition between crew members is the opposite of your job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard style tip: If you're balding, don't hide it. Own it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard cosmology tip: Six sevenths of all matter is undetectable, so stop thinking you know so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you hear yourself start to raise your voice, stop, take a breath, smile, then speak politely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know when to put on a happy face. It's part of adulthood, and essential for command.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If it feels like time is moving at the wrong speed, cancel a few meetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard anthropology tip: The very concept of a messiah is inherently authoritarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Leave the bridge sometimes. Other people can handle things fine without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard economic tip: The risks of confinement to a single planet exceed the costs of interstellar travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know when to put on a happy face. It's part of adulthood, and essential for command.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Run crisis drills when all is well. A real calamity is not a good time for training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Shakespeare tip: Our doubts are traitors and make us lose the good we oft might win by fearing to attempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If crew members have what they need to be comfortable, their work won't be all about money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard programming tip: When the holodeck malfunctions, stay in character. Don't piss off the computer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard individuality tip: Do something, anything, that no one else in your collective would ever do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard creativity tip: By all means, draw from your own experience, but also find enough empathy to draw from the experiences of others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard humor tip: Be thankful that April Fools' Day jokes fell out of common practice hundreds of years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tell your employees when they do well, even if you believe they are empathic and can read your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't waste time using social media. Pretend it was never invented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Work should be useful, stimulating, and challenging, not wasteful, tedious, nor impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: For each command, assign it to one person, or ask for a volunteer. Don't ask a crowd to take an action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you've gotten enough sleep, an impossible task becomes an interesting challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Give your crew the best technology available and you'll be amazed what they can do for your enterprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeSondow: ⚡️ “Riker Googling Time Travel” by @JoeSondow

https://t.co/7DXBiUDdDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Shakespeare tip: The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If people accuse your organization of endangering people who wear red shirts, put on a damn red shirt every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tolerate failure, not incompetence. Learn the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you stand up, straighten your shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard programming tip: The first version of any software will be buggy. That's why so many holodeck programs try to kill you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're not sure what to say, take a deep breath and a dramatic pause. Maybe somebody else will talk first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard technology tip: An advanced system isn't always easy to use. Improve the interface, or try pushing buttons at random.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you lose one crew member, mourn appropriately. If the whole ship explodes, don't worry; time travel will fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's okay not to know things. Practice saying "I don't know." Go ahead. Say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be patient with crew members' idiosyncrasies. They aren't machines. Well, most of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't assume anything is possible or impossible until you've asked the people who will be doing the work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The least you can do is to make everyone onboard feel acknowledged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Speak candidly, and encourage others to do likewise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take vacations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Try to understand more than half of the technobabble. Ask for metaphors to explain the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: A visit to a less pleasant organization can remind you how much you value your current job. https://t.co/4ssSTMCgSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Videoconference with your mortal enemies. The results may surprise you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you don't know what the hell you're doing, fake it until you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Watch over the crew. They're your responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: If your organization won't install fuses, don't touch any consoles while your ship is under attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Ensure chocolate is available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The line must be drawn somewhere. It might as well be here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: No kissing until after you've faced mortal peril together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: Antimatter is not a toy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Create an atmosphere of trust, not fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Data is easier to manage than humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It takes hard work to become a master at single-tasking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard conflict resolution tip: Only after all avenues of diplomacy and persuasion have been exhausted is violence a grudging option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Every officer needs to be in charge of something they understand, even if it's just radishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeSondow: I didn't even realize this was such a good joke setup. Read the replies. https://t.co/mIUMz5iMNE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>