<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Someone, thanks for making me smile, thanks for making me feel happy, and most of all thanks for being there when I need you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't expose your weaknesses. People are slow at understanding you, but very quick at taking advantage of the things you say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know crying won't solve anything. But I still cry, cause it makes me feel better somehow for letting those things outta my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't imagine living a happy life without you being a part of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone is strong enough to bring you down, show them that you are strong enough to get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the moment you decide to seize your goals, you deem yourself to succeed. If you do nothing, you are condemned to fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships include: fight, jealousy, arguments, faith, tears, disagreements. But REAL relationships fight through all that with love =).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like you. Why? Cause you are you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you grow bigger, you'll face bigger problems... But you must be big enough to handle all of those problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't change the past, but you can make adjustments in your present for a better future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 years old today have: Facebook, twitter, iPhones, and IPods.. When I was 8, I had a coloring book, crayons, and an imagination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you really care about someone you will make time for them. It's not hard to pick up a phone and send a text message. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to understand what love means to be able to love. You just have to feel it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have a smile on my face, but I'm just not happy inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T V W X Y Z. Did I miss something? Oh, I miss U.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life is hard, I thank God, since it makes me grow. When it seems to be no way, I find God, for He knows the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how strong a girl is, she has a weak point, and sometimes, all she needs is a tight hug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be alone rather than being with someone who makes you feel like you're alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think God doesn't hear your prayers. Your prayers aren't being ignored. He has something BETTER in store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how you look, what your weight is, or how much makeup you put on. The right guy will love you for what's inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel grateful for small things in your life, because when you put them all together you will see just how big they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to find someone perfect, you just need someone who you can make you smile, make you laugh, and you can be yourself around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we need to be apart to understand just how much we truly love each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl is in love with a boy, no one knows but her. When a boy is in love with a girl, everyone knows but her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, if you ask a girl who she likes and she says “nobody”, 1% are telling the truth, 5% are (cont) http://t.co/KAvAACLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He isn't perfect, I'm not perfect. Our feelings and lives aren't perfect, but we love each other and that's all that really matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what my future holds, but I hope you're in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy wants a good girl to be bad just for him. Every girl wants a bad boy to be good just for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he finally realizes how special I am, I'll already be with the guy who already knew from the start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny how someone can give such great advice to others, but can never follow it when it comes to themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say: "Find good people and leave bad ones". I think we should find the good in people and accept the bad in them. No one is perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may not be the brightest star, but I love you for who you are and I hope you feel the same too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too short to wake up in the morning with regrets. So, love the people who treat you right and forget about the ones who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why wish upon a star when you can pray to the one who made the star?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With you, I can forget all my problems. With you, time stands still. With you, there's no one else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you both stop kissing, look at each other, laugh, then kiss again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The couples that are meant to be, are the ones who go through everything that is meant to tear them apart, and come out even stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best feeling in the world is knowing you finally took a step in the right direction, a step towards a better future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody's perfect. I may not be the most beautiful girl in the world, but I don't pretend to be someone I'm not. I'm good at being me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go that extra mile for someone who isn't even worth the run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although time seems to fly, it never travels faster than one day at a time. Each day is a new opportunity to live your life to the fullest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith is not the belief that God will do what you want. It is the belief that God will do what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I look back loving you was not a mistake, it was a chance I was willing to take-- It made me grow as a person and for that I thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not about the mistakes we've made. It's about the lessons we've learned and the friends we've gained.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we put up walls not to keep people out, but to see who actually cares to knock them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to love someone when they least deserve it, because that is when they need your love most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I first met you, I never would have imagined that I would have such strong feelings for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iTweetFacts: Short women are more feminine than tall women b/c of high estrogen levels, causing men to biologically find them more a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 4 steps to happiness：1. You, 2. Me, 3. Our hearts, 4. Together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success never belong to someone who wait for it to come, but for those who work in patient and diligent to make the way of success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is always ready to listen anytime you are ready to talk to Him. Prayer is simply talking with God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words can explain how I feel about you, but sometimes I wonder how you feel about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want a perfect person. I just want someone I can be myself around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No camera will ever capture the look in my eyes or the feeling in my heart when I look at him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good relationships don't just happen. They take time, patience, and two people who truly want to be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before we ask God for what we WANT, we need to thank Him for what we HAVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time I'm gonna fall for someone who will make me feel that loving him is the greatest decision I ever made, not just another mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are my one in 6 billion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until you've walked a mile in someone's shoes, you can't possibly understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to give up on people. Not because you don't care but because they don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mereka yang tahu cara bersyukur adalah mereka yang bisa menikmati keindahan dunia dan arti kebahagiaan hidup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know someone means a lot to you when their mood affects yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius is one percent inspiration and ninety nine percent perspiration. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They always say time changes things, but you actually have to change them yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you don't understand me, it called 'Misunderstanding'. When I don't understand myself, it called 'Missing You'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't always change your problems, but you can always change the way you see your problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find a man who prays for a wife he can help, not for a wife who can help him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep SMILING, it increases your FACE value. Keep PRAYING, it increases your FAITH value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish I could read your mind to find out how you feel about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what I feel for you, but what I don't feel for anyone but you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A heartbreak is a blessing from God. It's just his way of letting you realize he saved you from the wrong one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to realize that he doesn't care. And you could be missing out on someone who does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words make things clear. It's pictures that say more than a thousand words, but your heart holds everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever doubt ur feelings &amp; intuition, bcoz that feeling u've never felt before is ur hearts way of telling u that he's the one for u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we lose love, we lose it for a reason. The reason may be hard, but know that God takes away when He has something better to give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 3 reasons why I love you: 1.) ..... 2.) ..... 3.) ...... I can't even find the reasons why, I just do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it weird the person who you're going to spend your whole life with is walking the earth right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when you know there's someone else besides you, even though they're not physically there with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone really loves you, they don't have to say they do, they can tell it by the way they treat you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's annoying when you know what's the best for you and you don't do it. It's not because you can't, but because you don't want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how badly people treat you, never drop down to their level, just know you're better and walk away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You speak to me in words and I look at you with feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how many friends you have, in the end you'll realize that the only person you can trust is yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all want someone we can't have, but we never notice who we truly love until we look in their eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There may be a million things to smile about, but you're definitely my favorite one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make a girl smile. Send her a cute goodnight text and a goodmorning text so she goes to sleep and wakes up with a smile on her face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is not a disney fairytale that always looks perfect but at least I could enjoy it and be happy with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the flowers or a ring I wear around my finger. There's nothing in all the world I need when I have you here beside me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why choose to be the second option to someone when you can be the ONLY ONE to another?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we just need a hug. A hug where someone wraps their arms around you so tight and assures that everything will be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are beautiful in your own way cause God makes no mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl is beautiful. You just need to find the right guy to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are trapped between your feelings &amp; what other people think is right, always go for whatever that makes you HAPPY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DESTINY... it's when both are brought to the right place, at the same time, and for a perfect reason. That's Love!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't promise to not get mad if you tell us the truth, guys. But we'll be even more mad if you tell us a lie. Honesty is the best policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fell in love with you because of the tiny things you never knew you were doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't judge a couple based on what you see, you don't know what those two people have been through together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to wake up every morning, look at my phone and see a missed call or text from that special someone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We met for a reason, either you're a blessing or a lesson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful life does not just happen, it is built daily by prayer, hard work, sacrifice, and love.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>