<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Aretha Franklin's wedding singer gig: Bill White and Bryan Eure weren't sure how Aretha Franklin would feel about performing as part of their wedding festivities. https://t.co/cMlS97NGJ5 https://t.co/mS2rI1QEdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a cop is convicted a reckless shooting: On Tuesday, a jury in Texas did what juries in the United States rarely do: convict a police officer for shooting and killing someone, in this case unarmed 15-year-old Jordan Edwards, while on duty.… https://t.co/QKLeZkxSpp https://t.co/e8O4Evsz8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Benefits –… https://t.co/dt5CiaCeRx https://t.co/udGvQMtd4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scallop Wars are no red herring: Forget territorial waters: Welcome to the Scallop Wars. https://t.co/P5PSof7va6 https://t.co/Nm71tam9VY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business One Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/QFmpZWMtcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead AEM Developer: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Lead AEM Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/kJM7CAoCT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substation Project Manager / Team Lead: Job Description Substation Project Manager / Team Lead Substation Project Manager / Team Lead (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we… https://t.co/DaFFCOzDGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How it all went wrong at JCPenney https://t.co/K8WWP8QREu https://t.co/eVCcbgE4V1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Backend Developer: Alliance Inspection Management (AiM) is the premier new and pre-owned vehicle inspection partnership in North America that combines breakthrough technology with deep industry experience to provide a trustworthy, independent bridge… https://t.co/MlB8mzgVpk https://t.co/AynP30LEXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: Job Description – Zeeland, MI, USA – Full Time If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career opportunity for you!… https://t.co/sEkjQndKFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer and Architect: Company Description Do you want to contribute ideas that will shape the future of mobility? As one of the worlds largest automotive suppliers, Bosch is driving change in the mobility sector. Join us and you can help… https://t.co/s5CZ1gaTlH https://t.co/6WEDbErGMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheriff: Uber driver stood his ground and killed man who threatened to shoot him: After a heated text message exchange with his on-again, off-again girlfriend, Jason Boek followed an Uber he thought was driving her home and swerved in front of it on a… https://t.co/gvMmx1qKv7 https://t.co/7dsEXagGGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Dawn Technologies – Home – Organization – Partners – Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use – Services – IT Strategy – Application Development – Mobile Application Development – Business Intelligence – Cloud Computing – QA Service Offerings –… https://t.co/rnA9TO1ZJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Software Engineer to join our public safety product development team. The engineer… https://t.co/BU1VDOprQm https://t.co/mJumqOCjVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMM Programmer/Quality Technician- 2nd or 3rd Shift: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No… https://t.co/5qyKt6j1Bm https://t.co/5cXCrrRXYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Analyst: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S Job Title: Sr. Systems Analyst Job Description: Job Duties: Under limited supervision,… https://t.co/kj0yuKRK1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor says Trump admin killed thousands through neglect: The Mayor of San Juan, Puerto Rico, said Wednesday that bureaucracy and inefficiency across local and federal government entities are to blame for the deaths of nearly 3,000 on the island in the… https://t.co/tt4T22ZfXE https://t.co/Sm31ugsyLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein wants Ashley Judd's suit dismissed: Harvey Weinstein's legal team has filed a motion to dismiss a lawsuit filed by actress Ashley Judd. https://t.co/v284dw4cqo https://t.co/ZSzsrfm7LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Software Engineer: Job Title Embedded Systems – Software Engineer Division Chassis and Safety Job Description Continental Engineering Services (CES) is seeking an embedded systems software engineer to design and develop electronic… https://t.co/aQQwWYh7Oz https://t.co/D8OFzXP8Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Developer: Summary:Job Description The Senior Web Developer builds quick concept prototypes, program for capabilities using client side technologies as well as frameworks, offer cross platform compatibility/support. Responsible for components… https://t.co/z09O5inupa https://t.co/4ma2eyB29i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33280 Location: Troy, Michigan Role : Java Developer Duration : 12 months Location : Troy, MI Job Description : "Java 8/9/10 certified ; J2EE: Spring Boot, Hibernate and JPA Webservices: RESTFUL API development… https://t.co/XosPh5gF1H https://t.co/ucRRE6cVzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer: Recruiter UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN Location Ann Arbor, United States Posted 01 Aug 2018 End of advertisement period 13 Aug 2018 Ref ****** Job Type Professional Services, IT Services Contract Type Permanent Hours Full Time You… https://t.co/vfyFJIhPwR https://t.co/8E7ZeTTCU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson art exhibit grapples with the singer's complicated legacy: From a bell-bottomed child prodigy performing in lockstep with his siblings to a gaunt recluse marred by scandal and addiction, Michael Jackson left behind no shortage of… https://t.co/0ogP7ozx8R https://t.co/rcqYMbGXY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GM Basic Software: Software Engineer – GM Basic Software – GPS******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/I1NEIlCF9n https://t.co/wman5yznID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test-Lead: Test Lead Populus Group seeks a Test Lead at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software quality assurance and participate in the full Software Test Life Cycle and Bug Life Cycle. Gather business requirements and… https://t.co/O5Q0tJnUfr https://t.co/dK6v0LuoXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Avlon breaks down unconstitutional redistricting: CNN's John Avlon takes a look at the states accused of unconstitutionally gerrymandering their congressional maps to favor one group or political party over another. https://t.co/O2thxt5oLD https://t.co/HsO5p6ianN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure-Solution-Architect AMANDA Lansing MI-: We are looking to hire Infrastructure Solution Architect who is proficient at the formulation of architectures, including requirements discovery and analysis, formulation of solution context, solution… https://t.co/upB6jv9zIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Dawn Technologies – Home – Organization – Partners – Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use – Services – IT Strategy – Application Development – Mobile Application Development – Business Intelligence – Cloud Computing – QA Service Offerings –… https://t.co/hqHFT0M70n https://t.co/moQcoJ7dX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie-backed Andrew Gillum scores surprise victory in Florida Democratic governor's race, CNN projects: Tallahassee Mayor Andrew Gillum will win the Democratic nomination for governor of Florida, CNN projects, scoring a major victory for the party's… https://t.co/rUxnoUf2Zt https://t.co/nogNHEhIdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android developers///Only Green Card and Citizens can apply: Jobs Toggle navigation – Failure Message – Sign In – Sign Up – Career Portal – How to Sign up to career portal? – How to login to Career Portal? How to Sign up to career portal? Once you are on… https://t.co/mEnSPLH4sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-33200 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Salesforce developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI – 7+ years of industry experience as a ************** and prior experience as a lead –… https://t.co/27biqSr0CG https://t.co/THcsB2o0kN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/4XlvqS8XMX https://t.co/cYB48186TX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Logistics Solutions: Job Description Project Manager – Logistics Solutions ABB Inc., is seeking a Project Manager – Logistics Solution to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics manufacturer to… https://t.co/ISgKQd8VvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: For Siemens Software Engineer job – Research &amp; Development – Troy, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – – Careers Home – Search Jobs –… https://t.co/tc6U2bAD69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Cook is about to get a $120 million payday https://t.co/qLLWSSBLH4 https://t.co/Qxe4vNK9ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Robotics Automation: Job Description Project Manager – Robotics Automation ABB Inc., in Auburn Hills, MI is seeking for an Project Manager to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics manufacturer to… https://t.co/AAOaHuwjWG https://t.co/LkM0uqIYpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced East Lansing, MI: For Siemens CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/I77ROPnBkB https://t.co/78cgeSAc7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Data Integration Group (TDIG) Analyst: Technical Data Integration Group (TDIG) Analyst – GPS******* in Pontiac (Global Propulsion Systems), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our… https://t.co/nIK1A1Fc12 https://t.co/rwObZ3CcQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was a trailblazer long before the Supreme Court: There is something in the current "Notorious RBG" fervor that offers the perfect paradox for a woman whose early career was marked by rejection and work in the trenches of anti-discrimination law. https://t.co/DAGF183lWG https://t.co/p3gj6cYjRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She tried to run for President, now she's in jail: Rwanda is a world leader for women in politics, but no woman has managed to become President and the last one who tried is now in jail. https://t.co/vQ247YWDx4 https://t.co/ThHWZaSQV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Implementation Specialist (Business Analyst): SAP Implementation Specialist (Business Analyst) Ref No.: 18-33377 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan +5 Years Implementation Specialist (Level 1), Business Process Analyst Manage a portfolio of customer… https://t.co/iEtcmPex57 https://t.co/H8DDjokgcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Fuel Exhaust Management: Job Title Project Manager – Fuel Exhaust Management Division Powertrain Job Description Overview: Lead FEM project activities related to the development, launch and sustaining engineering support of North American… https://t.co/uqrHR9rupX https://t.co/NgBPgifFyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She expected to die young. Then came the call that offered new life: Having spent a quarter of her life in the hospital, she knows how to sleep through noise. She's so good at it that she worried the phone call wouldn't wake her. https://t.co/rE2z0BJO1H https://t.co/BPXqy8vJNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-Mexico trade deal marks new friendship: The preliminary US-Mexico trade deal announced Monday is a positive step forward in the negotiation process and hopefully one which will bring the United States, Mexico and Canada back to the table to revise and… https://t.co/li25humZ52 https://t.co/eC4fHt3bYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Benefits –… https://t.co/wHEBebSIVa https://t.co/1D86QZlDMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans gather to view Aretha Franklin's body in Detroit: LaTonya McIntyre made sure she was first in line outside the Charles H. Wright Museum of African American History in Detroit to say goodbye to Aretha Franklin. https://t.co/2uCwn3GNpP https://t.co/m7Qd0vQ80r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procurement System Launch Analyst: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/iNGKUZ7AZv https://t.co/t8wC9LcxvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram and Tinder are rolling out features just for college kids https://t.co/AYU1sVPkPu https://t.co/CpuoNQk1Mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Backend Developer: Alliance Inspection Management (AiM) is the premier new and pre-owned vehicle inspection partnership in North America that combines breakthrough technology with deep industry experience to provide a trustworthy, independent bridge… https://t.co/I9kAVjmlTe https://t.co/g4j2eyVaZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect was interviewed in 2017: Two people are dead and nine others shot after a mass shooting at a Madden video game tournament in Jacksonville, Florida. https://t.co/1dbyHanz7W https://t.co/xl2ULheabc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: Job Description – Zeeland, MI, USA – Full Time If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career opportunity for you!… https://t.co/Yh85pyoYLj https://t.co/5Xxet74E7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI): Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development… https://t.co/IyymOJmVjW https://t.co/RrU8xvZjuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. ETL Developer: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job Duties : Under limited supervision design and maintain data warehouse applications; provide expertise during full SDLC; gather business requirements and prepare technical… https://t.co/8mQnfY9vu7 https://t.co/9WUoc1Bt29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/03TscFNX7p https://t.co/H1LmNYnFQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/oVvgNcUSWN https://t.co/pD63Yt6OU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Don't sugarcoat Jacksonville horror: There will be a temptation not to watch the graphic videos from Sunday's shooting in Jacksonville, Florida, that are playing across your TV screen and news feeds. The Madden NFL e-games tournament held at… https://t.co/UZcTu2NGz9 https://t.co/WsNOLUiy6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Analyst, SAP MM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as well as a… https://t.co/aH8TUWwb6I https://t.co/HhSOt8EIJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Technical Support Specialist Senior Service America, Inc. is recruiting for an Technical Support Specialist position in the Senior Environmental Employment (SEE) Program (55 years of age or older) at the U.S. Environmental… https://t.co/GrEvCb8JYh https://t.co/Uvcfrm3YO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NM compound family struggled off the grid: The compound was hiding in plain sight, a white smudge in the dusty green expanse of sagebrush and juniper stretching across the Colorado-New Mexico border. https://t.co/Z1J6Mw3bQC https://t.co/T8gtLeCj86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP WM Consultant: Trustek, Inc is a highly recognized provider of professional IT Consulting services in the US. We are actively seeking SAP WM Consultant for a client in Southfield, MI. This is a long term contract position. If you may not be looking… https://t.co/pvh0CNIm85 https://t.co/RoPjGs5Pqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – Engine / Transmission Controls Designs and integrates engine control software. The selected individual will work within DENSO’s Engine / Transmission Controls team. This individual will help integrate DENSO software… https://t.co/pRKaVJwSeq https://t.co/DsPjd1qKXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Advanced: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Advanced job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS –… https://t.co/y5BGblWrKl https://t.co/oteCGqFEc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Account Representative – IT Operations Management Soft…: SunIRef:Sales:title Sales Account Representative – IT Operations Management Software – Detroit, MI – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job… https://t.co/BR8M9m9V6A https://t.co/1ii4BtUjje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: A Lead Software Engineer (Operating System Software and Technical Lead) job in Pontiac, Michigan is currently available through Belcan. The Lead Software Engineer will be the technical lead for the development, verification,… https://t.co/EiFs3XPc4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Analyst: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S Job Title: Programmer/Analyst Job Description: Duties for this position will generally include… https://t.co/M6uzzCGNPe https://t.co/j30mjQOwrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Hardware Engineer: Principal Hardware Engineer HARMAN International Date: Aug 2, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Job Responsibilities: Leads the hardware development of audio head… https://t.co/mQrjM6uDsD https://t.co/9SJ7I8JvYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police identify suspect in shooting: Police provide details on who they believe to be the suspect of a fatal shooting at a Madden video game tournament in Jacksonville, Florida. https://t.co/9lPfmVe7v2 https://t.co/L3rPf09BtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33231 Location: Detroit, Michigan Position: Java Developer Location: Detroit, MI Duration: 12 Months Undergraduate Degree or Technical Certificate. – 5-7 years relevant experience. – Hands on experience in J2EE… https://t.co/x7aRBuFcmu https://t.co/IuMeYJ7QQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL's biggest names who may end up cut https://t.co/ystfVPoojL https://t.co/qmH4HJliwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer This is a mid-level position that will contribute to a team effort in all aspects of software engineering including design, development, testing, commissioning and support. Tasks * Write C# code to meet functional and… https://t.co/GqCJ0VpFSZ https://t.co/jjs8GbdwmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer and SharePoint Consultant: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Web Developer and SharePoint Consultant Key Role: Design and… https://t.co/ux1tPUIFfZ https://t.co/ZAythHfo5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Hardware Engineer: Principal Hardware Engineer HARMAN International Date: Aug 2, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Job Responsibilities: Leads the hardware development of audio head… https://t.co/5XWwZzxwYu https://t.co/nT32LjZb2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logistics Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-60139 Category Logistics/Distribution/Transportation Management Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 10-20% Position Code 9019 Position Description The Logistics Project Manager will… https://t.co/PqqZMDgzfj https://t.co/3CeII8xD4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The riveting Trump TV series https://t.co/KqRqBWlpv9 https://t.co/w6oceQxLr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job ID #******* Position Software Developer Description Summary: Job Duties: Design and develop enterprise applications on various platforms utilizing Agile and Waterfall… https://t.co/ibQZG5n5cM https://t.co/EN7GMtyy8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Hardware Engineer, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program –… https://t.co/PyJVCbhSPx https://t.co/PvCYcGVyPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Developer JavaScript: Job Description About Deque Our mission is Digital Equality. We believe everyone, regardless of their physical ability, should have equal access to everything online. Our focus is to train, equip, and help large… https://t.co/vanEQeZx46 https://t.co/7XrBJ31PEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No.… https://t.co/OXyLocdu8R https://t.co/gZeT2TgPOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution =============================== The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with… https://t.co/bG3khcLssJ https://t.co/rDdFPeN6MK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Hardware Designer: Job Offers | Rampf Group We also use Cookies. Why? Because we want to continually improve our website. You agree to the usage of cookies when you continue using this site. Find out more OK switch language RAMPF group worldwide… https://t.co/EmVdZkcbXQ https://t.co/OpJVEAd0Kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive: Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility –… https://t.co/0bk7rns8Lz https://t.co/x4Iv5PrVzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Implementation Specialist: SAP Implementation Specialist (Business Analyst) Ref No.: 18-33377 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan +5 Years Implementation Specialist (Level 1), Business Process Analyst Manage a portfolio of customer projects, ensuring a… https://t.co/HuFZQn80XE https://t.co/Z72e1m6gP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEM Developer: AEM Developer job | Cognizant job in Dearborn, Michigan, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values –… https://t.co/m0FBHUNEcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GM Basic Software: Software Engineer – GM Basic Software – GPS******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/iSoxMakUpf https://t.co/YFbudflmRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soccer star sets new scoring record https://t.co/ZQANktwnqR https://t.co/F2IKcFw3pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Logistics Solutions: Job Description Project Manager – Logistics Solutions ABB Inc., is seeking a Project Manager – Logistics Solution to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics manufacturer to… https://t.co/Tbg8wA8C2n https://t.co/jAO0Z7lkqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackbox-QA-Tester: Blackbox QA Tester Populus Group seeks a Blackbox QA Tester at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software quality assurance; provide the following types of testing: manual testing, user acceptance… https://t.co/W0zZopYcLd https://t.co/Lc39FVR0dS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonders of the universe: Wonders of the universe https://t.co/tEngHzPe16 https://t.co/UmwsXkrMpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: The product architect technically leads the development of connected navigation systems that the TomTom Custom Systems product unit develops for its business customers. The product architect is involved in both product… https://t.co/rrVhaxotHy https://t.co/piCngE5Nre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple raised $400K for homeless man, but are withholding money, attorney says: Johnny Bobbitt Jr. had a new life ahead of him. https://t.co/W1OkMUM65d https://t.co/zeovs48jjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/0a4iPiFvST https://t.co/YEYZvNyh5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Developer JavaScript: Job Description About Deque Our mission is Digital Equality. We believe everyone, regardless of their physical ability, should have equal access to everything online. Our focus is to train, equip, and help large… https://t.co/M38iZXUZlE https://t.co/3QuNETDfMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performers set for Aretha Franklin's funeral: Stevie Wonder, Jennifer Hudson, Yolanda Adams and Jennifer Holliday will be among those performing at Aretha Franklin's funeral. https://t.co/aEdCUgpbLI https://t.co/uudzInFBOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Power Generation: Job Description Senior Project Manager – Power Generation Senior Project Manager – Power Generation (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services.… https://t.co/axvbp9VUoa https://t.co/KwPPsE4BIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer The Technical Support Engineer is a critical role withing the TGW Lifetime Services (LTS) team, providing highly technical customer service and support, focusing on the TGW Software solutions. This… https://t.co/1p2ppQnPAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CES Interior Electronics – Senior Software Engineer: Job opening: CES Interior Electronics – Senior Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly… https://t.co/j20POOJszF https://t.co/Qq9sbTdYgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: SunIRef:Sales:title Sales Implementation Specialist – Detroit, MI 48202 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/ULihVTt7yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Administrator: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S Job Title: Sr. Database Administrator Job Description: Duties for this position will… https://t.co/WMgaWnUYQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Brooklyn is NYC's most exciting borough: Missy Robbins likes grappa. https://t.co/IusXYVmkbk https://t.co/OlXyvyH4CS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Dawn Technologies – Home – Organization – Partners – Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use – Services – IT Strategy – Application Development – Mobile Application Development – Business Intelligence – Cloud Computing – QA Service Offerings –… https://t.co/O1FYQ6aYPg https://t.co/Xwx8puJ1mj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>