<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/A7SGuAqgcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/Z7bM7xILyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/VZwOQqfCyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/daoieqKTHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/IsmVV2fNjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/fEAj7oNCrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/CjdaIogpwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/8R66PsGfE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop earning when you do what you love. - Asha Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/UXM1Zc2kvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/kBdLaXXfV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/W2xb2C38Zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/Qm6WIBwBcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/1DwgChI0cV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/9s0TwruEQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/fJ8gH7w33s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/lcf3apMM3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/DLgFNmVJQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/68X3BvHNhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/5FxbzyEZxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/j2rhcSGn5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/k5wHpZUWdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/3qFzQbiWqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/mWaC7FhyK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/axgIdUNVVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/8U3Sc5gcWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/nvxv7YKS8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/P4i0TfnQwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/LnrDLuu473]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/t4ZAU8ZUBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/ev4MhO2EPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/HHjwFVMBTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two-party political parties in the US consists of the appointed and the disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/q9oVajMVyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/JqyCYnHgJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/yN56j2Gvzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/XbfAf2tH4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/fEAj7oNCrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/VkHO4L89dA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/qWXfzi3prK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/xjZRGKDct2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/Ft1VlxeHtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TuVOa3PVvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/Z4R6sQxK19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/hb6UyxfsIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/7yKzEL5uxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/sU9xkl3ZR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/5w5TP8AIq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/AKfIJXXuu4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>