<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Job Locations US-WA-Vancouver Job ID 2018-5080 # of Openings 1 Qualifications Required Skillsets: * Excellent communication; both verbal and written, in English. * Developers need to be experienced (5+ years) with development of… https://t.co/06l8dAoa2R https://t.co/PcE0Odz43v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's Responsible for Your Bad Tech Habits? It's Complicated: As the conversation around tech is increasingly framed in terms of its impact on public health, the question of responsibility for our lopsided relationship with digital devices becomes more… https://t.co/9n9xVcp1ar https://t.co/uCdTyLN7Zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Analyst – US: Role Technology Analyst – US Auto req ID 29944BR Domain Manufacturing Skillset Extreme Data , Cassandra Java EE , SOA and Webservices , Spring Web Services Country USA State / Region / Province California Work Location Sunnyvale,… https://t.co/QavFL0s1U7 https://t.co/AjvcKXwj32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Admin with CI/CD: System Admin with CI/CD Ref No.: 18-32647 Location: Bellevue, Washington Strong background in Linux/Unix Administration – Strong experience with automation/configuration management tools (Jenkins or an equivalent) – Experience… https://t.co/KddawpbTXx https://t.co/SJAVZMY3Ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer: Java Application Developer Irving, TX $80-85K As an Application Developer at this Prestigious Company, you will create detailed technical specifications, develop application and system code, participate in code reviews and… https://t.co/EXQnDEiFPA https://t.co/O0Ud4UgHkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Heaven Will Be Mine' Review: In Space, No One Can Hear You Reach Out: Giant robots and melancholy pasts collide in the florid, impressionistic new visual novel. https://t.co/ljzUnXS1z0 https://t.co/gVUFULc6IW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: A^3 by Airbus LLC: Strategic Engagement Manager in San Jose, CA. Identify &amp; evaluate new partnership opportunities for A^3 &amp; A^3 aircraft &amp; aerospace projects, conduct partner outreach, &amp; facilitate partnership opportunities… https://t.co/BCWgLhqmum https://t.co/NApccXx1vF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Monitoring Isn’t a More Humane Form of Prison. Here’s Why.: Opinion: Electronic monitors violate people’s civil rights and carry unfair financial penalties. https://t.co/CVD1oeU4By https://t.co/GHuaRjetO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer – Sitecore #846918: CarMax Auto Superstores Services, Inc. in Richmond, VA seeks Sr. Software Developer – Sitecore to lead the software development team through support issues. Requires: Bachelor of Science plus 5 years experience;… https://t.co/FmixxAGHHH https://t.co/vdhVcEZi7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician #12483BR: 12483BR IT Support Technician Watkins Health Services Position Overview: The incumbent provides support services for the information technology systems at Watkins Health Services (SHS). The incumbent in this position will… https://t.co/NgWME8IRjs https://t.co/VroXOKcuH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23andMe's Pharma Deals Have Been the Plan All Along: A new partnership with GlaxoSmithKline drew intense scrutiny from customers, reflecting eroding public trust in companies' ability to protect private information. https://t.co/JWyjdZp7Lf https://t.co/9wtgNfz37j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Support Specialist: Job Details Description The IT Systems Support Specialist at C &amp; B Operations, LLC: Maintains and supports system applications, system hardware, telephony, and network infrastructure; Utilizes the Help Desk ticketing system… https://t.co/vrv0tEnL7r https://t.co/E2xkI6GXQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Digital Care, Chatbots, Elearning: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under management,… https://t.co/1P31pcccwI https://t.co/ecHZZ62atZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Principal Operations Analyst / Russian Linguist – TS/SCI – Quantico, VA: Requisition ID 2018-42008 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides military… https://t.co/q2nhOfTa1D https://t.co/ZN6GeqRnZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer / Engineer: GDIT is currently seeking a Software Developer in Keyport, WA to provide software development and maintenance in services support of the Naval Undersea Warfare Center (NUWC) Division Keyport. This position supports the… https://t.co/qw0ricMME7 https://t.co/wB4L8xAWG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Information War Is On. Are We Ready For It?: Disinformation, misinformation, and social media hoaxes have evolved into high-stakes information war. But our frameworks for dealing with them have remained the same. https://t.co/vLiSxZ0Jry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect : 18-02278 Ref No.: 18-02278 Location: McLean, Virginia Akraya is looking for a Solution Architect for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Shailly Verma at… https://t.co/sTB9Mdr5UN https://t.co/wH0xv2qvVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Network Engineer with TS/SCI clearance: Requisition ID 2018-43074 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the design and… https://t.co/7ts5NnvHmY https://t.co/wZR22JlHrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Ewan McGregor Doesn't Know If He's Coming Back to 'Star Wars': And his 'Christopher Robin' costar Hayley Atwell doesn’t know if she’s rejoining the Marvel universe, either. https://t.co/3ZI1SPkE4O https://t.co/mOL5i4gmLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior System Administrator (Combat System): Job Description – Perform system administration functions to ensure a high level of availability of the simulation systems as appropriate and required for each supported facility. – Receive, distribute,… https://t.co/dF1eAyGd5L https://t.co/RiFmv3Is9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk Wants to Put an Arcade in Your Tesla, and the Rest of the Week in Games: There's plenty to catch up on, including Valve remembering that they can actually make games. https://t.co/dkQkUruKTS https://t.co/ai6HhPIl1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Construction: Currently seeking a Construction Project Manager for great opportunity in the Appleton, WI area. The ideal candidate will possess at least 4 years experience in the commercial construction industry. Known for valuing its… https://t.co/8ZRhETpZvO https://t.co/Dv4WI7SfX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Please Note – This is an onsite Full Time opportunity. no Contracts or C2C Our client is looking for a front end iOS engineer. This role requires an understanding of Apple technologies and environments including Xcode, Objective-C, Swift… https://t.co/Yjde9kfHO1 https://t.co/MhuUnoEXPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: SUNDIAL SOFTWARE IS CURRENTLY RECRUITING FOR AN EXPERIENCED DATA PROFESSIONAL FOR A POSITION ENTITLED: BIG DATA ARCHITECT BIG DATA ARCHITECT DESCRIPTION Position Purpose: The purpose of this position is, but is not limited to,… https://t.co/NJMmgqlhLA https://t.co/YrTLa7JvEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: UI Developer Ref No.: 18-30210 Location: McLean, Virginia Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for UI Developer in McLean, VA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/Hnw9sooIrv https://t.co/hMmTlHs1EP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Description at City National Bank| Jobs and Careers at City National Bank Skip Navigation – Financial Information – Careers Home – Locations – Contact Us – News &amp; Insights – about – values – benefits – cnb stories –… https://t.co/UlwmaufAjD https://t.co/7yGBsauHsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mars and Saturn Are Ready for Their Close-ups: Mars and Saturn make their approaches to Earth, where Hubble has been waiting. https://t.co/H5RnehK4iN https://t.co/0RoSo2Z5wC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II, Product Platform: Software Engineer II, Product Platform with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox… https://t.co/kWZys0Y7wF https://t.co/kIWFVSwXGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Systems Analyst SD/LE/WM/MM: SAP Business Systems Analyst – SD/LE/WM/MM – Hillsboro, OR – Acumed Jobs Home JobsSAP Business Systems Analyst – SD/LE/WM/MM – Hillsboro, ORToggle navigation SAP Business Systems Analyst – SD/LE/WM/MM Jobs Login… https://t.co/Bgwg6nQptG https://t.co/LxuPGKpYPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: COMPANY * Preeminent reinsurance firm, very well established * Consolidated assets of $50B+ * Recognized by international industry institutions as Life Reinsurer of the Year BENEFITS AND FEATURES * Skill building: this firm encourages… https://t.co/QRpsxeA5UV https://t.co/2qmh4qg2jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Community Is Advocating for Air Quality—With Science: With the help of local scientists, the unincorporated community of Brandywine plans to collect its own air quality data to test the impacts of new power plants. https://t.co/gux1uszJ5t https://t.co/mRt6Exon5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services: ******/JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services Ref No.: 18-29613 Location: Richmond – Virginia, Virginia DEVELOPER-L3 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: JAX-RS – Java… https://t.co/AdaehWZnIh https://t.co/MV4tP9Km6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Ref No.:18-11805 Location: Brookfield, Wisconsin Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/05/2018 Sr. .Net Developer Brookfield, WI Contract Job Description: – Provide technical expertise and guidance for best… https://t.co/hRVvS0yWVn https://t.co/RIw4Ez50iW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Strange Life of a Murderer Turned Crime Blogger: Holland is home to a thriving community of journalists and bloggers who cover criminals and the drug trade. Those writers are often targeted by their subjects—and so was Martin Kok. https://t.co/ZvoqxFmo00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Software Engineer: Senior Lead Software Engineer Jobs in Oklahoma City at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services –… https://t.co/8OZ5FAAZeo https://t.co/i7YCleQVvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Systems Integrator: Location: Miami Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Instructors &amp; Trainers Jobs The Boeing Company is seeking a talented and motivated Training Systems Integrator for the Miami, Florida location. The Training… https://t.co/cjrtGrfAqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triatic – Data and Operations Center Management Job: Triatic – Data and Operations Center Management (Job Number:418479) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Perform systems engineering, requirements management, computer and network engineering and support the… https://t.co/GE4cU0O1Co https://t.co/zAfbsaQboj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reddit Got Hacked Thanks to a Woefully Insecure Two-Factor Setup: The tech community has known about the risk of using SMS in two-factor authentication for years. Reddit appears to have missed the memo. https://t.co/uOcUZyLXkI https://t.co/UoKCN2zJil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lightroom Web Developer: Job Description The Lightroom Web team is looking for an experienced web developer to work on the web portion of our connected photography solution for people who care about their photos. The right candidate for this position… https://t.co/xGww31t5dS https://t.co/WR5wwzRCn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Technician: Arkansas Valley Electric Cooperative Corporation Ozark, Arkansas-GIS Technician Arkansas Valley Electric Cooperative Corporation seeks a qualified candidate for the position of GIS Technician at the Ozark Headquarters. The successful… https://t.co/egHoACWRy2 https://t.co/ZeTcvngH2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: H &amp; R Block seeks a Senior Software Engineer in Kansas City, MO. Provide technical expertise to design and develop software components and products. Bach CS, CIS, IT, Electronic Eng+ 5 years desktop app &amp; web development exp.… https://t.co/1LoF8O0oJR https://t.co/Sc4yJepXTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Software Architect (Support Services) #40304: CEVA Logistics US Inc. seeks IT Software Architect (Support Services) to work in Jacksonville, FL to coordinate the Global Supply Chain. CoE Level 3 Support Services organization, which provides the third… https://t.co/CqZtrSAA74 https://t.co/n7ddn0Wxws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR BUSINESS ANALYST: Quest Diagnostics Inc seeks Senior Business Analyst in Lenexa, KS to liaise b/w business &amp; IT depts for all aspects of business &amp; product changes, &amp; to understand scope, solutions, constraints, &amp; risks of system changes w/i a… https://t.co/G2vSE1RZyy https://t.co/bVF0gDE62K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC Network Specialist: PC Network Specialist – Milton R. Young Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of PC Network Specialist located at our Milton R. Young Station near Center, ND. Responsible for placing safety and… https://t.co/CV2t15Fx4N https://t.co/tkUr41LD5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Engineer: COMPUTER/IT: ANSYS, Inc. seeks Senior Application Engineer to work in San Jose, CA. Leverag expert-levl engnrng knwldg &amp; relatnships to supprt regionl accounts w/ signfcnt impct on softwr revenue. Domestic travel req’d 50-60%… https://t.co/DbHMgM5Kh9 https://t.co/4NX6Bg0KKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers: Senior Software EngineersPhoton Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has multiple openings for Senior Software Engineers. Analyze the business requirements &amp; determining technical feasibility of implementing them.… https://t.co/Pb0zYsWr2p https://t.co/gnYczPWuhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying 'Pedophile' Is the Oldest Propaganda Trick in the Book: The far-right trolls accusing Tom Hanks of pedophilia aren’t original. They’re just the latest propagandists borrowing a tactic that long, long predates the internet. https://t.co/FEqyoxNkGs https://t.co/Splwj6OFH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager Client Services Iselin, New Jersey Medidata’s unified platform, pioneering analytics, and unrivaled expertise power the development of new therapies for over 1,000 pharmaceutical companies, biotech,… https://t.co/eHBTw7aAvW https://t.co/qw8G06ZxDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Environmental / Civil Engineering: AECOM is actively seeking a creative, highly talented Project Manager for Environmental and Civil Engineering projects for immediate employment in Oshkosh, WI but other locations in Wisconsin or… https://t.co/EGLfUyFfoX https://t.co/FHbDqjY8gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML: Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML Description at Microfocus Skip Navigation Work with us, doing what you do best. Search Jobs Keyword Search Location Search… https://t.co/DBajUiH8b0 https://t.co/2fTF0yYkZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio Programmer: ZeniMax Careers – Audio Programmer – id Software ZeniMax Jobs – ZENIMAX MEDIA – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS ROCKVILLE, MARYLAND – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS MONTREAL, CANADA – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS AUSTIN, TEXAS – ID SOFTWARE DALLAS, TEXAS – ID… https://t.co/15uDZmhMKy https://t.co/KMQJ53jWMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real-Time Software Engineer: U.S. Citizenship status is required as this position will need a U.S. Security Clearance within 1 year of start date. Employer BBN Technologies is seeking an Embedded Software Engineer in our Newport, RI office to develop… https://t.co/axlqFWBh0k https://t.co/BorzNYbGyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bioengineers Are Closer Than Ever To Lab-Grown Lungs: The first research team to bioengineer human lungs in a lab have now performed multiple successful transplants in pigs. https://t.co/KJWj4tJkRp https://t.co/ggxlKLUE00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Polar Bear Frolics on Sea Ice, and 13 Other Gorgeous Drone Photos: Florian Ledoux was named this year's Drone Photographer of the Year for his winning wildlife photo captured in Nunavut, Canada. https://t.co/gycNxkvXu1 https://t.co/2mYXg15msn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mila Kunis and Justin Theroux on the Proper Way to Play *Halo*: It involves a lot of monitors. https://t.co/2jzqogp3EQ https://t.co/HqXzDTSIk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fin7: The Inner Workings of a Billion-Dollar Hacking Group: The Justice Department announced the arrest of three members of notorious cybercrime group Fin7—and detailed some of their methods in the process. https://t.co/84xFr7BGRu https://t.co/5WpzVtxrAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Huntsville, AL Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Software Developer, Junior Key Role: Research, design,… https://t.co/86GOABLvzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Developer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the most… https://t.co/Ij8TDbhcWB https://t.co/oLGrFKIn6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager, Amazon Renewed: Job Description Senior Program Manager, Amazon Renewed Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Services, LLC Position Category: Project/Program/Product Management–Non-tech Job Description Amazon… https://t.co/qsntefW04Q https://t.co/BUsPTlD2UV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Waymo Self-Driving Cars Help Fix Phoenix's Public Transit?: The Silicon Valley self-driving company just announced a partnership with Phoenix’s Valley Metro, which prompts the age-old question: Can a private tech company provide solutions for the… https://t.co/3pSgeBgDHd https://t.co/9twQlbmarb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: ELP Aviation has an opening for Software Engineer in Conway Springs, KS to design software systems that utilizes complex logic to filter thru large SQL &amp; Pervasive databases. Write designed, testable, efficient code, produce test… https://t.co/umvwQ7o37i https://t.co/htLayIkCUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: IT/SOFTWARE Software Engineer for e-commerce platform – Oakland, CA. Software Engineer. Apply to Attn: HR at https://t.co/TJCrz2TJGT, Inc. at 125 Moen Street Cranford, NJ 07016, Ref. Job Code: BS0606recblid b2kuv5oz51v37u50h3vkvwj7gqzy6f https://t.co/QiCJbHO4MI https://t.co/e0BJUX2wfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It: IT POSITION Multiple positions available in Sunnyvale, CA. https://t.co/6O0PNFgac8 Services, Inc., A100 US LLC, and Amazon Web Services, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Software Development Engineer I, Job Code AZ0202: Design,… https://t.co/2cfbJkrHFi https://t.co/FqfOdykMpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise of the Computer-Generated Celebrity: A new breed of digital star is stealing the limelight. https://t.co/rv1aDa8fqs https://t.co/1ut1P1cetw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, QA Engineer – Selenium: Lead, QA Engineer – Selenium in Phoenix, Arizona, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – –… https://t.co/hTE0LZVJgs https://t.co/L4YmK0BKw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BurnBox Makes Hidden Files Look Like You've Deleted Them: Cryptographers have developed a new technology designed to protect your secrets at the border. https://t.co/b6pGQebzEA https://t.co/jywlS4X2Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Ref No.: 18-31342 Location: Englewood, Colorado Role: Solution Architect Location: Englewood – Colorado Type: Contract Job Description Key skills required for the job are: Java – Architecting (Mandatory)As an… https://t.co/gpespjMkk2 https://t.co/hF5er9toBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager PES Product Testing: ******/Project Manager PES Product Testing Ref No.: 18-32316 Location: Redmond – Washington, Washington PROJECT MANAGER-L2 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Project Manager with 5+ Years of experience with… https://t.co/2JSSbgz8EY https://t.co/gnsLJEUC8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Dev Ops Engineer – V3Main ************** – Home – About – Mission, Vision, &amp; Values – Leadership – Government &gt; – DIR Contracts – Cybersecurity – News – Services – IT Managed Services – Agile Software Development – Custom Software… https://t.co/01rANmNoUX https://t.co/u5Harf6IgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Technology Shapes the Way We Read: WIRED set out to examine how technology is shifting our relationships with books. Here's what we found out. https://t.co/iTh9Asa523 https://t.co/g26ux22VSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Sr.: Samsung Research America, Inc. has the following job opportunities in in Mountain View, CA: Software, Sr. Manager 5 (Req #8GJ0316) Define the processes needed to achieve operational excellence in all areas, including project… https://t.co/TWXYBsbVao https://t.co/dqgKguzavu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Statistician: H &amp; R Block seeks a Senior Statistician – Pricing in Kansas City, MO. Build and maintain predictive models. MasterStats, Math, Econ, MIS+ 2 years stat. exp. For complete details and to apply, please go to: https://t.co/7GY9mzm4mI and… https://t.co/zoeOnCfuun https://t.co/ufs5Gng3Kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROGRAMMER ANALYSTS: IT professionals in Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: PROGRAMMER ANALYSTS: Create, modify, test the code, design &amp; develop technology solutions. Assist software developers in correcting errors,… https://t.co/COux2sfiyI https://t.co/HCZIG4g3r2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Weekend, Here’s DJ Khaled on a Lyft E-Scooter: The first look at the ride-hail company’s newest line of business, courtesy of the ‘gram. https://t.co/FEfEUyyp5H https://t.co/5DBB1NK13k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Technical Support Product Specialist: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/MMeUsFLTlO https://t.co/b2WSkiLlC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer: Sr. Specialist Developer Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for data, workflow, logical… https://t.co/tPnmu55BXA https://t.co/lyV4HMPj0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst Lead: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Business Operations Analyst Lead for our San Antonio, TX facility. Leveraging data and analytics (requires developing high proficiency in contact center data environment),… https://t.co/HgLnEaVVsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Boston, MA Full-time $120k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Full-Stack Developer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – MongoDB – Node.js – GIT –… https://t.co/P97d20B4Qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airstream's $40,000 Basecamp Gets an Off-Road Upgrade: The new "X-Package" gives the little trailer a 3-inch lift kit that increases ground clearance, plus all-terrain tires from Goodyear. https://t.co/yC24ZWowBv https://t.co/Laubz0cBhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Business Analyst: Position ResponsibilitiesRequirements: Employer has built a specific case management system for dispute management called Employer Chargeback ("CBK"). CBK is designed for processing of disputed transactions in the… https://t.co/P8WeYKbt4L https://t.co/dT0rLVpTsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Germany Can't Quit Coal, Can Anyone Else?: Germany's last black-coal mine will close next month. But that doesn't mean the country has weaned itself off the emissions-spewing stuff. https://t.co/sLEfoon6u8 https://t.co/7K7qFjZfzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC Network Specialist: PC Network Specialist – Milton R. Young Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of PC Network Specialist located at our Milton R. Young Station near Center, ND. Responsible for placing safety and… https://t.co/6OAjbSoLaU https://t.co/nsHAl21SbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/W Dvlprs: SOFTWARE DVLPRS HGST, Inc. has opptys in Newark, CA for Staff Dvlprs. Mail resume to Attn: HR, 951 SanDisk Dr, MS:HRGM, Milpitas, CA 95035; Ref #NEWVPA. Must be legally auth to work in the U.S. w/o spnsrshp. EOErecblid… https://t.co/zcMHu6sdXf https://t.co/cDXZ3E3u4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Net Application Developer: Multiple Openings InnoCore Solutions, Inc. Irving, TX InnoCore Solutions, Inc. has multiple openings for the following positions to work in Irving, TX and/or various client sites throughout the U.S. Must be willing to… https://t.co/q49qcGCFwm https://t.co/FhZGmA7bqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partner Marketing Manager: MARKETING Partner Marketing Mgr (PMM-SW) Influence partner-driven/co-mtkg initiatives from value proposition dvlmt &amp; segmentation to channel, messaging &amp; creative strategy. BS+2 yrs exp. Send resume to Helix Employment, Attn:… https://t.co/llcNXqJ5eu https://t.co/1m05i1vgPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying Cars, the Real E-Scooter Riders, and More in the Future of Cars: Flying cars sound fun! But flying car regulations do not. The baby Airstream is so tiny and adorable! But that baby Airstream's price tag is not. Plus: more ups and downs in the… https://t.co/ZpNK1bAsfL https://t.co/21rui8z1Wn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile developer with AngularJS Exp: Mobile developer with AngularJS Exp Ref No.: 18-28275 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position: Mobile developer with AngularJS Exp. Location: Washington, DC – Candidate should have 8+ years of Total IT… https://t.co/QD11t4jmyb https://t.co/D2jygP4HWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Land Representative – Project Manager: Maintain close communications with the Land Manager and Client Representative. Reports Land progress, problems and possible resolution to pertinent issues impeding project completion Identifies negative trends,… https://t.co/yb7qmzLKE8 https://t.co/vPHa6WgS6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Project Manager – IPTL: 114060BR Senior Principal Project Manager – IPTL CA – El Segundo 114060BR This position is for a Senior Principal Electrical Engineer with experience in Technical lead and Project management of RF sub-systems.… https://t.co/nFB9mvIlxH https://t.co/QMfEsfh2b3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I’m Deleting All My Old Tweets: If you want to delete yours too, here's how. https://t.co/IwUPKkL1ev https://t.co/AgiBqDmKZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active Directory Specialist: Active Directory Specialist Location: Arlington, VA Job Code: 3565 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and… https://t.co/8jD9ykPm5l https://t.co/E3fkrDUopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Jobs in Huntsville at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services – Innovation – Our History –… https://t.co/l7OZlDhOBX https://t.co/pzpG50OMIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Podcasters of 'The Good Place’ Are Smart Motherforkers: And their show is part of NBC's ever-evolving experiment with digital engagement. https://t.co/HCuQ7Dy9fS https://t.co/lheUTooJzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: – Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: June 30, 2018 – Position Title:Senior Project Manager – Company Name:Chubb About Chubb For more than 125 years, the Chubb Group of Insurance… https://t.co/6TG1iZqeDi https://t.co/IUZNghv95X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Senior Business Analyst at Fiserv, Inc. Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield –… https://t.co/pkyjUCEGJP https://t.co/0nWxS1rXsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Requirements This project manager will be responsible for managing the Marketing activities / milestones associated with the Adobe Campaign Manager and Attribution Model initiatives. These are cross-LOB efforts with several… https://t.co/DgxT3KIeto https://t.co/98PmLazSxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Hackers, a Bluetooth Flaw, and More Security News This Week: A Google security key, Russian hackers, and more of the week's top security news. https://t.co/vLweX0dUgx https://t.co/yMhnKLuviJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff DevOps Engineer: What you’ll be doing. Verizon is hiring a Staff DevOps Engineer that will be responsible for deploying and maintaining PB scale big data applications for Verizon. Role will be responsible for operationalizing cutting edge big data… https://t.co/ATts6cUgK0 https://t.co/UVUJVV4USp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager Fire Services: **Associate Project Manager – Fire Services** Locations:Pelham, Alabama Job Family: Project Management New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building Technologies **Business Unit:** Field… https://t.co/otVDavM2OS https://t.co/042f35Vxzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect Manager: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Lead team of Solutions Architects to drive excellence in solutions development, solutions selling, and opportunity closure through strategic engagement with assigned customer base… https://t.co/7QDWkFa7Ir https://t.co/wQap6tl3CG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>