<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian and Stacie’s conversation is flowing. #FirstDates https://t.co/3YbNUuvXlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule one on a first date - don’t talk about your fucking ex.  #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This the most beautifully awkward introduction ever...... 5 months down the line they’ll be using gimp masks and latex #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessDunne91 It’s on BBC2 HD not BBC2 NI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah I think I’ll just stick to the pack of spoons from Dealz for €1.50 rather than than two for €35000 #latelate #latelateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity he didn’t give @BionicWoman_IE quarter of the time he gave Russell and his band. I’d listen to her all night #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve a feeling Russell’s band won’t be headlining Glastonbury anytime soon. #latelate #latelateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy to Russell Crowe tonight a rugby jersey and teabags, he’ll be shining his shoes next #latelateshow #LateLate https://t.co/XWTsXPtZTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patricia Callan won't hear any of the anti-drink sentiment. She also loves the Guinness ad #CBLive https://t.co/Ngt52kcE8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duffycj Of course he doesn't, he might catch something off the working class people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[€120 million subsidies for private schools while kids in 'disadvantaged' schools are still doing lessons in porta cabins.  #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Bruton says 'my own area in Darndale' stop will ya the only time you go near the place is when you're looking for a vote #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was in school the teachers didn't give a fiddlers about the students they gave no encouragement at all #theclassroomdivide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never knew Joe Duffy was a working class lad from Ballyfermot he's never mentioned it before #theclassroomdivide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Tubridy running to the airport to get Ibrahim Halawa on the #latelate this Friday https://t.co/NlNtENDv4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ouralteredlife: Someone is reporting my son's face &amp; #Instagram agree saying it doesn't meet their guidelines before removing it. RT to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sporcle hey, I love your site I play everyday but the last few days I can't play an ad keeps coming up and redirecting away from the site]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't be surprised if Miriam O'Callaghan was to put on an  Orange sash and start shouting NO SURRENDER! ULSTER IS BRITISH!  #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should send all Mr O’Neill’s tenants down to his mansion in Kilkenny see how he likes living in a kip then #rteinvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin City Council are as much a disgrace as the landlords. They couldn’t care less it’s just causing them hassle it seems #rteinvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do ya know what will be done about this Absolutely nothing a bit of lip service tomorrow and then it’ll be forgotten about #rteinvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Shatter is like that guy in the office don’t really like him in work but get a few pints in and he’s great craic #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Gloria Hunniford is having her own little chat show on #CuttingEdge it’s called ‘your most painful memories with Gloria’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t mind Alan Shatter, yes I just said that #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was too young to remember MTUSA but that was a great doc about a revolutionary guy most people my age have never heard of. #fabvinny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They shouldn’t have said that ‘you won’t like her when she’s angry’ #SalonConfidential https://t.co/gdxWk8v7D8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t buy her a bag of chips never mind a handbag #SalonConfidential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy after the young lad gets bored bullying him on the court #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/qgpHvteN09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharon Ní Bheoláin at home watching this interview #latelate #LateLateShow https://t.co/QtYUZJXfy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s making this sound like indecent proposal #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Declan O’Rourke, Mumford &amp; Sons more disheveled Irish cousin #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate: pint? 
Me: nah I’m staying in to tweet about the #LateLateShow
Mate: what? 
Me: it’s my thing now 
Mate: ⬇️ #latelate https://t.co/74fbZl9s0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve got my own website jayo.ie good man Jayo getting that in before the interview ends  #latelate #LateLateShow https://t.co/2GqaX32h1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like Jason Sherlock he seems like a sound auld skin #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Consuela, do you like Tubridy? #latelate #LateLateShow https://t.co/xWYM7fJ5PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladbible Did he trip over his jeans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never had this carry on when it was the Coca-Cola Cup.  #CarabaoCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not Paddy Power’s fault there’s gambling addicts the same way it’s not Jack Daniels fault there’s alcoholics.  #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@X_Burnside_X I’d love to, it’s a cracker in fairness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always liked Fr Brian Darcy always comes across as a genuine sound chap who is full of compassion and love. 
#CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m putting this out here I love Steph she looks like serious craic even though she thinks her kids are Farrell children #salonconfidential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPads and iPhones are like heroin to kids after a while it’s nonstop badgering until you hand it over #salonconfidential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAKATVIRELAND You should I’m still watching and tweeting about it, it’s what you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RTÉ trying to be cool with a stoner getting his haircut #salonconfidential https://t.co/YXMJkhq2tV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could moan about  #salonconfidential but I can’t turn it off, it’s horrible tv but it’s addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next week on Channel 4 the Black &amp; White minstrels make a return to our screens  #MyWeekAsAMuslim #myweekas https://t.co/ydnxKtpl00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The biggest thing for me I’d miss is alcohol’ you’re pretending to be Muslim for a week not converting.  #myweekasamuslim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 of the 11 players in the FIFA team are aged 29 or over, are older players better or is it lack of talent coming through #TheBest #FIFABest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjanemurf @philipnolan1 I very rarely frequent old man pubs now I’ve heard enough of the phrase ‘you don’t know you’re born young man’ to last a lifetime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s a Michael Harding in every old man pub in the country #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harding is type of man when you’re in an old man pub having a pint and he starts talking to ya but doesn’t shut up  #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said ‘I take my hat off to you’ but he didn’t take his hat off, pure liar #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the old dears in the morning when they can’t figure out how to print their recipe for beef stroganoff #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/MPGtokJ7j2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pete Conway looks like he runs the ‘Mans Shop’ in the town you live in #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a Meath accent she was trying to do there btw #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s like an 80s tribute act on the  #latelate you have 
Tom Petty
Jason Donovan 
Pete Burns and 
Holly Johnson on the couch #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus this is absolute waffle it’s the type of waffle you overhear a bunch of girlos talking about on a night out #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/DtrUiKRMBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing Tubridy stayed indoors during #Ophelia there’s a good chance he’d have blown up to Siberia #LateLateShow  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dodo: Can you spot the lost dog in the mural? For every retweet @Whistlelabs will donate $1 to Family Dog Rescue. Help them reach their…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Journal.ie commenters welcoming Ibrahim Halawa home at Dublin Airport https://t.co/UckvzZTm5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuillemBalague Stop trying to be a troll and stick to what you’re good at, being a fraud. That’s what you’re good at wrongly predicting football matters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha they changed it from ‘Malahide Socialite’ to ‘Malahide Single’ it’ll soon be Malahide Cat Lady #salonconfidential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The face I’d make if my barber started asking me these questions while getting my haircut #salonconfidential https://t.co/Nz8lLgMb1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s a Malahide socialite? It’s basically a person who drinks shitloads of wine in pubs in Malahide #salonconfidential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ophelia like every woman in my life came storming in blew real hard and fucked off the same day and I’m left wondering what just happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tree aged over 100 years in the Grand Canal in Naas #Ophelia https://t.co/3Fj8EW4ISC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers all over the country right now #Ophelia https://t.co/Fc341HCiXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand day for it in Naas #Ophelia https://t.co/g33QlXumt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Irish lads hair going out for a walk today #Opheila https://t.co/mftpMM7wyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a good thing Mickey D Higgins is in Australia we wouldn’t want him being blown away on us #Ophelia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maorty496 You stay safe as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maorty496 No need to apologise, you have a very pleasant evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maorty496 Ok cheers, thanks for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ulster says NO to #Ophelia https://t.co/YASWiZTGbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MetEireann: SEVERE WEATHER WARNING LEVEL RED FOR IRELAND.https://t.co/9BeK3UcAwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know the weather is gonna be shite when this lad gets rolled out #Ophelia https://t.co/vCZqGNEe1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane in USA: people boarding up houses and moving out of town
Hurricane in Ireland Jaysus I better take the wheelie bin in #Ophelia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terry is prone to talk a lot of shite #TheLateLate #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lady from Cork after been told she’s getting a wedding dress for free #TheLateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/BDEumnDNKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franc could do with a few tips himself on how to buy a decent suit #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan to priest ‘you’re a bigger man than I’ll ever be’ fuck sake Ryan kick a man while he’s down.  #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Eddie is a low rent Louis Walsh and that’s saying something #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say what you want about the Karaoke it’s shite but not as shite as Nathan Carter #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenanneMalone My Ma loves him it must be a generational thing, I don’t get him at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nathan Carter obviously has very naughty pictures of someone in RTÉ it’s my only explanation of why he’s always on #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendan O’Carroll’s comedy is very 1990s he should have left it there #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SomeMightSayNI My heart raced when she said she wants to move to Dublin, my heart stopped when she said lower down Ireland but yeah she’s pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuddlemahumph Aye, I’ll be waiting in Connolly station when she gets off the train and I’ll show her around the country including left &amp; right Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love living in lower down Ireland it’s a lot better than further up Ireland #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a joke Northern Ireland is still tribalistic that people still use flags to mark out their territory Shameful really #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you’re chatting shit about somebody and they walk in mid rant #NolanLIVE https://t.co/D9pU1dXFvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was this guy who invaded the stage  #NolanLIVE https://t.co/TVxpY3BWrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniels extension is gonna be as square as he is since Dermot Bannon got his hands on it #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These 4 kids are already better than I’ll ever be, fair play to them so selfless #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Barry sitting in the Greenroom while everybody walks off bored to tears with his tricks #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/A5ieYqRvs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*trick obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Toy Show will be over by the time this truck finishes #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There seems to be more plants in the audience than in a Vietnamese grow house in Offaly #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frances Fitzgerald getting the dreaded vote of confidence from the Taoiseach, he’s hardly gonna say he’s seeking her resignation on live tv. #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tv presenter who deals in politics doesn’t read never reads that says it all about Stephen Nolan #NolanLIVE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>