<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer / Developer: Automation Engineer / Developer Location: Wayne, PA J.G. Wentworth Home Lending is seeking a motivated, energetic Automation Engineer / Developer for our Wayne, PA location. We are looking for a team player with strong… https://t.co/S5hmrbcJNX https://t.co/MiV6TueNFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for an 8-12- month contract in Tempe, AZ focusing on the implementation of MS Project Online PPM tool. The client is open to either long-term contract… https://t.co/PJczXg1Hyb https://t.co/k05s2xYYpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: JOB DESCRIPTION Leidos is seeking several Software Developers for a growing mission critical program.  The Software Engineer will provide technical expertise in software engineering, have troubleshooting abilities within… https://t.co/EboMuLIPrz https://t.co/RWko8D0n62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 2: At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our work preserves freedom and… https://t.co/sJ6PYVjNWi https://t.co/eRft2HIHjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – FE NXT: About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people to advance the social… https://t.co/qjmUGcTXak https://t.co/wK4GubjkGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET WPF Developer: Triage Consulting Group is one of the nation’s leading hospital revenue review consultancies, with offices in San Francisco and Atlanta. Triage is one of Modern Healthcare’s “Best Places to Work in Healthcare” in 2016, a “Best Small &amp;… https://t.co/M3VREJPmjJ https://t.co/wNnHTthJph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Lead development of excellent solutions to company strategic and operational requirements. Understand core business functions at a deep level. Work with stakeholders to select and configure IT Business systems. Design,… https://t.co/nGlxjK07aE https://t.co/XO8l4c2Ixv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Description The Information Technology Sr. Project Manager is responsible for either a portfolio of complex / critical projects or planning and managing a large project through the entire life cycle, ensuring delivery to time, cost and… https://t.co/HyPTRLC2Jz https://t.co/dOSMFdosps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Master: McLean 1 (19050), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a… https://t.co/unCr4KAj2V https://t.co/OdEs0h5vi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 421404BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : This position is for a software engineer to support the Advanced Programs projects. The candidate will work in an agile scrum development environment to… https://t.co/mCuK2ySDXu https://t.co/1Odm0wK5SK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Java Application Programmer Job: Junior Java Application Programmer Job Solutions &amp; Services Markets About CONTACT CAREERS Search by Keyword this Job Email similar jobs to me Please enable JavaScript to subscribe. – – Join with LinkedIn – Join Now… https://t.co/cQtNIjt0VT https://t.co/3mVwZoJ0Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Level 1: The software engineer is responsible for developing all the code in the enterprise. Applications are written in a variety of languages including Angular/TypeScript/JavaScript/C#/Python/Java, as well as mobile iOS/Android and… https://t.co/FrGr4X42f3 https://t.co/nkUI1Yynsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master:   Job Description – Scrum Master (18006569) Scrum Master Requisition ID : 18006569 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance may be available… https://t.co/hKDlMhoIt0 https://t.co/QAyvXtnEei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/g1ROGXkMUu https://t.co/kPUwDJnH0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Applications Architect: Anonyome Labs was created to give people control and freedom over their personal and private information. We believe that people should be able to determine how, what, and with whom they share their personal details. We are… https://t.co/rjx2oRmf7O https://t.co/Z48UQ0g6IN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer: About Us Republic Services is an industry leader in U.S. recycling and non-hazardous solid waste. Through our subsidiaries, Republics collection companies, recycling centers, transfer stations, and landfills focus on providing… https://t.co/zY43pHe3eK https://t.co/5DLmkSxOO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? Every industry has to come to grips with the ramifications of being in an increasingly connected world. From cars, to heavy vehicles, to fleets, to industrial equipment, today’s vehicles increasingly run on… https://t.co/f4yATlnIJf https://t.co/1y3kWu77ZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: The scrum master is responsible for executing the SAFe scrum process for an agile team of ~9 people. The scrum master must facilitate the daily scrum, participate in sprint planning with the Product Owner, and contribute to the sprint demo… https://t.co/ctLVUyPZ1M https://t.co/okAdrKkRJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: CONTRACT SCRUM MASTER MUST BE LOCAL TO ISELIN NJ AND AVAILABLE TO INTERVIEW IN PERSON IMMEDIATELY. Our client is searching for a Scrum Master with Agile Development experience Must have Scrum certification and heavy Agile Development… https://t.co/6Y254oFKhW https://t.co/VGzcYeXVDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Associate, Scrum Master: Job Description Job ID: R44093 McLean 1 (19050), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/ApjIMvEWP5 https://t.co/Cv6DyWn6zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KjYs2joyNt Developer:  Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/i1xcNH5NaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Front End): Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/SEtxDdH3Be https://t.co/2MuMBH7oGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We currently have an opening for an IT Project Manager in our PRS IT team. The IT Project Manager will have responsibility for the management and coordination of multiple concurrent projects within the PRS Product portfolio. IT projects… https://t.co/4txqvIYg8V https://t.co/v3EnMQy6Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: O3 World is seeking a DevOps Engineer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************************************************** You will… https://t.co/HEF7uUxxxg https://t.co/vD6sKntZrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Game Artist: Funkitron is the creator and developer of the top grossing Cascade game published by Big Fish Games. We are looking for talented and experienced Mobile Game Artists with experience working in Unity3d for an upcoming project. Looking… https://t.co/yAZgTiYfef https://t.co/32VYvdxspa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South Pacific Jobs – Latin America &amp;… https://t.co/NPHMiFNYKv https://t.co/ZIjh0fkEs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip, trendsetting company looking for… https://t.co/09N39e2AI5 https://t.co/vxDTDcEOv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Design Engineer: UX Design Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design, Optimize, and add features to an existing HTML/JavaScript user interface Debug and fix all issues related to new features added Demonstrate progress to the… https://t.co/8cHdGfZ7kn https://t.co/FN04tnJOHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager (Agile/Scrum): Job TitleSr. Project Manager (Agile/Scrum) – ID:31354 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFinance/Banking experience , Agile Scrum Mgmt LocationPlano, TX Date Posted03/29/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS… https://t.co/O9ohEQqnAi https://t.co/Zdl1dllZK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: 7900 Westpark Drive (12131), United States of America, Tysons, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One… https://t.co/z6JTxPHU2Z https://t.co/CVLwD7VBCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Scrum Master: Project Manager – Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-00727 Location: Costa Mesa, California Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 04/06/2018 Required Experience 4-5 years Scrum Master 8-10 years of Project Management… https://t.co/Kb82J38Tsk https://t.co/Wb2WU0TaQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Experienced Software PM): Since 2006, WMC Global has worked with digital services providers around the world to deliver insight into digital threats targeting consumers. By monitoring channels for threat delivery, analyzing relevant… https://t.co/XMqUUtAknK https://t.co/eJOzCaJMB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/iAAgDoRTwy https://t.co/DtrXIbbBh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer Manager: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/XOAGgWeOdH https://t.co/6LqoT6v2Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Careers that Change Lives Impact patient outcomes. Come for a job, stay for a career. Medtronic Cardiac Rhythm and Heart Failure (CRHF) R&amp;D teams develop the medical technologies that save lives and… https://t.co/XAI15je3Uu https://t.co/t9Y9yGM9FO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for a 8-12- month contract in Rosemont, Illinois. The individual should have at least ten years of Project Management experience, managing multiple… https://t.co/OhbeUzxQVQ https://t.co/KGgB5FjPS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/DGLmhNoHcc https://t.co/kTYcGSWKpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/9jliqh1l5q https://t.co/bp482t4gBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Senior Technical PM with Strong Mobile application and API Contract: 6+ Months Location: Chicago, IL Qualifying area : Strong mobile application and API/Integration. Responsibilities: * Standard PMP project management… https://t.co/R51rsoumty https://t.co/FdGTQb2nl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job ID  2018-16687 Primary Location  New Jersey, Jersey City Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  .. Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this job The Scrum Master is a servant leader, helping the rest… https://t.co/2DNZatkzmT https://t.co/Hog4s1mzMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Position Summary: The Scrum Master is responsible for the planning and execution of company strategy. The Scrum Master will also be responsible for reporting and team visibility as well as ensuring the teams desired outcomes are met. Job… https://t.co/mlbWW0AaZL https://t.co/2eillqDyw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google in talks to buy Nokia's airplane broadband business: Bloomberg: (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's Google is in talks to buy Nokia Oyj's airplane broadband business, Bloomberg reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter. https://t.co/tXfs2NldTy https://t.co/942BQy3FKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Senior Project Manager: An employee-owned company with more than $4 billion in sales, Scoular employs more 1,000 people in over 100 offices and facilities in North and South America, and Asia. For 125 years, feed and food customers have been counting… https://t.co/LSHGNmkF6i https://t.co/VDLM9P6tUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Level 1: The software engineer is responsible for developing all the code in the enterprise. Applications are written in a variety of languages including Angular/TypeScript/JavaScript/C#/Python/Java, as well as mobile iOS/Android and… https://t.co/1eUXbqKyZM https://t.co/f6MrGfxfSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Looking for an experienced Agile Coach to join our team supporting SSA in Woodlawn, MD MUST be US Citizen or green card holder Key Required Skills: Agile Coaching, Training, Agile Implementation experience using Scrum, Kanban, Lean, etc.,… https://t.co/nH4W7OuHHf https://t.co/uccSHKI1ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: O3 World is seeking a Full Stack Developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************** You will work with some of the… https://t.co/iDzrPZhk1h https://t.co/wAwyb5Jz18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 4 / SCRUM Master:   Job Description – Engineer Software 4 / SCRUM Master (18006569) Engineer Software 4 / SCRUM Master Requisition ID : 18006569 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes… https://t.co/yOujP8cX1z https://t.co/SxFaEqlK3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: O3 World is seeking a DevOps Engineer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************************************************** You will… https://t.co/s85jeDU7y7 https://t.co/uS1Qr6eZcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Ant ups fundraising target, valuation could hit $150 billion: sources: HONG KONG/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - China's Ant Financial Services Group is in talks with investors to boost its fundraising target to at least $8 billion, which could see its… https://t.co/DuVKpqA9fb https://t.co/31XkqPCn4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix): 109879BR Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix) MA – Woburn Job Description: An opportunity exists for a Senior Software Engineer I within the Missile Defense Radar Software Department in Woburn,… https://t.co/fFCqVj9pVu https://t.co/M8dGdD63lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite JavaScript Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for JavaScript Developers to join one of our projects in Allen Park or downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location… https://t.co/RAHtLmvk3p https://t.co/JRcS82Ctvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager (Scrum Master): Project manager (Scrum Master) Ref No.: 18-00610 Location: Mount laurel, New Jersey Start Date / End Date: 04/01/2018 to 04/01/2019 Technical/Functional Skills – Knowledge of agile methodology and frameworks like Scrum,… https://t.co/HREVgQCVEf https://t.co/hH5dkm331i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/D3n5XTejtM https://t.co/mBfeEoWOW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst (Portland, Oregon): ZappiStore are looking for an Application Support Analyst to join our team in Portland, Oregon to provide a high level of service for our clients. You’ll have a keen interest in solving complex problems, an… https://t.co/fDOfzp83Cu https://t.co/If0V9PJyA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate plans future hearing on Cambridge Analytica, other firms: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee plans to hold a future hearing on Cambridge Analytica and other companies that may have improperly obtained Facebook Inc user data,… https://t.co/695JhCtXFh https://t.co/muWavdXLZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: MuleSoft sits at the heart of all convergent technologies trends (SaaS, big data, APIs, microservices, etc.), and our developers are tackling some of the most challenging problems in technology today. As a Software Engineer at… https://t.co/aOFucppRJv https://t.co/e6UljAzfCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Front End): Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/HGlPR2amZ0 https://t.co/cWPzWHRDYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR800) Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR800) (Job Number:435230) Description: Job Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/k9B5H84vQn https://t.co/zWiGiJJbco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job ID  2018-16687 Primary Location  New Jersey, Jersey City Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  .. Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this job The Scrum Master is a servant leader, helping the rest… https://t.co/fPaG7vgobF https://t.co/4HgcvSRHlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Corporate – St. Louis, MO: Role Overview: We are seeking an Angular developer with a C# .NET background to join our team in St. Louis, MO. You will have the opportunity to utilize a wide range of new development technologies while… https://t.co/GucdK8XyzK https://t.co/M5LOvEokaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber launches new app for drivers: (Reuters) - Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] on Tuesday unveiled a new app for its drivers that includes a real-time earnings tracker, the latest effort by the ride-hailing service to improve an often contentious… https://t.co/Du8zjTBVMi https://t.co/JISteJdvKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labs Release Manager: Overview The Release Program Manager is responsible to work across departments to set release strategy, methodology, initiatives and act as an escalation point for any release issues. Release Program Manager reports to the Director,… https://t.co/V7ZCzKiSmv https://t.co/vFZP85syzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Networking Software Engineer: Were looking for a dedicated and passionate Sr. Engineer to join our cloud networking team. If you have experience building scalable, cloud based, web applications, are excited about impacting millions of users, look no… https://t.co/Pepsn5JFEO https://t.co/H85gVS13sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Job #:180028444: Job #:180028444 Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Duties: Provide quality technology solutions that address line of business needs by contributing to writing Pega applications, developing stored procedures and general… https://t.co/xOi9g5JVmB https://t.co/guHVPX3N8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 376186BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Participate in full lifecycle software development as part of a 5-8 person scrum team utilizing state of the art technologies, methodologies and… https://t.co/8PnxTjjyk4 https://t.co/N0RZu2Fwxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer Software Engineer: VeriCheck, Inc. (*************) is in the online payment processing industry. We are currently seeking a Full-Time Mid-Level Software Engineer to join our development team. You have the ability to gather requirements,… https://t.co/urkRRBSab2 https://t.co/5OziAWGJ2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development, Lead – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 216286 Who We Are: Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed… https://t.co/8scI2dOMb5 https://t.co/Gy1Zs8EE57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli agency investigating Apple over handling of iPhone slowdown: JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Israel's consumer protection bureau said on Tuesday it was investigating Apple over a failure to disclose to consumers that its software could slow performance in… https://t.co/OpyzjN3JKM https://t.co/kArdVByYx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Senior: Req ID 97134BR Business Title Software Developer, Senior Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed None Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities · ManTech, a well-respected industry… https://t.co/Ni30XhDm5M https://t.co/J6XnW2zbxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/PM: IT Careers – About Us – Our Culture – In the Community – Leadership – Our Services – Enterprise Strategies – IT Planning – Enterprise Portfolio Management – Process Quality Assessment – Managed Solutions – Project Based Services –… https://t.co/qVk1c3oN7a https://t.co/y4gMCJSKZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix): 109879BR Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix) MA – Woburn Job Description: An opportunity exists for a Senior Software Engineer I within the Missile Defense Radar Software Department in Woburn,… https://t.co/ifdlCZE67y https://t.co/3U9XCQ4tya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer, Principal: Req ID 91987BR Business Title CNO Developer, Principal Group MCIS Location USA COLORADO Aurora Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is looking for a Principal CNO Developer to join… https://t.co/V2wUbQzzDY https://t.co/j0bTprAini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany ready to support electric car battery makers, says minister: BERLIN (Reuters) - The German government is ready to offer support to the makers of batteries for electric vehicles, Economy Minister Peter Altmaier said on Tuesday, saying one… https://t.co/91DA6znXzl https://t.co/qQeP9pFJH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Responsibilities * * Develops, maintains, and enhances complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development, manipulation of extremely large data sets, real-time systems, and business… https://t.co/Ngp9YvtdJ3 https://t.co/xFZZeUqPeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II: Overview Business Analyst II (BA) will be assigned items from our road map and will be tasked with creating requirements/user stories &amp; acceptance criteria by eliciting feedback from internal and external stakeholders.  The BSA works… https://t.co/MePk0GJlUk https://t.co/NA4YpkJpMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR782) Job: Scrum Master (SR782) (Job Number:435250) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and agile team environment to incrementally plan, build and… https://t.co/kVo0lcgpT4 https://t.co/HIIB4xqi9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III / Domain Data Steward: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/kj17dh8MEs https://t.co/4GTqAddg6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for a 8-12- month contract in Rosemont, Illinois. The individual should have at least ten years of Project Management experience, managing multiple… https://t.co/qVxFoNCL0t https://t.co/LPnDs1IgX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: Aristotle is looking for a UI/UX Designer (with some JS development experience) that believe those companies that champion a design-centric approach to their product interfaces are the ones that rise above the rest. You live and breathe… https://t.co/zlJ4yDU4Xh https://t.co/xC3rW1EWO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba's Jack Ma urges Facebook to fix privacy issues: BOAO, China (Reuters) - Jack Ma, founder of Chinese e-commerce giant Alibaba, on Monday urged Facebook Inc to resolve its data privacy problems, a day before the social media giant's founder, Mark… https://t.co/5TuLQm9uuS https://t.co/rfRRfLSm13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master role in Murrysville, PA: SCRUM MASTER ROLE LOCATION: MURRYSVILLE, PA 15668 OVERVIEW: * Serve the role of Scrum Master as defined in the Scrum Guide * Guide the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values * Assess the… https://t.co/jX85PREKrI https://t.co/rvRVVhF3uW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/6Ep5bRXtay https://t.co/VBoJd6tBO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/sXSalWM3p1 https://t.co/8Osv92QntZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/EODH4jgxcb https://t.co/9B3TePlgLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Serves as a Java developer whose code is clean, efficient, and well documented. Candidate will design and develop solutions to meet the business requirements in support of the Armys mission, ensuring technical capabilities are secure,… https://t.co/7QRbDpFE2a https://t.co/4nUkRjJVNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verifone to be taken private for $2.6 billion in cash: (Reuters) - Payments technology company Verifone Systems Inc on Monday agreed to be taken private by an investor group led by Francisco Partners for $2.58 billion in cash. https://t.co/W6HB2Hs28A https://t.co/15ZAn1JoMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Scrum Master: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/sqYGOrKJfY https://t.co/xuONbe8gnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Engineer – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 214876 Who We Are:Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed hosting… https://t.co/nJvsVuMkAW https://t.co/ibkdNnIqIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: CONTRACT SCRUM MASTER MUST BE LOCAL TO ISELIN NJ AND AVAILABLE TO INTERVIEW IN PERSON IMMEDIATELY. Our client is searching for a Scrum Master with Agile Development experience Must have Scrum certification and heavy Agile Development… https://t.co/C9ATUZfkv3 https://t.co/jI4RRHpzTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10518 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Pittsburg, PA //… https://t.co/uloiBrgrNg https://t.co/USnSmn5kyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master Certified (CSM), Professional Scrum Master… https://t.co/5E6TP6Z3yq https://t.co/vAFgLJe3VO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Engineer III: Client Reference Code: 216084 Job Scope: We’re looking for a highly motivated individual to join the Video Operations Automation and Tools team. The successful candidate will be part of a group responsible for engineering… https://t.co/XN6myKWrWh https://t.co/Q19MRFBu4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona election database targeted in 2016 by criminals, not Russia: source: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A hack on an Arizona election database during the 2016 U.S. presidential campaign was carried out by suspected criminal actors and not the Russian… https://t.co/OdkgcpGcQw https://t.co/1TxG7xx0ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scrum master: scrum master Ref No.: 18-10389 Location: plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Columbus ,Ohio //… https://t.co/j7c4JmMH1a https://t.co/XaOLKAKEPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KjYs2joyNt Developer: Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/m8Qypm4eWK https://t.co/KqHpDrAmU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/BdRahLJ6Jm https://t.co/5pqv0eX5fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Product Manager – Eden Prairie, MN: Optum is the industry leader delivering health services dedicated to one goal: making the health system work better for everyone. For those who need care, provide care and pay for care, we deliver integrated,… https://t.co/ofYNSN23NY https://t.co/1GdYAVfMr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/D8dEXINcnR https://t.co/OylFZBvm2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job ID  2018-16687 Primary Location  New Jersey, Jersey City Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  .. Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this job The Scrum Master is a servant leader, helping the rest… https://t.co/m9xG9qTUJL https://t.co/s88u1UVfX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran hit by global cyber attack that left U.S. flag on screens: DUBAI (Reuters) - Hackers have attacked networks in a number of countries including data centers in Iran where they left the image of a U.S. flag on screens along with a warning: "Don't mess… https://t.co/KW86FYT2CM https://t.co/db0zbeBF0x]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>