<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/7u38xLB2rA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/9xGDOn4WLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/RCQG18qnWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/LkgxyqzbL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/l4PcRJvjvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/EyuVXNOWDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/9gtejNTVDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/SJsmJ8PLMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/2E84fMYHYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/x0XvngXMdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/SMHa5mL3Ut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/EKmkpgWQEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/jPuEco9IUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/bdQSnhmKKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/xKZbNyLo2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/uElsrQodmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/cBvxRwJ3py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/SJsmJ8PLMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/CbgHGVYJub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/07NCQ5eVHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/M6OGC0s8qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/X7W5fN2J5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/p9E81oQDra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/9501UewdX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/hd7ueF6kva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/IEtf1Tnk0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/NvKj8MQWpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not really interested in making money. Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/bukZYbw91Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/zejbfpLe86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/ldSszQvX8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/AkX6aFSVf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/Skm0eEtN3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/TAvMnQvDzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/UJ4AjRVoGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/xiY0hOEPzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/svR5oOzH4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/jePqeIZo4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/Vhe1AVOaMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/njvGaH8WRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/3NOe2PbaTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last words to the 'Star Spangled Banner?' 'Play ball!' - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/a2MOEUWwuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/bZ00nPcMku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/tKhkdc71r9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/zc428Wynt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/grr71ZqOcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/VoZHta0YRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/TQ7THsBl9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/QJB6VERJ50]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>