<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenrdarcy I had to ignore the rain possibility due to the heat; so it's a linen blazer with a white shirt and medium blue tie with white accents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hot and I'm in a suit so I just took an Uber to avoid a five minute walk, AMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nickconfessore: Beltway dream sequence: After stepping down, Nielsen is shunned by Washington and unable to find a job.
Beltway reality…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimWhiteRI Preferred BMWs. The nickname comes from his skill at stealing them as a young hood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuing the "Bad Vox Takes" trends; nation building in Central America and Mexico is probably the least cost effective way to deal with immigration. Plus, if we did it, the left would complain about "neoliberal imperialism" https://t.co/zv0xMbXohW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a feminist asked, "How can we compete with Jordan Peterson's 'lobsters have hierarchy so hierarchy is natural and an affirmative good' animal analogy hot take?" https://t.co/P25cLp1kEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HudakZak: Striking but unsurprising results in this @pewresearch study on Americans' ability, or lack thereof, to differentiate btwn fa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai This might be your worst opinion ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlanMCole: Sandra Bullock can get me to root for anything. 

Watching the beginning of Ocean's 8 I'm all like "you go Sandra, con those…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YeahEStilwell I have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MiekeEoyang: Just a reminder, as @BenFreemanDC and I found, Putin is more popular than @SenateMajLdr among Republicans. 

https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai Because we're Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAaboutCA I will die on this hill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, this is totally doable. Let's say you buy 10 suits and 5 sportcoats for each of the four seasons; at an average of $15,000 each. That's $900,000 without buying a single shirt, tie, or shoe. Not to mention if you start to buy cufflinks with precious metals. https://t.co/sMYphROjty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me $500,000 and I'll show you. https://t.co/njfMHyfZ9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the court considers his dependents, by which I mean the beautiful suits that will be left abandoned in a closet if he's imprisoned. https://t.co/mmzOUmjmJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @bergmayer I think this guy is the henchman to a D-list Batman villain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan Aka: It looks like Anastasia Williams will definitely win in the House D-9 Democratic primary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @JohnCollins I'm so excited to read this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @JohnCollins The phrase "Fort Lauderdale slut water" made me burst out laughing on the T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_emmahinchliffe: I love this movie theater in New Jersey that only plays indie movies but is also still playing Book Club because its c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bureau of Labor Statistics says our labor force has 161,539,000 workers so unless we've adopted Venezuelan economic policies without anyone telling me, this stat is bogus. https://t.co/vwA2jkPbtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not me of course. You can trust me, I'm not like the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's your regular reminder that a lot of political consulting is a con to separate wealthy donors from their money. https://t.co/lPCqlIkafp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbarro: The proposed capacity of this thing is 2,000 passengers per hour. You can fit that many people on a single New York City subway…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SethAMandel: Have they met children? When I was a kid we had a game we just called “guns.” Wanna play guns? Heck yeah I wanna play guns…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana @RSI @kevinrkosar @donlemon He also did a great job pairing a tie with seersucker, which is tricky business. Nice color contrast without being over saturated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davegray: Google discovered that giving every employee a credit card and trusting them to follow policy on expenses, even with some bad…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RyanLizza: A comment like this from Obama would have defined him on the right for his entire presidency and would have been endlessly r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daveweigel: Corey Stewart is a US Senate nominee. Mark Sanford may lose his House seat. If you're an anti-Trump Republican, your only c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Redistrict: Rep. Mark Sanford (R)'s increasingly probable defeat in #SC01 means vocally Trump-skeptic Rs essentially have two choices:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianros1: The attitude built and nurtured by conservative media. People want politicians who sound like their favorite hosts. Used to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kasie: I feel like I have been a broken record on this point, and every time I make it someone somewhere accuses me of being a (Paul Ry…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter his faults, Nixon was one of our great Presidents. There was nobody else who could or would have opened up "Red China" and made a nuclear deal with the Soviets. When Watergate is a footnote in history, those will still be consequential. https://t.co/0GKLz9CVwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CalebHowe: msnbc has a reporter live on scene from a farm before dawn.

you guys know a trade "war" is more like, on paper, right? Like…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanCritt Monster but only if you dilute the chemicals with some healthy vodka. I normally like Stoli but you'd want something lighter, like Gray Goose or Rekya for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustEric: We tried to make her go to rehab. She said no, no, no. https://t.co/3w117yeA2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgrantaddison @senatorshoshana Sounds like a fucking great motherfucking podcast, motherfuckers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a future conservative middle aged politico, I am refusing to learn this lesson. https://t.co/qBxn1xjkMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @416Bando: The bible says Adam and Eve not florence and the machine https://t.co/XKH77oPP60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SJSchauer: An HGTV show where they help new college graduates decorate their apartment with furniture found exclusively on the side of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannincurry: a dating app that matches horse girls with men who exclusively take pictures holding fish. rt if u agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mvendituoli I fly by griffin. Best way to beat the traffic. My startup is Uber but for flying mythical beasts, we only accept payment in GriffCoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philipaklein: While just 32% of Americans approved of Trump's performance in Helsinki -- 68% of Republicans did. Good indicator of why…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadioFreeTom: Look, I’m not a fan of @benshapiro, but if a liberal like @MarkDuplass wants to follow him and thinks he’s interesting, t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamgoodman3 He had beautiful ads that, as an up-and-coming strategist, I've been hugely influenced by. He was also exceedingly kind when he met me as an intern in D.C. who wanted to babble at him about media consulting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysteriousrook They're also all competing in a primary where 80+% of likely voters are staunch Trump supporters. I'd imagine Kingston and Lindstrom would be a lot different if they were in the general right now, instead of being worried about giving Diehl wedge issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan When people wonder why Providence's economy is less dynamic than similar cities, its nonsense like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murphymike Those great high production spots (Cattle Drive!) and jingles (Don Young, Alaskan Like You!) Him and Garth were the two greatest, most creative ad men I've seen. Sad that modern practitioners have traded in storytelling and narrative for raw, brute force GRPs and scary narrators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mollyohoran: The phrasing of this headline is... unfortunate.

#mapoli https://t.co/LyTzwHQuIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana @IAtheTeapot @clark_packard @RSI Earlier in the thread. It was hard to find something alliterative with Zegna, but I managed. This is why you pay me the big bucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAtheTeapot @clark_packard @senatorshoshana @RSI Zachariah has strong opinions and I won't let him be silenced by your anti-inanimate object biases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAtheTeapot @senatorshoshana @RSI @clark_packard @clark_packard I'll put you in touch with Zachariah "Zanny" Zegna, my gray chalkstripe. He has a lot of opinions about trade policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @baseballcrank: Periodic reminder:

-The things Obama did wrong are still wrong no matter what Trump does.

-The things Obama did wrong…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RSI @IAtheTeapot @senatorshoshana @clark_packard I don't come here to be made sport of. #triggered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAtheTeapot @senatorshoshana @RSI So you're both aware, my suits have strong opinions anout tariffs since they rely on foreign tradesmen to assemble them to crisp, canvassed perfection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xan_desanctis: Days like today remind me how much absolute garbage there is lurking on the right. Five years ago, the idea of defending…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing besides empty criticism. They know primary voters don't care about the Russian issue, they know they are more likely to lose a primary than a general election, ergo.... https://t.co/Cm3PdmCZ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaayleyCoates In your defense, that's really tiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skoczela @LaurenDezenski In the wise words of @dick_nixon "ambition must always be concealed by avarice."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexburnsNYT: Republicans used to call this kind of thing “Blame America First” https://t.co/C7ssdJVu9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoraCrowley @DanMcGowan To be fair, signs are as much about mollifying donors/volunteers as they are about persuading voters and raising your passive name ID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Thanksmitch: If lighting didn't naturally happen on Earth and some sci-fi writer pitched it for the gimmick of a Star Trek episode or s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyMaggiacomo @senatorshoshana @pedialyte I'm keeping it jargon-free for a neophyte.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana @pedialyte Screwdrivers can work if you don't have Arnold Palmer, but you really want its thick, almost sludgy texture. For ideal results keep it really cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana @pedialyte Rookie move. You want Arnold Palmer and vodka. The thick, viscous Arnold Palmer will give you the sugar you need, the vodka is self-explanatory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emzanotti: This is not, in fact, a quot from Abraham Lincoln. It's a misattributed quote from the trailer for the Channing Tatum movie,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessDKelley: https://t.co/mDzaXSBhPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuockerWodging @JoshuaGreen @dandrezner @DouthatNYT Depends on the overarching strategic concept, resources available, and research data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGreen @dandrezner @DouthatNYT They were doing what I advise underfunded candidates to do in much smaller races. Assume the necessary but not sufficient conditions for victory will occur, focus your resources on achieving your path to victory if exogenous factors align in your favor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDon @RepMoira_Jayne @LGDanMcKee What's the context? Dan criticized party's decision to endorse Michael. As a reporter, you know there's plenty of situations/events where candidates who disagree stand near each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costareports @JasonKander Buddy Cianci, my first boss in politics, explained, "being mayor is the best job because you're a king. Governors deal with legislators, Senators just talk all day, mayors are like a medieval lord. You run a police force, a fire department, and you're in fucking charge."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billscher: "These Democrats are running in GOP-held CD’s, not safely Democratic New York city. All were against abolishing ICE. None ar…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamanthaRocci I feel the same about Boston. Let another city get the crippling traffic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaitlynKiley Thanks Mitch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaitlynKiley Were you a "bi-opic" person? Don't feel bad, mispronunciation is the mark of a reader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAtheTeapot @jneeley78 Eventually I'll write my, "I don't agree with anything the Republican Party believes, I'm just an elitist jerk" take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jneeley78 Genuinely interested in the burnt steak to right-wing politics nexus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RSI @drinksreform @cjdieterle @YABOYFANNYPACK I'm assuming this is a precaution for R Street's all-staff meeting. Bet those get raucous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @IAaboutCA @RSI The real question: how many holes does a straw have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottferson He could have a bone protruding from his skin and I'd assume it's a flop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CydMckenna This fills me with joy. He's three years, tops, away from his first contrast collar shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @avermeule: Alternative take: religious conviction is the *only* reason that anyone either opposes or supports Roe. It is the place wher…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmartNYT: Really good piece.  

If a Republican made the equivalent “but Bernie won here” argument about Trump having won the Massachus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @ISDM27 I'll never understand you olive eaters. Why would I want salt and sour flavors in my birdbath of gin or vodka?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @ISDM27 I'm okay with this. #TwistOnly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in reality: The professionalism of the average American urban police department has increased exponentially in the past fifty years, though mostly plateauing in the 2000s. https://t.co/NsfCSFXx2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeerJeet: If we've learned anything from every Mummy movie of the last 100 years, its that this sarcophagus must not be opened. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maryy_Alexandra This fills me with joy. Was the documentary homemade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admire Dershowitz's commitment to recommending high conflict options. Facing a special counsel? Argue the President is essentially immune to prosecution like an imperial monarch. Republicans won't confirm your judge? Just swear him in because l'etat c'est moi. https://t.co/pCl1MvGGeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a name for judges who a politician can fire at a whim — apparatchiks. https://t.co/g4DG4Nizsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jessesingal: Vox: Caves, Explained

Slate: Why Thai Authorities Should Have Left The Soccer Team In That Cave A Little Longer

Breitbar…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjane87 Hey, somebody's gotta fill the void in the Torturer's Lobby left by Paul Manafort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mottocto @MarkMellman @axios *The inability of the media, candidates, donors, and way too many "consultants" to read and understand surveys is perplexing.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan Location is everything. Signs cost money so a good campaign has a relatively small amount but gets high passive Name ID benefits through locations. Only reason to give a sign to someone in a remote location is because they're a donor or vol who needs to be mollified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aronsbarron: NIMBY pot communities shouldn't share in marijuana tax revenues. 
https://t.co/EBahyb7q5c #RecreationalMarijuana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A major strand of continental European conservatism was about defending the right of the "throne and alter" to arbitrarily sacrifice their citizens life and dignity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even ignoring the merits of pro-life versus pro-choice; this is intellectually vacuous nonsense that ignores the historical tradition of conservatism, where "human dignity" was a marginal concern at best and an obstacle to be overcome at worst. https://t.co/RET7ehExJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai @DaniSButcher Screwdrivers or John Daly's (Arnold Palmer with vodka) are the best morning drinks, followed by prosecco, followed by a gin martini. Bloodys are probably at the bottom, right below plain Rubinoff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmartNYT: Cagle says out loud (and on tape) what many elected Rs believe about their base 

https://t.co/KoWSrgpNSO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>