<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Analyst II: Development Analyst II needed in Tulsa, Oklahoma. To participate in most aspects of software enhancement primarily for packaged applications, including configuration, testing, deployment and maintenance activities. Applicants must… https://t.co/GPgI6CPKkU https://t.co/TDmGiBSAaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL backend coding, knowledge of UWP, WinForms,… https://t.co/OiMRAefDhc https://t.co/09scRGbPNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst: Sr Analyst, Asset Mgmt – Perform complex financial investment analyses for Asset Mgmt Business, incl analysis of equities, fixed income securities, private investments &amp; other instruments using advanced mathematical, statistical &amp; financial… https://t.co/Hkabxtbe0j https://t.co/vTLWrGHSNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Information Technology: DIRECTOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Tribal Office Building Closing date: 4/10/18 or until filled.   Qualifications: * An undergraduate degree in Computer Science or equivalent field.  (Master’s degree preferred, or… https://t.co/KrmKUGwGEB https://t.co/RWslgOqRuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Vice President, Messaging Middleware Support: IT-Vice President, Messaging Middleware Support (Research Triangle Park, NC): Develop &amp; deploy enhancements &amp; new releases to Messaging Middleware Platform using IBM WebSphere Message Broker, IBM WebSphere… https://t.co/JnCrmiQI9l https://t.co/OMC9zXy5Rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[deleted https://t.co/zpn5LyRnTc https://t.co/UefzA6ePfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Speaker Deals: Sony, JBL, Ultimate Ears, Insignia: We've found awesome deals on some rockin' speakers. https://t.co/X6w9Jxqu0p https://t.co/xPYWp78VVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Support Engineer II: IT/Software Applications Support Engineer II: Bachelor’s degree in Computer science, Engineer, or related &amp; 5 years related experience.   recblid fsx99odvqmqwtqzs6livexmn535emz https://t.co/KTEWTD7UuV https://t.co/gXhAhi3OcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geographic Information System Analyst: Geographic Information System Analyst The Geographic Information Systems (GIS) Analyst leads Sonoma County Water Agency Geographic Information Systems-related projects; creates metadata and manages long-term mapping… https://t.co/RFvoPmVNkj https://t.co/Shi6pxStQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager/Economist/Systems Engineer: Transportation Technology Center Inc. is the nation’s premiere transportation research and testing organization. With cutting edge labs, 52 miles of test tracks, and a full-scale hazmat training… https://t.co/54PdRjgSng https://t.co/N4935ble18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/T6PkNPhMDj https://t.co/NGsVihU0Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Consultation Agent: What does a Geek Squad Consultation Agent do? Do all things technology fire you up? Can you swap a motherboard or hook up a home theater system blindfolded? Does the thought of installing an LCD in an SUV, and getting paid… https://t.co/efqiARIvof https://t.co/AsIVKi8T4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Exploitation Analyst 2 (TS/SCI with poly required): ABOUT THE JOB Our client is seeking a talented Network Exploitation Analyst to its team. This position is located in Ft. Meade, Maryland. Network Exploitation Analyst evaluates target… https://t.co/8WIVkJzDZb https://t.co/WJ6nTmcDEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Tableau Developer Job: Date: Mar 5, 2018 Location: Arlington, VA, US Company: SAIC Data Scientist – Tableau Developer (Job Number:434706) Description: Job Description – Ideal candidate will be responsible for creating dashboard… https://t.co/VHLhMEOgRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Application Security Engineer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Sr. Web Application Security Engineer. Candidate will provide solutions to complex security, and provide strategies, policies standards, guidelines and… https://t.co/hVKiZ9qktE https://t.co/qFhcBquJVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect, Aruba Distributed Enterprise Solutions: Senior Solutions Architect, Aruba Distributed Enterprise Solutions at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and… https://t.co/LztOd8UMhs https://t.co/S1Ox5oixUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Systems Administrator: Our client located in Portland is looking for a Windows Systems Administrator for a 6 month renewable contract. Required skills include Microsoft Exchange 2013 and Skype for Business 2015. Other desired skills include… https://t.co/zCeRsp60Ih https://t.co/yddgoNuqju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/6AlWtH6ASL https://t.co/eASZQDygSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap PS4 and PS4 Pro Bundles and Deals (2018): If you're hunting for a PS4 or PS4 Pro, these are the cheapest bundles you're going to find. https://t.co/2431cq5eLo https://t.co/IRxDmSCSAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers (Code SE): Talented IT, Inc. has multiple openings for the following positions in Naperville, IL and various unanticipated locations throughout the US: Software Engineers (Code SE) design, develop, implement &amp; test business &amp; computer… https://t.co/FAcDJYvvRV https://t.co/kuSgnHbHCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Processor: Description: MSW-ARS performs global market research, primarily through online surveys. By collecting information on consumers’ needs and preferences, market research enables informed decision making. Data Processors transform raw data… https://t.co/oBq4raBaQc https://t.co/Ha7KriVHUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[deleted https://t.co/KxvCpKfaJR https://t.co/6GjFSDRUFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA APPLICATION DEVELOPER: KRONSYS is hiring for 2 positions (travel req): Java Application Developer – MS CS, EE or closely rel. XML, Oracle, Java; Business Data Analyst – MS Comp App, Info Sys, MBA or closely rel. + 2 yrs exp. or BS + 5 yrs exp. or… https://t.co/X163zgisTL https://t.co/gFBhvCQPKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator Below you will find the details for the position including any supplementary documentation and questions you should review before applying for the opening.  Posting Details: Position Information: Position… https://t.co/te14O4U9nm https://t.co/L8iHUor7MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42201: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R42201. Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA. Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/P6nHClHS8r https://t.co/5WkpasfiKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scientist: PROJECT SCIENTIST sought by University of California, Irvine in Irvine, CA. Conduct research on human-computer interaction applied to the “Internet of Things” including electronic devices and software applications for advancements in… https://t.co/vWIzxHkwjM https://t.co/wJDetjE5yH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager #80165P: IT Project Manager (Vacancy #80165P) IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking qualified applicants for an experienced IT Project Manager. This position will be responsible for managing small to large technology related… https://t.co/q8t2SFJ4TJ https://t.co/59nedRUoxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: * Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. * Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/VXcEiBHW1u https://t.co/o9z193QItJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer The Office of the Revisor of Statutes, a nonpartisan office in the Minnesota Legislature, is seeking applicants for a Systems Analyst/Programmer I position. The office has implemented an XML-based, bill drafting,… https://t.co/iLAXZbj2xu https://t.co/A3a97WPgK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail IT Specialist: TOSHIBA GLOBAL COMMERCE SOLUTIONS, INC., seeks a Retail IT Specialist Tech Lead in Durham, NC to provide IT services in a billable project. Req. MS + 1 yr exp or BS + 5 yrs exp. Mail resume to: Jeff Baker, Sr Mgr Global Talent… https://t.co/jKlZRtHH9Z https://t.co/z9UH4MVT8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Easter Tech Sales (2018): Nintendo, Apple, Dyson, Lenovo: When you're done painting eggs and munching on candy, check out these Easter tech deals. https://t.co/FPD9kCvcg2 https://t.co/c2EpMcICkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecom Analyst #80159P: Telecom Analyst The Telecommunications Analyst position is a technical role to support the telemanagement system responsible for inside and outside cable plant records. This position will create and maintain accurate… https://t.co/tXBwtZkImv https://t.co/bkDyvjJBka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Manager #YK0318: Business Systems Manager Logistics and Operations Cypress, CA. Administer and maintain IT application portfolio.  recblid xvskgtm5m1tlv2wcxrket3nertchmq https://t.co/yel3wVl1Un https://t.co/1fmKFc0yRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Consultant: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/gKMbMXLj4b https://t.co/cwJJCcNdPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner: Description: The Leidos Health Products &amp; Service Group has an opening for an Agile Product Owner with experience in the commercial healthcare or related industry to support the design, integration, testing and delivery of the Leidos… https://t.co/oLw4zpxZg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: CO-OP Financial Servicesprovides technically superior products and services to financial institutions across the nation. We are seeking a talentedProject Manager Ito be responsible for applying fundamental project management knowledge… https://t.co/6mvTQDBN0W https://t.co/3vrB8DetRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Business Analyst: Salesforce Business Analyst Full Time Position Lisle, IL Job Description: As a Salesforce Business Analyst, you will be part of a team responsible for delivering enterprise cloud technology solutions. Our Salesforce Business… https://t.co/AfYAA5zokv https://t.co/anUWhnEvaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Automation Developer: Software Test Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime position Job Description: Responsible for writing test cases, executing tests and automating tests for the OPAE, which is the software infrastructure for Intel… https://t.co/luYG7434D4 https://t.co/InkXABfLAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Analyst (Job Code CT: Computer Programmer Analyst, Job Code CT 222 (CitiusTech, Princeton, NJ) Responsibilities include project management and hands on development in the healthcare sector which must conform to healthcare standards… https://t.co/uQ0ydZV8Un https://t.co/HRf6EwVuih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Optimization Specialist: More information about this job Overview Operations Optimization Specialist This newly designed role will assist in the optimization of Heartland Dentals supported office portfolio. You will be responsible for… https://t.co/8eRPEGhq3w https://t.co/k1fXXtaoJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BPM Developer: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed Search – IT Staffing – Our Story –… https://t.co/nNrmjshcyP https://t.co/WWHud1kbPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Automation Architect: NETWORK SECURITY AUTOMATION ARCHITECT The Network Security Automation Architect is responsible for designing and engineering global solutions to include FW, Proxy, End User and Automation as a primary focus. OUR… https://t.co/yHjVqoKD1B https://t.co/FEiXWTCinq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Security DevOps Engineer: With over 200 million users in 196 countries, ********** is the worlds largest technology platform for social change. Our team spans 18 countries and empowers hundreds of millions of people to have a voice and fight… https://t.co/4O3IpyFFw6 https://t.co/epjnaHdqVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Stop Eye Strain: Tips, Tricks, and Apps: The aching eyes, sore muscles, and headaches caused by eye strain can be prevented by following these tips. https://t.co/TEW6YGPPIa https://t.co/xo9lia6vwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Description: Application Support Analyst needed to join our dynamic Customer Support Center as part of our Software Escalation team.  Our proprietary web-based software products deliver industry-leading digital communications… https://t.co/rVeoLe9sd4 https://t.co/vmEbG0lTAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Developer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA… https://t.co/4mkwNcjnlF https://t.co/evedwpzDI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Enablement Manager: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/E3jYXNeum7 https://t.co/OjRVqYoAFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed security… https://t.co/rrQO86g69u https://t.co/qFnDm8LJwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Service Delivery Manager – Storage: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/DiEHGwH05H https://t.co/wEgnPRJxnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: * Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. * Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/QUQLd1grGk https://t.co/hYH5ngZPuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Development: Senior Manager of Development (https://t.co/6tTWQ1Ax8j, Inc., Midvale, UT) Multiple openings available. Lead multiple teams working on significant &amp; critical projects, provide tech &amp; team leadership &amp; mentorship. Work with… https://t.co/jCfaNCrH26 https://t.co/uIFGB59kVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner- ServiceNow: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/oUdiNfitlv https://t.co/ffecEiDPsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test I: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/H4sCuwzHm8 https://t.co/CET9dj8NGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banquet Server: Banquets Server (Full Time) Westin Country Club Savannah-Westin Start Your Journey With Us At Westin, we are committed to empowering the well-being of our guests by providing a refreshing environment, thoughtful amenities, and… https://t.co/T6oY2dDijb https://t.co/kUtygHTgFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   Leidos has an opening for a… https://t.co/eDGM5LkrHV https://t.co/DiNaP39obC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead: Proj Lead, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Define &amp; dvlp UNIX S-TAP release test plan &amp; execution process. Design &amp; implement quality processes &amp; metrics. Anlyze changes &amp; new features based on functional &amp; design reqs. Recommend test strategies.… https://t.co/kycZdFEVM9 https://t.co/jvLu3nSyZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Tools to Help With Hand and Arm Injuries: For those who have recently injured or lost their dominant hand, everything from apps to bungees exist to ease the frustration. https://t.co/9tzjw5EQxj https://t.co/VtcJ97FHIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Operations Support Specialist II: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/1QNwTgT5I1 https://t.co/jsHsd47LaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIns 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   The Mission Systems… https://t.co/JHpW6pebz8 https://t.co/7IOArakJmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple Positions:  American Airlines has multiple openings for the following positions in Ft. Worth, TX: Sr. Analyst AAdvantage (REF#17453) resp for co-brand portfolio growth by leveraging data insights fr AA &amp; its co-brand partners – Citibank &amp;… https://t.co/F7CnzhFfxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Developer: The Company and Opportunity Axius provides smart home management – think of us like your personal IT Help Desk. By creating a fully inclusive service layer for the home, Axius adds remote support, network security and… https://t.co/TOOe3IjQyP https://t.co/xU5NFTnsr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required:   Job Description – Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required (17027927) Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required Requisition ID : 17027927… https://t.co/hacUigLUuB https://t.co/g1uYtpcIpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest people you will ever meet in any particular… https://t.co/VBqFaoyeOs https://t.co/scGb7XkXqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Development Solution Consultant – ServiceNow Platform: Highmetric is seeking a ServiceNow Solutions Consultant to be responsible for leading the successful delivery of ServiceNow solutions and services, in a client-consulting environment. This… https://t.co/ywMlNbbn1j https://t.co/THX4utdQw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax Manager (International Tax): Emeryville, CA Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today Title: International Tax Manager Salary: $110,000 – $130,000 Location: Oakland, CA Specialty: International Tax, CPA, ASC 740, Federal Income Tax, and Foreign Tax Credit… https://t.co/b23aduaFbm https://t.co/KJGE9VhrNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract DevOps Engineer: ARE YOU LOCAL TO NEW YORK AND ABLE TO WORK ON SITE 40 HOURS A WEEK?We are looking for a DevOps Engineer that knows release management in-and-out and wants to own it! WHATS THE JOB? This is onsite in our Midtown Manhattan… https://t.co/DmF8SDAEiO https://t.co/J7ZzQaTl4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – St-Ives, UK Location: Advantech Wireless is seeking a dynamic and motivated professional to fill the position Software Engineer our St-ives, UK Office. The role of Software Engineer is to maintain, develop and support Advantech… https://t.co/tr0HPlP2HI https://t.co/3IPbRzCnIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SQL Server DBA: SR SQL Server DBA Oak Brook, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/29/18, Posted Date – 03/29/18 Primary SkillsSR SQL Server DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Chamberlain Group Role: SR SQL Server DBA Duration: 6 + Openings: 1… https://t.co/Jxh85r2xrA https://t.co/xZkQwiBfEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Inside Story of Reddit's Redesign: Goodbye, dystopian Craigslist. There's a new Reddit, and it's all grown up. https://t.co/4eToEgviDd https://t.co/DC9thb4esa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage Admin/Engineer: Description: The Civil Health group is currently seeking a storage admin/engineer lead to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   Standard Job Description: Performs a variety of activities related to the engineering… https://t.co/cuSnxdFnNH https://t.co/Q0fTOaw1bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Full Stack Software Engineer – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our… https://t.co/LFNpAQJZ4v https://t.co/DBpWYky3OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Description: Leidos seeks a Business Systems Analyst to support the DSI program. Primary Responsibilities below: Ability to assist customers with Customer Relationship Management (CRM) technical support issues as well as… https://t.co/GvXunZRXga https://t.co/Ozb3SSg66P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accountant: Accountant sought by Healthmate International, LLC in Lenexa, Kansas: Perfm reconc &amp; prep fin stmts, compile &amp; rpt biz metrics; Devlp budgs, anlyz biz oprs, prjt futr rev &amp; expns; Mng Netsuit ERP cost systms, imprv intrnl cost acctg procdr &amp;… https://t.co/4huTJJjO9s https://t.co/7UKy8Y7GXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Manager: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Aliso Viejo, CA for Technical Product Manager Principal to define the product direction, roadmap, budget, unique value proposition, comparative competitive advantages, &amp; investment… https://t.co/cwI1I1RqvF https://t.co/6nIYihXSqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Description: JOB DESCRIPTION/RESPONSIBILITIES: The Database Administrator is responsible for overseeing day to day operations and maintenance of Oracle databases.  Candidate must poses a working knowledge of Oracle database… https://t.co/nmiOqhrPga https://t.co/FPQaU6lMWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Application Architect DHS00531823 *Marshalltown, IA* Under administrative direction, responsible for taking a œsolution area from the current IT state to a future state which aligns with the long term business and technology… https://t.co/shRTSJSIRJ https://t.co/wVrn0S11hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. PwC Advisory helps our clients with their most challenging imperatives from strategy through execution. We… https://t.co/cXalWbPht8 https://t.co/BXRwvp0agO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Analyst: Description: The DoD Information Systems Division of Leidos is seeking a Systems Integration Analyst for the Defense Civilian Personnel Data System (DCPDS) program at San Antonio, Texas.   Job Description: The System… https://t.co/0UZFuHeprc https://t.co/ZCRyE68Y0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Line Workers: Production Line Workers Benson’s Old Home Kitchens Bakery, in Bogart, has employment opportunities available for Production Line Workers, 2nd shift, 10-12 hours per shift. Applicants must be available to work weekends. Starting… https://t.co/2NxkhBQ53f https://t.co/TsMs1hcwHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Acquisitions Team: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/PJRz8FUOjy https://t.co/3bIAufnx1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer: Description: Leidos has an immediate opening for a Cyber Security Engineer located in Bethesda, MD. We are looking for an energetic, motivated, independent, self starter for a position supporting a dynamic organization that… https://t.co/Vw4JdaLNPr https://t.co/OjwIuEjrhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Fold 5 High-Flying Stunt Paper Airplanes: "The Paper Airplane Guy" John Collins shows us how to fold planes that do loops, flap their wings, and fly world-record distances. https://t.co/fmikC4dLzh https://t.co/T8WBBeKHnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/EwHnssdCNE https://t.co/lZZMUevkzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description: The Civil Health Group is currently seeking a System Administrator to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful candidate will work within an ITIL environment and be… https://t.co/zeHWqrjTER https://t.co/EMl3EKetxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: Leidos is looking for a Software Engineer to support the Army Geospatial Center focused on Geospatial application development in the areas of data transformation, test and evaluation, validation and tool development. The… https://t.co/aSZOtunyLZ https://t.co/l2jXHmjlAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Ruby on Rails: We focus on results, encourage mastery, and enjoy the benefits of being part of something big without the frustrations of corporate work culture. Intriguing, right?! That’s how one of our Developers described Stonecrop… https://t.co/DipltMM3Yh https://t.co/2xIycwTCKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Project Manager: ENVIRONMENTAL PROJECT MANAGER PSI, an Intertek Company is currently seeking an Environmental Project Manager who has an interest in developing long-term client relationships with increasing project and professional… https://t.co/x3PRZFiImB https://t.co/89c9AUa010]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Designer: Interested in working for a growing, fast-paced company with diverse projects and technologies? COLAB is looking for talented team members to help shape the companys future. At COLAB, we have a close-knit team with no office… https://t.co/l7cyMmiwxo https://t.co/yfd39HVebN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend Web Developer (for arts, academic, non-profit projects): We need a front-end developer to join our team and help us build well thought-out, highly usable web sites and web applications for our clients. You’re looking for a satisfying work… https://t.co/9mmg6cKbtr https://t.co/kLHyxkkKDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DPHM, ATG Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62177BR Date posted 03/02/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Pratt &amp; Whitney, a recognized leading producer of the world’s most advanced jet engines, is looking for… https://t.co/ernviRPr59 https://t.co/wyuPMcF0R0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/f1CD6ubQ8O https://t.co/1YS4f2HBWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Hybris Consultant: SAP Hybris Consultant Ref No.: 18-11742 Location: Dallas, Texas Title: SAP Hybris Consultant Location: Minneapolis, MN; Dallas, TX Duration: Full Time Job Description: Job Title SAP Hybris Billing Relevant Experience (in Yrs)… https://t.co/2OzgadHsYF https://t.co/IqvgAPfUmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMMEDIATE OPENING: Written Content Creator / HTML Developer: Los Angeles Website Design and Software Engineering Jobs &amp; Viral Marketing Careers: Join Us and Become an Artisan Crew Mmber Design, Web, System and Software Jobs in Los Angeles / Torrance – –… https://t.co/XirWsVUX9M https://t.co/1aI4PKsOeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Manager (Deskside Support), FULL-TIME: As one of the nations leading pediatric health care systems, Nemours is committed to providing all children with their best chance to grow up healthy. We offer integrated, family-centered care to more than… https://t.co/OlT0AoZYU4 https://t.co/33OuzItcFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Fold a World-Record-Setting Paper Airplane: John Collins shows you how to fold the innovative paper airplane design that earned him a spot in the Guinness Book of World Records. https://t.co/13m8MOw1zY https://t.co/k4i7ogKY8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Intelligence Developer (FULL-TIME): As one of the nations leading pediatric health care systems, Nemours is committed to providing all children with their best chance to grow up healthy. We offer integrated, family-centered care to more than… https://t.co/ehAYVxkgTk https://t.co/II0oNza0Ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile FullStack JAVA Developer [USC Only]: ** U.S CITIZENSHIP IS REQUIRED ** Infostellar, Inc is a VA based company, dedicated to providing agile development and dev ops services to Government and Commercial clients. We offer fun, learning, and… https://t.co/0r163c3zdu https://t.co/surHoYwBhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: _INTERESTED IN LEARNING HOW SILICON VALLEY TICKS? WANT TO NETWORK WITH FORMER GOOGLE ENGINEERS AND CEOS WITH TENS OF MILLIONS IN VENTURE FUNDING?_ _We are a stealth-mode recruiting firm in San Francisco. Our Account Managers/Technical… https://t.co/BKEm5Q4sYX https://t.co/bTZyTXAVDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Platform Software Engineer (iOS): Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered… https://t.co/13DuBrpkLe https://t.co/jLMM6XJ7hP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satellite Software Engineer: Satellite Software Engineer About SpaceQuest, Ltd. SpaceQuest, Ltd. is an entrepreneurial commercial space company located just outside Washington DC in Fairfax Virginia. We are a leading developer of satellite technology and… https://t.co/keI9YWmQWZ https://t.co/e7AcWwtZFX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>