<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/QfVco76dha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/EDxUa0gHlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/7bg5GprEEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VO4VzcfakL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/1eJmAcn3jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/FxvhriH6lI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/6XdgTe7DRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/FCI5slz7Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/1omQHvMwja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/PChlgo7ndy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KWtl7yr1hB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/UYj6JDNqAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/i1glAY5C7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/blkGp4JUT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/KIs7XTUPVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/HXlZ6OzjLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/ASPEBfl17n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/ZBKgUaCv0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/5NIpkUojwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/EE9pbI7FED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/guStUEcRte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/CSLeOojlur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/CpM2rzf2FJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/lxLDeZQ4L8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/ATYkux9CNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/1omQHvMwja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/zCTEQzWRbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/FFq2BJI7eM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/qc4Oas4oqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/QjZs6ikqYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/V1kfkodQF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/c4lV8IhMBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/eFAtFOKmVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/MOPXneVyPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/wV653p4btd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/PcML8Us5IY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/oTQ9c9trMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/v0ysGbhBKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/9YZdPzCc5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/GdUXcga1iM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/OD18WUBNty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/TlXeECCAPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/FNmU3pRRRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/C8XGJPQRQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/cg3VcNTjX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/HkztMoyKnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/LAy48qoGxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/reruytT1GI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>