<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/aRwYpBCDqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/3LroDiCDAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/x3BB3EkAXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/f1ce18UkR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/9VGXDnlMg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/TEpBadwpxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/iMWuuJT2XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/4Ee8KnRHHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/2HuXKl4jDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/DDZD7Zihh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/imBQ5eAQRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 106 miles to Chicago, we've got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes, it's dark &amp; we're wearing sunglasses. Hit it! - Elwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/GKFCdYdqJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/FeyA3nV4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/PaoufvMMac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/420GRWq9dU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/wvNzlLb4gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/2ALRLDVX02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/m0wRfxpQ0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/ykkniAoTxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/bkZkswSo8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/XQeAEhdfBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/6X3oDxnPWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/o2ofdNzcCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/YUj3oZ354I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/0NQ7jFVbaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/319UE0sLwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/NTIIM1H9Jt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/TLH8FpQ5Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/y6ClcbTjAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/N3UoOW7dn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/SfGFuOspIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/ESe567z464]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/R4JRxNBE88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/AmoOvKGG4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/cWAQMJWiBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/LgMe184htT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/qG5MxaPNWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/JNeywEmvNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/ZBFaaDb72T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/NGEHOCGZ9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/M7ld6RJ3xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/1f3yMoYlun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/sJifqTHR4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/s6wIpcSOaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/v86p3JAX04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/2mZeBhYf81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/UDErQ329MO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/HoMBtMkzRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/xzUiNneONj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>