<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of food transfers for people living with HIV/AIDS: Evidence from Zambia http://t.co/9kLC9IZjxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Is There More than Milk? The Impact of Heifer International’s Livestock Donation Program on Rural Livel... http://t.co/jP8UMbo9d8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural Technology Adoption and Child Nutrition: Improved Maize Varieties in Rural Ethiopia http://t.co/jOOt0mx0U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittance Responses to Temporary Discounts: A Field Experiment among Central American Migrants http://t.co/TYDB0Nls44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Poverty and the spatial distribution of rural population http://t.co/F2EH5HmqTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do Remittances Alter Household Nutrition? Evidence from Rural Kilimanjaro in Tanzania http://t.co/nEXVILNxFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does malaria control impact education? A study of the Global Fund in Africa http://t.co/82W8ELEXAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: (Measured) Profit is Not Welfare: Evidence from an Experiment on Bundling Microcredit and Insurance http://t.co/UiCU8IcyJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Economic Development and the Effectiveness of Foreign Aid: A Historical Perspective http://t.co/2PB2ix7mYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Social capital, product imitation and growth with learning externalities http://t.co/IRhxRINIAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Econometrica: The Intrinsic Value of Decision Rights http://t.co/fGDRXgOyfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Hicksian separability does not hold over space: Implications for the design of household surveys and pric... http://t.co/8l0xckx0fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Firm heterogeneity in food safety provision: evidence from aflatoxin tests in Kenya http://t.co/CSCYMCx7RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Preferences for Attributes of Conservation Agriculture in Eastern Uganda http://t.co/KdmGLljzkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do input subsidies reduce poverty among smallholder farm households? Evidence from Zambia http://t.co/jELaKZWpix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Direct and Indirect Effects of Cash Transfers on Entrepreneurship http://t.co/wgOUY7xLFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Carbon sensitive productivity, climate and institutions http://t.co/dKYLxpTcBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: COMMERCIALIZATION EFFECTS ON HOUSEHOLD INCOME, POVERTY, AND DIVERSIFICATION: A COUNTERFACTUAL ANALYSIS ... http://t.co/NRhGGPuG4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Sustainable Choice: How Gendered Difference in the Importance of Ecological Benefits Affect Product... http://t.co/931uiBDlfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Looking for Causes of Effects: Imperfect Contract Enforcement in Kenya's French Bean Market http://t.co/YhVLR8tRLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: When do textbooks matter for achievement? Evidence from African primary schools http://t.co/iwYvax33o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Decentralization of National Transfer Programs: compliance, local revealed equivalence scales, and effi... http://t.co/junHZUhV2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Smallholder Participation in Contract Farming and Food Security http://t.co/3TnuD3UZkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does social action fund promote schooling in conflict affected countries? Mixed evidence from Angola http://t.co/jA5GmR8aqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Climate Variability, Shocks and Non-farm Employment: Evidence from Rural Households in Northeast Thailand http://t.co/azAT0DCMNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Natural Resource Collection and Children’s Literacy: Empirical Evidence from Panel Data in Rural Ethiopia http://t.co/CEnsnlmG2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does livestock ownership affect animal source foods consumption and child nutritional status ? evidence... http://t.co/80Jrh81ohM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Land Access, Land Rental and Food Security: Evidence from Kenya http://t.co/nZ7RL2Vf6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Corrupt governments do not receive more state-to-state aid: Governance and the delivery of foreign aid th... http://t.co/foQ3Qo7Hii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Kinship, Trust and Moral Hazard in the Motorcycle-Taxi Market in Togo and Benin http://t.co/gFdtmQWr0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Durable goods and poverty measurement http://t.co/k9cxiaZFja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPubE: Optimal higher education enrollment and productivity externalities in a two-sector model http://t.co/7wF692UkUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Africa Rising: Harnessing the Demographic Dividend http://t.co/taZJP5pMlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender and Ethnicity in Bolivia, Ecuador and Guatemala http://t.co/xfWvKEPTW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Climate and Conflict http://t.co/C3j7fXNnI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do Cows Have Negative Returns? The Evidence Revisited http://t.co/Zc8xC5cYCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of microfinance on factors empowering women: Differences in regional and delivery mechanisms... http://t.co/bOndvMxQq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Financial Services and Divisible Technology Dis-adoption among Farm Households: Theory and Empirical Ap... http://t.co/RpoXceiUIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: A First Step up the Energy Ladder? Low Cost Solar Kits and Household's Welfare in Rural Rwanda http://t.co/DQmEOF7Sbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of WIC program participation on food expenditures http://t.co/N342hJDzka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Estimating the Resiliency of Zambian Smallholder Farmers: Evidence from a Three-Wave Panel http://t.co/YrSownqGVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Credit Constraints and Impact on Farm Household Welfare: Evidence from Vietnam’s North Central Coast region http://t.co/2QOOh94n8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Multidimensional Household Food Security Measurement in Rural Zambia http://t.co/oIn4wGBarc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Saving for a (not so) Rainy Day: A Randomized Evaluation of Savings Groups in Mali http://t.co/fua0xbZlZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Households’ investments in durable and productive assets in Niger: quasi-experimental evidences from a ... http://t.co/DWHH77yyMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Off-Farm Labor Supply and Correlated Shocks: New Theoretical Insights and Evidence from Malawi http://t.co/kvgxjzqFbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: The Han-Minority Achievement Gap, Language, and Returns to Schools in Rural China http://t.co/yxwXr9nig1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: The Impact of Land Mines on Child Health: Evidence from Angola http://t.co/WzsrTfkkV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Labor Market Effects of Intrauterine Exposure to Nutritional Deficiency: Evidence from Administrative Da... http://t.co/DhGS230kcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Child Labor, the Wealth Paradox, and Common Forest Management in Bolivia http://t.co/uEB7xBMjGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Protected areas and deforestation : new results from high resolution panel data http://t.co/VwqNH0SDTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: On the Impact of Weather Variability and Climate Change on Agriculture: Evidence from Ethiopia http://t.co/0WF4ollBPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Resistance to the Regulation of Common Resources in Rural Tunisia http://t.co/K7VO54n6oR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can agricultural households farm their way out of poverty ? http://t.co/oWhw36ixAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The effect of unconditional cash transfers on adult labour supply: A unitary discrete choice model for ... http://t.co/V7zSylvJlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Effects of Protected Areas on Forest Cover Change and Local Communities http://t.co/CO9Tq7yKZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income diversification patterns in rural Sub-Saharan Africa : reassessing the evidence http://t.co/0uUAOW9h3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Choosing to Be Trained: Do Behavioral Traits Matter? http://t.co/RpRu0phLEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can Computers Increase Human Capital in Developing Countries? An Evaluation of Nepal’s One Laptop per C... http://t.co/UxGE9pm3GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Role of Social Networks in Diversification o Income Sources in Rural India http://t.co/8p79QD03FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Food Price Subsidies and Nutrition: Evidence from State Reforms to India's Public Distribution System http://t.co/EiHMfjKX19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Daycare, Durables, and Credit Constraints: Evidence from Rio de Janeiro http://t.co/728ZebYIr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AER: The Impact of the Great Migration on Mortality of African Americans: Evidence from the Deep South http://t.co/bKtuj7i93j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of public spending on health and education of children in India: A Panel data simultaneous equat... http://t.co/TEMxwsSUFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: The Maturity and Payment Schedule of Sovereign Debt -- by Yan Bai, Seon Tae Kim, Gabriel P. Mihalache http://t.co/F8e95jBP8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: The Power of Transparency: Information, Identification Cards and Food Subsidy Programs in Indonesia -- b... http://t.co/Nn3pGBcdaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Evaluating nutrition and health impacts of agricultural innovations http://t.co/OgJbPA62AA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impacts of supermarkets on farm household nutrition in Kenya http://t.co/yMhcioPlcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender Gaps in Completed Fertility http://t.co/YFRJxyjOpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Nutrition Transition and Indicators of Child Malnutrition http://t.co/HA8t1jgmFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can basic entrepreneurship transform the economic lives of the poor? http://t.co/Ye7uG00f9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Sustainability standards, gender, and nutrition among smallholder farmers in Uganda http://t.co/oxGSTCesdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Education, HIV, and Early Fertility: Experimental Evidence from Kenya http://t.co/CFlvJ4BOMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Non-Farm Sector Employment Reduce Rural Poverty and Vulnerability? Evidence from Vietnam and India http://t.co/rkk5qjVDla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Inter-temporal and Spatial Price Dispersion Patterns and the Well-Being of Maize Producers in Southern Tanzania http://t.co/GsixOHXvkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: On the Origins of Dishonesty: From Parents to Children -- by Daniel Houser, John A. List, Marco Piovesan... http://t.co/h9nabDXpEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Nominal GDP Targeting for Developing Countries -- by Pranjul Bhandari, Jeffrey A. Frankel http://t.co/opksUmSOdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Development theory and poverty. A review http://t.co/rU5D0j503H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does food aid disrupt local food market? http://t.co/qR4uOsIxuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Determinants of food production in Sub Saharan Africa: the impact of policy, market access and governance http://t.co/tvPfyDBPIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Social Capital and Disaster Recovery: Evidence from Sichuan Earthquake in 2008 http://t.co/ArTtd5J41g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Food and Nutrient Demand in the context of the Conditional Cash Transfer “Oportunidades” in Mexico http://t.co/sbWkHMLsms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Accuracy and Poverty Impacts of Proxy Means-Tested Transfers: An Empirical Assessment for Bolivia http://t.co/MgMAnN5zEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Promoting handwashing and sanitation : evidence from a large-scale randomized trial in rural Tanzania http://t.co/fHtVQfuTCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Climatic anomalies and conflicts: the role of tenure security on land disputes http://t.co/LTGoWDZNB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: IMPACT OF REMITTANCE ON FOOD SECURITY IN BANGLADESH http://t.co/LrB4DbsDNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of integrated programs for monthly households consumption expenditure: empirical evidence from N... http://t.co/IdWWeVkMqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Education and Human Capital Externalities: Evidence from Colonial Benin http://t.co/07IbtE8amH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Living on the edge : vulnerability to poverty and public transfers in Mexico http://t.co/V2LNb6Clqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Leveling Up: Early Results from a Randomized Evaluation of Post-Secondary Aid http://t.co/XqCCfQ3hLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Index Insurance and Cash Transfers: A Comparative Analysis from Northern Kenya http://t.co/Wf9esh2mcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Migration, Youth, and Agricultural Productivity in Ethiopia http://t.co/ZHky8hG5gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Are There Nutrient-based Poverty Traps? Evidence on Iron Deficiency and Schooling Attainment in Peru http://t.co/oidEM9K1HD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact evaluation helps deliver development projects http://t.co/ZCN1ZTW65E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Improved seeds, fertilizer or natural resource management? Evidence from Kenya’s smallholder maize farmers http://t.co/GXtBLEZqms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Cost-Benefit Analysis of the Cocoa Livelihoods Program in Sub-Saharan Africa http://t.co/cKlJvsmdo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JIE: Intellectual Property Rights, Diasporas, and Domestic Innovation http://t.co/wF6fus6sR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Role of Gender in Agricultural Productivity in the Philippines: The Average Treatment Effect http://t.co/lLlZQLMDj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Technology adoption and the multiple dimensions of food security: the case of maize in Tanzania http://t.co/LZuwQTtHcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural extension in eastern DR Congo: Does Gender Matter? http://t.co/UY172ANYVL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>