<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving a @HoxtonMiniPress talk tonight at old st tube unit 2 in 30 mins! Tix sold out but still some squeeze space http://t.co/S1X2tXOhld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eFrame I politely request you do not use my work w/o permission or fake an (ugly) frame or proliferate the abuse people's work for profit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robevansphoto: Such a lovely book @MartinUsborne printed by @HoxtonMiniPressz thanks for my good friends @isyandleigh for the gift. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ldnmimi: Thanks @125Mag for putting on very inspiring #creativitytalks by @deanchalkley_ @BLOWPR &amp; @MartinUsborne last night! http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TraylerTrayler: @125Mag thank you for the #125live event #creativitytalks with @deanchalkley_ @BLOWPR  and @MartinUsborne #inspired X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @portrait_salon: 2 days to go and then @Photomonitor @MartinUsborne @OandtheFoxes will be looking through all the submissions for Portra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading off to give talk tonight about @HoxtonMiniPress and Indy publishing with @125Mag in Shoreditch. Free tix here http://t.co/59SSJVpkD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet hi marc a friend is planning on buying from labradoodlesDotcodotuk In Wales. Anyway of finding out if they are legit? Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely new popup shop on broadway market @rachelgaledraws http://t.co/9G5TdNhm1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @juhipande: I had the pleasure of meeting @MartinUsborne and learning about his brilliant new book. Take a look.
https://t.co/gg8eFkkuwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StyleTails: Where Hunting Dogs Rest - @MartinUsborne captures the beauty &amp; sadness of the #galgos: http://t.co/K9hgDsusGv http://t.co/s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the latest issue of the very best magazine on dogs and art @fourandsons here http://t.co/sZfU5TPMbc. My work features too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeTransfer seems to be up again! thanks for the quick response. don't envy you having to reply to all these queries!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeTransfer any idea when the site will be up and running again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SPCAINT: RT @mikewhorley2: The Spanish Hunting Dog. A remarkable project by @MartinUsborne http://t.co/ADbGqP1OC3 @SPCAINT @112CarlotaG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorginaParry1 thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missdgw_debbie @kickstarter thanks for helping to spread the word. Really appreciate your support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickygervais I've making a photobook on the plight of Spanish hunting dogs. Please watch/ RT this link if you can http://t.co/zZ5on0qroA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hi @marcthevet hope well? I've just finished photobook on plight of Spanish hunt dogs. Please share this if you http://t.co/zZ5on0qroA thnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeflanagan1 hi Joe. Love this photo. Wondering where / how you sourced it as looking for something similar for the intro to a book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craighansen74 @kickstarter many thanks for your support!!! Can't wait to get the book to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srtasinestesica @pajaritos please take a look at the kickstarter campaign as well! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenneth_gray @Freddythehound please check out the #kickstarter campaign as well to order a copy of the book! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_juliananderson amazing. thank you so much! can't wait to get the book to you this summer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks for sharing @MrMattWilley! Please check out the @kickstarter campaign as well! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @_juliananderson have you seen the @kickstarter as well where you can pre-order the bok? http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thanks Chris! Please take a look at the @kickstarter project as well for the book!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL @designs_photos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Gould PS. Have you seen the @kickstarter project as well where you can pre-order the book?! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @GreyhoundGap for sharing. Please check out the @kickstarter campaign as well where you can pre-order a book! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elgalgoazul thank you!! please help to spread the word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[many thanks for sharing!! @eyemagazine please take a look at the @kickstarter campaign as well http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks for sharing @Edebonneval @Photo12Galerie please check out the @kickstarter campaign as well! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks edward @cotton please check out the @kickstarter project as well http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Usborne launches EAST LONDON book publishing company - http://t.co/EY3rmMJgmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JennyMMackenzie: Dosh saved drinking less #wine ATM, spending some on @Kickstarter. A #photography book http://t.co/UxaU8b0maP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreyhoundGap: Photographer @MartinUsborne has produced a truly stunning body of work about Spanish hunting dogs. Take a look. http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Gould thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalYodel: Check out this new project from @MartinUsborne - looking good.  https://t.co/3cuRI6vBRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photographs from my new book on Spanish Hunting Dogs now on my website http://t.co/SLdpuDUHHC http://t.co/phZAaAkMyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arktweeting: Please can you support this beautiful book by the very talented photographer Martin Usbourne  who became a friend... http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamPowell_ @kickstarter thanks graham! can't wait to get the book out to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonofaBeth @kickstarter MANY THANKS !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sonofaBeth: Please check out @MartinUsborne's The story of the Spanish Hunting Dog @Kickstarter http://t.co/QRioLx09Rc http://t.co/BJKv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @WimberryDesigns please take a look at my new photo book featuring spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeyondBarking thanks for helping spanish hunting dog. love you to check out my photo project on the same subject: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ttkove you might want to check out my new photo project on the plight of the spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Karen @karenkraze thanks for helping to support this cause. you might be interested in my project on galgos here: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sylwiassta @rencontresarles sadly none so far....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thank you @_juliananderson for your pledge and for helping to spread the word. can't wait to get the book out to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@galgoycolibri thanks so much for helping to spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @galgoycolibri: a #spanish #Greyhound or #Galgo
great project from @MartinUsborne 
► (https://t.co/gvpDSxjoSW)
good luck and thank U htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sylwiassta many thanks for your support!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sylwiassta: For all the great photography and dog lovers out there, please go &amp; support @MartinUsborne new book https://t.co/TQMT85Seti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @perroverde_pc please take a look and share my project featuring the plight of the spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks for this @ineedaguide I have a new project currently seeking funding on @kickstarter http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL please take a look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @SamOltman @azambelich hope you will check out my latest series featuring spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @galgoycolibri Please take a look at my new project featuring spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @annamillerart @JuxtapozMag I have a new project currently seeking funding on @kickstarter http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL please take a look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @Christina_Force ! I have a new project currently seeking funding on @kickstarter http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL please take a look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImageWorkshop thanks for this. please check out my latest project on spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @GlobalYodel Please take a look at my latest project featuring spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @Pousta for the feature! hope you will check out my latest project on spanish hunting dogs on @kickstarter now http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeddyCalavera glad you like 'Dogs In Cars'. please check out my new series on spanish hunting dogs here: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsidemag thanks for featuring Dogs in Cars! Hope you will take a look at my new photo project here: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsYutani many thanks for your support!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noticiasperros Hope you will take a look at my new project featuring spanish hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thank you @AnnMariePayne13 for helping to spread the word! I really appreciate your support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Heijman many thanks for your pledge! can't wait to get the book out to you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@studio937 @kickstarter many thanks for your support Troy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lesleyj28: @MartinUsborne Oh god that would break your heart.  Amazing photographs, yet again.  Love the classical theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lesleyj28 thanks so much Lesley. very kind of you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elgalgoazul lovely illustrations!! please take a look at my photo series featuring galgos  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatvalwrites @lesleyj28 @kaytans hi Valerie. Please check out my new series on @kickstarter featuring hunting dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmandoEllo @kickstarter thanks for your support and for helping to spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JULIEELLIS5 thanks for your support Julie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sqezekid @kickstarter thanks Gill!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sqezekid: The story of the Spanish Hunting Dog - a photography book is popular on @Kickstarter! http://t.co/EJWegGZEUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindipatter @kickstarter thanks so much for your pledge and for helping to spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindipatter: I just backed The story of the Spanish Hunting Dog - a photography book on @Kickstarter http://t.co/qfBmlIaX2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@copperpower thank you so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paumac: The story of the Spanish Hunting Dog - a photography book, via @Kickstarter @macpicu  https://t.co/6R11BE8c5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @ComLeonie thanks for the RT. Hope you will check out my work on the plight of spanish hunting dogs here: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOWOWOWnow please help me spread the word about my project on Spanish hunting dogs https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@driftingcamera thanks so much for helping to spread the word Brian! Really appreciate your support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @driftingcamera: Have a look at @MartinUsborne project on Spanish Hunting Dogs https://t.co/Tvhtqngg22 and help if you can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Mirra @Animantium1 you might be interested in my photo series on #galgos https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yvonnethomas14 please take a look at my photo series on the plight of the Spanish hunting dog https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Teresa @copperpower please take a look at my project featuring Spanish Hunting Dogs and their plight. https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogTreatNews please take a look at my project featuring Spanish hunting dogs https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalgoAmigo many thanks for following! Please check out my project on Spanish hunting dogs https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerryGilling that would be amazing. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gwyned: Martin Usborne - The Story of the ... http://t.co/8K0ZJWQ3wE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerryGilling many thanks for sharing Kerry. Really hope to also reach a new audience with this book who aren't aware of the problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoxtonMiniPress: @sophiebiddulph_ ps. Have you seen @MartinUsborne 's new dog project on @kickstarter?  https://t.co/ve9i4za8s8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerryGilling oh no. Sorry about that! Try this one: https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Miranda4Animals: Pls view photography book by @MartinUsborne on the plight of #hunting #dogs in #Spain
https://t.co/V4zTtzAbpe
@rickyge…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianneCMB please take a look and share my new photography book on the plight of the #galgos https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomojuntomo please take a look at my new photography book on the plight of Spanish Hunting Dogs https://t.co/qOzYYIotJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MOARRRmagazine thanks for sharing Dogs In Cars. Hope you will take a look at my new series on Spanish Hunting Dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zimmerlicious as you enjoyed Dogs In Cars I hope you will check out my new series on Spanish Hunting Dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>