<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“Some #training days u don't feel like u have it, but u still do it, which means u got it.” via @ncjack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities. -Janos Arany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In every walk with nature one receives far more than he seeks. ~ John Muir ---&gt; experience your #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless.”
― Mother Teresa via @CharityIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Courage is the discovery that you may not win, and trying when you know you can lose.~ Tom Krause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope that I may always desire more than I can accomplish. Michelangelo #determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fine but am in search for the Doctor who has a solution other than 'Don't run for 60 days' ~ Macon on getting injured” via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope to die in the saddle seat. ~Albert Ellis #run #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love recognizes no barriers. It jumps hurdles, leaps fences, penetrates walls to arrive at it destination full of hope. Maya Angelou  #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The race is not always to the swift... but to those who keep on #running” via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your #fears are not walls, but hurdles. - Millman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One mile at a time" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each of us has a fire in our hearts for something. It's our goal in life to find it #reach #change #passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some #hearts do not need speed training, they were just simply made to give life everything" RQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will #persist without exception. ~Andy Andrews via @chrisvoss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To #live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that’s all.~Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Dreamers are not people disconnected from reality. Dreamers are people fully connected to reality's potential.” via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If everything seems under control, you're just not going fast enough." ~ Mario Andretti #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My 1st thought on my birthday 'One more year until I move into another age group!' I guess I'm a #runner." -- Karen Austin via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without #ambition one starts nothing. Without work one finishes nothing. via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People ask, "But what if #positive thinking doesn't work?" Better to ask, "What if negative thinking does?" via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop dreaming, ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You were never created to reach a certain level and then plateau. You were created to #excel.” via @coacheye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Thankful for our amazing followers! Thanks for sharing your running inspirations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Thankful for my running friends who think what we all do is perfectly normal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Thankful for the freedom to run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have a regimented training plan. I run entirely how I feel. -- Gary Allen via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can either live or watch other people do it for you" RQ #your #choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True friends are special gifts. Take care of them, listen to them, thank them, and never forget to be a #friend back" unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all #possible objections must first be overcome." - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep digging deeper.. you will find what you #passionately pursue for! via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A single act of courage is often the tipping point for something extraordinary." via @AnnTran_  #start #run #finish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone can run 20 miles. It's the next six that count." - Barry Magee #running #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#change #life #live #dream #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Mentoring is your true legacy. It is the greatest inheritance you can give to others. To teach and be taught.”John Wooden, #coaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a bad plan that allows no room for #modification - Publius Syrus via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me strength, reserve control 
Give me heart and give me soul ~ Coldplay #marathon #Ironman #ultra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the streets alight, maybe the trees are gone..I feel my heart start beating to my favourite song ~Coldplay  #run #feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not be afraid of death. Be afraid of the half-lived life!" - Laird Hamilton #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never settle, set your sights high. If you aim your #goals too low, you might just hit them.” via @TheNoteboook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question isn't who's going to let me; the question is who's going to #stop me. ♥ Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a million open doors to opportunity and no waiting. When you do what others won't, the lines are shorter.” via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If good things come to those who wait, then I must have something ridiculously #amazing coming!” via @TheNoteboook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is a  #runner. Some just haven't figured it out.” via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love what you do. Do what you love." - Wayne Dyer  #passion #run #love #makedifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Laziness is nothing more than the habit of resting before you get tired." Jules Renard via @ninagarcia #train #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think you won’t make a difference with one run? You wont make any difference doing nothing via @running_junkie #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is either a daring adventure or nothing." Helen Keller #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the road ahead seems too long, look back to see how far you’ve come. #triathlon #progress via @zumadog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is more fun with other #runners via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Confidence is contagious. So is lack of #confidence." -Vincent T Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we do not take advantage of our  #opportunities, it is our own fault." -- Thomas J. Watson via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace the souls that dare to reach out a hand in kindness ~ unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running helps me believe I can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["open doors let life pleasures in, closed doors do not" unknown #life #risks #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All #marathons are 26 miles 385 yards. Anything longer & race is ultramarathon. Anything less & course was mismeasured~via @higdonmarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that you can't go a day without thinking about. via @DrAndyBaldwin  #life #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every step you take brings you closer to the #finish line.” via @higdonmarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will do this! #run #marathon #ironman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain is the sensation that reminds you that you are still  #alive - R Marchenko via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My philosophy on  #running is, I don't dwell on it, I do it." Joan Benoit Samuelson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who say that I will lose and am finished will have to  #run over my body to beat me.~Said Aouita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Love the life you live. Live the life you love." - Bob Marley  #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the extra mile. It's never crowded. ~Author Unknown  #giveback via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your #possibilities are absolutely endless. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.” via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the biggest accomplishment is not who finishes first, but who #finishes last!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #run on purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a little like wrestling a gorilla. You don't quit when you're tired you quit when the gorilla is tired ~Strauss via @Malibumarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people just exist. Go #live! via @DrAndyBaldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Limitations live only in our minds. But if we use our #imaginations, our possibilities become limitless.” Paolinetti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not running this #race to win, but to give it everything I got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To settle is a choice, you can choose to #run after your dreams”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter our age or condition, there are still untapped  #possibilities within us & new beauty waiting to be born ~Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't feel the finish line, if you don't start #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't just race for time, race for the love of the race, the people you meet along the way, and the strangers & friends you #inspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["None are so old as those who lose their #enthusiasm." ~Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endurance? You’ve only got to get out there and do it. Face up to it: man was meant to #run – Percy Cerutty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if you give, you begin to live." — Dave Matthews Band  #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Take what you can from your dreams, make them as real as anything.” Dave Matthews Band  #choose #life #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world only gets better, if people risk something to make it better via @Kcancer #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2005 I thought that completing an ironman was impossible. I said 'you must be crazy' to do them. Now look at me ~ @chrissiesmiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go after your #dream, no matter how unattainable others think it is." -Linda Mastandrea via @ESPNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemistry can come in many forms #friends #love #passion #runningpartners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The day came when the #risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." ~ Anais Nin via @charityideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do something wonderful, people may imitate it." ~ Albert Schweitzer #quote via @charityideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You cant get much done in life if you only work on the days when you feel good.” ~Jerry West #running #quotes via @running_junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did you know that running uphill, at race pace; will strengthen your legs better than any weight training you could do?" via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To go fast, go alone; to go far, go together. -Warren Buffett via @CharityIdeas #run #endure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big secret in #life is that there is no big secret. Whatever ur #goal, u can get there if u’re willing to work. -Oprah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Coach said we do what's hard, to make us hard, which makes us hard to beat.” via @gosonja #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Choose to persist without exception." - Andy Andrews #run #distance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've grown certain that the root of all #fear is that we've been forced to deny who we are. ~Frances Moore Lappe via @iheartquotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belief is a dream's accelerator and doubt its speed limit. #run #believe (via @AffirmationSpot)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are designed to #run - and we increase our chance of daily #happiness when we do so." via @jeffgalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to believe in yourself when no one else does; that makes you a winner right there." -- Venus Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You will never succeed beyond your wildest #dreams unless you are willing to have some wild dreams.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion is energy. Passion is desire. Passion makes you smiles when nobody is watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I #practice, the luckier I get.  -Jerry Barber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Settle.... So keep looking until you find it. Don’t settle.” Steve Jobs #inspiration]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>