<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RPalacholla Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KimZetter: This thread from the head of Apple is a privacy manifesto for the corporate world that is long overdue. https://t.co/dMUDonq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: Self-care should start with managing your personal digital identity and health information, by @unclenate https://t.co/xBiIsr8lw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavageLucia If you have time, there's a question for you about device data: https://t.co/X4DmSXjfA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samquinones7 Happy to report that @SecAzar also mentioned DREAMLAND today at #MIFHS (a big health tech meeting here in DC). We are thankful for your reporting on both sides of the aisle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comment from @MightyCasey: there's a health data gold rush happening and I want MY cut https://t.co/kiEBMFEIyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ePatientDave @jhoronjeff @fastercures @MilkenInstitute @K_Sheridan1 I was adding to an ongoing list of roles - nobody on the panel was leaving patients and caregivers out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m wearing my #theWalkingGallery jacket here at #MIFHS - if you see me, please say hi https://t.co/Z5BZstTz45 https://t.co/Um6iWM8xkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLizArmy Congratulations! I'll update my post where I cite the 30M as a sign of positive disruption: https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DREAMLAND by @samquinones7 is a book that draws attention when I pull it out on a plane -- in a good, sad, meaningful way. Everyone should read it. https://t.co/RT0ULi5v7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclinical Thanks! Part of it is the Tao of @tedeytan: the conversation is never over (and let's get everyone in on it). Part of it is an anxiety hack: I've shared it so if I forget to say it on stage, it's OK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VentureValkyrie @drnic1 Yes! I have told him about the upgrade I got as a teenager to an extra-long phone cord so I could talk to friends in my room]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drnic1 My kid came home from school talking about how his teacher was explaining the concept of Blockbuster, that you had to physically go to a store to get a movie and the one you want may already be rented. Bizarre to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drnic1 Agree! Here's the tweet I shared right before this one: https://t.co/uTjumUaUOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The tools are out there. The technology for accomplishing this is real. We need to stand together." - the comments are heating up on my data disruption post! https://t.co/2nOlH5O4ma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAOHare Great to see you too! I'm in the middle of a punishing travel schedule but let's connect soon. Would love to share what I'm working on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_HHNYC Thank you! If you have time please post a comment on my blog so others benefit (and it will last longer than a tweet, which will scroll away) https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GANNBAKER: Empower patients and their caregivers with data they can easily understand and help them engage. Thanks @susannahfox for the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raminb: There is a once-a-day pill that prevents HIV by 95%+.

Last weeks CDC study showed only 7% are taking it (of those who could be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louise_schaper Thanks for sharing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisabari I grabbed your awesome thread and included it here: https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @undarkmag: "When a patient with a complex medical history like Michael arrives under my care, it’s like opening a book to page 200 and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReginaHolliday @nbc @ePatientDave Once again you inspire me! https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavageLucia Yes! I quoted you here: https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rotival @Cambia @carinalliance Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BFMack Thank you for having me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patients and caregivers should be part of the disruption conversation (again, obvious, but let's discuss) #MIFHS https://t.co/9lb243ydFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about how the concept of "owning" health data is tied up in the old way of owning the physical file folder, like owning a CD of music. Obvious, but I was struck by the image again. (Photo credit: Penn State on Flickr) https://t.co/NoEfnFQNJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theferocity: Good morning, Twitter. https://t.co/jbjFPz0PPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's conference season! I'm unpacking my bag from #connect2health, repacking for #GLHCSummit18 and looking forward to the Future of Health Summit #MIFHS https://t.co/x92HSHEPbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilbanks @fastercures See you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelDFratkin Thanks! I’m not officially working on LAUNCH but @BradHesse and @dahern1 can help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SueWoods: Pretty cool when @jnd1er and @donberwick @SusannahFox promote #LetPatientsHelp in designing better care in #rural communities…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natalie_Furn: @SusannahFox Every patient I saw in clinic received and email with a list of support groups suited to their needs. I trai…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kimkater: @dahern1 @BradHesse speaking on digital cancer care share helpful resource and data #Connect2Health https://t.co/yvyjE25K4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to #connect2health I grabbed the NYT magazine to read on the T and there's my co-panelist @jnd1er (come to the Innovation Zone at 12noon today!) https://t.co/LbXqW8TOU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UrmimalaSarkar: I'm increasingly convinced that harnessing online communities for peer-to-peer engagement and support is critical to #r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you live with a rare condition like Marfan syndrome, you are vigilant about looking for ways to contribute, including your personal data - @MichaelWeamer of @MarfanFdn #connect2health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caregiving As a researcher I follow you. As a caregiver I learn from you. Thank YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @caregiving: Most likely you know a family caregiver. Family caregivers rate their stress as 4.14 on a scale of 1 to 5 (5 being the most…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preview of our panel about rural cancer care at #Connect2Health with Don Norman (yes, THAT Don Norman) and @donberwick (yes, THAT Don Berwick) https://t.co/73JO97DAZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you part of a health-related group on Facebook? Please take &amp; share this short survey (it's not mine - I'm helping the organizers get the word out) https://t.co/UHekR0MBLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vjrideout @Hopelab @WellBeingTrust @SherryEmery @healthcommphd Love this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rock_Health: How @wildflowerhlth builds product for Medicaid population: 
- Mobile-centric. 85% of patients use smartphones heavily and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another health hashtag to follow today: #HQT2018 

"Patients, front-line physicians, nurses and other providers, researchers and policy makers gathered to discuss quality care in Ontario" - @HQOntario https://t.co/IBP7JPeD8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jasonbobe: #SPM2018 meeting kicked-off by @DrDannySands with an analogy for healthcare as a carwash and how it doesn't really work quit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@healthyjack @wegohealth Hope so! &lt;checks convention center map, re-orients compass, laces up sneakers&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLizArmy Conference season is intense. Best approach: tweet what you know, what you learn, model the sharing economy of ideas (and kick away FOMO - other people can rep our views &amp; data when we're not there!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make the data available to patients and it becomes instantly portable."- Anil Sethi, @ciitizencorp https://t.co/S2nitiZotP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you be at #Connect2Health in Boston? Please come find me in the LAUNCH booth on Friday, where I'll be part of an extraordinary panel: Lisa Klesges, Don Norman, and @donberwick https://t.co/jZCnmpNT6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Imagine a life record — not an EHR or a PHR, but a record of you, and your whole health, from your perspective, not that of your doctor or anyone else." - @Lygeia on what @cariumcares is working on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culture, technology, and policy are lined up for @Lygeia to join a digital health startup - love how she brings us along on her decision-making process: https://t.co/cfh6CqOghK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic! https://t.co/fMptNgoOKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lygeia Excited for you -- and all of us! Looking forward to seeing how @cariumcares grows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OberandOut: This is the most honest and devastating obituary you will ever read about a person who died from opioid addiction: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewresearch: 81% of Democratic voters say gun violence is a very big problem for the country, compared with just 25% of Republican vote…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAOHare Thank you but I will have to follow from afar. I will arrive the next day - Thurs - for Connected Health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burtrosen Sadly no. Obligations here that day but I will be at Connected Health, hanging out in the Innovation Zone w the LAUNCH crew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome line-up of speakers for #SPM2018 includes my shero @NLMdirector https://t.co/W51VvckEOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My desired superpower is to be in two places at once. Until then, I'll follow hashtags. This week: Society for Participatory Medicine conference https://t.co/jcj1Cgqx50 #SPM2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joyclee: “By radically democratizing the tools of medical creation, we seek to enable front line patients and providers to invent answe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hmkyale: And here is the link to the original article. #openaccess @JAMANetworkOpen https://t.co/tYJqSs86yO https://t.co/bayYnwDNWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SavageLucia: Can you imagine an iPhone not making calls to an android? Policy makers can't either. Here are some thoughts on why health…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ciitizencorp: Despite what your hospital may tell you, you have the right to access ALL of your #healthdata. Our own @HealthPrivacy exp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health geeks: Monday reading, in case you missed these stories from last week... (RTs to follow)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip: Buy 2+ @MomsDemand shirts. My friend was visiting from San Diego and I said, "Sure we can hang out today. Put on this shirt and let's go knock on some doors!"#WeekendOfAction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day knocking on doors for @JenniferWexton with @MomsDemand - thanks for hosting this DC volunteer! https://t.co/mvd2bhUKbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ecoppage: So many hardworking, dedicated, enthusiastic @MomsDemand members out canvassing in Loudoun, VA for Gun Sense candidate @Jenni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: Thousands of @MomsDemand volunteers are canvassing, phone banking and writing postcards this weekend. From Anchorage to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DMcK20: Peer support: Patients helping patients while bringing confidence &amp; support during uncertain times. https://t.co/XlMEQQcVoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to create a forum for #PeerHealthAdvice https://t.co/whcTXYx5V7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mooresara: 24 days, 24 days, 24 days! 
Get off the sidelines and get involved in helping to elect #GunSenseCandidates with @MomsDemand…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @abbymnorman: If you can, please get a safe, effective, + free #flushot 💉. Not just for yourself and the people you know, but for those…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting off the weekend right by getting my #flushot - quick &amp; easy thanks to @MinuteClinic in @gloverpark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeattleMamaDoc: 1 week ago I got my flu shot. Feeling great, I did have slight arm soreness for few days. I felt the poke (!)- like man…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @inquisithealth: Our peer-based interventions have shown impressive efficacy. Across all commercial, Medicare, &amp; Medicaid pops currently…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @euanashley: 1/ Quick thread on our paper published yesterday from the Undiagnosed Diseases Network https://t.co/CdKhcx5f7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In many situations, finding just one similar case can be critical in proving the causality of a putative mechanism." - @euanashley and team in @NEJM 

(Translation: #PeerHealthAdvice can help people find answers.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We also encourage and help [Undiagnosed Disease Network] patients to make use of the Internet and social-media platforms to find similar patients." - @euanashley and team in @NEJM #PeerHealthAdvice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like a truffle pig I find #PeerHealthAdvice buried inside articles: https://t.co/0xg9rdBd8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMRAnswers Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GillianA: How beautiful to see so much love and support in this community for @abbymnorman. If you're able, lets see how much more we c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGottliebFDA: My op ed today in the @washingtonpost with @HHS Secretary Alex Azar @SecAzar - "We cannot let e-cigarettes become an on-r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Nataliea @CassiusCCIDog Needed that laugh - thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetSocialHealth @LyndaGMitchell @MayoClinic Thank you! I have a feeling that #MCSMN will be another campfire-type gathering https://t.co/NK7Xs3Db3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @girlsalliance: Today on International #DayoftheGirl, the @ObamaFoundation is proud to launch the #GlobalGirlsAlliance—a program to empo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Patient involvement in clinical research: increasingly mainstream" - love this post by @Katherine_JLA https://t.co/nBqKAvEOXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @euanashley: New from the Undiagnosed Diseases Network! In 20 months, 1519 referred, 601 accepted. Diagnoses made in 35%. Almost 80% of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReginaHolliday: Thank you @NBC for sharing the importance medical records access and interviewing @ePatientDave and I about why we figh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManeeshJuneja @stephen_friend Thank you for tweeting - keep going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @miller7: Our country, our world, is hurting. It's time we realize that not addressing and investing in #mentalhealth is to our detrimen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @miller7: For #WorldMentalHealthDay I am proud to highlight some of the work @WellBeingTrust is doing to advance #mentalhealth. For a sn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HHSGov: If you're in the path of #HurricaneMichael and rely on medications or electric-powered medical equipment, follow these importan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GLHC_HIE: GLHC is thrilled to welcome @SusannahFox as our Keynote Speaker for #GLHCSummit18 - West Michigan, on October 22nd at the Pri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amcunningham Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Init4Health Thank you for sharing it! Kudos to @Katherine_JLA for exploring &amp; capturing these insights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sharing Is Caring: Our 5Q with Anil Sethi" - @TinctureHealth https://t.co/Zt03lXfBNk https://t.co/j1749lI5KL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnandWrites: If you have a long drive coming up this weekend, listen to this podcast I did with @ezraklein. When an interviewer is as s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I joined https://t.co/5Tz52OzDq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnpaulfarmer: Do you live in AZ, AR, FL, GA, IN, KY, LA, MI, MS, NM, NV, OH, PA, TN or TX? Do you know people who do?

If so, TODAY i…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>