<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Customer Service / Dev Tools): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the… https://t.co/frEn1VoxnD https://t.co/at0tG3mYtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Ethernet Solution Architect: Project Description Luxoft UTH ("Under to Hood"), a department of Luxoft’s Automotive Line of Business, is an expert and delivery center for design, implementation and test of embedded architecture and software solutions… https://t.co/qJ0RHCQadm https://t.co/V6AROzdsNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon HQ2 search ignites public hunt for clues https://t.co/qsfSylkpd1 https://t.co/obBshDmYsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Center for Autonomous Vehicle Development – AV Sensor Performance Engineer: Center for Autonomous Vehicle Development – AV Sensor Performance Engineer – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home… https://t.co/zv93yXp1TE https://t.co/vJBzuug58I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SOA Consulant: Oracle SOA Consulant Responsibilities: – Participate in technical planning &amp; requirements gathering phases including Design, code, test, troubleshoot, and document engineering software applications. – Ensuring that technical… https://t.co/HfPKLR2WEr https://t.co/aUaT2lMPAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Specialist: Software Support Specialist =========================== In this role, you will support our mission-critical software applications, modules and underlying infrastructure in a demanding technical environment. This highly… https://t.co/yAIJHNqWrO https://t.co/g9FGIW57kt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber gets a marriage license: Will wedding bells for Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin be ringing soon? https://t.co/UXMbdb6ZJN https://t.co/dTFJSnZwZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Analyst, SAP MM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as well as a… https://t.co/pwSeDE1Khv https://t.co/wk3G9eaMP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loan Officer – Hastings, MI: Job Title: Loan Officer – Hastings, MI Location: Hastings, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: GreenStone Farm Credit Services Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Finance, Banking, Insurance and Real Estate… https://t.co/FqqUymncQU https://t.co/C7woVbgLzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Ethernet Solution Architect: Project Description Luxoft UTH (‘Under to Hood’), a department of Luxoft’s Automotive Line of Business, is an expert and delivery center for design, implementation and test of embedded architecture and software solutions… https://t.co/a2Yu2bXiWo https://t.co/hP4xQMofji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verification Validation Engineer – Data Analyst: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Ref No.: 18-40093 Location: Troy, Michigan Position: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Location: Troy, MI Duration: 12+ months contract to… https://t.co/l980s6LkCV https://t.co/45fs74gYiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst – Data Analytics: At Roush, we fuse technology and engineering to provide product development solutions to customers in a diverse range of industries. Widely recognized for providing engineering, testing, prototype, and manufacturing… https://t.co/qShFyd0RZz https://t.co/K6aj2mRILF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive: Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility –… https://t.co/c1nV0Z7SIT https://t.co/JHGicXMXJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL informatica developer: ETL informatica developer Ref No.: 18-40512 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Role:-ETL developer Location:-Aurbun Hilss,MIJob Description(As per hiring manager) Minimum of 6+ years overall IT experience: including 4+ years of… https://t.co/J3BtseOIun https://t.co/B7nGEAwsMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackbox-QA-Tester: Blackbox QA Tester Populus Group seeks a Blackbox QA Tester at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software quality assurance; provide the following types of testing: manual testing, user acceptance… https://t.co/msn9zDTbB9 https://t.co/bp4DtRfRdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henri Bendel is closing after 123 years https://t.co/L4OC6C3nw9 https://t.co/CW9FT6zG2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Okemos , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Work collaboratively in an Agile team to deliver high quality source code to… https://t.co/V5Grjd9lVV https://t.co/5zG65yTZ0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuomo easily defeats 'Sex and the City' star: New York. Gov. Andrew Cuomo will win the Democratic nomination for a third term, CNN projects, easily defeating a challenge from his left by progressive activist and actress Cynthia Nixon. https://t.co/Qq9sNUc9wD https://t.co/gfLLRhNFTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers] Careers Main… https://t.co/7l9AXvtzSZ https://t.co/pBfpubN197]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seasonal Jobs – Drive with Lyft – $250 Bonus Available: Note: To apply for this job, submit your application by clicking on the Apply Now button on this page What is Employer? Employer matches drivers with passengers who request rides through the… https://t.co/DG2fX50Pr0 https://t.co/bE1TDpafex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 100 people have been plucked from storm surge. More than 430,000 customers are without power.: Storm tracker | Sign up for email alerts | Slow connection? https://t.co/ZIMnwzep7a https://t.co/VyTVfnZLrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Analyst, SAP MM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as well as a… https://t.co/jhUkYJbYWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Ethernet Solution Architect: Project Description Luxoft UTH ("Under to Hood"), a department of Luxoft’s Automotive Line of Business, is an expert and delivery center for design, implementation and test of embedded architecture and software solutions… https://t.co/fJOyomjOVd https://t.co/hn5M9yen7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capacity Management Technical Consultant: Capacity Management Technical Consultant Location: Pontiac, MI Job Code: 3743 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information… https://t.co/axuSnqEWZR https://t.co/PiD07BIgIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats send information concerning Kavanaugh nomination to FBI: Senate Democrats have referred "information concerning the nomination" of Brett Kavanaugh to the FBI, they said Thursday, and called for the Judiciary Committee to delay a vote. https://t.co/GyKY5IcTBl https://t.co/UJlw5kpIVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Safety Technical Support: Job Title: Process Safety Technical Support Location: Wyandotte, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: BASF – We Create Chemistry Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Chemical, Pesticide and Fertilizer Career… https://t.co/XajfUO7yW1 https://t.co/IZQDzGl1TE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's most popular airplane journey revealed: The US may have the world's largest aviation market, but it's Asia that rules the skies when it comes to in-demand air routes. https://t.co/Yjixt1pIvA https://t.co/m2TVi4j0B4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge waves crash onto Outer Banks, NC https://t.co/Rdje6V2Q0A https://t.co/oV9Tigguvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Public Safety Solution: Project Manager, Public Safety Solution ======================================= The Project Manager successfully manages the implementation of Tyler software for new and existing accounts, from the contract… https://t.co/HY1UF5lzIt https://t.co/2KlE3HdBuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be more productive, try skipping the schedule: It can seem like there's never enough time -- not enough for sleep and not enough for play, not enough for cooking and not enough for exercise. https://t.co/oazFcYnNwR https://t.co/FzRxqXJPVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump's hurricane tweets show he can always go lower: On Thursday morning, Donald Trump tweeted: https://t.co/qXG2x9cHVe https://t.co/noiMxJulTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5485 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=JBBRD_INDEED Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted.… https://t.co/mZdr27gujy https://t.co/fAxfqqQjQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software-Developer: Software Developer Populus Group seeks a Software Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to design, develop, modify, and test large-scale, Object-Oriented, multi-tier software applications utilizing the… https://t.co/J81sq7OzpO https://t.co/oLmdVOUNii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How these newlyweds survived a harrowing romance: There's nothing sweet or adorable about the way newlyweds Brittany and Ryan Coleman first met -- no "meet cute" like in rom-com movies or romance novels. https://t.co/49pCcWwIqo https://t.co/pWMggBLo4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These pet-owners aren't evacuating: See why these families are refusing to evacuate ahead of Hurricane Florence despite warnings. https://t.co/gD9MyMwTgg https://t.co/ImqvvC4TDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio Hardware/Software Engineer: VP2 Radio Hardware/Software Engineer, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – English – Italiano – Franais – Espaol – Portugus – – English English en – Italiano Italiano it – Franais Franais fr-ca –… https://t.co/xyFRrbFLnD https://t.co/cjFVEiINxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodward: Nervous breakdown in executive power https://t.co/EBbjN3LmxV https://t.co/JW8xZjQ0R8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Software Engineer to join our public safety product development team. The engineer… https://t.co/K0h4pDVKXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Mill Set-Up Programmer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/TD33X6jdfD https://t.co/GMfL4i0IXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackbox-QA-Tester: Blackbox QA Tester Populus Group seeks a Blackbox QA Tester at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software quality assurance; provide the following types of testing: manual testing, user acceptance… https://t.co/oet67x1W8T https://t.co/D0vj9k6m4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/GUg4sSvwa0 https://t.co/r7xkIagyfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former PM calls US politics a 'global soap opera': Former British Prime Minister Tony Blair calls US politics a "global soap opera" in an interview with CNN's Alisyn Camerota. https://t.co/rxLHEbvrYH https://t.co/VKZlN42NKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Senior Project Manager Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including… https://t.co/l0ZD3Hjm0N https://t.co/5SXoV0WilD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FEMA says funding transferred to ICE won't harm hurricane response: Officials from the Federal Emergency Management Agency insisted Wednesday that the transfer of nearly $10 million of its budget to US Immigration and Customs Enforcement will not affect… https://t.co/bMAVzk4WXi https://t.co/zSiEkDPQXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer: Job opening: Senior Staff Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective links: – 0 Navigation –… https://t.co/Tsi8xIXBqr https://t.co/KdBdaFMxDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No.… https://t.co/LjBCR66SgK https://t.co/TR3lIBO0ZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad Meltzer: Why this astronaut is making news: Neil Armstrong is making news again. Some might think it's because of the upcoming 50th anniversary of the moon landing, or the new Ryan Gosling film "First Man," or especially the fact that Donald Trump… https://t.co/JfemIfR8qS https://t.co/Qv7cVzMMfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: Title PHP Developer ============= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin,… https://t.co/iHRSJPw7kT https://t.co/SSpZdxKkc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager | Position Available | Avomeen – Analytical Sciences – Life Sciences – Product Development ************ MENUMENU – Industries – – – Chemicals &amp; Materials – Life Sciences – Consumer Products – Food &amp; Beverage – – Legal &amp;… https://t.co/q5C8RPbtEJ https://t.co/zxB52vTODf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Lead Developer: Salesforce Lead Developer Ref No.: 18-36407 Location: Troy, Michigan Job Role: Salesforce Lead Developer Location: Troy, MI Contract Role Skills Required: Salesforce Cloud, Service Cloud, Marketing Cloud, Salesforce Communities… https://t.co/B9qmRb4ViJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Global Deployment Manager: SAP Global Deployment Manager, General Motors, Detroit, MI. Define reqmts, dvlp, test, control &amp; manage deployment of Global Enterprise SAP Template incldg customized transactions according to project schedule to meet… https://t.co/T8slZDNMJG https://t.co/rqY0Bwr3dv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europeans are living longer -- but how long will it last?: Europeans are living longer, but health officials say certain risks -- such as obesity and undervaccination -- threaten to slow or even reverse this progress, according to the European health… https://t.co/0fMIi2iRJS https://t.co/CbkDdCdbzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering Jobs –… https://t.co/0pR6zdsRSc https://t.co/zQ5sJ5qLg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software-Developer: Software Developer Populus Group seeks a Software Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to design, develop, modify, and test large-scale, Object-Oriented, multi-tier software applications utilizing the… https://t.co/JTtv8zIg1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job ID : 74265BR Location : US – Michigan – Kalamazoo : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With revenues of… https://t.co/mG2WfgVXTH https://t.co/ho22c54cp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Specialist: Software Support Specialist =========================== In this role, you will support our mission-critical software applications, modules and underlying infrastructure in a demanding technical environment. This highly… https://t.co/gUeChmLZSa https://t.co/8BN0PGKCGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Smart reacts to news that woman who helped kidnap her will be released: The woman who helped kidnap Elizabeth Smart, and was was sentenced to 15 years in federal prison for it, will be released next week. https://t.co/Ql3MSs313U https://t.co/W9U08sMCoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billie Jean King: Serena was 'out of line,' but umpire 'blew it': Speaking about Saturday's controversial US Open final, Billie Jean King, the tennis legend and equal rights advocate, told CNN's Christiane Amanpour that Serena Williams was "out of line,"… https://t.co/vKWIL4u0MF https://t.co/fILwBSl68u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented, passionate Software Engineer to enhance and maintain our Law Enforcement and Fire Records, and… https://t.co/e7h0hGNFfG https://t.co/5byyadqrYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Analyst, Software Developer: Job #72869 Title: Programmer/Analyst, Software Developer Location: Troy, MI Type: Contract to Hire / Direct Hire Responsible For: – Designing, developing, testing, implementing, and maintaining software systems,… https://t.co/C6UzxvwFHF https://t.co/WSyl9viTxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – Engine / Transmission Controls Designs and integrates engine control software. The selected individual will work within DENSO’s Engine / Transmission Controls team. This individual will help integrate DENSO software… https://t.co/7FiOiOWs94 https://t.co/hJuz2ilIyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution =============================== The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with… https://t.co/mIQnDa3BDB https://t.co/XdZwMOxoDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1988 meeting that shaped the world we live in: In August 1988, nine men met in Osama Bin Laden's house in Peshawar, Pakistan, to start a group that would end up playing a dramatic role in shaping the United States of the early 21st century. They… https://t.co/mRlRtfiLNj https://t.co/V9NKcO1TBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IIB Developer: Sr. IIB Developer – TGT – Farmington Hills, MI | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Sr. IIB Developer… https://t.co/u3Y2DSQYnK https://t.co/SPdWNchjPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Ethernet Solution Architect: Project Description Luxoft UTH ("Under to Hood"), a department of Luxoft’s Automotive Line of Business, is an expert and delivery center for design, implementation and test of embedded architecture and software solutions… https://t.co/vE1KYTKv2T https://t.co/ARmPF5F8N8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racer pulls rival's brake at 130 mph: Moto2 rider Romano Fenati has been dropped from the Marinelli Snipers Team after the dangerous incident where he pulled a rival's brake lever mid-race. https://t.co/F5s4I4VvoC https://t.co/HchrGyUWHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw footage offers rare look inside attacks: On September 11, 2001, two filmmakers making a documentary about a New York firefighter found themselves instead documenting the attacks in Lower Manhattan. Right after the first plane crashed, Jules Naudet… https://t.co/FAMIPnIiOb https://t.co/KaYL0UJUTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Hardware Engineer, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program –… https://t.co/elt0bV4Tcc https://t.co/9gorBBnypN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job opening: Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective links: – 0 Navigation – 1 Job openings – 2… https://t.co/pa8ZQaH8qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's approval rating among independents is at its lowest point: President Donald Trump's approval rating has fallen 6 points in the last month and stands at a new low among political independents, according to a new CNN Poll conducted by SSRS. https://t.co/ZoOpE1Me9J https://t.co/NL3OaUBAVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer for In-Vehicle-Infotainment and Instrumentation systems: Company Description Do you want to contribute ideas that will shape the future of mobility? As one of the world’s largest automotive suppliers, Bosch is driving change in the… https://t.co/eMHLr9phU6 https://t.co/KwQeeB7bb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer: Job opening: CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the… https://t.co/qYcWcSSlnE https://t.co/kmzKMwGPOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated Driving Software Engineer: Automated Driving Software Engineer, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – English – Italiano – Franais – Espaol – Portugus – – Japanese – Korean – English English en – Italiano Italiano it –… https://t.co/wAk029tTpk https://t.co/ivhJJYJ691]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMM Programmer/Quality Technician- 2nd or 3rd Shift: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No… https://t.co/aPv0RfArID https://t.co/eTQoS4Ttig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL-Developer: ETL Developer Populus Group seeks an ETL Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide database development in the healthcare industry; develop, design, debug, test, and document ETL process for Date… https://t.co/Sx5WFRsWgd https://t.co/5ZxLDnSU7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/AdpKESKbDj https://t.co/NlhvTzyNeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found out a colleague makes more than you? Here's what to do https://t.co/2oDh4QejKi https://t.co/Uzz5ZO82ds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career… https://t.co/IwnAKa2lyU https://t.co/naqMVFWwje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BUSINESS SYSTEM ANALYST: BUSINESS SYSTEM ANALYST Ref No.: 18-39855 Location: AUBURN HILL, Michigan Minimum of 6 years overall IT experience: including 3+ years of systems analyst and 2+ years of application development experience – Analyze user needs,… https://t.co/CrTZuJZ0VT https://t.co/Cprj6wDr4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pelosi: As long as Trump is here, 'I'm here': Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi, who served as the first woman Speaker of the US House of Representatives, told CNN that while "it's time for new blood" in her party, she also thinks it's a gamble in the current… https://t.co/fRX6WAaQ6E https://t.co/DkBBVObwg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/gYI37cJE4a https://t.co/4n1QMrfUTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right away.Your… https://t.co/wH0o7meLF4 https://t.co/wYQJjNS22a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/yEl0wGiVPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz: Democrats want Texas to be like California, have tofu and dyed hair: Texas Republican Sen. Ted Cruz told supporters at a rally on Saturday that Democrats wanted to make Texas like California and listed off a few things as stereotypical staples of… https://t.co/Jl10e1zFHO https://t.co/kQT2lIZ7qU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Miami Dolphins kneel for National Anthem: Miami Dolphins wide receivers Kenny Stills and Albert Wilson both took a knee near the team bench during the National Anthem ahead of the team's season opener. https://t.co/w7RVKPkdJT https://t.co/ye9c2mlWKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer The Technical Support Engineer is a critical role withing the TGW Lifetime Services (LTS) team, providing highly technical customer service and support, focusing on the TGW Software solutions. This… https://t.co/6WlccQN5pI https://t.co/8MSTvRzXUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Trump in crisis, Pence waits in his shadow: Vice President Mike Pence was among the first to make the "I didn't write it" pledge in the wake of a shocking anonymous essay -- "I Am Part of the Resistance" -- that revealed a conspiracy to save America… https://t.co/tfooQf7kul https://t.co/1lkb1iYWyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching experienced Embedded Software Developer for fast growing team in Detroit area. Team develops innovating testing development environment for one of the Luxoft… https://t.co/y2ojp6rHgO https://t.co/pGJrfv3FKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Robotics Automation: Job Description Project Manager – Robotics Automation ABB Inc., in Auburn Hills, MI is seeking for an Project Manager to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics manufacturer to… https://t.co/D626zFypOm https://t.co/45LHVF3HmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/PskwgcqpCl https://t.co/lXkz62m15w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Analyst: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/eOGq3DTbn2 https://t.co/Ea7xKoY1iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nikki Haley: Combating corruption is about ensuring peace and security: On December 17, 2010, one young man took a stand against corruption, and changed the course of history. Mohamed Bouazizi, a 26 year-old fruit vendor in Tunisia, set himself on fire… https://t.co/qftLpKG9cL https://t.co/ll6d2Q05EU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan war has new senseless face: killing of journalists: The war in Afghanistan has changed in many ways since its start in 2001, when the US attacked the Taliban and drove them out as a result of the 9/11 terror attacks. But now, in addition to… https://t.co/pLwh01UaP6 https://t.co/yAtU7WQ4e0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Test Lead: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking QA Test Lead for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Required Skills/Experience At least 5 years of experience in the below Facets… https://t.co/QFkuNGxPhc https://t.co/o6P8mcm7Bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Oracle Apps DBA: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Michigan Address: Post Date: 14/08/2018 00:08 Req ID: 27047 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/e8kDntIhDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Requirements Engineer: Job opening: System Architect &amp; Requirements Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective… https://t.co/FDCfSZXGFk https://t.co/ASedIibnGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Java Architect Ref No.: 18-36599 Location: FARMINGTON HILLS, New Jersey Key skills required for the job are: Java – Architecting-L3 (Mandatory) Spring-L3 Hibernate-L3 As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of analysts,… https://t.co/AhV53jh8c2 https://t.co/8lmdNjhc1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manual Test Lead: Job ID 2016-1570 # of Openings 1 Category Hidden (8723) Overview SQS-USA is looking for a candidate in Product engineering with knowledge of Part, BOM, CAD tool – catia V5 and its integration with Teamcenter TCIC. This candidate must… https://t.co/EwNpVQ1vux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Solutions Business Analyst II – Detroit, MI: Job Description CEVA Logistics, one of the world’s leading supply chain companies, designs and implements industry leading solutions for large and medium-size national and multinational companies.… https://t.co/R769NvXvQw https://t.co/zSzck3W5Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-39478 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Salesforce Developer job description Job brief The Salesforce Developer will perform hands-on technical implementation, with a focus on delivering functional… https://t.co/CJpXnL2FSQ https://t.co/Ae71e0oWCJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>