<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/gBIlg4jIlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/aiQSsGcup6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/taC1ChBwUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/elOcfXNOLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/90bS5rTI7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/awnpxJwVPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/UUdCDfRgQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/1jnXNA9Sem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/HyuYN7HPPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/nJqpEbwbSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/9T27NpZjTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/8XgJSGBtHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/DElXShDPf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/35pJS7RHbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/x7qK8QCr3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/PujJft1SH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/ICDnxZCPec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/GMRwZU8Z0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/Rxp5u0wLPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/sFp8EkHJtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/F8mdM3O015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/YC7Y9ulupl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/NXwEqc4GHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/TiPLZvt1KU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/9Y44zm4fkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/uRypKr4eUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/KlsdthlMsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/wYWV1F8LwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/dsRCH0bPrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/SI4Bn54kPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/wUQxTrAqX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/n3M8BqrFnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/S1qYHQrv8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/ddPkskgGLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/L6DtsQavCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/eeRcIzv4oO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/gfKpURgext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/sEpU0tzsmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/L1vrvXwIhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/KfcAzLzBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/KfcAzLzBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/cEzqfoapw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/60QhsWHgtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/N54ABEJ8Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/ZM1NCIP8mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dG6T9TvKQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/LmQrOqzRyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/yVX4UQVGxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/Y2P2oT48Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/yjXOESuP5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/Efhr7x2JwQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>