<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Obstacles are those frightening things that become visible when we take our eyes off our goals." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be faithful in small things because it is in them that your strength lies." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Energy and persistence conquer all things." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's easy to make a buck. It's a lot tougher to make a difference." - Tom Brokaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you have the courage to begin, you have the courage to succeed." - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Efficiency is doing things right; effectiveness is doing the right things." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched. They must be felt with the heart." - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you are out to describe the truth, leave elegance to the tailor." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A bird doesn't sing because it has an answer, it sings because it has a song." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never grow a wishbone where your backbone ought to be." - Dorothy Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You may delay, but time will not." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have often regretted my speech, never my silence." - Xenocrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never regret. If it's good, it's wonderful. If it's bad, it's experience." - Victoria Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Getting something done is an accomplishment; getting something done right is an achievement." - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Persistent people begin their success where others end in failure." - Edward Eggleston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is achieved and maintained by those who try and keep trying." - W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Few things are harder to put up with than a good example." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Action is the real measure of intelligence." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man must make his opportunity, as oft as find it." - Francis Bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Realise that true happiness lies within you." - Lucian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am not discouraged, because every wrong attempt discarded is another step forward." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most of the shadows of life are caused by standing in our own sunshine." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember happiness doesn't depend upon who you are or what you have; it depends solely on what you think." - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The achievements of an organisation are the results of the combined effort of each individual." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The wisest men follow their own direction." - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good things happen to those who hustle." -Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change is the law of life and those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every artist was first an amateur." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the midst of winter, I finally learned that there was in me an invincible summer." - Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not go where the path may lead; go instead where there is no path and leave a trail." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes it is not good enough to do your best; you have to do what's required." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are no gains without pains." - Adlai Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only those who will risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go." - T. S. Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't go into business to get rich. Do it to enrich people. It will come back to you." - Stew Leonard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Worry does not empty tomorrow of its sorrow; it empties today of its strength." - Corrie Ten Boom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must take action now that will move you towards your goals. Develop a sense of urgency in your life." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is so fatiguing as the eternal hanging on of an uncompleted task." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Manifest plainness, embrace simplicity. Reduce selfishness, have few desires." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This time, like all times, is a very good one, if we but know what to do with it." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game." - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A wise man is he who does not grieve for the things which he has not, but rejoices for those which he has." - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I had to pick myself up and get on with it, do it all over again, only even better this time." - Sam Walton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Genius is one percent inspiration and ninety-nine percent perspiration." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't worry about the world coming to an end today. It's already tomorrow in Australia." - Charles Schulz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look for a situation in which your work will give you as much happiness as your spare time." - Edward L. Bernays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I figured that if I said it enough, I would convince the world that I really was the greatest." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man is most nearly himself when he achieves the seriousness of a child at play." -  Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things turn out best for the people who make the best out of the way things turn out." - Titus Livius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Courage is knowing what not to fear." - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can't take any credit for our talents. It's how we use them that counts." - Madeleine L'Engle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One of the best uses of your time is to increase your competence in your key result areas." - Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To live a creative life we must lose our fear of being wrong." - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An easy task becomes difficult when you do it with reluctance." - Terence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Become a student of change. It is the only thing that will remain constant." - Anthony J. D'Angelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The purpose of learning is growth, and our minds, unlike our bodies, can continue growing as long as we live." - Mortimer Adler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Behold the turtle. He makes progress only when he sticks his neck out." - James. B. Conant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In spite of your fear, do what you have to do." - Chin-Ning Chu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever the mind can conceive and believe, the mind can achieve." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We become what we habitually contemplate." - George Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only those who dare to fail greatly can ever achieve greatly." - Robert F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By being yourself, you put something wonderful in the world that was not there before." - Edwin Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is a continuation of happenings which are not resisted." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'll go anywhere as long as it's forward." - David Livingstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All misfortune is but a stepping stone to fortune." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Goodness is the only investment that never fails." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The height of your accomplishments will equal the depth of your convictions." - William F. Scholavino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do your work with all your heart and you will succeed." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As a man thinketh in his heart, so is he." - King Solomon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man is what he things about all day long." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can find common ground only by moving to higher ground." - Jim Wallis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thinking too well of people often allows them to be better than they otherwise would." - Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Many of life's failures are people who did not realise how close they were to success when they gave up." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to be all used up when I die." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change is as inexorable as time, yet nothing meets with more resistance." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new." -  Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Today is your day, your mountain is waiting, so get on your way." - Dr Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Follow your honest convictions and be strong." - William Makepeace Thackeray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To achieve greatness, start where you are, use what you have, do what you can." - Arthur Ashe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The young man knows the rules but the old man knows the exceptions." - Oliver Wendell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are two ways to spread happiness; either be the light who shines it or be the mirror who reflects it." - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Magic is believing in yourself, if you can do that, you can make anything happen." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make it your business to know yourself, which is the most difficult lesson in the world." - Miguel De Cervantes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bravery never goes out of fashion." - William Makepeace Thackeray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We may affirm absolutely that nothing great in the world has been accomplished without passion." - Hegel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Time is what we want most, but what we use worst." - William Penn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't turn back the clock. But you can wind it up again." - Bonnie Prudden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The superior man is modest in his speech, but exceeds in his actions." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As a well spent day brings happy sleep, so a life well spent brings happy death." - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By failing to prepare, you are preparing to fail." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the middle of a difficulty lies opportunity." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Better three hours too soon than a minute too late." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They who have conquered doubt and fear have conquered failure." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is contented is rich." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most complicated achievements of thought are possible without the assistance of consciousness." - Sigmund Freud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never let your memories be greater than your dreams." - Doug Ivester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An inconvenience is an unrecognised opportunity." - Confucius]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>