<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager with sharepoint exp: Project manager with sharepoint exp Ref No.: 18-11897 Location: Redmond, Washington Job Description:- Position : Project manager with sharepoint exp Location : Redmond, WA Type : Contract (12 Months) a) Taking… https://t.co/CeJFvlWVq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – SharePoint – Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/vWBQdJmuG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/q95bbtYgU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Feds most… https://t.co/823xQxK22P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Computer Information Systems Operations Analyst 16506: #CyberJobs #CamberIT Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical… https://t.co/Jaiz7wySRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/qtLJb3MoPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16080: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/2Nm7FlVZIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer w/.NET *HOT CONTRACT*: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/12WGrqQH9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Business/ SharePoint Administrator or Web Designer:   Job Description &amp;#8211; Sr Analyst, Business/ SharePoint Administrator or Web Designer (1802245) Job Description  Sr Analyst, Business/ SharePoint Administrator or Web Designer &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/Fci5UNuggC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security – Senior Developer: Supports the development, configuration, testing and deployment and integration of PeopleSoft/OIAM Application Security for the IPPS-A project. Provides support for systems development and database administration… https://t.co/Xifise7Hag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 2: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do.… https://t.co/YBFFcz9Bu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/vIub70WEts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Discover Technologies, LLC provides SharePoint professional services in both the commercial and public sectors to ensure effective delivery of contracted services to customers world-wide. In this role, Discover Technologies… https://t.co/jtzlVduT19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/cTikWtvKpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/Ynkn3UPz5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 2: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do.… https://t.co/enxxTllFbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: NETE Point Developer Rockville, MD 20852 NET ESOLUTIONS CORPORATION (NETE) is a multi-award winning company founded in 1999. NETE is a full service Information Technology (IT) company dedicated to providing value focused consulting… https://t.co/MorWcEWqq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator: Description:Leidos has a career opportunity for a SharePoint Administrator at Nellis AFB in Las Vegas, NV. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; Applicants will support… https://t.co/svSR9qxFF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Business Intelligence Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Antonio, TX Job Type: Strategy &amp;#8211; Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the… https://t.co/30Urppy0vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Technology: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/OxIFtWdoRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Systems Integration Specialist: Overview Love working with people? Passionate about technology? We’re looking for a tech enthusiast with a project manager mindset to join our team as an Integration Specialist II, where you’ll serve as the technical… https://t.co/51y2OkxHxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Contingent Workforce Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications, hosting, cloud and IT services company enabling millions of customers to transform their businesses and their lives through innovative technology solutions.… https://t.co/ZCD9qbIdeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administration and Operations Analyst: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for a Network Administration and Operations Analyst at the DISA… https://t.co/j23KhaiGTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on Ft. Meade, MD. Job… https://t.co/Y8ZfkqLaQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[o365 / SharePoint Collaboration Tools Specialist: Fivesky is looking for a highly motivated and talented Collaboration Tools Specialist to join a fast-paced, dynamic, and challenging environment. The ideal candidate must have a background of working with… https://t.co/PO0ru4Iwqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint BI Developer With Microstrategy: point BI Developer With Microstrategy Wayne, Michigan ID ******* Overview: Our Client is Global leader in IT services, digital and business solutions that partners with its client to simplify, strengthen and… https://t.co/m2LtFyuXoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/Hw0vTcrVNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Apps Support # 180031171: Associate, Apps Support Columbus, OH. Provide app support for ETL apps. Perform management &amp;#38; problem resolution. Master&amp;#8217;s or equivalent in CS, Engineering (any), or related field + 2 years relevant… https://t.co/FaGIaRYshG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/dNHOAWf36e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/9NgqrlkDWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/gP5r7vKmhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#.NET/SharePoint Developer: C#.NET/SharePoint Developer =========================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: DOJ MBIClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Duties and… https://t.co/XtcfCTYs88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/ywXIXg34SL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/NsI3C3zy7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eDiscovery Analyst: Description:The Civil Health Solutions Operation is currently seeking an eDiscovery Analyst to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore. &amp;#160; Leidos is looking for an eDiscovery Analyst to join our eDiscovery team and work… https://t.co/THQ8C6Q3eI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/A8nIKwHQCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAVPower Power Bank Exclusive Deal: A WIRED deal on an outstanding battery pack, Air Force-grade smartwatch, and other gadgets galore. https://t.co/NCnHYDfGZZ https://t.co/MriOSdmFwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/p1FL7KLief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Discover Technologies, LLC provides SharePoint professional services in both the commercial and public sectors to ensure effective delivery of contracted services to customers world-wide. In this role, Discover Technologies… https://t.co/SHTf98Sxn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administration T3: Description:JOB DESCRIPTION:&amp;#160; Leidos is looking for a System Administrator to join our Origin program team. The ideal candidate will serve as an engineer on the Service Operations Team on a classified government contract.… https://t.co/3UJc6ThmPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP Networks, OptumServe – Telecommute: OptumServe provides health services and proven expertise to help federal government agencies tackle some of the biggest challenges in health care. We partner with the Departments of Defense, Health and Human… https://t.co/Q7CPFMgZI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for a Network Operations Analyst at the DISA Headquarters Command Center on Ft. Meade,… https://t.co/wsC6585DjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/LgZGEsQLpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Analyst: Description: The job of the Configuration Management (CM) Analyst is to perform the necessary functions to maintain configuration control of aircraft system hardware and software configurations. PRIMARY… https://t.co/8KlGHAP82D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Watch Officer: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security&amp;#160;Watch Officer&amp;#160;at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on… https://t.co/nmHxtP83k0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Discover Technologies, LLC provides SharePoint professional services in both the commercial and public sectors to ensure effective delivery of contracted services to customers world-wide. In this role, Discover Technologies… https://t.co/gyPGccaqiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on Ft. Meade, MD. Job… https://t.co/2rg75f7lp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/iccgzPbZUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/RFmrba3wL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/l6luAnWdnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/Ga0AdDLOJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/O4bUwO5qPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/K7nWiexd6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: NETE Point Developer Rockville, MD 20852 NET ESOLUTIONS CORPORATION (NETE) is a multi-award winning company founded in 1999. NETE is a full service Information Technology (IT) company dedicated to providing value focused consulting… https://t.co/jyByxa63YP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporting Analyst III: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/rhP3UtUrG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/L676DW1zE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT DEVELOPER LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a talented SharePoint Developer to provide on-site enterprise… https://t.co/28OQCTbIXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer w/.NET *HOT CONTRACT*: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/tgGcmHl1E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/y5FIRAnFok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/Uixk0Fye2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/AGM86ll58n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gently Breathing Somnox Robot Cuddles You to Sleep: The Somnox is a fuzzy, bean-shaped robot that mimics human breathing to help the human holding it fall asleep. https://t.co/vD2KPWagu6 https://t.co/efbhV3hZWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/HuKdMddNM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager with sharepoint exp: Project manager with sharepoint exp Ref No.: 18-11897 Location: Redmond, Washington Job Description:- Position : Project manager with sharepoint exp Location : Redmond, WA Type : Contract (12 Months) a) Taking… https://t.co/6EYKTuWOak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/6h3a72pqso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/hx0LAfulZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager with sharepoint exp: Project manager with sharepoint exp Ref No.: 18-11897 Location: Redmond, Washington Job Description:- Position : Project manager with sharepoint exp Location : Redmond, WA Type : Contract (12 Months) a) Taking… https://t.co/nEDzoGGJdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst Subject Matter Expert 16496: #CyberJobs #CamberIT Technical Solutions Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides… https://t.co/c7rhb8letf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description:The Origin program is in need of an experienced SharePoint developer to design, build, configure, maintain and conceptualize complex and detailed SharePoint sites for our customer on various customer systems.&amp;#160; There… https://t.co/JwpF8jKXVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/KRnixYliYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager JOB SUMMARY The Associate Project Manager supports cross-functional program teams to ensure projects meet objectives and are delivered on-time. Under the general supervision of a Manager or Director,… https://t.co/QDOT0g460F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16080: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/vpOE5wlEJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Engineer V: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/58I4HaClOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Check If Cambridge Analytica Could Access Your Facebook Data: Facebook has released a tool that lets you see if you were caught up in the Cambridge Analytica fiasco—and what other apps know about you know. https://t.co/G5o4wh74sm https://t.co/697bDCXrvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Analyst: Description: The job of the Configuration Management (CM) Analyst is to perform the necessary functions to maintain configuration control of aircraft system hardware and software configurations. PRIMARY… https://t.co/h0fOI98Vdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executive Communications/Tasking Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for an Executive Communications/Tasking Analyst at JFHQ-DODIN at Ft.… https://t.co/Mt5Jr81aMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/dQsIbhKmim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:Leidos has a great opportunity for a Senior Software&amp;#160;Developer at Lackland AFB in San Antonio, TX. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; The selected… https://t.co/0vEfp9LIDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/FAx3uJljlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/53LyIwhCoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect – Chicago, IL: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:12th February 2018Location:Chicago, IllinoisContact Name:Christopher CriscuoloTelephone:Reference:NFI272018CC2 Salary:$100000 &amp;#8211; $120000 per annum SharePoint Architect &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/qdGOnQa3qH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern, Data Analytics/Software Engineer: SSL is a leading provider of commercial satellites and spacecraft systems, with broad expertise to support satellite operators and innovative space related missions. The company designs and manufactures… https://t.co/ip5A0vpPBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/JSVyNfXUar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Watch Officer: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security&amp;#160;Watch Officer&amp;#160;at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on… https://t.co/9xGObnrbBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/V3Wp9j7I1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/3z2wUcYySy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Best Smartphones of 2018: Guide to Android, Samsung Galaxy, iPhone: If you're on the prowl for a new Android, Galaxy, or iPhone, read our full guide to the best smartphones of 2018. https://t.co/CAjEHV5vux https://t.co/OT384iwyzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email System Administrator: Why Join Altec? If you&amp;#8217;re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there&amp;#8217;s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the customer first, and view people as our greatest… https://t.co/1n5R8yfQY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Integration Architect, Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/azj2S045Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/dy7mXQ2f7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CND Analyst (Network Senior) – 16399: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/OpTBLUsHLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused &amp;#8211; employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team… https://t.co/0OUpgtCs0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer w/.NET *HOT CONTRACT*: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/bNGJ2Hxzq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/zSM3mfynXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Systems Administrator: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a talented SharePoint Systems Administrator… https://t.co/ZBYS7zZ1X1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/QBsEn3KuJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / Web Developer: Would you like to perform rewarding work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company? Pragmatics, Inc. is seeking ***** / Web Developer to support a Government customer in Washington, DC. As the .NET / Web… https://t.co/rxmWNSyDME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Manager (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The SE&amp;#38;I Change Manager will establish and manage a structured change management program on behalf of US Census Bureaus (USCB) System Engineering and Integration (SE&amp;#38;I) team. &amp;#160; Responsibilities:… https://t.co/yPJ5veA5ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Great Weekend Tech Deals: Nintendo, Apple, Tile, Eufy, Vive Pro: This weekend, ramble around a VR world of your choosing or smartify your coffeemaker with these tech deals. https://t.co/Ei6qsgaPl0 https://t.co/TqFL0CGz7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Feds most… https://t.co/ogTjtFDXFO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>