<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#nonGMO is often a shortcut for free from #Glyphosate, but it doesn't always work. A new certificate though would https://t.co/XCTuXtgioH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will @SparklingIce's decision to triple its ad spend take it from an impulse purchase to having a spot on the list? https://t.co/gOkTlV9BPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonasF80: From #snacks17: before focusing on new flavors, must protect flank using core flavors or you’ll lose long term velocity game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to SPINS data, sales of dried seaweed snacks are up 10.8% in the yr ending Dec. 25, 2016 @CBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FDAfood: FDA will hold a public meeting on March 9 in Rockville, MD to discuss use of the term "healthy" in food labeling https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl are wary of health claims on snacks @DangFoods warns. @EatProtes says cos should ensure claims are based on srvg not pack size #snacks17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 veg/fruit chip trends: conventional is growing; me-too items abound; coconut/banana chips are up; kale is down, says @DangFoods #snacks17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is cricket protein a flash in pan? Brad Barnhorn thinks it will methodically grow, but doubts it will explode. #snacks17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though nutrition bar space is crowded, it is a good platform for driving consumer trial of new ideas  says Brad Barnhorn at #snacks17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there still room for innovation and new players in the nutrition bar space, @EWatsonWrites asks at #snacks17 debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meat snacks, RTE popcorn, seaweed &amp; puffed snacks growing fast Spins data shows during Snacking Innovation debate #snacks17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it take to thaw sales and innovation in the frozen dessert category? https://t.co/2Xsv8qjZg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What might a partnership between Silicon Valley and Salinas Valley mean for #agriculture? https://t.co/59tezdHg9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is drinking vinegar ready to hit the road as a go-to beverage at gyms, yoga studios and on airplanes? https://t.co/vFswfeCh5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will black packaging help you stand out against colorful competition? Or will it become lost on the shelf? https://t.co/G8niuAgbPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DairyFree frozen #dessert sales are climbing, but is it at the expense of conventional options? https://t.co/2Xsv8qBAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting #agtech needs to be a priority for the new administration, #agriculture stakeholders argue https://t.co/59tezdHg9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If drinking vinegar is ever going to go mainstream, it needs to be convenient https://t.co/vFswfekGe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does your packaging reinforce your brand, or is it just pretty wallpaper? https://t.co/G8niuAgbPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The popularity of bean-based snacks get a bump from consumer desire for #plantbased protein https://t.co/XEvFDkqh5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the top claims helping to drive sales of #icecream? @packaged_facts has the answer: https://t.co/2Xsv8qBAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bean based snacks aren't just for the specialty stores anymore, now they are going mainstream https://t.co/XEvFDkHSul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NutraUSA: Among the "Frances, Canadas, and Japans" of the world, the #USA ranked last...
@ECrawfordwrites
https://t.co/xsu4EA5WDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should be at the top of #Trump's #agriculture agenda? https://t.co/59tezdHg9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four strategies to help drinking vinegar take off in the US https://t.co/vFswfekGe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three questions you should ask when designing packaging to ensure it delivers the best marketing results https://t.co/G8niuAgbPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More ppl are trusting their gut, or vocal influencers, instead of experts when it comes to choosing food &amp; beverages https://t.co/Gmd1Cp7H7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can health claims and #sugar co-exist? https://t.co/uXBcm2zJtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RhythmSuperfood's got the #beet: https://t.co/IfSNjhAkZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaming up with competitors could actually help some companies carve out shelf space in new areas of the store https://t.co/AzcwHFr4Mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPG companies are cashing in on butter-is-back trend: https://t.co/0X90YMzKOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a 20% tariff on imports from Mexico even possible? The CEO of @UFPA101 weighs in: https://t.co/SOno4rD0Zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the long-term potential of algae-based foods in the US? https://t.co/k5r4oUEFv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AgBioWorld: Forget Food Babe, here comes @TheSciBabe profanely debunking dumb food myths! was non-GMO &amp; pro-organic, saw light  https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A case study of how doing-good can be good for business: https://t.co/5gf1LW6xmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what claims are most effective in driving #meat sales: https://t.co/Yq3IurNHPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #souping the new #juicing? @ZupaNoma says yes: https://t.co/acrMJEfwDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 strategies to help improve #foodsafety: https://t.co/VTpWfCi214]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 tips for involving FDA in drafting guidance documents for best practices: https://t.co/Hnd4AmjZRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the unique benefits of selling products online through @amazon: https://t.co/sIiZkFGVf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#honey is the sweetener of choice for 80% of consumers, according to research by @NaturesBakery https://t.co/3bAyaj4apD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meat jerky continues to thrive https://t.co/eacHA6u20N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food banks need donations all year -- not just at the holidays. Find out how @thesoulfullproj is helping https://t.co/STk7GrZRMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plant-based alternatives to animal products want to use terms like milk to help consumers understand their products https://t.co/VwcgvJMxCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 tips for success for #Entrepreneurs and #startups in food and beverage sector from @Chobani CEO https://t.co/aVK9w4CJOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @illyUSA made the Ethisphere most ethical company list 5 yrs running https://t.co/kpGrpCwcby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do #meat and #dairy really deserve their bad rap when it comes to #Sustainability and the environment? https://t.co/tGM4FYbMBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffNedelman I often wonder this too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top leadership changes at @SparklingIce https://t.co/9iyt286y7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KINDSnacks expands its footprint in the #breakfast bar category with #protein option https://t.co/R3Y5C5Wnrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grass fed claims were everywhere at #ExpoWest2017 https://t.co/YoeZxI1JDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A closer look at Trump's nominee to lead FDA https://t.co/9SY1W1dy7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quarter of consumers are eating more spicy foods than a year ago: https://t.co/mU8ZVBHwEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the next hot ingredient in herbal #tea? @Pukkaherbs says at #expowest shatavari is one to watch https://t.co/s38inGKHy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People want thin, crispy &amp; convenient snacks, and @barnana  is happy to provide w new brittle https://t.co/FRqnmGph82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the top trends spotted at #ExpoWest2017 https://t.co/qOB77r4EeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicinal #mushrooms can help cos mt consumer demand for #functional foods. Find out how in this wk's #podcast https://t.co/vuzBF8R7oI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @LonoLife succeed where @CampbellSoupCo failed with the launch of a k-cup based bone broth? https://t.co/PcZMfzIdvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Known primarily for its fig bar, @NaturesBakery is expanding its product line and updating its branding https://t.co/3bAyaj4apD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the value medicinal #mushrooms can add to CPGs in this wk's #podcast w @purelyelizabeth &amp; @ommushrooms https://t.co/vuzBF8zwxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @ConagraBrands is reshaping its portfolio as more premium https://t.co/eacHA6u20N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think one person can't change the world? @thesoulfullproj thinks otherwise: https://t.co/STk7GrIgUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are an #entrepreneur of a #startup and turn your phone off at night, @Chobani CEO wants you to think again https://t.co/aVK9w4CJOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do milk and cars have in common? https://t.co/VwcgvJMxCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[56% of consumers stop buying from brands they believe are unethical https://t.co/kpGrpCeBk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PRE Brands 'obsessively curates' meat for the modern shopper https://t.co/NeWReZfHbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GroceryMakers gives vote of confidence to Trump's nominee to lead FDA https://t.co/9SY1W0VWIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Kevin Klock suddenly step down from his successful position as CEO of @SparklingIce? https://t.co/9iyt286y7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which healthy categories are driving growth in food and beverage? https://t.co/kBAh4qvB2g #ExpoWest2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @KINDSnacks is changing the script for the controversial fruit snack segment https://t.co/zRW2k0TCPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: Shatavari... the adaptogen to watch in the tea market? Checkout this @ECrawfordwrites interview with Pukka #expowest htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making #bonebroth just got easier thanks to the launch of @LonoLife's k-cups https://t.co/PcZMfzqC6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NaturesBakery is making strides towards its goal to be the Little Debbie of the natural snacks market https://t.co/3bAyaj4apD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicken soup is not the only thing that is good for the soul, so is hot cereal if it comes from @thesoulfullproj https://t.co/STk7GrIgUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After taking @SparklingIce from $10M to $650M in sales in 6 yrs, Talking Rain CEO Klock exits suddenly https://t.co/9iyt286y7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PRE Brands' fresh take on selling fresh meat https://t.co/NeWReZfHbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @KashiFoods' certified transitional helps conventional farmers switch to #organic in this wk's #podcast https://t.co/u4YVjV7It4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KINDSnacks enters children's #snack market with fruit snacks made from ... shocker! ... real fruit https://t.co/R3Y5C5EMzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of #natural &amp; #organic are up 7.7% even as the rest of the industry is flat, according to data at #expowest https://t.co/70nZBaztWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bonebroth retail sales are projected to reach $600 mill in next 5 yrs says @kettleandfire which grew 158% in last 6 months #ExpoWest2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The market opportunity for meat #snacks is endless says @ChopsSnacks  says at #ExpoWest2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Chobani founder tells graduating incubator class of #Entrepreneurs not to turn off their cells EVER bc they might miss opp. #ExpoWest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not an #entrepreneur but even I'm inspired by @Chobani founder Ulukaya's advice on growing business @ incubator 1st graduation #ExpoWest https://t.co/RxlH28G2os]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankyiannas: Trendy "artisanal raw milk cheese" (https://t.co/4E6gIP81Bd) causes two deaths.  (https://t.co/iNAw2LMvqy). Promote food…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would recasting debate on eating animal products as an environmental issue vs a welfare issue convince more ppl to be #vegan? #ExpoWest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animal welfare now is where #organic was 30 yrs ago. There is some awakening, certification &amp; a lot of fraud, @WholeFoods CEO says #ExpoWest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research presented by @OrganicTrade at #ExpoWest show organic milk has 56% more omega3s, organic meat has 47% more omega3s than conventional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing #GMO can improve #sustainability one #farmer argues, adding he is 'not the devil w horns' https://t.co/SuqwOZhRiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers want #GMO disclosures on pack &amp; online says @CampbellSoupCo. Find out what else it learned https://t.co/F42O85PwUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EatBobos ditched the fried banana chips in its snack bars for @barnana bits: https://t.co/FNLmLqr4UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is next for the #plantbased #protein trend? @Sunwarrior CEO has a few ideas in this wk's Soup-to-Nuts #podcast https://t.co/KpCShmVAP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EatBobos says its oat bars are the best for snacking w #coffee: https://t.co/FNLmLqIFMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By ditching preservatives, AquaBall water for kids scored distribution in schools https://t.co/UC07KL8rsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grocers fight back against food service https://t.co/5mOHvlt8C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#organic is a shortcut for consumers that must be upheld by manufacturers, regulators and farmers https://t.co/dK4qvblMmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#protein powder has long been grounded in sweets (think chocolate shakes), but @Sunwarrior CEO says savory is next https://t.co/KpCShmVAP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how shifting shopping habits are changing how #beverage companies do business at our free forum March 22 https://t.co/BP0MYCTiGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online discovery platform @Range_Me adds 1,000 new CPGs to help retailers discover next big thing https://t.co/F9x3wGQXom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OrganicTrade says at USDA #agriculture mtg the high import of #organic crops is a missed opportunity for #farmers https://t.co/agA0yQVuLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Snackapade's SmashMallows are successful in part bc they are an intuitive #snack that Americans already understand https://t.co/499cPfD1Po]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>