<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[River Engineer – Birmingham, UK: CH2M are looking for a Senior Civil Engineer to join our established and dynamic River Engineering practice, working on a range of projects that make a difference to local communities and the environment. The successful… https://t.co/oHuxGkmf35 https://t.co/H31RAdoymP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Design Engineer – Singapore: Telecoms Engineer to support the long term growth of Singapore and Asia Pacific mission critical team * Serve as a ICT services design discipline lead for the preparation of the design of ICT, telecommunications and ELV… https://t.co/eKoIy9B4AP https://t.co/jQhmJrDARR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-Mobile agrees to acquire Sprint: (Reuters) - T-Mobile US Inc agreed on Sunday to acquire peer Sprint Corp , in an all-stock deal that will combine the third and fourth largest U.S. wireless carriers and is expected to attract regulatory scrutiny over… https://t.co/pAHRQyjZrz https://t.co/Xxpiz8JNeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic Engineer: Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment opportunities located… https://t.co/xv3EhRBiNm https://t.co/XOGZ7ElW5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP HANA Developer: Hi, Greetings from Macropace Technologies !! Hope you have great day. We have a job opening which might suit you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested for this position. SAP HANA + DS Fulltime… https://t.co/tUL0O62PUR https://t.co/ovAHHGhmeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst/Developer: Systems Analyst/Developer About Horizon: Horizon Behavioral Health has been the premier behavioral healthcare provider in Central Virginia for more than 46 years. In the last year, Horizon provided clinical services to more… https://t.co/D815kRkasq https://t.co/z733yF2l6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecom Italia CEO says his position 'untenable' if Elliott wins board majority: MILAN (Reuters) - Telecom Italia (TIM) CEO Amos Genish said his position at Italy's biggest phone group would be "untenable" if activist fund Elliott manages to win the… https://t.co/yXGmerGUcS https://t.co/Go0HxZao8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent: Seattle, WA Full-time $85k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a full-service general contractor and construction management company. Our team develops… https://t.co/arO3elyk6Z https://t.co/DYBWZZ0F71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4:   Job Description – Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 (18005519) Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 Requisition ID : 18005519 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship… https://t.co/dQ7XnD2jjL https://t.co/nkkYBs1gMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Mission Assurance 5:   Job Description – Engineer Mission Assurance 5 (18008499) Engineer Mission Assurance 5 Requisition ID : 18008499 Location : United States-Maryland-Baltimore US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/2vuedR4EsF https://t.co/Xv4KnZZpVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Data Analyst (Cogo Labs): Quantitative Data Analyst (Cogo Labs) – Cogo Labs CogoLabs AboutPortfolioCareersInternshipsBlog TwitterGitHubGlassdoorFacebookLinkedInYouTubeFlickrInstagram This: Quantitative Data Analyst (Cogo Labs) – on Twitter –… https://t.co/cnx0x0g2vx https://t.co/wWIhiNm3BY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Security System Specialist, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Computer Security System Specialist, Mid Key Role: Provide Cybersecurity and privacy analysis and consulting throughout the security assessment and compliance… https://t.co/cETcPKVBeo https://t.co/maKrj5fguE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Consultant Sr: Position Overview As a Business Analytics Consultant Sr. within PNC’s Corporate and Institutional Banking organization, you will be based in Pittsburgh. You will be joining the Data Analytics and Solutions team, to work… https://t.co/8MHUEfurAt https://t.co/rjc7v0oYdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maturity Analyst Sr: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Maturity Analyst Senior / Senior… https://t.co/zlmd8HeDQ1 https://t.co/SzxbthxfLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage breaks out after Whole Foods partners with Yellow Fever eatery: LOS ANGELES (Reuters) - https://t.co/s2foRsMat5's Whole Foods Market sparked social media outrage after its newest store in its 365 grocery chain partnered with an Asian restaurant… https://t.co/GSBoaiu3oD https://t.co/aKmcXqnqWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle APEX/J2EE Developer: Oracle APEX/J2EE Developer VDH75527973 *Richmond, VA* An experienced and creative Oracle Apex Developer who wants to work collaboratively with others in a fast-paced environment.  Applicant should have In depth knowledge of… https://t.co/j8JmWWcMxY https://t.co/xmdLZxyhZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Lead: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Business Analytics Lead within… https://t.co/2HQ7iXmDtS https://t.co/Q4CVqIRr1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Fitchburg): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/2zXaKJmZvb https://t.co/8WOscqQ0dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Sterling): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/Y5mSZUxWDt https://t.co/H9myt3r4My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Cybersecurity Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/jPZs0oVTAq https://t.co/5PdOMEIs33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU digital tax on corporate turnover faces uphill road: SOFIA (Reuters) - A European Commission plan to tax the digital turnover of large companies drew scepticism on Saturday from the global rule-setting body on tax matters and some EU states, which… https://t.co/FTfirRfjgb https://t.co/fXSo4nPXUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: About the role The Solutions Development team designs, deploys and tests solutions such as web services, applications and enterprise portals to meet client needs. This team works closely with the technical leadership and functional… https://t.co/NhohGt1yM1 https://t.co/YoGwNMb9Sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer – Embedded / Communications Systems: Req ID : 415110BR Job Code/Title : E1464:Systems Engineer Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying… https://t.co/xFKlrP3UWP https://t.co/kD1xkhKijl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineer- Active Top Secret Clearance: Washington, DC Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Support Engineer with an Active Top Secret Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us -Opportunity to work on… https://t.co/xjJSFxqFNz https://t.co/NSfLUxrir3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. keeps China, puts Canada on IP priority watch list: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The Trump administration on Friday labelled 36 countries as inadequately protecting U.S. intellectual property rights, keeping China on a priority watch list and adding… https://t.co/erILw0JBAr https://t.co/27UKGcIyhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems and Software Engineering &amp; Integration Associate Manager: Req ID : 431121BR Job Code/Title : L3034:Mult Func Engrg &amp; Sci Asc Mgr Job Description : This position is for a Systems and Software Engineering &amp; Integration Associate Manager to work in… https://t.co/njaFZwYUtC https://t.co/2ysqO4cfPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruiting Manager-IT-DC: WE GROW OUR OWN FUTURE LEADERS YOU CHOOSE YOUR PATH Why Work For HAYS HAYS celebrates and empowers those employees who made it all possible. A career at HAYS means great people, a great atmosphere, and career advancement… https://t.co/vK1djzCwLO https://t.co/HmKf95BAVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager: Job Description The Senior Program Manager owns every detail of a program’s operation and delivery, and makes life on the program the best it can be. Often the Program Manager will partner closely with an Account Manager/Lead.… https://t.co/ZuurXMRTtN https://t.co/ALYXdvXDpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – US: InfosysFinancial Services Senior Project Manager – US Project Management Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/tjobgFjyGO https://t.co/0gDToWaQdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Associate, Programming-IHM: Job Description JOB: DFS Corporate Services LLC seeks a Senior Associate, Programming in Riverwoods, Illinois to analyze business requirements and create technical design documents and detailed technical specifications… https://t.co/YsXAkrDnLD https://t.co/tWL964H4XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: TECHNOLOGY LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0418MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies; Data Scientist (6597.2558) Work with a team of… https://t.co/OCmoOind66 https://t.co/yCxjqVPJz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's Sergey Brin says company must assume greater responsibility: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc President Sergey Brin said on Friday that technology companies must take greater responsibility for the social impact of their work, his first… https://t.co/6OyoAIxV1T https://t.co/lX5GZCzVI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. keeps China, puts Canada on IP priority watch list: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The Trump administration on Friday labeled 36 countries as inadequately protecting U.S. intellectual property rights, keeping China on a priority watch list and adding Canada… https://t.co/WmrTA3EVqd https://t.co/h9L5uteerC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: The Role: CCRi is looking for a software engineer grounded in the full software lifecycle, from architecture and design through coding, testing, documentation, deployment, and support/maintenance. Our engineers take cutting-edge… https://t.co/1H67GgAVLZ https://t.co/rPFpwny4Kb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony targets eventual repeat of last year's record after flagging profit dip: TOKYO (Reuters) - Sony Corp will work to ensure last year's record profit was not a one-off, its new management said on Friday, after the Japanese conglomerate forecast a dip… https://t.co/fAk9DYiJtW https://t.co/fOe7lOqJQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ASIC &amp; FPGA Design Engineer: Req ID : 398085BR_3 Job Code/Title : E2523:ASIC &amp; FPGA Design Eng Sr Job Description : Digital Processor ASIC/FPGA Designer: The Senior ASIC/FPGA Design Engineer will be working in the RF Center of Excellence (RF CoE).… https://t.co/PiyNoWAleg https://t.co/fNxYDXuDhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – File Transfer Services: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective… https://t.co/9pGqNDmAhc https://t.co/lWFT83srvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Project Analyst – (Development / Regulatory): Job ID 2018-1698 # of Openings 1 Category Information Technology Overview The Business Project Analyst will partner with assigned functional areas to enhance and optimize technology solutions into… https://t.co/3EJfKTjxkV https://t.co/t0vrF2RBnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Financial Services Technology Lead – US Java/J2EE/Web Services Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital… https://t.co/dBSWGCU7n3 https://t.co/QtNsOFUijA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel results beat on demand for data center chips: (Reuters) - Intel Corp beat revenue and profit expectations for the first quarter on Thursday, driven by higher demand for chips from data centers and personal computers. https://t.co/rzxROoXnKf https://t.co/XyyDnkiY7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD WAN Technician III – IP: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/UwdhHwtySW https://t.co/37rfAn6wkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Natick): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/27Ba3ioyhc https://t.co/obRGSCNv8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kitchen and Bathroom Remodel Project Manager: We are seeking a highly motivated and experienced Construction Project Manager to join our well-established business with an excellent reputation for quality. This is a full-time position; standard workdays… https://t.co/b6sDlz05pY https://t.co/HM6L3ahU22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Sales Manager Central Region (Heavy Duty):   Job Description – Regional Sales Manager Central Region (Heavy Duty) (39458) Job Description  Regional Sales Manager Central Region (Heavy Duty)-39458 Description   Position Overview:   This… https://t.co/4RgZG6AavZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Analyst (Job Code CT101): Computer Programmer Analyst, Job Code CT101 (CitiusTech, Princeton, NJ) Analyze and evaluate existing or proposed systems, and devise computer programs, systems and related procedures to process data. Prepare… https://t.co/c5HeAVvXtO https://t.co/GkT54KoV4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program/Project Manager 6: Program/Project Manager 6 Date: Apr 15, 2018 Location: Tualatin, OR, US, 0 Performs non-technical project completion using an internal customer perspective, typically from initiation through delivery. Coordinate… https://t.co/3Sz5P99j8J https://t.co/yVxGj5EYik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Elec flags mobile weakness as chips power record first profit: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics Co Ltd said weakness in the global smartphone market would slow earnings growth, as it reported record quarterly profit on Thursday thanks to… https://t.co/Jkd4nUHJYn https://t.co/ao9l8abyyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer #SSD022818SST &amp; Software Developer #SD042018SST: Multiple openings in Tampa, FL. Travel is not required but candidates must be willing to relocate to unanticipated locations across the country. Sr. Software Developer (job code… https://t.co/VT7tgsf44p https://t.co/qlrPd90hoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Management Advisor: COMPUTER/IT Program Management Advisor needed by STMicroelectronics, Inc. in Santa Clara, CA to author and specify high quality and thorough engineering requirement specifications for optical filters, including performance,… https://t.co/KhMGBIpy36 https://t.co/JPAb9pDx6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Information Officer: Washington County is currently seeking a Chief Information Officer for the Information Technology Department. This is a key management role providing leadership in the strategic planning, development, acquisition,… https://t.co/oh2dgwyuXf https://t.co/MJ9uPC8kYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Apple CEO Cook meet at White House with trade the focus: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Donald Trump met with Apple Inc Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook on Wednesday to discuss trade issues as the technology industry grapples with a U.S. spat… https://t.co/0oBZHuoT8z https://t.co/aRcik94mQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotel key cards, even invalid ones, help hackers break into rooms: HELSINKI (Reuters) - By getting hold of a widely used hotel key card, an attacker could create a master key to unlock any room in the building without leaving a trace, Finnish security… https://t.co/HfmqRaoSgX https://t.co/ZPsqUpoitp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Quant Developer – Capital Markets Application Systems Engineer 1: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed… https://t.co/wGpjonI6cO https://t.co/1P9CIBB4dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Analyst (Professional Services): A global professional services firm seeks a Senior Analyst to join their dynamic team. Responsibilites include the following: Analyzing historical data, modeling fee arrangements, coordinating approvals… https://t.co/Ih46BrkzMk https://t.co/uiAr27oYUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analog Design Engineer – High Speed: Job ID 22341BR Job Posting Title Analog Design Engineer – High Speed Job Description As a global semiconductor company operating in 35 countries, Texas Instruments (TI) is first and foremost a reflection of its… https://t.co/bq7VLK8OXn https://t.co/8n3EOxX4tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Engineering: Job Description Project Manager- Engineering Project Manager- Engineering (******) About UsAt HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are most well-known for adding… https://t.co/Pgq50sBgx2 https://t.co/tDhlCcbLry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: About the position Prudential Customer Office is building a startup culture in the company that is touching 20 Million+ lives, yet thinks agile. A company where talent drives success and your work touches everyone from a 25-year-old to… https://t.co/gtHWKHcqNM https://t.co/D0buNxGzRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's LG Display looks up after posting first loss in 6 years: SEOUL (Reuters) - South Korea's LG Display Co Ltd forecast higher panel shipments and more stable prices in the second quarter as it reported its first operating loss in six years on… https://t.co/ePfwFnShG8 https://t.co/D8uD6qwcua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer COMPUTER/IT Softwr Dvlpr, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Provide scalable &amp; high performing cloud srvcs, incl IaaS, PaaS, &amp; SaaS. Review functional UI reqs, w/ focus on workflow &amp; usability. Implement UI functionality.… https://t.co/e2ujRs5x2A https://t.co/MMpmmA6X0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Production Crew: Love Rock and Roll? Join the Valley’s Best Production Team! Alchemy AVCS seeks Part Time AV Production Crew Experience Preferred Essential Information An audio-visual production specialist assembles, adjusts and operates… https://t.co/joCWbbXo7a https://t.co/mQq1FucQqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Enterprise Application Analyst-ELM Developer: POSITION SUMMARY: The Principal Enterprise Application Analysts role provides high quality expertise to ensure functional business requirements and process issues are resolved using comprehensive… https://t.co/gWiKLf7gFR https://t.co/hI7hfLauyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Join our team of Development Consultants and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Full-Stack development in… https://t.co/dKKYyQQFKm https://t.co/4In2Xakej3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Development Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/13/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2297 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in… https://t.co/RsRAEnD9eM https://t.co/sAUPjAvq2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Application Architect II or III: Basin Electric Power Cooperative Dakota Gasification Company Enterprise Application Architect II or Enterprise Application Architect III • Responsible for the conceptualizing, designing, development,… https://t.co/pNvWDOVD07 https://t.co/bW6xUwwLY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Manager: COMPUTER/IT: ANSYS, Inc. Sr Manager, Software Development to work in San Jose, CA. Driv innovatn in semicondctr dsgn &amp; manuf to enabl smallr devic archictr w/ hghr perfrmnc &amp; enrgy efficncy for pow-rng the smart prdct revolutn. Degree &amp;… https://t.co/K52anuvyar https://t.co/xMPxLm020j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (East Providence): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes… https://t.co/tKPcQe0Exs https://t.co/g1O8KZ9uYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian motorcycle taxi drivers protest low online tariffs: JAKARTA (Reuters) - Hundreds of Indonesian motorcycle taxi drivers working for start-ups Grab and Go-Jek called on Monday for an end to low online fares and demanded tighter regulation of… https://t.co/2P8xi9zBiQ https://t.co/abflrqLh6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Business Systems Consultant: Job Description We are seeking to hire a senior analyst with CRM experience for Customer Relationship View (CRV) initiative as part of Branch, ATM and Enterprise Business Technology Services group. CRV is a CRM platform… https://t.co/7mFFV3fgeK https://t.co/SftiDAU4ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Fairfield, CT Full-time $120k – $200k Posted Today Solution Architect – Presales Engineer, Infrastructure, Datacenter, System Architecture, Storage The ideal location for candidate will be in Fairfield County with a territory covering… https://t.co/4MF9piZl81 https://t.co/5badXaiwwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Terrorism Specialist: 30267BR Anti-Terrorism Specialist Springfield Virginia United States Supports Agency planning against Anti-Terrorism (AT) to include risk management, planning, training and exercise, resource application, and program reviews.… https://t.co/S1egp130ty https://t.co/fR4SoadykG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix): 109879BR Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix) MA – Woburn 109879BR Job Description: An opportunity exists for a Senior Software Engineer I within the Missile Defense Radar Software Department in… https://t.co/awiqGhcQg4 https://t.co/G50ABl3zwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Director of Space Based Operations, Sustainment and Logistics: Req ID : 429644BR Job Code/Title : L3047B:Program Management Dir Job Description : This critical position will lead the Operations, Sustainment and Logistics (OSL) Mission Area for… https://t.co/rx4H3IppXk https://t.co/oD6owNzyFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China fund managers slash ZTE valuation after U.S. sanction: SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Chinese funds have slashed valuations of ZTE Corp after the United States banned American companies from selling components to the telecoms equipment maker for seven years,… https://t.co/Ocinzg2ukx https://t.co/HElOeRNf6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist 16422: Are you passionate about data? We are searching for a team member who can transform how we do business simply by understanding data. Our company, Huntington Ingalls Industries (Camber Corporation), is best in class for providing… https://t.co/qxrNJiSILS https://t.co/xqlTfth3bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Staff Software Engineer (System Control): Responsible to develop software for advanced E-beam inspection tools and solutions. Utilize software architecture, OOD, motion and electron optic system control knowledge to design, implement and optimize… https://t.co/uOdsnLKvno https://t.co/OyJE39VAVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon to double down on groceries; foray deeper into fresh produce in India: BENGALURU (Reuters) - https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc expects groceries and household products to account for over half of its business in India in the next five years, as it moves… https://t.co/EiEP2acT5y https://t.co/kHRYVc20Vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Application Security Analyst: * Primary Location: United States,Kentucky,Florence * Education: High School Diploma/GED * Job Function: Technology * Schedule: Full-time * Shift: Day Job * Employee Status: Regular * Travel Time: Yes, 10 % of the Time… https://t.co/NDwioPVefG https://t.co/IDGltS8otb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Norwell): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/zB3gcG5zcg https://t.co/zAZMNhpZ9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Analyst Integration (full-time): Job Description req2339 Sr Systems Analyst Integration (full-time) Full Time, FTE: 1 Administration Center Green Valley, CA This position reports to the Director of Clinical Systems and is responsible for the… https://t.co/bRAvVVvpJR https://t.co/aqcYAtw6ba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Safety Manager (ISO25119/ISO26262): Functional Safety Manager (ISO25119/ISO26262) Location: US – CO, Westminster ID: 9223 Time Type: Regular # of Openings: 0 Description Trimble is seeking a Functional Safety Manager (ISO25119/ISO26262) to be… https://t.co/P9TyuQ6JWq https://t.co/vWC10fGOSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Architect Manager: job detailsJob Number:1213036Job Title:Network Architect ManagerJob Type:Full-timeLocation:New York, NYHours:Post Date:Jan 8 2018Salary:$160K-$170KDetailed Job Description: Team Lead for Network Architecture. Must be hands on.… https://t.co/4yLQ0HfS49 https://t.co/DWRY7NrcYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Fluidic Device Product Engineer, Sequencing: At Roche, 94,000 people across 100 countries are pushing back the frontiers of healthcare. Working together, we’ve become one of the world’s leading research-focused healthcare groups. Our success is… https://t.co/QETu2Mk4R5 https://t.co/StwdUBFxCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IP Litigation Counsel: IP Litigation Counsel Job Number: 113690764 Santa Clara Valley, California, United States Posted: Apr. 16, 2018 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job Summary We are looking for a patent litigator with 7-15 years of experience, great judgment and… https://t.co/x1UesEQqMm https://t.co/HgqM9pPVgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba eyes cancelling chip unit sale if no China approval by May: media: TOKYO (Reuters) - Japan's Toshiba Corp has decided it will cancel the planned $18.6 billion sale of its memory chip unit if it does not get approval from China's anti-monopoly… https://t.co/M3TfEzKz9f https://t.co/bsQGdynibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect, Informatics: Job Overview Informatics at Covance is a high profile, high impact team that is charged with creating world-class, innovative data-driven solutions to improve the speed, cost and quality of drug development and help… https://t.co/yRhKLq13u2 https://t.co/1c2Seo4enb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: We are looking for a qualified Digital project manager to join our team. You will be responsible for the day-to-day management and smooth operation of various digital projects, including site launches, online tools, web… https://t.co/y0p81zVLzl https://t.co/oHNNa5RoyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber thieves claim to hit two big Canadian banks: TORONTO (Reuters) - Bank of Montreal and Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce said on Monday that cyber attackers may have stolen the data of potentially tens of thousands of customers in what could be the… https://t.co/KnOsAMujfi https://t.co/GchtSDK1s3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India Uber president to head Asia Pacific operations: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - Uber's India President Amit Jain has been promoted to head of the global ride-hailing firm's Asia Pacific operations, which includes Australia, New Zealand, Japan, Hong Kong and… https://t.co/sNPMvkmyZW https://t.co/5Z3R801qGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: – Associate Software Engineer – BLOG – COMMUNITY – LOGIN – Solutions – Customers – Platform – Apps – Resources – About – Get demo Associate Software Engineer Development San Francisco, United States Apply now Description… https://t.co/tzZkFJ3DjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/kTIestA7e1 https://t.co/wqaEixpJrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/MeI7ggbO2j https://t.co/a9yWKMT9vE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/JPr0lgIfF0 https://t.co/cWcDTKMb4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France, Germany push for EU funding for technology start-ups: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - France and Germany are pushing for an EU-wide initiative to fund innovation and research in tech start-up projects across the bloc so that Europe can compete more… https://t.co/h279lgbvph https://t.co/e48lCb1oJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/eij5mMw5Hm https://t.co/1t7t8ARHYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/RAulpKHePv https://t.co/GStv8pj3Fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/q02EPziGBu https://t.co/yIdjIuEvtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[devops engineer: Location: San Francisco, CA- United States Job ID: 18WD26949 Position Overview To maintain our leadership position in a fast moving, ever-changing, competitive environment, Autodesk’s engineering organization is going through a number of… https://t.co/uStJCNQWfa https://t.co/Lsm4QH8o5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vehicle Performance Engineer Job: Requisition Summary The Technical Center is seeking a Vehicle Performance Engineer to conduct heavy truck performance evaluations and validation testing. The successful candidate will possess a fundamental knowledge of… https://t.co/jhG9rIxYZv https://t.co/dUV9f91Zm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent chairman pledges to advance China chip industry after ZTE 'wake-up' call: reports: HONG KONG (Reuters) - Tencent Holdings chairman pledged to advance China's semiconductor industry, saying the blow to ZTE Corp from Washington's ban on U.S. firms… https://t.co/qBwprY23FV https://t.co/Pb4K6t3Alg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Architect – Android Technology Planning: Senior Architect – Android Technology Planning Ref No.: 18-20911 Location: Santa Clara, California Description: Senior Architect – Android Technology Planning Huaweiis a leading global information and… https://t.co/UMbF6smidm https://t.co/K5zUurDB3L]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>