<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods struggles but makes the cut 13 shots off the lead https://t.co/3sBEpLRcwK https://t.co/Aats0qxFRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/gonB8liP9e https://t.co/vNmz2KyzNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/NzVqavykUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/4mdGutG2XN https://t.co/J9nb24dBDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/vVu0ZRWGNS https://t.co/I1Fk2BSsyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/JG5oaZlkAt https://t.co/UNMIdYcYud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Information Security Compliance Specialist: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/2TCZ8HyTg2 https://t.co/b5EZ7oii29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/Fybcu2icwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compliance Senior Specialist: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/arrUtCwagc https://t.co/Ugvl3vAFLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/1uljQq1tIA https://t.co/jXUxBasd6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds Seize https://t.co/ytJh3FFrrn, Site Linked to Sex Trafficking: A notice on the website of https://t.co/ytJh3FFrrn said it had been seized by multiple federal agencies. The site was at the center of a debate over amending a bedrock internet law. https://t.co/AeDUAFcCZd https://t.co/lWVvSHglsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/LMBSISSxvz https://t.co/Ro8gL9bSeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/IEtQjjGjvX https://t.co/qTYXtR66pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Manager (Veracode Support): PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/ocThBLllF4 https://t.co/uNpnHMrQmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adviser played key role in pursuit of possible Clinton emails from dark web before election: A Donald Trump foreign policy adviser pushed government agencies to review materials from the dark web in the summer of 2016 that he thought were Hillary… https://t.co/eVpaSLQ2BG https://t.co/hvzB0gDIjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/ytKTF3DrHr https://t.co/SsFb4r2olv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/Apuk42ze5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/d7PC8VOhjZ https://t.co/7tdlGpIgnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identity Management Program Lead: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/2X21QHHPFd https://t.co/etJwyRZyeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Imposes New Restrictions on Ads and Popular Pages: The social network will now require ads about political issues, not just elections, to be verified. It will also begin vetting Pages with large numbers of followers. https://t.co/L5jlJBE8uq https://t.co/O8LucHl8TC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Android Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for an Android developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. The… https://t.co/4PeyGO9boF https://t.co/GjmqYsxaTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Service Analyst – Hygiene: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/cAWOrTvKb9 https://t.co/OaIw8X786V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/kAknz9i0Oi https://t.co/AToOILoUVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Woman Got Facebook to Police Opioid Sales On Instagram: After years of media reports and complaints, Instagram recently moved to restrict hashtags related to opioids and deleted some accounts. https://t.co/uVuGjS1jTk https://t.co/9JduLCCGqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Service Analyst – Logging: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/nJ4ryd1i0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/uc8dICGluc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/GiKPCwWCcu https://t.co/ZHDbBaCzRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/2RIazEJX2q https://t.co/uXyxMd9aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/o2BdxBP22V https://t.co/n2t72SwNvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transformation Project Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/aO1f6aeSNI https://t.co/kla6O7USfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/UJDaTYssOJ https://t.co/QpZdiqCYZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple gets $37M in talcum powder case: A jury in Middlesex County, New Jersey, awarded $30 million in compensatory damages on Thursday to a man who got cancer after decades of using talcum powder. His wife was awarded $7 million in damages. https://t.co/Zj6ueG8spY https://t.co/gcLIVmOgqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/TQnpUMemKB https://t.co/EbEew2DvpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/CGPdQa9cJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/0SCugtlozT https://t.co/O5Dtt1pNi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/WamjXQCkkX https://t.co/oiIRmFEO9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/X7aP0mijnQ https://t.co/zyBSlfCiHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/eDHoWavxGN https://t.co/uPEvWMoL9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/fkQVlygML7 https://t.co/zBKpXNjCxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/wu3mR0Ogtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/YLBGzYEMs7 https://t.co/95BwJg9Jmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/I39PhJbkMt https://t.co/u6DuFe5NkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/zdSH4iRUn8 https://t.co/tL6wUBkxEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/ojoIXE4e8t https://t.co/V3pXEKueZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/MkrFfnaUVy https://t.co/FygMLU4M6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Putin Trump's top adviser on Syria? https://t.co/hqeks41ESP https://t.co/Ie8FWAImvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/7ingBprhek https://t.co/9Elu7pVYkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/oZFTRvH54J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/LVkrxV0vtP https://t.co/5dHKCjOjHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/a5Bu2ueVHn https://t.co/rLh69X5XiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Turns to Users to Improve Its AI Chops Outside the US: A Google team created an app that asks users in India and elsewhere to identify household objects and public places, to boost the accuracy of its image-recognition services. https://t.co/8Qq9St2kaq https://t.co/YoRt27cN2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/UiU32UTR8w https://t.co/VnnN5kcnbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/ZrjSjQ2v9V https://t.co/JwnwYDPyUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg Should Answer This One Question When He Testifies Before Congress: Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg has finally agreed to appear before Congress—which means he might finally get at the real issue behind Facebook's woes. https://t.co/ubS54SC5Uh https://t.co/9SbJIwh2Fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/ZsD8ufm0iC https://t.co/EZyebMLsfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/C16XYorwXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/mdUU5dz88b https://t.co/8qO3we5hof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/LRrLLUTWw0 https://t.co/ExC80iNYEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Google Executive Opens a School for AI, With China's Help: Kai-Fu Lee, head of the investment firm Sinovation Ventures, is training Chinese professors to teach artificial-intelligence techniques. https://t.co/Xp3O6SbUrc https://t.co/QoPnBldNxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Application Developer Detroit, MI Skills Required: * Angular 1.5 * HTML5 * CSS 3 * Content management systems – Adobe CMS/ AEM * Spring MVC * SSO * Soap Webservices, Rest Webservices * SQL- Requirements Java/J2EE, Angular,… https://t.co/SdG1OzkcC0 https://t.co/ymWPg42XwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/y6cdeCyA4c https://t.co/RlZA1uxt6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Android Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for an Android developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. The… https://t.co/2A4yvt4ELl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY officers kill black man after mistaking metal pipe for gun: New York City police officers shot and killed a black man after he pointed what they believed was a gun at them, but turned out to be a metal pipe, authorities said. https://t.co/iOvfwm5UgU https://t.co/2jUuAiSfE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/CJgd7KZxEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/Ka0ngDn6wP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/ME8FI5M84K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/xHg2FZzmOu https://t.co/Bd91XMUFkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/GfSZBZZcqf https://t.co/MdCjgyrIWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/KdIfEOyanv https://t.co/jkslvi4Axe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/6T9oEYoDX3 https://t.co/v0E9ohIn6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/n30IMCx9el https://t.co/5tyJJAsWzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/xKQ54wiOyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/EdmRAuoSHU https://t.co/nQS9Mgk121]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Application Developer Detroit, MI Skills Required: * Angular 1.5 * HTML5 * CSS 3 * Content management systems – Adobe CMS/ AEM * Spring MVC * SSO * Soap Webservices, Rest Webservices * SQL- Requirements Java/J2EE, Angular,… https://t.co/YKWIrATFzg https://t.co/BHEU641rXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/AG4dQf2zb8 https://t.co/7I3Od0Bz8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/7WEWOhQr6T https://t.co/usbeZrOBto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA head calls for mandatory education to fight opioid crisis: The head of the US Food and Drug Administration, Dr. Scott Gottlieb, believes that the nation's physicians should undergo mandatory training on pain management and the prescribing of opioid… https://t.co/XFnTHtL4Tv https://t.co/mRMO7grRgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Exposed 87 Million Users to Cambridge Analytica: Racebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg says the fixes to Facebook's data-sharing woes will be a "multi-year" process. https://t.co/h65eGWD9dz https://t.co/SPr7nKnG1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/cCLgnzHqvV https://t.co/aZCPVvyxgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/DbHRVGsO96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/M3KccMjrKZ https://t.co/RAIVQA5MVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/GW3Usr0lqy https://t.co/zzYYsWvnSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Say YouTube Policies Motivated Shooter Nasim Aghdam: San Bruno police identified the attacker as Nasim Najafi Aghdam, a woman in her late 30s from San Diego. https://t.co/V3nOLVyRtt https://t.co/AuSgz2HvNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/0tDaXCXyLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/s6vie3wsNw https://t.co/6iHSYBR59i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/RUlJdxIPVI https://t.co/UntvDNZHOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/lF3VXng93X https://t.co/CzcM6tkZgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/WMQKFVVloY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/Zf7Y1guoL5 https://t.co/zE5vdXPDk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/YsbZA6EF1I https://t.co/FeR6B12qhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cryptocurrency Industry Might Actually Benefit From an Ad Ban: Google, Facebook, Twitter, Reddit, Snap, and MailChimp have all decided to shut out cryptocurrency advertising, but some blockchain enthusiasts say that might not be such a bad thing. https://t.co/4hJxjuHZ2D https://t.co/tHWEaojvzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/au3zh5bK8p https://t.co/7rKfhpS7Je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/2PWrqIPZPY https://t.co/0JOK5jLWcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/24xVW9ECKa https://t.co/Ilz2KKmKIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow set to tumble after China announces new tariffs https://t.co/EQZ1iVYpv3 https://t.co/iJOUOsaJrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/OYt5OnuLDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/jp7D3x0HrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/yAxXCNdvNP https://t.co/j99Xr18ktV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/1DlsPoJUAH https://t.co/M65Lu5HCrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/nzSY0OwnAI https://t.co/gG99oIcqhG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>