<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/oOWrgpVpWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/jofbp8oIB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/N47ARItWp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/zSUmaw7woa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/Y8j4gRu890]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/QeVAr6E0Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/xxWBHHJIo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/n3r8HHNCMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/YQCdzdVIJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/BBlPDnrVhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/vrhZqwNXxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/ACJ5S7xrFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/oloe35cpGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/u2PW8ZoFTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/rhzb6CTHdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/tCoXJAKvih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/ghzprF1P2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/dRCp8apJ0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/9wXsgblXyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/hONTemX3Fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/hlrrgEBJQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/n6osg3ELfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/8BDqe3fqbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/iGp2dTwypN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/ZArTVPdmbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/gxHnplqmBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/ihdwqULyeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has great marketing, among the best PR and marketing in the world. - Ron Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/R2J4AXCNLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/dXcP3Xt5Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/hSqFofcFyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/B7SFaHHVTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/gmSBwBQiyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/gZifDHKh7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/uPJSAZTtCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/lLA3cyEYfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/PIxjBgbH5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/rreIgJj3UR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/D97UoebiLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't satisfied just to earn a good living. I was looking to make a statement. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/cPuDwlAvmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/DuDh0P6TbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/YUf4ero3YP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/1VQHZwgKlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/XxWKENgbYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/z2L59Gg4mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/IyVJU0Uygp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/ACJ5S7xrFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/WROaxuobly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/3NnP5Bnwf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/UDy6BBWJO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/3BaaMt4ns6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>