<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YuriEngelhardt: Nice and thorough catalogue of datavis types:
https://t.co/2pfLUuodo7
(Reminiscent of the admirable https://t.co/ORjRh7…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakerkm45 @mattyglesias This and similar work by @illuminator99 have targeted Trump properties, I believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricLiptonNYT: 1) Over 1,900 items have been removed from EPA's website. Environmental Defense Fund FOIAed them. Here they are, reborn,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joseiswriting: Dear Well-Meaning White People Who Want Nothing To Do With Alt-Right:

We, people of color, cannot carry this burden.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hannah_recht: Couldn't find any tools to pull the Census data I needed, so I built a package myself. Now it has over 1000 downloads. #W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannah_recht I love this. You're the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JedKolko: Alright, time for a summertime Friday discussion that &lt;5 people care about. 

What are your biggest current U.S. geography-da…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Elijah_Meeks: Thanks to stupid @visualisingdata's stupid catalog of stupid visualization methods I will never feel the sun on my face a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ILSecOfState So, thanks @ILSecOfState. Feeling really welcome. Almost feels like the DMV is a revenue oriented mechanism, rather than a city service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ILSecOfState Two for "Improper Placement of Sticker"- fines easier avoided with a warning, or if anyone mentioned sticker placement during my 3hrs at DMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a Chicago City Sticker for one week and I have three parking tickets. One obviously erroneous at a meter I paid for. @ILSecOfState]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenancona Second City for comedy, Kingston Mines for jazz, Half Acre for beer, but hey, I just got here. Pretty cool city though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sxsw He's @urbaninstitute's Chief Methodologist, @AAPOR's former president, @AmstatNews's former vice president, and an all-around awesome human.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for Rob Santos's @sxsw Panel on #BigData &amp; Survey Methods: https://t.co/TtKdREK1M5 #datascience #analytics #policy https://t.co/teefhPZ0Pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoCDO @chihacknight Without intending to throw shade at anyone in particular, this is absolutely not the case in many cities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very impressed w/ @ChicagoCDO's collaboration w/ the Hacker Community &amp; commitment to #opensource. I'm new, but loud applause @chihacknight. https://t.co/QPZQAtUEHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UChicagoCAPP: Fascinating: @Geneorama presenting on @ChicagoCDO Office's West Nike Virus prediction work. Mixed effects GLM worked best…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chihacknight That was in sample accuracy! The 65% was out of sample predictive accuracy. Very tough problem though, so understandable percentage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler @hannah_recht This was super useful, and you were exactly as prepared for this question as @hannah_recht said you would be. Many thanks! Hope NYU is great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler @hannah_recht Right ok - so there's a ton of variance between jurisdictions, makes sense. Anything specific to one important dataset?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler Something that might have disastrous consequences for an analyst who didn't know it would be great. BTW @hannah_recht nominated you for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler Like, something specific to justice policy research/data, but you'd know it if you were an expert in the field and worked with that data]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler I'm looking for an example of a fact that you would NEED to know to properly examine a (any) justice policy dataset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbieler Damnit Sam - I have a question for you but apparently you don't follow me so I've gotta do this nonsense w/o direct messenger...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HarrisPolicy: Join the dynamic team at Harris! We're currently looking for a Comms. Coordinator. Find listing at https://t.co/dtNjL8jsI…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jschwabish @flowingdata Which is nice, since it's based in #ggplot2, so @BenChartoff's / @awunderground's Urban Institute theme works: https://t.co/FkDysaJjlo https://t.co/9BXAvoFagD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jschwabish @flowingdata And there's also the #rstats waffle package: https://t.co/yCgKjzo7Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jschwabish @flowingdata I'm pretty sure he did, based on this lovely tutorial: https://t.co/Bdz2kQs0wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DataLensDC: please always depict DC like this in senate vote maps https://t.co/qMJgHPdivs https://t.co/bcW20qbCoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I approve of this use of #ICYMI https://t.co/yGT50LMz7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dataandme: 🎉 useful cheat sheet: "Basic Regular Expressions in R" by Ian Kopacka https://t.co/q2AlmRjOnp #RegEx #rstats #SoDS17 https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not great reporting by @NPR. Ed/legal experts don't expect this to affect 501c3 and govt employees (like teachers and officers). https://t.co/ZftZXyezA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good one. Though I still think we need a different acronym to distinguish from Latent Dirchlet Allocation. Supervised sLDA vs. unsup uLDA? https://t.co/vBwdH2MTkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An oversimplification, but I was considering the typologies of math necessary for depth in #DataScience, &amp; what they get you. Thoughts? https://t.co/gz26AzX9XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digiphile @WorldBank Do you know if the World Bank Innovation Labs is still going? Their work looked fantastic, see this page: https://t.co/reo3Rc0yK4 @trevmon28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hspter Any advice from them on how to do this? Or are they open to being contacted? This is a serious/important endeavor I am just now embarking on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@minebocek Curious if you're going to DataDayTexas in January - I'm considering proposing a Data Sci Education Panel and obvi thought of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperstitch I had "Seem crazy to me" but ran out of characters. =p

It just seems like so much has changed, you'd think there'd be room for improvement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's crazy that the preeminent #bigdata system[1] is using Fortran code from 1979[2]

1: https://t.co/L0Wv2NXpD3
2: https://t.co/n8TaAK7WdL https://t.co/obknOf8ORG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you open sublime and are greeted by the last find-and-replace you ran... 

🤔 https://t.co/1MB9Xlr1Or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @urbaninstitute: Could "the hollowing out of the American middle class" actually be a good thing? @AllisonSchrager explains: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drob @sgrifter Wish I could be there! Can you point me towards the full bubble map? Cool to see DC so prominent / also curious about my new home (Chicago).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drob: If you're at #JSM2017, don't miss my talk 2:55 tomorrow: "Visualizing the Changing Landscape of Software Developers" https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So.

@McCourtSchool has "Fall Semester"

&amp;

@HarrisPolicy has "Autumn Quarter"

Great. I'm going to go back to bungling this in every email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akm @chrisalbon @Adversarial_L Hmmm so is that as specific as it sounds? Not uninteresting but a little outside of my bailiwick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filar I could listen to that man say '...it was a disaster' all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should almost certainly add one or both of the python ones, though both are new to me. Many thanks! https://t.co/0S82O8uGwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amanda_Kass @thedailylinechi @jeremyscahill Def adding Amicus - I've heard good things. Intelligence Squared is intriguing, too. That's policy debates?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisalbon Whatcha got that I'm missing? Gotta be one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TlkngMchns @lawrennd Also, @lawrennnd's tree metaphor for why observations, examined visually, appear close to mean, but never are in high-dimensional space is 💯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started listening to @TlkngMchns for like 5 seconds &amp; I can't believe I lapsed.

Best line so far, @lawrennd: "The truth is intractable"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok daily driving commute to work. Let's do this. Very open to suggestions as to what I'm missing. https://t.co/GFw3uOUVLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @neiltyson: In school, we rarely learn probability &amp; statistics, leaving us victims of our mind’s own inability to process random events.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this could be very interesting. https://t.co/5IN90Si1GJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrClimate @ResBaz @dfflanders @nikkirubinstein Also there's a tremendous amount of health data analysis in R and SAS. That part is very surprising, but could be related to this sample.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrClimate @ResBaz @dfflanders @nikkirubinstein This feels awfully qualitative given the subject - any chance you made a dataset in collecting this information?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very likely an important factor. https://t.co/2mXMsYVjq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu @SlaughterAM @NewAmerica @Google @WashPostDC One read into @SlaughterAM's response, and I don't think it really addressed the questions that I have: https://t.co/RcXz8lydZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awunderground Literally hiding part of the graph by default. Most haven't been problematic, afew have, but not novel enough to be exciting given that flaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awunderground I mean, small multiple density charts are fine. There's just no clear reason for them to overlap by default, especially w/o transparency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awunderground There's no specific name for that, which is fine. It doesn't need one and frankly neither did #joyplots, whose bandwagon I'm not on so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awunderground One data point gets one circle here. So it's really just overlapping small multiples of scaled half-circle plots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awunderground I think not, despite looking similar. Joy plots are overlapping small multiples of smoothed histograms. No binning/kernel density here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cblatts: In college, I believed this deeply. It's fundamental to justify libertarian stance. Learning it was empirically false changed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealDerv: lol if you think i actually hired a photographer to take pictures of my new puppy then you're exactly right bc i totally d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CookieSci @drob @nytgraphics Sure, but harder to mentally aggregate (sum to their total) across bars than with scaled circles, treemaps, or similar graphs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drob @nytgraphics In the NYT example there is added info in the ability to look at groups (compare all red to all green) you would not get in bar plot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drob Stronger example of this graph done well comes from @nytgraphics where the ordering and color adds value https://t.co/xJC4UGcnTF https://t.co/HBqS0Lfysm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drob Hm. Well scaled circles have notably better properties than word clouds. Words as visual encoding are imprecise &amp; easy to misinterpret size]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @albertocairo: I share @visualisingdata's contempt for radial bar charts. They neither clarify nor make your graphic look good https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Etai_Mizrav Thanks buddy! A great point. It also helps that genuine passion and shared interests can make networking much easier, hah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oof. Hit me right in the feels. 

I miss you too Wingo's, I miss you too. 

@Georgetown @Wingos #HoyaSaxa https://t.co/uzNVnLsL7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UChicagoCAPP: @HarrisPolicy Meaning that there is a direct connection between these concepts and understanding self-driving cars or aut…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu @SlaughterAM @NewAmerica @Google Meanwhile Barry Lynn is convinced it was largely @Google influencing @SlaughterAM's decision. His @WashPostDC op-ed: https://t.co/k2WSK1Aywe https://t.co/d0RcBcQXxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu @SlaughterAM @NewAmerica And even if that's 80% the case (again, no evidence at this stage) and 20% "@Google said so", that's still incredibly damning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu @SlaughterAM @NewAmerica Lack of professional courtesy is not a remotely believable reason to let go a valuable, high quality, ten person research team. It's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu Also, I should note that while @SlaughterAM tweeted this retraction of her earlier "This Story is False" tweet, @NewAmerica has not. https://t.co/FewGb8eATf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The below statement really needs to be backed up - there's no public evidence that this is the case. And @PaulBlu's reporting undermines it. https://t.co/aotlhPfAhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @logic_magazine: In 1983, female computer scientists at MIT wrote a report on how sexism was pushing women out of their--historically fe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @juliasilge: @jtleek @seankross @coursera Did you know this is how I started learning R?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vicapow: Honored to be interviewed and featured in @alignedleft's Interactive Data Visualization for the Web https://t.co/b9jjoIEoXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gimperion @PaulBlu @NewAmerica @Google I had the exact same thought. How can we be expected to choose between DevTools and Democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole thread (with additional emails) by @PaulBlu adds more reasons to be concerned by (and skeptical of) @NewAmerica's actions. https://t.co/b6bfIHJBxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulBlu: @danielmarans The release was missing other emails, which I've now been able to see and they do not back up the narrative that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @linamkhan: 1. My team at Open Markets and I are leaving New America https://t.co/ALqppNwT6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eisingerj: I am a New America fellow. Folks there have treated me very well &amp; generously. But this is deeply troubling. https://t.co/Px…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hadleywickham: Please use as much or as little of the #tidyverse as you feel useful. I want to be as effective in #rstats as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewmethods: You don’t need to be a statistician or a pollster to learn from our Methods 101 video series. First up: what is random samp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thomasp85: A new family of geoms enters #ggforce - geom_mark_*.

First off: geom_mark_hull() #rstats #ggplot2 https://t.co/NDwoTT1Lsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man can give a speech. @SenSanders https://t.co/RFJEwndgqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @congressfellows: Starting in 50 minutes: TechCongress info call about the 2018 Congressional Innovation Fellowship!  Join us!  https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UChicago No but really the place I work. https://t.co/WvLLVYaEoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GUPolitics: Have a great first day of classes, @Georgetown Hoyas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is (my tweet) my fav point from @profjensludwig on ML and policy. In many cases, subjectivity is horrifying, and Math can be better. https://t.co/Jph8iuLv9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lizthegrey: "Women had to be 2.5x more productive than men to be rated equally scientifically competent by senior scientists evaluating…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elijah_Meeks Ah ok. Those extensions are maybe more analogous to d3's layouts? I'd still put ggplot fairly high on the expressiveness scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elijah_Meeks You're referring to qplot and ggplot as the two methods?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elijah_Meeks I tend to think on a scale of expressiveness, in which d3 is at the very top, and chart makers (Excel/tableau) are the very bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note from an old colleague upon hearing I moved to Chicago "A fun fact you may need this winter: Fahrenheit and Celsius scales meet at -40°"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvoEcoEric @nj_tierney @rdpeng @robjhyndman @hadleywickham @KerrieMengersen @visnut @drob @hspter And this makes sense when you look at quantities of data. 100 rows of data. 20 columns of data. 10 GB of data. Decent example on wikipedia: https://t.co/lfd5KY0mrp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>