<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Barista wrote a slur on a Latino customer's cup: As Starbucks prepares to close its stores later this month for mandatory racial-bias training, an incident in suburban Los Angeles is showing why that training is needed. https://t.co/O4BTP4hIde https://t.co/I2r30MVYRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former spy inside al Qaeda speaks: The secret agent who was arguably the West's most important spy inside al Qaeda has never told his full story - until now. https://t.co/PbyVRgebHw https://t.co/BC7vCxTtZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Clarkson jokes about her weight loss: During a press conference, Kelly Clarkson was recently asked about how she lost so much weight and she brushed it off with a joke. https://t.co/18jsQLkQ25 https://t.co/WdjIkgJfym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA player had hands in pockets before being tackled and tased: Milwaukee's police chief apologized on Wednesday for the actions of officers involved in the January arrest of Milwaukee Bucks rookie Sterling Brown. https://t.co/Qt4rvRXYt9 https://t.co/pwMYPCmwNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They spoke out against immigrants. So she unearthed their own immigrant ancestors: If you think the ongoing immigration debates don't apply to you, Jennifer Mendelsohn has some news: They probably do. https://t.co/A0ITHpENHw https://t.co/lXmo6Ael1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL commissioner explains the decision: This season, NFL players must stand during the National Anthem, team owners decided. There will also be an option for players to remain in the locker room while the anthem is played. https://t.co/i78BueGvt9 https://t.co/psymVD6nyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving while black: Police handcuff man for 'vegetation' in car window: When police in Winfield, Kansas, pulled Rudy Samuel over, the 31-year-old felt he had done nothing wrong. So he started recording the encounter on Facebook Live. https://t.co/9bHcGjiHb4 https://t.co/f3UTe8sCZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg's big European test did not go well https://t.co/Sav1GFVxML https://t.co/Pvuc9qZNLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram will let you mute annoying accounts https://t.co/hkG1LLJVxo https://t.co/HBt77HeH5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bluths are back in 'Arrested Development': "Arrested Development" is back, after an experimental fourth season that the parties appear to be tacitly admitting didn't entirely work, given that the producers re-edited the episodes. Returning to more… https://t.co/wIZVh86qLY https://t.co/hF1OUGh4VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GE can't get rid of its light bulb business https://t.co/nJRRuPI2tk https://t.co/zYCVcQbSHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['American Idol' crowns winner -- with a twist: There was love in the air during the "American Idol" finale Monday night. https://t.co/kZRvV0bdpa https://t.co/ej8cF8hVeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He started selling T-shirts from a van. Now he's an investor on 'Shark Tank' https://t.co/Y5eRj0DYTA https://t.co/Arzw3Ll7NY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See lava from Hawaii volcano reach the ocean: First it was catastrophic lava. Then it was sulfur dioxide. Now Hawaii's residents have yet another danger to worry about - laze. https://t.co/j61UcxN2n2 https://t.co/r3vi7hyDOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's cereal, soda and soup companies in turmoil https://t.co/7nYdrgmx7u https://t.co/MK3ULnjH53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuelan President is re-elected: Venezuelans trekked to the polls Sunday to elect a new president, amid widespread economic anxiety and voter apathy. https://t.co/Aw2u9LYYsU https://t.co/XgdVJNqVyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wants a military parade. Here's how other countries do it: President Donald Trump wants a military parade. We look at which other countries around the world can show him how its done. https://t.co/QHlB8Kd5fX https://t.co/peJZyDTYot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cougar kills mountain biker in rare attack: The survivor of a cougar attack in the Cascade Mountains near Seattle is recounting a harrowing story that left a fellow cyclist dead. https://t.co/HvpKu2rMLM https://t.co/RmnCUVbdvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 people hospitalized in New York from what cops think was synthetic pot: Twenty-five people have been hospitalized in the same area of Brooklyn after having negative reactions from what's believed to synthetic marijuana known as K2, according to Lt.… https://t.co/316voTvwmK https://t.co/zomSnMXahu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the victims of the shooting: There were 10 people shot and killed in Friday's shooting at Santa Fe High School in Texas. Ten others were wounded. https://t.co/7RN3UUdXHO https://t.co/IvC0TbKRio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heck of a wedding: Highlights from Harry and Meghan's big day: What a wedding! https://t.co/5eZu1mf7FS https://t.co/s7vSAiKg37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan debuts second wedding dress: Prince Harry and Meghan Markle depart for Frogmore House to attend a more intimate reception thrown by Prince Charles. Meghan Markle debuts her evening gown designed by Stella McCartney. https://t.co/f0DwJz2jpy https://t.co/wxR7MwyKQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Millennials aren't feeling the boom in household wealth https://t.co/771w5leAU8 https://t.co/8KYOCqcNZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the fear, the gunshots and the trauma of the Texas school shooting, she wasn't surprised: Paige Curry was visibly shaken during her interview Friday. https://t.co/boobYk7T2g https://t.co/Lvpeh0G73f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not just you: Everything really is getting more expensive https://t.co/9WCquCYyov https://t.co/qDsRdD3T4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US kept B-52s from Korean Peninsula after North Korea threatened Trump summit: The US, South Korea and Japan agreed this week to shift a planned flight of at least two nuclear-capable B-52 bombers so they would not fly over the Korean Peninsula,… https://t.co/YRYMwTwCin https://t.co/XGYg7Dm4N3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possible accomplice in custody, law enforcement official in Texas says https://t.co/20ZEWN3mMZ https://t.co/b6uv9A2k01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to keep travel snacks healthy: Traveling can wreak havoc on our diets, but packing a nutritious snack or meal before heading out the door can get us started on the right healthy eating track and perhaps give us a bit of wiggle room for indulgences… https://t.co/5035Dlbo6e https://t.co/neuYiUkP3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani defends 'stormtroopers' comments about FBI: Rudy Giuliani on Friday stood by his belief that the FBI agents who raided President Donald Trump's personal attorney Michael Cohen home, office and hotel room last month were "stormtroopers." https://t.co/G53gKmgOaO https://t.co/ZThyfWcDIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['China's SpaceX' launches first private rocket https://t.co/Y9WUT0LXvG https://t.co/8uVIWXYC9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you should (and shouldn't) do to defuse a racist tirade in public: When you watch public, racist tirades online -- like the recent one at a New York City restaurant -- it's easy to cringe from behind a screen or lob some choice words of your own. https://t.co/j3RaJgkjNf https://t.co/yZKZF8UZTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vintage posters from travel's golden age https://t.co/tMZR89zgjc https://t.co/qwZD1KVDE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: The biggest political story no one is talking about: On Wednesday, two more Republicans signed on to a petition that would force an open-ended and unpredictable immigration debate onto the House floor -- a nightmare scenario that the White… https://t.co/lts0ddkGkl https://t.co/yd8S8kocY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/b0sZjbTqBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotel housekeeper describes interaction with Las Vegas gunman: Authorities in Las Vegas have released more documents from the investigation into the October 2017 shooting in which 58 people were killed and almost 500 others were wounded. https://t.co/qmhmZe4Bib https://t.co/Pa0row5iQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Steve Bannon used Cambridge Analytica to further his alt-right vision for America: Long before Donald Trump declared his presidential candidacy, conservative strategist Steve Bannon sought to leverage data-driven technology to push the hearts and… https://t.co/4Ah9WSaAtb https://t.co/WUoXQ18XJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't a car crash, it's a high school senior prank: Seniors at a Wisconsin high school pulled off what police are calling one of the best senior pranks they've ever seen. https://t.co/zyP4oUrzyD https://t.co/18fdE2FzVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marco Rubio: It's time to push for Maduro's exit https://t.co/nl1cdRPHnd https://t.co/veSuTjo1H3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This state only has men in Congress. That's about to change: Pennsylvania's congressional delegation next year will no longer be made up of only men. https://t.co/N8BDi14OMW https://t.co/2tMkXchHZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea has history of failed talks: Brian Todd reports on North Korea's latest threats to pull out of a meeting with President Donald Trump and other times they've balked in negotiations, or gone back on a deal. https://t.co/JfhC8Ykky9 https://t.co/VEZaMF3oKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you eat 24K gold chicken wings? https://t.co/RlOcaq65zv https://t.co/NoA2zcJ5JM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A window broke and the co-pilot was sucked halfway out of the plane: A Sichuan Airlines co-pilot was sucked halfway out of an aircraft's cockpit when its windshield shattered during a flight, Chinese state media has reported. https://t.co/2e3ojwnFQX https://t.co/tMRmZEozi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idaho woman hopes to become nation's first Native American governor: "No chance in hell." https://t.co/9RcYKPX5Rl https://t.co/e6IxEjdgM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House caught off guard, aides say https://t.co/GqZ12zd8b2 https://t.co/RJabE39GV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey: 68% of flight attendants have been sexually harassed https://t.co/UL95Ae7mbz https://t.co/CTQMV1jEwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell pays tribute to John McCain following Arizona visit: Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell traveled to Arizona over the weekend to visit Republican Sen. John McCain, according to a statement from McConnell's office. https://t.co/cczrjBYuqw https://t.co/7vUOT53Wlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five myths about US embassy move to Jerusalem https://t.co/qPcU0AlbV0 https://t.co/qqRH5gDt7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lava bombs fly as Kilauea's eruption shows no sign of slowing down: Scalding, black lava crept out of the largest fissure ripped open by Hawaii's Kilauea Volcano, consuming the lush, green landscape around it and lobbing balls of magma known as "spatter… https://t.co/ALYprnlfDS https://t.co/wj9YEvvXWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans tune into 'Harry &amp; Meghan' Lifetime movie: From the casting to the dialogue, the Lifetime TV movie "Harry &amp; Meghan: A Royal Romance," which aired Sunday night, gave fans lots to talk about. https://t.co/rhOdNwngs4 https://t.co/Fh7DmrMeNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Diana's influence on Harry and Meghan's wedding: When Prince Harry and Meghan Markle tie the knot in Windsor's St. George's Chapel, there's one person whose absence will be keenly felt: Diana, Princess of Wales. https://t.co/H4nJr2JWwH https://t.co/aehg9XfaOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters hurl Molotov cocktails and stones at Israeli soldiers: Nine Palestinians were killed during protests in Gaza on Monday, hours before the new US embassy was due to officially open in Jerusalem, the Palestinian Ministry of Health announced. https://t.co/hNfFkZBnWw https://t.co/xam2vXc0lW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game show host makes major blunder: The host of Britain's edition of "Who Wants to be a Millionaire?" made a major gaffe by prematurely congratulating a contestant. https://t.co/wHPJB3autE https://t.co/QNOkEbK1an]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT: More than 2 dozen people have died after leaving on their keyless cars https://t.co/lizSgNbj1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani shows up in court, but not for Trump: After Rudy Giuliani announced he was leaving his law firm to offer his "sole concentration" to President Donald Trump, Giuliani appeared in a Broward County, Florida, courtroom to represent a woman accused… https://t.co/pJ8JzYCikV https://t.co/YUyzjEIUNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What women should know before seeing 'Tully': For most of cinematic history, on-screen mothers have been a tame bunch. They were observers and healers, drivers and cheek-crumb wipers. They could be wise but rarely were given the chance to reveal how they… https://t.co/eDRpfulBgm https://t.co/ebVkxsVQHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W. Kamau Bell: The Gullah Geechee culture is uniquely American: One of the themes of this season of "United Shades of America" is "Black is not a monolith." And by that I mean that in the United States we often act as if every black person thinks the… https://t.co/AQ3zc9svOB https://t.co/fVF6IydDVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could make you happier, study suggests: On Saturday, 26 countries stand to be a lot happier -- simply by taking part in an iconic singing competition. https://t.co/KFBGxLaS0w https://t.co/IWA02LKiw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Cohen offered his services to Ford Motor Co., too, but was rebuffed: Michael Cohen unsuccessfully offered up his consulting services to Ford Motor Co. during a phone call following President Donald Trump's election victory, The Wall Street… https://t.co/7mXny0E6gb https://t.co/K5hUoxCGVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This generation get its version of 'Little Women': Every generation probably deserves its own version of "Little Women" -- having previously been adapted in 1933, '49 and '94 -- and a new 21st-century "Masterpiece" version of Louisa May Alcott's story in… https://t.co/xTRaZgpue5 https://t.co/jaKnvaYJz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Governor signs adoption law that LGBT groups call discriminatory: Oklahoma Gov. Mary Fallin on Friday signed a law that says no child-placement agency will be required to put children up for adoption or in foster care in situations that "violate the… https://t.co/XCnTWSRfRg https://t.co/4Y5jGudhBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proms reflect our racist reality: It's prom season again: your social media is about to be overrun with pictures of teenagers in formal clothes and giant smiles, maybe evoking "Pretty in Pink" or "Carrie," depending on your high school experience. As a… https://t.co/dVCBXQGaIA https://t.co/5USUalaBwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volcanologist: Why Hawaii's volcano is in danger of going ballistic: Everyone has been looking at Kilauea volcano's lava flows. Sure, a wall of molten rock consuming a car is quite the sight. But as we all focus on the damage at Leilani Estates, we… https://t.co/XRGWCP6zwr https://t.co/jPQq8AMhf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo owes $97 million to California workers https://t.co/BY9dL1ryBQ https://t.co/IVZdW0kFV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly E. coli outbreak tied to romaine spreads: An outbreak of E. coli linked to romaine lettuce from the Yuma, Arizona, growing region has spread to four additional states, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention announced Wednesday. Florida,… https://t.co/GZlXazy4E6 https://t.co/4rasQ5uM1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive eruptions added to list of fears for Hawaii residents: Zivile Roditis has spent the last week anxiously watching the Kilauea volcano, belching and churning molten lava into her neighborhood in Leilani Estates. https://t.co/cYOCiP2QLM https://t.co/0MLhYAfB4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Island could face acid rain and blast projectiles: After surviving earthquakes and molten lava, residents of Hawaii's Big Island now have new threats to worry about: steam-driven explosions, hazardous volcanic smog and acid rain. https://t.co/dTUASRwZyN https://t.co/qGjDLOAKiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli official: Trump made the right choice on Iran: Israelis are celebrating. https://t.co/NHEMejQkgi https://t.co/UbMPe4sNtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona GOP calls for lawmaker to resign for calling immigration an 'existential threat': The Arizona Republican Party is calling on a Republican state lawmaker to resign after he said that "immigration today represents an existential threat to the… https://t.co/j8jIjqW4K7 https://t.co/EgU2rYLIui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Bachelorette' contestant convicted of indecent assault: "The Bachelorette" contestant Lincoln Adim was convicted of indecent assault and battery for groping and assaulting a woman in 2016. https://t.co/KhAnZRHYTY https://t.co/8ZLbrMkZpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China: 'The US has launched a trade war' https://t.co/gbTEPc4ZBM https://t.co/ZdDGNiStqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if Obama had done this?: If Barack Obama had behaved the way President Donald Trump has, Republicans would be demanding investigations and an impeachment proceeding. https://t.co/HY3jy3Rq78 https://t.co/mO2pSqBSJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newspaper fires critical cartoonist: Veteran cartoonist Rob Rogers has been fired from the Pittsburgh Post Gazette after 25 years. He speaks with CNN's Erin Burnett about his firing. https://t.co/d7eVE7yGxi https://t.co/xqpTMiNbtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Stranger Things' actress leaves Twitter: Millie Bobby Brown has deactivated her Twitter account after becoming the target of a cruel hashtag and meme. https://t.co/5IFF3JnP43 https://t.co/aBQSrZLhSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's doctors call for gun control measures: Frustrated with a lack of action on gun control by the country's lawmakers, the American Medical Association adopted a series of sweeping policies aimed at preventing gun violence this week during its… https://t.co/VtfjXAABQZ https://t.co/yK5PEARyIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using spider silk to boost our immune systems: Using synthetic spider silk, researchers have created a type of microcapsule that can deliver vaccines straight to the heart of our immune cells. https://t.co/nA1yEFpfgk https://t.co/reVF1EmACg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 hurt from storms in Pennsylvania: Strong storms smacked eastern Pennsylvania Wednesday night, leaving six people wounded and causing significant damage to several buildings. https://t.co/AverXevw2n https://t.co/xwkRcb8M0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan lowers its age of adulthood: The Japanese government enacted a bill Wednesday lowering the age of adulthood from 20 to 18, but teenagers beware: the legal age of drinking will stay fixed at 20. https://t.co/OWmLF7Bsct https://t.co/qFGNBfHKHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Gutierrez says Sessions wants black people 'in the back of the bus again': Rep. Luis Gutierrez stood by his comments that Attorney General Jeff Sessions wants "black people to be in the back of the bus again." https://t.co/me3z67X2fA https://t.co/Pwpf9yYWOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why CNN anchor told colleague her salary: The most recent list of the 100 highest-paid athletes in the world doesn't include a single woman. CNN's Brooke Baldwin says it's time for women to start speaking up. https://t.co/geHQB9CxOy https://t.co/g35xMeUJcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starved for cash, an iconic American company takes apart its legacy https://t.co/QIFENSv4o4 https://t.co/NSskpd5nOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenager fought tumor that left him unable to smile: Kevin Portillo practices smiling every day at home. https://t.co/3wWWqVBGeR https://t.co/oIXDaDhTgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should you root for in the World Cup when your country isn't even in it: For the next month, the world will be glued to the biggest sporting event on the globe: the World Cup. Thirty two countries qualified, but alas, yours isn't among them. (We're… https://t.co/dkDI5PD2rp https://t.co/Fqjoshi41w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France's secret city of cliffs: An undiscovered beach town in Mediterranean Europe? Well, almost. https://t.co/DvqbOQX6Zu https://t.co/fd9bUvS8Ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico releases records of deaths since Maria: The Puerto Rican government on Tuesday released to CNN and another news organization a database of information on all deaths that occurred after Hurricane Maria, which pummeled this US commonwealth on… https://t.co/mU8zxYnYzE https://t.co/cxfeiKuyBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed man takes hostages in Paris: At least two people were reportedly been taken hostage in Paris on Tuesday, CNN affiliate BFMTV reported. https://t.co/d7zF6SjG2z https://t.co/tNMivgeJDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump's wildest summit quotes: Before hopping aboard Air Force One to head back to the United States after his historic summit in Singapore with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, President Donald Trump spent more than an hour(!) talking and… https://t.co/KMgTkGSZdr https://t.co/wML4w23FI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rand Paul: Graham a danger to US: Republican Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) said his colleague Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) is a "danger to the country" for suggesting that Congress sign an authorization to use military force against North Korea if President Trump… https://t.co/cpE4AsyuYh https://t.co/EAGB3JJnSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the luxury hotel where Kim leader stayed https://t.co/hYhTwZpRLG https://t.co/iFlokSoAQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 key House races move toward Dems, 3 move toward GOP: The dust has mostly settled from last week's primaries in eight states, clearing the air enough to update a few of CNN's House Race Ratings. https://t.co/lRirMy4E3t https://t.co/ND4C2bJTXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are windowless planes the future of travel? https://t.co/wC9WP83zhN https://t.co/N9G2iL6wl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton: 'Norms have changed' for what you can do to somebody against their will: Former President Bill Clinton suggested the "norms have changed" in society for what "you can do to somebody against their will" in response to a question about former… https://t.co/3aOcUXzrdp https://t.co/pft1eu1Wvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Trump, Kim Jong Un speak before summit: President Trump and Kim Jong Un made short statements before heading into a one-on-one talk at the Capella Hotel in Singapore. https://t.co/UIQxmF1Y11 https://t.co/F43FCc0WhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the full list of Tony Awards winners: The Tony Awards celebrated the best of Broadway on Sunday night. https://t.co/WCKm9z5pPp https://t.co/eEA1oqvzp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsey Vonn is dating a hockey superstar https://t.co/KoqTQUgBSt https://t.co/ZGKwlPI6WY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Maher is wrong to root for a recession: Bill Maher may have made his cruelest and most ill-informed comment yet -- and that says a lot, given his track record -- on his HBO show Friday night. https://t.co/hfpzLdoKot https://t.co/SD6CocYXiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actor Jackson Odell of TV's 'Goldbergs' found dead at 20: Actor Jackson Odell, 20, was found unresponsive at a home in Tarzana, California on Friday, the LA County Medical Examiner's Office said. https://t.co/bpfbRzRuQs https://t.co/h2XtEL5bnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This small town has a very big appetite https://t.co/a9BvJ17d1u https://t.co/VVglrwF150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still in 'championship mode' after losing, LeBron's future is clear https://t.co/QK3dx6ZpjU https://t.co/Y3fZOQ8qIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga shines in 'A Star is Born' preview: The trailer for Bradley Cooper's anticipated directorial debut is here, and so far, it sounds like a winner. https://t.co/WJbJDkUiWH https://t.co/HPsryMEHAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Sanders to Cuomo: Do your homework: Sen. Bernie Sanders tells CNN's Chris Cuomo to do more homework on his concept of socialized health care, which Sanders calls "Medicare for all." https://t.co/UNLJECaVEs https://t.co/DcifsouctH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>