<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/w8enz6WIXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/mLRd6BMnzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/CvNaGT7VVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/nNtKqmUtnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/TLzFnNy9cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/dxTua2BlHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/j2kAczP4Yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/O4AIbXVjr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/OBF22UwTQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/hl7xsj7xbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/Ka34P2zyas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/OCBpGhuEFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/OF9rAadD73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/zaczOACYNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/Q03et2FWEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/GH2eOZu41Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/CmAn1JSLXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/SHSNHa1Hna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/Uv9qMGw82p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/LqzxPgg6FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/9ZMnQ0e95y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/60Q8C6WkNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/gbGuRSjquL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/Yym7dfuSQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Zvi8wS7iSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/sMQOMMOBPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/QQ5mLlEgwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/1Q23IJUZIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/bjImYaSwrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/Psm7UuZz8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/FwrMff0Qy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/JZmGQtF7Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/hZycfoWHa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/JZNCYiFDRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/i9ZYgJCDgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/OudeppqQa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/HPBt7TBChL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/6FFzBpcP2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/f6tUR9jQJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/UmUTKWDpkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/MjavCbxJRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/tEfHPPu70p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/IM5zmmjuoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/qo3PM62The]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/gHsPj096UR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/zaczOACYNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animals are such agreeable friends - they ask no questions, they pass no criticisms. - George Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/1Q23IJUZIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/39lF9pWh6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/m5kxLH6aOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/eQXvnBUp98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/ACt6mVbMBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/QLIkLndqL3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>