<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server 2012 DBA Ref No.: 18-29328 Location: Loveland, Colorado SQL Server DBA: Bachelor’s degree required, preferably in computer science or a field closely related to computer science. Individuals without a degree may be considered… https://t.co/JBqF8v9JNs https://t.co/i067BqQhPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's most luxurious train trip?: From Jaipur to Jodhpur, India's northerly Rajasthan region is famous for its ancient forts, opulent palaces and gleaming marble monuments. https://t.co/FQ7r4lhx0Z https://t.co/02X5aie2jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server DBA Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3592 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/0sxSa9PHko https://t.co/k1jbucgZB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer/SQL Developer (Business Intelligence): Overview * Develop, test and deploy various ETL jobs * Participate in data conversion and data migration efforts * Create Stored Procedures, Functions and Views from scratch * Model and then implement… https://t.co/5sWp5C3ZKs https://t.co/8iEHgrpG47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller refers foreign agent inquiries to New York prosecutors: Special counsel Robert Mueller has referred a collection of cases to New York federal prosecutors concerning whether several high-profile American lobbyists and operatives failed to register… https://t.co/IZXK6KiA68 https://t.co/cugBGJiX2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL – Senior Database Administrator (DBA): The Senior Data Administrator defines and standardizes data used by the firm. This individual also serves as a resource to junior members of the data administration team through establishing guidelines according… https://t.co/98YOZVnLUg https://t.co/Q90qyZIlhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Trump aides don't belong on campus https://t.co/ifY0Gjb1Jo https://t.co/PsiXtamcqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: Requisition ID 2018-41177 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Here’s an opportunity to join a dynamic company, GDIT, on one of our engaging… https://t.co/pS20S7Vssf https://t.co/QsXhZJkqoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Mueller can't afford to lose this trial: The first trial of Special Counsel Robert Mueller's Russian probe presents multiple challenges to both the prosecution and defense. https://t.co/plmZsDLuju https://t.co/8JiqBi53N8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: Requisition ID 2018-41177 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Here’s an opportunity to join a dynamic company, GDIT, on one of our engaging… https://t.co/THcQnoUIvW https://t.co/hq0E1Y4yWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D guns: Untraceable and unstoppable?: Not long ago it was the stuff of science fiction, but now US officials and lawmakers are grappling with a new reality -- the ability for citizens to print firearms at home. https://t.co/KztCyPxPCT https://t.co/3rI9NMcWPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: GM Financial seeks: ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: Req. BS in EE, CS, CIS, MIS &amp; 5 yrs of exp in Asset Backed Securitization reporting, ETL coding and SQL. Economist II: Req. MS in Applied Stat, Applied Math,… https://t.co/kJT2RFHn1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rare dolphin-whale hybrid spotted near Hawaii: Scientists from the Cascadia Research Collective have discovered a rare dolphin-whale hybrid off the coast of Kauai, Hawaii, according to a report published last week. https://t.co/3rDZ85AMSu https://t.co/eMkqZzgusX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/xUeIPVWlsx https://t.co/FnUCuEjZgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Investment Services Domain): Software Developer (Investment Services Domain) – FirstPRO Inc. Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Supply Chain, Engineering, and Logistics – Meet… https://t.co/hSVsO54K4X https://t.co/hLa0MFHbCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Datastage Developer @@ Kansas City, MO: Datastage Developer @@ Kansas City, MO – Sriven Systems Inc. – Kansas City, KS – 07-13-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary… https://t.co/PtKJUgG2xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron: Trump is using sports to divide us: LeBron James thinks the President is using athletics, and athletes, to split up the country. And he's rejecting the premise like an opponent's ill-advised layup. https://t.co/TYkFRiTZRF https://t.co/VHHtdmBzpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Resource Planning: Job Description Job Description The Customer Service organization is looking for an energetic, self-directed, detail oriented candidate for the position of Sr. Analyst, Resource Planning. This person will evaluate T-Mobile… https://t.co/dtQMtUSJLQ https://t.co/oEKuSBWBkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet helps finish Giuliani's tweet: Rudy Giuliani pulls a "covfefe" with a one-word tweet and Twitter finishes it for him. CNN's Jeanne Moos fills in the blanks. https://t.co/tDwbLFa5b9 https://t.co/hWRi11x1cb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Markit Digital is looking for a talented SQL Server Database Developer/Analyst who is interested in working with large, complex data sets. Our growing development team is looking for folks eager to take on the challenge of efficiently and… https://t.co/gXcfRrsVK6 https://t.co/MsA5XTwbmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer NET, C#, SQL Server Exchange Traded Funds: Job Description Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server – Exchange Traded Funds The Exchange Traded Funds Technology Team creates application-layer solutions to streamline and… https://t.co/mnN5cKkRg1 https://t.co/Y8WjRDNeQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 6th concussion, NFLer retires at 24 https://t.co/NoJrGC8IAT https://t.co/6AxmsxAOoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst Senior (SQL): Position ResponsibilitiesRequirements: WHO ARE WE? Employer is the world’s largest global provider dedicated to financial technology solutions. Employer empowers the financial world with software, services, consulting and… https://t.co/lE1ryGgviS https://t.co/7ZIEEgcTVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSIS SSRS SQL Server Developer with Python knowledge: SSIS SSRS SQL Server Developer with Python knowledge Ref No.: 18-29431 Location: Woodland hills, California Role: SSIS SSRS SQL Server Developer with Python knowledge Location:Woodland hills CA… https://t.co/7OGDE5vSXF https://t.co/bz6C3j9Sg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things you should know today: Want to really know if your significant other is right for you? Take a trip together, because travel really is the ultimate test of a relationship. Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door.… https://t.co/dTIPG2gne2 https://t.co/4u3APmFBrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer — https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Specialist Developer ‘ *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be… https://t.co/CRScKYMCCw https://t.co/VrMTLdhBjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What… https://t.co/lVSaSDGAVH https://t.co/YtnD2w8TbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans freak over reported engagement of Nick Jonas and Priyanka Chopra: Be easy on the Nick Jonas and Priyanka Chopra fans today, please. https://t.co/MYhecKhjw6 https://t.co/PTt71VBjxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Systems Analyst: SR. FINANCIAL SYSTEMS ANALYST QUALIFICATIONS/REQUIREMENTS * Bachelor’s degree in Business, Finance or Accounting. * 6+ years experience supporting accounting and finance functions. * Proficient with SQL and relational… https://t.co/8SVq4igQi6 https://t.co/sPy56jhZWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 missing as deadly wildfire grows: At least 12 people were missing in Shasta County, California, as the monstrous Carr Fire continued to grow Sunday, authorities said. https://t.co/B2wSvklebT https://t.co/lHirrHcFcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/vVhT132kRM https://t.co/HJHjVBMKch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 07/03/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview SQL DBA CO-OP Financial Long Term Contract Dallas, TX RESPONSIBILITIES: * Develop and maintain new and existing… https://t.co/hiNGSJYdqq https://t.co/WR0xbj2lPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesys Solutions Architect: Requisition ID 2018-42192 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description As senior solution architect, the following task would be essential to… https://t.co/9zbTJQZm2o https://t.co/lHKtQDUmlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cupp: For once, a united press corps?: HLN's SE Cupp praises the press for its show of solidarity after CNN's Kaitlan Collins was barred from an open press event in the White House Rose Garden for asking what the White House called "inappropriate"… https://t.co/z3Shhxm9xk https://t.co/ttwIqR5I3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA star reveals depression struggles in book https://t.co/RLevYIxvjz https://t.co/8STW95gvJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job ID: ********-10050-LEK Company Name: Argus Description: LCI is an industry leader at analytical and technological services to the financial industry. Founded over 25 years ago, we handle over 1.3 billion accounts a year for the… https://t.co/MhsItWRPTI https://t.co/K61VdBkrUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California's top court rules workers must be paid for off-the-clock tasks https://t.co/P8Ng3rrJGK https://t.co/MwRXsR5YEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-31508 Location: Englewood, Colorado Job Responsibilities: Develop, implement Stored procedures, Functions, and Triggers using Microsoft SQL Server Review and interpret ongoing business report requirements Research… https://t.co/9NFYMViUo5 https://t.co/fZEAp8BwjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Business Analyst Insurance Development Team: Quality Assurance/Business Analyst – Insurance Development Team The Insurance Team supports the development of the Eagle STAR Insurance product. Eagle’s STAR Insurance product is a proven… https://t.co/IDdBvXlH75 https://t.co/MXDfLwpWRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gorgeous city that has it all: Cape Town is one of the world's most beautiful cities. From almost any vantage point, there's a mountain or an ocean in view, and often both. https://t.co/1EOU2YCydq https://t.co/sGsGrXbZ6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II: Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II at PATTERSON COMPANIES Skip Navigation – Corporate Site – Company Overview – News and Events – Working at Patterson – Environmental Impact Sign In Search Jobs… https://t.co/IprMkTff90 https://t.co/W9SO07tRFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official: Gunman killed 4 before killing himself: A gunman killed two people at his Texas home before going to a nearby nursing home and killing two others and himself in what investigators believe are related incidents, an official said. https://t.co/jq0spgfvAK https://t.co/ePFdZFqmNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of MLB's worst teams could make the biggest deal at trade deadline https://t.co/cFRoqMe1pP https://t.co/1jGHLxYDxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database Administrator who will be responsible for ensuring the performance, availability, and security of MySQL instances. You will also be responsible for orchestrating… https://t.co/D9l2kYFIxZ https://t.co/ZdLmwl8rjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: ******/SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-31083 Location: San Diego – California, California Ensure all database servers are backed up in a way that meets the business’s Recovery. Troubleshoot SQL Server service outages Configure SQL Server monitoring… https://t.co/2cxsXghpnK https://t.co/R76Hsi3pWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: ******/SQL Server Ref No.: 18-29052 Location: Lincolnshire, Illinois LEAD-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: Java-J2EE-L3 (Mandatory) SQL Server-L3 As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a… https://t.co/lKYsjHuYey https://t.co/2IgSwMpihy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened last time a President chose enemies over friends https://t.co/RDr6tLnX9w https://t.co/EixVnwQgRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing… https://t.co/zaCXhHmxQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prisoners hack tablets and give themselves $225K credit: Hundreds of Idaho inmates exploited a vulnerability in their personal tablets and gave themselves thousands of dollars in credits used to download music and games and use email, officials said… https://t.co/Z2HYelJF8b https://t.co/Uy7e89ayPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data with Java: Big Data with Java / J2EE Ref No.: 18-30764 Location: Phoenix, Arizona JOB ROLE: Big Data Developer with Java Location: Phoenix, AZ Contract Role Job Description: Big Data Engineer with Java / J2EE Hadoop Hive Algorithm Data… https://t.co/qR7ghQ7LVF https://t.co/sGMyHZk2LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In photos: The blood moon lunar eclipse: A total lunar eclipse -- the longest of the century -- was visible for much of the Eastern Hemisphere on Friday night. https://t.co/7IrnAL2UZj https://t.co/jMpEagidba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – Intermediate (SQL): Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Intermediate (SQL) Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Quality Department: Center Quality Imp-Innov… https://t.co/aUharbNOci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer – Strong Java Javascript, Node.js needed: For American Express Sr. Engineer – Strong Java/J2EE, Javascript, Node.js needed job – Digital Commerce, Technology – Phoenix, Arizona Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation American Express… https://t.co/ePtd8PS9VY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Integration Engineer: Costa Mesa, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today YOU ARE A passionate SQL Engineer that loves solving problems! In this role you will be analyzing and integrating data from many sources with minimal documentation. We are… https://t.co/s9eOQZvkgH https://t.co/csIH4h5DyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing. – Work autonomously with Marketing, Finance, and IT to interpret business requirements to SQL code in order to anticipate, investigate, and resolve issues related to new and ongoing projects. –… https://t.co/CC1mlFm5aJ https://t.co/KGdXS8fax4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook should pay you cash https://t.co/0ALy4qz76o https://t.co/VRZTLc5AsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Java / SQL: Software Developer – Java / SQL Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 2 Role Description * Consults with clients to gather information about program needs, objectives, functions, features, and input and output… https://t.co/Y0Mz7p7PCs https://t.co/g3dKiYEknI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep. called people on government assistance 'parasites': Republican Rep. Jason Lewis has repeatedly demeaned recipients of welfare and government assistance, calling them "parasites" and "scoundrels," and said the black community had "traded one… https://t.co/b0hw8fItHL https://t.co/NpC1MrtWOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tableau Developer: – Develop WHC Tableau Dashboards: Requirement gathering/analysis, design, development, testing, production rollover and post-production support/maintenance for reporting &amp; analysis projects – Produce attractive visuals/dashboards to… https://t.co/gsn4RbdR7i https://t.co/DN6Ltgmyhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby Developer: Ruby Developer Ref No.: 18-28412 Location: Phoenix, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for Ruby Developer in Phoenix, AZ. Please Let me know if you are looking for a new project. Role : Ruby Developer… https://t.co/NGU928CGK3 https://t.co/j2Kbo33Xil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Here's why Jim Jordan is running for House speaker: Conservative firebrand Jim Jordan is running for speaker of the House. https://t.co/toXTAqpn9u https://t.co/7anfxY1O5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Overland park, Kansas – United States Job Start Date – 06/27/18, Posted Date – 06/27/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12+ months contract. Phone and Skype. Candidate must have atleast 1 real time project in… https://t.co/3ATXMz2Ldb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer – Java, API, SQL/No SQL exp. required: American Express is in the midst of an exciting Product and Digital enterprise evolution driven by an energetic team of high performers. If you have the talent and desire to deliver innovative payment… https://t.co/M588XyZAla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Admin/Developer: SQL Server Admin/Developer Ref No.: 18-28320 Location: Torrance, California Role: Sql Server DBA Location: Torrance, CA Duration: 12 + Months primary skill : DBA SQL secondary skill : Microsoft SQL Server Database Developer… https://t.co/PA8HXPco0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia fires cops who arrested woman after appearing to use coin flip app: Two police officers in an Atlanta suburb who joked about using a coin-flip phone app before one of the officers arrested a woman for reckless driving have been fired, Roswell,… https://t.co/fcAMDjEQRB https://t.co/yt2LrJ3XmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Miami, Florida – United States Job Start Date – 06/08/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview We have an opening down in Miami for an SSIS developer for one of our Fortune 500 clients. This candidate… https://t.co/N0LgBWKkvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Database Specialist – SQL: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR –… https://t.co/9iljSnJuSC https://t.co/kPtCq1nVHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southwest's accident cost it $100 million https://t.co/eNzKEf2N8J https://t.co/v5ZMKMYz26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Analyst: Oracle PL/SQL Analyst Ref No.: 18-28124 Location: Pasadena, California – Oracle PL/SQL – Knowledge on System development life cycle – Hands on experience in Programming languages – Experience in Product and vendor evaluation –… https://t.co/p1fa1l8Ar6 https://t.co/fUxkyJ4900]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor who treated former President Bush likely targeted when killed, police say: Houston's police chief said Wednesday he believes there is a high probability a cardiologist who treated former President George H.W. Bush was targeted when he was fatally… https://t.co/C9tTDWnvG8 https://t.co/4YlacfgSzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer in Richmond, Virginia, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values –… https://t.co/cFQtjebLwK https://t.co/NjIPXRVabE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. SQL Database Administrator: Greensboro, NC 27408 #2018-26522 DescriptionOverview The Fresh Market currently has an opening for a Jr. SQL Database Administrator at our Corporate Offices in Greensboro, North Carolina.Responsibilities – Provide support… https://t.co/v36UExulBk https://t.co/KXjKfxZ3Di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pompeo claps back: I understand the game you're playing: Secretary of State Mike Pompeo defends President Donald Trump's meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin during a contentious hearing in front of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee. https://t.co/9mow8lxzEt https://t.co/7Mtg3bLjnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/DB Developer: Java/DB Developer Ref No.: 18-28240 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Hello, Greetings for the day! We have an urgent requirement for Java/DB Developer. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. Title:- Java/DB Developer… https://t.co/LW3XZc9rRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talend Developer: Position: Talend Developer Location: Palo Alto, CA Length of Assignment: 6 month contract to hire Description/Requirements: – Design, develop, validate and deploy the Talend / Any other ETL Tools’ processes – Talend knowledge needed… https://t.co/DhKRagY5cQ https://t.co/vUd9xcxGjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What… https://t.co/6yvpBFG3E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Project Manager 3rd party Governance, Tech Knowledge: Job Description Specialist Project Manager – 3rd party Governance, Tech Knowledge As a Third Party Governance engagement manager, you are responsible for the oversight of bank’s governance… https://t.co/3xFtcqGiGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US and EU agree to work toward zero tariffs: President Donald Trump said Wednesday that he and European Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker agreed to work toward eliminating tariffs and barriers between products, reducing tensions for now in a… https://t.co/ErCenF9wrb https://t.co/HP05FzuHbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer/Implementation/SQL Server: Job Description Transforming the future of healthcare isn’t something we take lightly. It takes teams of the best and the brightest, working together to make an impact. As one of the largest healthcare technology… https://t.co/0qDb63XO84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Miami, Florida – United States Job Start Date – 06/08/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview We have an opening down in Miami for an SSIS developer for one of our Fortune 500 clients. This candidate… https://t.co/Rt0IYMLisD https://t.co/c72R3EFx3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe and the US have the world's most important business ties https://t.co/XyEjBej2t6 https://t.co/zRPc7dPSkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aly Raisman is taking destiny into her own hands https://t.co/uBNRIT3EWB https://t.co/6GtlQTTLFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSRS SQL Server Reporting Services: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services Ref No.: 18-27583 Location: columbia, Maryland Key skills required for the job are: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services-L3 (Mandatory) As a develoer, you are responsible for… https://t.co/vQq7lQq1kP https://t.co/rC5Yd2MQ5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to work in core components for the Ariba cloud that includes application, persistence, meta-data, object model framework, common data server, customization and UI frameworks. Bach in Comp… https://t.co/P6IM2MfPRK https://t.co/cA5KTSrcxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cars turned to molten metal as Greek wildfires wipe villages off the map: Dried pools of molten aluminum dot the charred roads of a small Greek village ravaged by fire this week. The flames were so hot that cars in their path began to melt, metal… https://t.co/stOIESoQYL https://t.co/5mLwtNgUap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California sells sole winning lottery ticket: For at least one lucky person, this week just got a whole lot better. https://t.co/0w6TAOr9dy https://t.co/MI5Sgh1Dzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Requisition ID 2018-40506 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsibilities Provides full lifecycle software development to include the… https://t.co/HJY2b34aEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper calls out Trump: Wait, what changed?: CNN's Anderson Cooper wonders what changed since President Donald Trump's summit with Russian President Vladimir Putin to make him suddenly believe Russia could hack the 2018 election. https://t.co/ZRptbEyspW https://t.co/3kKuqdSpmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Developer w/Poly: Requisition ID 2018-41792 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Researches, designs, develops and/or modifies… https://t.co/Dpxka8teEt https://t.co/OyTj4oK1Dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA MySQL Developer: JAVA – MySQL Developer Ref No.: 18-28163 Location: Columbus, Ohio Foundation : MySQL, Assurance : Java Unit Testing Frameworks (Junit, *Unit, *Mock, Cactus, etc), Foundation : Java EE – EJB 3.0/JPA, Spring MVC https://t.co/6MqYLGVmdp https://t.co/e22RkichbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/16/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Data Scientist The Challenge: Are you excited at the prospect of unlocking the… https://t.co/gT96wIlppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebola outbreak in Congo declared over: The Ministry of Health in the Democratic Republic of Congo officially declared on Tuesday that the country's battle against a ravaging Ebola outbreak has come to an end, according to the World Health Organization. https://t.co/ek6exVCTMY https://t.co/29ZHCdaHcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victim's girlfriend: He didn't have to go like this: The family of Markeis McGlockton reacts to the news that police will not charge Michael Drejka, the man who fatally shot McGlockton, under Florida's "stand your ground" law. https://t.co/85G5b4uEVN https://t.co/rptv3HCcHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows/SQL Server Systems Administrator: Windows/SQL Server Systems Administrator Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10592 Minimum Clearance Required Public Trust Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Windows /… https://t.co/bLWPG3GQJL https://t.co/K54lgiF44M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Title: SQL Developer Organization Name: Energy Exemplar Division: Market Research &amp; Analysis Openings: One Work Schedule: 8:00 am to 5:00 pm Hours per Week: 40 Salary: Based on qualifications Employment Start Date: As early as August 10th,… https://t.co/EwbQMKSuE7 https://t.co/AxyEIz7i5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese search engine sues comedian over a joke https://t.co/kEptS6lkf1 https://t.co/GzIfnYNR71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/Share Point Developer: Career Opportunities at New Horizons St. Louis Student Login Search Site search – – – – Cart St. Louis &amp; Southern Illinois ************ – Home – Training and Certifications – Microsoft Office – Office 365 – Access – Excel –… https://t.co/tW9f8DQH0c https://t.co/O2S8WkqsDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump just keeps claiming things he said on tape aren't real: On Thursday morning, President Donald Trump claimed a taped interview with NBC's Lester Holt in 2017 was somehow doctored to make him look bad. https://t.co/rhCbDoBV5D https://t.co/AOCzq6Hn8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer with strong DB experience (NoSQL/Mongo): Date: Aug 26, 2018 Location: Jersey City, NJ, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 16819 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/TUawdyVv0o https://t.co/LnQfl88VcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21-year-old MLBer being compared to MVPs https://t.co/BUE1eITt2g https://t.co/1F3jYNXY6G]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>