<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/SWgYDA3xq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/5HE0wIqeGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/AfrpbtKPdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/beHGmkMRXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/eQReSFQ8WL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of America  http://t.co/MqhK0Kncm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/4yJJaRZGxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/2qBQWMYyye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/o9FXjQFBvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/noI1p1a0FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/BNMqHFrr3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/lZOMumFRgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/6i25lXzPhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/WUM8DNnLZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/cGEll79S8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/HABmgJzobn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/SSvt8q3HhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/LNSHldn7cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/Itmt4IAYB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/TwiHdqHyrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/3sNDFOXB7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/xI0GInGw0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/9fzZJI0RkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/xMXwWDrQLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/RDkq3iA7da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/wIXEAJsyeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/HUliOd2BUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/Frlbdx6UQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/bUwV0onLUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/qBKpYLrcmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/Jsq4DPcJRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/ZjzJpItZNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/CLfr5bRiGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Peter Frampton  http://t.co/qmXxfXGwiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/Ysxt8OO53u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/ijvCOax3b1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/H6nrBa3OID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jammin Pet Hoodies for Your Little Furry Loved Ones :&gt;) http://t.co/kh3Utl5wrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/SHvQh7mzsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/jw9Sv6YukQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/A9uSIJCZh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/vg5uOerAs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/5sfIfQs0vG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>