<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/TCBCi5DgjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/67g7svPuSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/zTiGNfi8sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/4Sfl340Pm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/RZkvdyBBfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/T6aWCeO5VU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/60rdJ9a4dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/JqCFtkjst0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/MT20Oc6twx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/wciZeBYpvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/KUFS5sooOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/Z6DVvvRj4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/gaiKGauct2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/Opc0jWAqZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/VfUcJRJxbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/QFgnfymeuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/RpnSjHQZ29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/PqE3IajGEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/L4aWu8GOVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/R6qVzJKLd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/ZG0fxNRmYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/DZJ5Y2420x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/Qx20KCp1re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/P1IGWGk8st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/FeOrFvDRct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/RqCmVMQBid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/Qx3g5MZc55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/vJYYMrADS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/1T01VgaPPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/39DiRyS2DI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/wBmMz5udAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/07xRzmCYBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/qogfArrcAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/OnZpME0wPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/nYSL4kZvtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/LmnO8DFsfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/IJIEYkOUjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/9MBAKKaYCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/YmKKDBGMbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these spooky skull candles!  http://t.co/B82ezAnkGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/pZqnEppDDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/cNMf6JQxfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/OjtiCrRauf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/jTxJ8ywKse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/PTXJFpvWH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/9PHdbZjsfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/Y8j4gRcx0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/nyXb1cnXiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Q9CrAio5Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>