<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/bRVde4QTOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/LUlSN9kMlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/Zzq2saQZO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/GEmrDYfugr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel's The Avengers - ALL FOUR Movies in one Collection - including The Avengers - VERY COOL!!!! http://t.co/fc0Lya44Ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/cklwiXY4hS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/GeZq8eKBXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/1jfTQ0nG6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/yhri8bwT2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/FQBONIeUq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/j35GDPrt6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/QODCYAJFi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird of paradise alights only upon the hand that does not grasp. - John Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/ctsPoPJyOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/0N6Veq4A3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/RKhXfjEaKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/szp7pPZC4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/k5wJPUxhch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/gMhtlEh3I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/SzhMv4fyWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/hMJflBkHOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/ZK2p86eAh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/eSse1n69li]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/tZ8Qoc8v41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/x1XCdA16m2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/esHCMzpXcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/7cpE6wbp3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/SKt763qnHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/A6KZDSB6LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/yhri8bwT2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/7d8fJbcm8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/dYbC2ierY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/Fy36NjWigY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/ft767PYUYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/szp7pPZC4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/7R4Oh0Pn70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/JmOrNd89lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/VmtrC3JHIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/f8od0NaRpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/A6KZDSB6LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/ZpDPvSDpZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/4YidtnYqTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/3AAgQm6G5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/32Rsg4EQal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/CtKAyYyMTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/zjaMicXym1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/5sVadHNejd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/IndT2uI3mR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/L1rwyBi2q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/ANMADw319C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/sHc0WtnPKp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>