<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/FU1F7eNuPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/MUtTjJIHDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/roOWXV3HnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/hja0zKrUlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/0ZwCz4VS8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/eSSMy2PX1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/AbQlv7mWmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/I4cplie1V7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/lwHpXRr5ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/ib54cZoyZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/BvkN9s6SLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/u3Zz6NkFue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/VXMEDCZ4vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/n3qujp5IWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last word of the Emperor Montezuma, "Someone tell those Marines to stop singing in the halls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/i7M2tYrohL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/SWoGIRrmAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/kbQqmyBAiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/eSSMy2PX1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/8EPB80wba2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/qmw0qPaJ7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/y8GWXco79Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/PCkwfA421K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/rQKwOr6BS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/yybqVh0nWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/Mtgxdnn6WX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/1JOAXkcq6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/5oy1I5T6Ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/2eyyYIcAyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/UHs0cVhT6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. - Marcia Wieder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/068tkZ58Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/xqCWJ0Qabi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/AmVvFg0tvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/QvjB7yLAwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/Y12wCGMIfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/8odE2v478B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/vD0Ne2mDVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/FiMNxVklZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/MqdWnv9Vn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/wZK6lrNAeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/Lyh4BWmmEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/h3zGScxDoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/6AHymfzxjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/GRCPwcg9wn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/cvl300hIrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/AC4cJwok8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>