<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "I did plenty today." 
Jerry: "Like what?" 
George: "I bought a new recliner with a fridge built right into it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/soz1xLOfNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kramer https://t.co/ompsDWHQ2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aMAqC6B4jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tAtxRHrVS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1yTTnyDkiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You broke up with her because she beat you at chess? That's pretty sick." -Jerry to George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2z47QOwRK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Costanza https://t.co/wjRC9EG7TP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0GoYx5ifsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can't carry a pen, I'm afraid I'll puncture my scrotum" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cheap fabric, and dim lighting. That's how you move merchandise!" -Morty Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To the idiot-mobile!" - Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "Every day is a date." 
Jerry: "That's one of Dante's nine stages of hell, isn't it?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why did I tell her I like her!? I have this sick compulsion to tell women how I feel" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't turn down money! It's what separates us from the animals" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: http://t.co/dJyAmyUN91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/PXjRKFXcFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To the idiot-mobile!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/3NygWkRHyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Cheap fabric, and dim lighting. That’s how you move merchandise” -Morty Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/nLvlZKkpFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The light is blinking: "Come and listen to the idiot!" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Vandelay Industries, Kel Varnsen speaking. May we help you?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/48q46xh54B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I couldn't raise a kid? C'mon, I love bossing people around."- Elaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/HCGXRIeIGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I relate to George through you. We're more like friends-in-law." - Elaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Q0rSOQjTJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need the secure packaging of Jockeys. My boys need a house!" - Kramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: Fish. What do they do? Elaine: What do you do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: "I long for you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/pF1K9goUhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we not human?! If we pick, do we not bleed?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/OI7k1ycIOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine: Who walks into a women's bedroom without knocking?! Kramer: I thought it was a closet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pity is very underrated" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Kramer Poster!! http://t.co/m8CBYp4DyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: I was audited last year. At first I thought well, IRS kinda sounds like Toys 'R Us maybe won't be so bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Here’s to those that wish us well…and all all the rest can go to hell” -Elaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/x1opxKlq8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've always been a stall man" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: Looking for the quotes. Gotta check the quotes. Love a good quote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The sea was angry that day my friends, like an old man trying to send back soup at a deli” -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: I never feel comfortable in the woman's department. I feel like I'm a little too close to trying on a dress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I long for you" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't think I'm special. My mother always said I'm not special" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like the button fly. That is one place on my wardrobe I do not need sharp interlocking metal teeth. Its a mink trap down there" -Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/IE3h6kGrlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An affair? That's so adult. It's like martinis and stockings and William Holden" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not into working out. My philosophy: No pain, no pain" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/AEsdJXpD28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My parents didn't want to move to Florida, but they turned sixty, and that's the law" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/nGhc9Xu2rR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who read the tabloids deserve to be lied to" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/cCPqxoF44f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: "Toasting makes me uncomfortable. But toast I love. Never start the day without a good piece of toast. In fact, let's toast…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jnfEA2BVs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Here’s to feeling good all the time!” -Kramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/TfyYPxGCPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“They always remember the first time. I don’t want to be remembered. I want to be forgotten.” -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/WEKLG6U5RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have never been anyone's type, but apparently, this Marisa Tomei loves funny, quirky, bald men." - George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/i3K9pbbfpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newman: "I mean parcels are rarely damaged during shipping." Jerry: "Define rarely." Newman: "Frequently."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/zy7xx4QmR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do they call it a "building"? It looks like they're finished. Why isn't it a "built?" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: http://t.co/oOoxA5RHkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We’re just raindrops on a windshield” -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/BZL8zqZkef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’m like a phoenix, rising from Arizona!” —Frank Costanza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Pvo04vXIA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ve figured out that the non-event is the best part of life" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody is sicker than me." - George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hawaii... The most sought-after postal route of them all. The air is so dewy-sweet you don't even have to lick the stamps." - Newman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: http://t.co/XNbT7owKC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/NvQlAPs9Gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes the road less traveled is less traveled for a reason" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/YDmNRkiP3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not into working out. My philosophy: No pain, no pain" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/6UHFDku5lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men want the same thing from their underwear that they want from women: a little bit of support, and a little bit of freedom -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/69IPV87dCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“How do you guys walk around with those things?” -Elaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/irQFCZFqLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: What kind of a person are you? Jerry: I think I'm pretty much like you, only successful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/yYRgXkW37O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CostanzaQs: http://t.co/FzLNGhtVJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who buys an umbrella anyway? You can get them for free at the coffee shop in those metal cans" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: "Looking at cleavage is like looking at the sun. You don't stare at it. You get a sense of it and you look away."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody takes better care of their hair than me. You can serve dinner on my head" - Elaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the cops arrest a mime, do they tell him he has the right to remain silent?" -Jerry Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: You will be stunned. Elaine: Stunned by soup? Jerry: You can't eat this soup standing up. Your knees buckle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/v4bKk3dqlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would give up red meat just to get a glimpse of you in a bra" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/wT337FnHRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine: My father thinks George is gay. Jerry: Because of all the singing? Elaine: No, he pretty much thinks everyone is gay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/kTmFLgtYJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're gonna be all over that shuffleboard court!" -Frank Costanza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/MQ5oVNrTHi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>