<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Walmart shopper is accused of making more than 1,000 fake returns: A 23-year-old Walmart shopper is accused of making fraudulent returns at more than 1,000 of the chain's stores across the country. https://t.co/QR0Mu76sVa https://t.co/vtL9l0U2Dc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Network Engineers Job: Date: Mar 13, 2018 Location: North Las Vegas, NV, US Company: SAIC Cloud Network Engineers (Job Number:434796) Description: Job Description – Responsible for supporting the delivery of Enterprise Architecture (EA) for a large… https://t.co/4hQxNAZQHL https://t.co/CWokXYH7zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer / Architect: About Us Altamira Technologies has a long and successful history providing innovative solutions throughout the U.S. National Security community. Headquartered in McLean, Virginia, Altamira serves the defense,… https://t.co/ahAL2BZeHp https://t.co/CRSKpWZLkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump's Twitter feed is getting more and more bizarre: It's hard to say that President Donald Trump's Twitter habits are getting stranger. After all, this is a President who has, from the start of his presidential campaign, used the social… https://t.co/GCmS1fGjwS https://t.co/444P9Wt0Sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering: Software Engineering – Seattle, WA. Work closely with client mgmt. to identify &amp; specify complex business requirement and processes for supported applications. Equal Opportunity Employer, Affirmative Action Employer,… https://t.co/1t5l0afMSZ https://t.co/kO9dWYhGbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer I: Application Developer I Since 1928 The Concord Group Insurance Company has been protecting the interests of residents and business owners. We are a well-established Property and Casualty Mutual Insurance Company located in… https://t.co/mLl0OBtb6Z https://t.co/gXbBN27sKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: UX Designer| Daimler &gt; Karriere &gt; Jobsuche &gt; Stellenausschreibungen Wonach suchen Sie? UX Designer Mai 2018 Mercedes-Benz Research &amp; Development North America, Inc. UX Designer Aufgaben Embedded in a worldwide network Mercedes-Benz Research… https://t.co/XuV4VaYSLg https://t.co/dLuS2YNgcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer- JAVA: Backend Software Engineer- JAVA/J2EE Ref No.: 18-26083 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey Backend Software Engineer- JAVA/J2EE, Spring framework including Spring Boot and STS, SOA and microservices, GIT, REST APIs https://t.co/u9eh26NWtg https://t.co/1ZOk0amvs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Internship Data Analyst: ATLAS COPCO COMPRESSORS LLC Company Description: Atlas Copco Compressors LLC is part of the Compressor Technique Business Area, and its headquarters are located in Rock Hill, S.C. The company manufactures, markets, and… https://t.co/kamAeoGVfr https://t.co/JQaHxdzF64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Technical Support Representative Our Technical Support Representatives are the front line support for more than 290 million customers. As a Technical Support Representative, you will: – Maintain exceptional customer… https://t.co/pOQA2leN50 https://t.co/aYnqWtK76q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk SME: Splunk SME Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10155 Minimum Clearance Required Secret Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Splunk Subject Matter Expert (SME). The successful candidate should be… https://t.co/ImorNHZsX4 https://t.co/kDDfPiMP3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Model Based Systems Engineers-Aurora, CO:   Job Description – Model Based Systems Engineers-Aurora, CO (18011125) Model Based Systems Engineers-Aurora, CO Requisition ID : 18011125 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/UQbQWaIaHN https://t.co/98EM2gczAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack Software Developer: Tresata has an immediate full time opening for a full-stack software developer position in the Charlotte office to assist in development of our game changing predictive analytics platform. We are looking for someone who… https://t.co/Z1dMx9RA64 https://t.co/hLxEGjTSHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: What you're seeing is not what's happening: While addressing veterans at a Missouri convention, President Donald Trump encouraged his supporters to stick with him, even if they're seeing signs of trouble. https://t.co/r8fADBMrFE https://t.co/c70O9LRziL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Description: Position Requires a Top Secret (TS/SCI) Clearance with a Polygraph. ***OPEN TO ALL SKILL LEVELS*** Customer is looking for a Web Developer – Subject Matter Expert with experience in designing and developing complex, dynamic… https://t.co/ih2jtgHjIb https://t.co/Ekfas90KjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer: Description: Position Requires a Top Secret (TS/SCI) Clearance with a Polygraph. ******* OPEN TO ALL SKILL LEVELS*********** The Sponsor is seeking an Applications Developer to develop and support enterprise web applications. The… https://t.co/t3PKajSCjS https://t.co/drquW6EqDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Analyst (IdenTrust): – Technical Support Analyst (IdenTrust) &gt; Technical Support Analyst (IdenTrust) Full-timeHID Global 2017-02-09Region: North America Salt Lake City, UT North AmericaUSSalt Lake City, UT HID Global is the trusted… https://t.co/ClOi6jNXgw https://t.co/qUcz4ESRW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst/Requirements Manager: Business Analyst/Requirements Manager ===================================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must… https://t.co/pADfMZATUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Single Family Land Development: Santa Ana, CA Full-time $85k – $200k Posted Today If you are a Senior Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive salary depending on experience. –… https://t.co/8PWz2EfwJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property Administrator 2 – Clearance Required:   Job Description – Property Administrator 2 – Clearance Required (18013447) Property Administrator 2 – Clearance Required Requisition ID : 18013447 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US… https://t.co/m0TYtqyspu https://t.co/GNtEJSFmdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Incident Response Analyst 2/3: Company Overview For 29 years, clients in the private and public sectors have relied upon SOS International LLC (SOSi) for critical operations in the world’s most challenging environments. SOSi is privately held, was… https://t.co/B7fSLCEHfE https://t.co/LqltnLFS7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance – IT: A Quality Assurance Specialist in Information Technology leads compliance initiatives in support of company policies and Regulatory requirements to support product and internal IT controls related to 21 CFR Part 820 &amp; Part 11,… https://t.co/OviSuHZJ8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge grants immunity for five witnesses in Manafort case: A federal judge in Alexandria, Virginia, has granted the request for five witnesses to testify with immunity in the criminal trial of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort. https://t.co/cHiPjPz8xR https://t.co/FKgJVyjxhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Analysis Specialist: IT Analysis Specialist. Analyze clinical trial experiment data for Pharm. co. in Rancho Cucamon-ga, CA. Require Master’s Degree in Statistics or Applied Mathematics &amp; Statistics; SAS Certified Advanced Programmer for SAS 9… https://t.co/3wIRcGg5OK https://t.co/hcmYVMEdDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D Artist: 3D Artist – Create visual concepts. Develop graphic designs for game product. Requires Bachelor’s of Fine Arts in Game Design or related field. Any suitable combo of education, training &amp;/or experience is acceptable. Jobsite: Irvine, CA.… https://t.co/EXEo1wIPn4 https://t.co/5R4B3VL7iQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto gunman kills 2, injures 12, police say: Multiple people were shot outside of a Toronto, Canada, restaurant around 10 p.m. Sunday, Toronto police Sgt. Glenn Russell tells CNN. https://t.co/HdMGNm3XMS https://t.co/WjBOJwu3Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SOFTWARE/IT Project Manager at Palo Alto, CA: Res for customer satisfaction by ensuring that value outlined in purchase process is achieved, documented, communicated, &amp; delivered throughout engagement. Frequent travel to customer sites… https://t.co/uQzKrFN8i7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Student Communities/Learning and Career Development: Job Description Tracking Code A18-65-S21410/S20001 Job Description The American Chemical Society is looking for a Project Manager, Student Communities to join the Education Division.… https://t.co/tTlpXBcrFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-38428 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description This is an opportunity to join a team building a… https://t.co/r2NCBkHZtF https://t.co/cdoa4tlcOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rail Electro/Mechanical Product Marketing Specialist Rail Automation: **Rail Electro/Mechanical Product Marketing Specialist – Rail Automation** Multiple Locations:Louisville, Kentucky; Munhall, Pennsylvania; Jacksonville, Florida Job Family: Marketing… https://t.co/7Se76kfAs1 https://t.co/oChriPVphG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Level Network Architect 5:   Job Description – Enterprise Level Network Architect 5 (18013887) Enterprise Level Network Architect 5 Requisition ID : 18013887 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/FayEaK1efq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Customer Data Services: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management,… https://t.co/Q17FY5hKJq https://t.co/XQIPCU8frI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Industrial experience: Java Developer with Industrial experience Ref No.: 18-31550 Location: Plano, Texas Java Developer with Industrial experience Plano, TX Need Java developers with any industrial background. Please don’t submit… https://t.co/iHvrBxS7Cw https://t.co/xoW8zSho07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Programmer – NJ: Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to: – Clinical trial databases: – Review synopsis and/or protocol and provide Data Manager with comments for the Synopsis Review Committee (SRC) meeting – Review protocols for… https://t.co/K1evvG1b7P https://t.co/NMM6ij1lt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: Careers Center | ETL Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/hqkhOKUDS5 https://t.co/3LCBoQ3IQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The recent indictment of 12 Russian agents could be the high point for Mueller. Or it could be the crest of one of several coming waves.: With the recent criminal indictment of 12 Russian intelligence agents, the special counsel's office made clear it… https://t.co/1mz2y432TT https://t.co/TEBg0J9O0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Trail Running Shoes (2018): Salewa, Vasque, Hoka One One, and More: These light, nimble, and rugged trail runners will become your favorite all-purpose outdoor shoes. https://t.co/drE3MaYXwR https://t.co/XacqOTLFQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Information Technology Systems Administrator (MITSA) Associate – Up to $5 Sign-on Bonus: Requisition ID 2018-41466 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description… https://t.co/GuXtllV2oN https://t.co/YU4cmAVFvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Development Representative II (SAP Ariba): SunIRef:Sales:title Sales Development Representative II (SAP Ariba) SAP 1,617 reviews – Alpharetta, GA 30004 Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Sales Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional… https://t.co/zHD1kdvnWw https://t.co/Ex3cmZj0Xa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: **Technical Support Engineer** Locations:Buffalo Grove, Illinois Job Family: Engineering New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building Technologies **Business Unit:** Region Americas **Requisition… https://t.co/pm9fvjwLmW https://t.co/DimCvhXRNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer at Liberty Mutual Group Skip Navigation – Personal Insurance – Business Insurance – About Liberty Mutual – Our Company – International – Careers MenuLiberty Mutual InsuranceHome CloseLiberty Mutual Insurance – Home – Working… https://t.co/5zOpR9c88v https://t.co/r86d1YVGz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yankees fans boo pitcher off the mound https://t.co/PWLHjy2fB8 https://t.co/fJzg42VH48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigation into tragedy could take up to a year: The investigation into the sinking of a duck boat that killed 17 people in Missouri --- including nine from one family -- could take up to a year to complete, the National Transportation Safety Board… https://t.co/UuDVR08nD1 https://t.co/BxGlSSBkNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A second Trump-Putin meeting would be careless: Donald Trump is President, but he is not king of America; the country is not his private property. https://t.co/7BxuvFWyUZ https://t.co/Kl9uPxnN6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Software Engineer: For Johnson &amp; Johnson Front-end Software Engineer job – Engineering (IT) – Portland, Oregon Skip to Main Content Our Stories – Latest News – Innovation – Caring &amp; Giving – Personal Stories – Health &amp; Wellness – Our Heritage… https://t.co/f7H8aKPGJ7 https://t.co/UfrErNm12s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Ref No.:18-15216 Location: Overland Park, Kansas Scope of Work Network Engineer is responsible for diverse network platforms/topologies within a network management center or organization. The candidate provides… https://t.co/RBOsQi9PpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPC Systems Administrator: Job Description Candidates shall have a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related field, and have ten years of demonstrable experience in system administration and support of a large client-server based IT enterprise. Or… https://t.co/gm54lntMOi https://t.co/8QcTw4dHfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator Junior: Tracking Code FTEUS-18-1142-F Job Code 18-1142 Posting Title Systems Administrator – Junior Post Date 6/28/2018 Full Time / Part-Time Full Time Travel No Travel Required City Newport News State VA Country US Description… https://t.co/kYPsaLiYqp https://t.co/PgE3lFp1vO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: What We Do: Temenos Group is a market leading banking software provider, partnering with banks and other financial institutions to transform their businesses and stay ahead of a changing marketplace. Headquartered in Geneva and with… https://t.co/MZvywUu6vH https://t.co/HQYF1tqD9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D Pastry Chef: R&amp;D Pastry Chef Baked goods manufacture seeks 1 R&amp;D Pastry Chef. Required 6 months experience as head bakery chef scheduling &amp; ordering raw materials; planning raw material allocation; overseeing staff allocation. Must be proficient with… https://t.co/WjKatzWqeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two Americas. Sometimes in the same state.: A tale of two Virginia districts explains why the geographic, demographic and cultural chasm between the parties in the House of Representatives is about to grow much wider -- with ominous… https://t.co/4J8dSIG9Ty https://t.co/uCDAemgnLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Backpacks for Work (2018): GoRuck, Peak Design, Chrome, Tom Bihn: These are the work bags that we absolutely adore. https://t.co/LEWTmvYTMz https://t.co/N5Pfey16nV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 dead after tourist boat capsizes in Missouri: A day after a duck boat capsized and sank during a severe storm at a southern Missouri lake, killing at least 11 people, divers are resuming a search for six people who remain missing. https://t.co/gMbanv1kCs https://t.co/2EHY3S65xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROGRAMMER ANALYSTS: PROGRAMMER ANALYSTS: Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: Design, develop multi-tier applications. Gather, analyze business requirements. Create ,execute functional &amp; design specifications. Execute,… https://t.co/szo08Xhpu6 https://t.co/CAaiexPR3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-Prime Day Deals: Dell, Bose, Urbanears: Did you miss the excellent deals this week? Don't worry. We got you. https://t.co/g71hinYFqg https://t.co/yPX1ToBwbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Operations Professional: Network Security Operations Professional $90-110K Reston, VA The Technology Services Group is responsible for providing a sound and robust technology infrastructure for our business and systems. The Network… https://t.co/irTPMZWnit https://t.co/9krlzpRHP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Enterprise Application Architect: Director, Enterprise Application Architect Enterprise Applications Foster City, California Description Qualys is looking for a Senior Business Systems Analyst who can lead, coordinate, plan and facilitate end… https://t.co/MHbdaM5dke https://t.co/YPfOeBkiYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description: Position Requires a Top Secret (TS/SCI) Clearance with a Polygraph. Seeking a System Administrator with a diverse skillset. You will support an important and complex customer communication system. The Candidate is… https://t.co/QH5Xm0l4HO https://t.co/EvtoAPr0es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Russian accused of using sex, lies and guns to infiltrate US politics: The young Russian gun enthusiast was struggling. Maria Butina had twice applied for visas to attend the National Rifle Association's glitzy annual meeting. But she said she was… https://t.co/SrbGuve91q https://t.co/zLXSyiARSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Software Engineering Manager – $100k/yr – REMOTE WORK: We’re running an Online Hiring Tournament on July 28th to hire Ruby on Rails Software Engineering Managers (USD $100K/yr). This event will include all testing for the role. Upon grading… https://t.co/ZT9I9Bq44E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Systems Engineer: SAP Systems Engineer Fleur De Lis Energy, LLC Irving, TX Fleur De Lis Energy, LLC in Irving, TX seeks SAP Systems Engineer to test, maintain, and monitor computer programs and systems, including coordinating installation of computer… https://t.co/7w5tcZ5D7M https://t.co/3CrHj91q41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorilla Glass 6 Is More Durable and Built For the Future: The next generation of Corning's Gorilla Glass can withstand repeated drops—and is built for the future of smartphones. https://t.co/QdnYWUo0TD https://t.co/CNxMWXbSbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Schoolhouse Rock' pokes fun at Trump: "The Late Show with Stephen Colbert" uses "Schoolhouse Rock" to explain double negatives after President Trump said he misspoke when he said "would" instead of "wouldn't" during his press conference with Vladimir… https://t.co/hrFASunHoi https://t.co/KfOwIzwpW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Campaign Developer: Adobe Campaign Developer in Winston Salem, North Carolina, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant –… https://t.co/gRjebwdZcK https://t.co/JJGRbLGjBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics CRM Software Engineer: Are you a Pioneering Spirit? Lowe’s is looking for Visionaries, Risk-takers, Adventurers. Lowes is looking for someone that is driven by potentialA trailblazer of innovation. We are a multi-billion dollar company with 5… https://t.co/f8ud8fsaFZ https://t.co/XX6gmZ1x3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/RMppXSKAkc, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in situations of moderate complexity. May also be… https://t.co/TImdWRr5o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Putin: the pictures tell the story https://t.co/dRv2c4Yrvl https://t.co/95MYKzFtpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer Sr: Req ID : 428744BR_5 Job Code/Title : E1953:Project Engineer Sr Job Description : Lockheed Martin Enterprise Business Services (EBS) organization is seeking a highly skilled, team-oriented project engineer to join in supporting the… https://t.co/c6OUcBAzie https://t.co/g2CKShwem4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Public Safety Solution: Software Developer, Public Safety Solution ========================================== Tyler Technologies is looking for a passionate, talented Software Developer with an interest in software build and… https://t.co/6jpluZybZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Job Description LocationSan Jose – CA, US LevelPhD Experience2-5 Professional Available since3/7/2018 Functional areaResearch &amp; Development, Information Technology, Electrical Engineering BackgroundPhysics, Physics / Mathematics, Software… https://t.co/9RZx7CD0He https://t.co/L3sqHD5eGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Senior Analyst: TECHNOLOGYDeloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Senior Analyst in Kansas City, MO and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Assist in providing IT consulting services… https://t.co/syjU6qXcoo https://t.co/9DPyOhm3ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Donald Trump just said one thing, but meant something else -- again: This exchange, between President Donald Trump and ABC's Cecilia Vega at the close of a Cabinet meeting on Wednesday, is breathtaking: https://t.co/6qckcjg1QV https://t.co/PlCF3Y7dfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Home Depot USA, Inc. Has multiple openings for Data Scientists to formulate and apply mathematical modeling and other optimizing methods to develop and interpret information to assist management with decision making, policy formulation,… https://t.co/ugfIWyDHiG https://t.co/nm65pKfSxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Administrator: Social Media Administrator Eden Foods (Lenawee County, MI) seeks a full-time Social Media Administrator for an internal marketing team – experienced, organized and motivated. Teamwork and communication skills are critical.… https://t.co/nIE0wmNxYz https://t.co/dhlon0xGHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #IR1017PB: Senior Software Engineer sought by Crowdstrike, Inc., Irvine, CA: Lead backend engineering efforts from rapid prototypes to large-scale applications across CrowdStrike products.   recblid b7oxh9qlvlvglbdiil6yy6fgl4aghk https://t.co/ABBXXpQqeB https://t.co/o5u3KiPgqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst Staff: Job ID #: 10824 – Position Type: Regular Full Time – Location: La Crosse, WI – Shift: 1st – Department: Information Technology and Technical Support – Education Required: Bachelors Degree – Experience Required: 1 – 3 Years… https://t.co/EiJovOnSuT https://t.co/SDNXAM2b1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Pleasanton, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/26/18, Posted Date – 06/26/18 Primary SkillsDevOpsTax TermsFull TimeOverview DevOps Engineer Pleasanton CA Salary :- 70K Job Overview and Essential Functions:… https://t.co/7SsqkA3ZN5 https://t.co/eHhs39NUOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MGM sues Las Vegas shooting victims: The owner of the Mandalay Bay hotel says it bears no liability in last year's Las Vegas concert massacre and is asking the courts to extend it federal protections that shield companies who provide anti-terrorism… https://t.co/eR4ub7Ysbq https://t.co/12bcarMIa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visual Designer II: Join us to do the best work of your life. At frog we are united by our shared passion for outcomes that transform the human experience. We accomplish these outcomes by taking on complex challenges, big asks, and things that have never… https://t.co/aosCRjAeol https://t.co/s1qshEXLxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: Description Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers, Trustwave… https://t.co/FZLkuRWuCZ https://t.co/974dspQfa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Applications Support: Job Description Job Description Engage with the product at every stage, from design, through testing and then into production and support. Support the business and other application support teams in delivering a… https://t.co/Lq1kTqDfPC https://t.co/SDb8ESSvJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A storm ruined her beach wedding. Then a total stranger saved the day: It was a wedding-day nightmare. The sky was dark, thunder rumbled, lightning cracked across the sky and large raindrops soaked the flower-petal pathway and chairs waiting for wedding… https://t.co/IiWCkCO6kU https://t.co/MbEWgouwfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Manager, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/TMaQ5UxhBI https://t.co/youLjZPgHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Our team in Winston-Salem, NC supports a very large policy/billing system used by National General Insurance which causes the group to continue growing and adding new headcount. Primary Purpose: This position coordinates and participates… https://t.co/tz8ngjDWQc https://t.co/tTZ6QURsG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community Manager: Menlo Park, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Community Manager with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing • Retain clients by consistently meeting needs and having effect relationships •… https://t.co/Rl7Vj1eHSw https://t.co/Nhq8UUTNm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Ref No.:18-00320 Category: ************* Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type:Full-time Experience Level: 3 Years Start Date: 07/12/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work Schedule:7:30 –… https://t.co/Le5lrelw1f https://t.co/cDxWjNqXrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III #58808: Software Engineer III sought by Accolade, Inc. in Plymouth Meeting, PA. Job # 58808. Resolve complex technical issues and deliver innovative solutions that improve user engagement, system availability, resiliency, and… https://t.co/qbqgjiRTCe https://t.co/BN5qLUicg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Amazon Prime Day Deals (2018): Home, Laptops, Echo, Kindle: Prime Day is finally here! We have the deals you're looking for. https://t.co/93CXH8tVCA https://t.co/2tFGjjemew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: V. Murphy. Please reference job # below: Software Engineer positions (Mountain View/Palo Alto/San Bruno, CA) Design, develop, modify, and/or… https://t.co/E4SmWV0PzQ https://t.co/QkvVB8jr7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roku TV Wireless Speakers: Price, Specs, and Release Date: Roku's new $199 wireless speakers are matched with an optional wireless button you place in another room and use as a voice remote. https://t.co/FtfIrMjKRt https://t.co/ACr5RP7K0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago police release body camera footage of man killed by officers: Chicago police have identified the man whose death at the hands of an officer led to heated protests in the city this weekend. https://t.co/mvvEVjvqil https://t.co/xS1UpaJmr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIVIL ENGINEERING PROJECT MANAGER / OFFICE MANAGER: Title: CIVIL ENGINEERING PROJECT MANAGER / OFFICE MANAGER Location: Mechanicsburg, PA Job ID: 36046 col-wide Job Description: ARRO Consulting, Inc. is always eager to add new talent to our team of… https://t.co/UgV3wJOq8K https://t.co/axuPQ2IZm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandra Oh's Emmy nom represents new wave https://t.co/OtNCBIk3Vz https://t.co/9RD5Cgz0JT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Jersey City, NJ Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/10/2017 Job Description Job Description The IT Project Manger role is to drive the development and execution… https://t.co/OSV29QGlsS https://t.co/OvKrBZsrFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sofware Engineer (All levels, must have CS or similar degree and be clearable): Sofware Engineer (All levels, must have CS or similar degree and be clearable) in Sterling, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do… https://t.co/IihW3l7vX8 https://t.co/27UsngTi2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architectural Project Manager: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $85k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with 5+ years of experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Based in beautiful Los Angeles, CA we are an interior design and… https://t.co/5ICWfnxnf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manufacturing Engineer: Senior Manufacturing Engineer  REQ# 180000BK Position Overview: As a Senior Manufacturing Engineer at Entrust Datacard you will have opportunities to: ·Work on new product development teams ·Work with state-of-the art tools… https://t.co/SN4duawICF https://t.co/MqW0NG0gMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Project Manager: Job Details Req ID 14354 Title SAP Project Manager City Racine State Wisconsin Job Function Info Tech Salaried / Hourly Salaried Job Description Through its people and brands, CNH Industrial delivers power, technology and innovation… https://t.co/LoOe7ey8ll https://t.co/amXBhqmANF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal Developer: Drupal Developer Ref No.: 18-30233 Location: Loveland, Colorado Title: Drupal Developer Location: Loveland, CO 9 to 12 months OPT will not applicable Job Description: Preferably from a physical sciences, engineering, or computer science… https://t.co/4jfOgDC28K https://t.co/vc10fMSUoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of 'loner' culture: In a striking image by Korean photographer Nina Ahn, a solitary figure stands by a window, street lights glimmering around her. Another shows a woman in her 20s sitting alone on a guardrail beside an empty highway in Seoul. https://t.co/T3RdkugCCs https://t.co/kraDxMPJJG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>