<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Addy is a one year-old Boxer puppy who enjoyed her milelong walk in a light mist over to the Cathedral Close and back home.  She regrets that the St. Francis… https://t.co/sELvo45F3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maggie enjoyed her walk, but she liked lolling around in her crate afterwards on this rainy day even more!  Her older brother Monty gets the sofa after his… https://t.co/z8kswau5tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: If you are turned away at the polls because your name is not on the register, don’t walk away. Say this: I REQUEST A PROVI…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinMKruse: “The government of the United States is not, in any sense, founded on the Christian religion.” — The Treaty of Tripoli, 17…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politvidchannel: BREAKING: WOW the Des Moines Register Which Leans Conservative just endorsed ALL DEMOCRATS, Said GOP  “needs to be vot…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As seen on the Cathedral Close.  #unitywalk #unitywalk2018 @ Washington National Cathedral https://t.co/vvHf9Fp9Qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IronStache: Don’t worry about how I’m dealing with the hit ads.

We knew this was coming because they can’t win on ideas.

Worry about…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dianabutlerbass: No words. https://t.co/4Ng6dNS0qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: Trump has a record of attacking the rights of protesters nationwide, and now his administration is targeting the First Amendment…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: Delawareans: You're up. Today is your final deadline to register to vote—make sure you're counted: https://t.co/tTgeqxN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren Thank you! https://t.co/exfhWkxAea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterbakernyt: Who was it that said the Saudis have messed with the wrong newspaper? If they think this is going away without answers,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgie really seemed to enjoy being out in the cooler weather, and covered over a mile on her walk.  She found a stick early on and carried it with pride —… https://t.co/MJhjVggtcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monty pondered what delicious delicacies might once have graced these https://t.co/Vkij5ccFaz boxes, now put out for recycling on a neighbor’s curb... ah, the mysteries of… https://t.co/cOP1cw8Yvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoarseWisperer: Trump isn’t upset that Saudi Arabia killed a dissident.

He’s jealous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: The Trump administration is proposing to dramatically limit spontaneous demonstrations, protests near the White House and Nationa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: New Yorkers and Oklahomans: Today is your last chance to register to vote. 

Take two minutes now to check your registr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: Retweet if you’re proud to be an impolite, arrogant woman. #BlahBlahBlah  https://t.co/7IXQH9adaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jax and I retraced our afternoon walk steps, covering almost a mile and a half again in the neighborhood.  I taught him the expression,”It’s raining cats and… https://t.co/kWLjriWjit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine https://t.co/Xm25fqDp1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rhollerith: So proud that the Cathedral will be Matthew’s final resting place. God bless and keep him. https://t.co/acAU5k3g2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: Seriously, you asked Russia to hack me on national television. https://t.co/YPktJyQ7Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halloween is coming, and things are starting to get a bit spooky in Jax’s neighborhood, starting with these unexpected ghosts who have the audacity to remain… https://t.co/f0qLdb4228]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: The Ryan-backed @CLFSuperPAC has spent hundreds of thousands of dollars propping up my opponent @RepJohnKatko's campaign.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmbassadorRice: Why is this outrage getting so little attention? https://t.co/VGEHpCz7PZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WNCathedral: .@WNCathedral is collecting messages of love and support for Matthew Shepard's family as we prepare to welcome him home on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: The @GOP #TaxScam gives 83% of the benefits to millionaires, billionaires, &amp; big corporations. I want at tax plan that wor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Winslow, a 17 month-old Cavachon who thinks the world is a mighty fine place!  We covered a mile and a half on his midday walk, during which he succeeded… https://t.co/6RBBXZlFyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndivisibleNY24: Constituent calls out @RepJohnKatko for his dishonest attack ads. Instead of offering thoughtful solutions to our heal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: A young boy’s life has been cut short to senseless gun violence. My heart goes out to his family and friends. 

This is th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WNCathedral: 20 years after his death, Matthew Shepard will be interred at @WNCathedral on 10/26 at 10 am.  More details at https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @dog_feelings A 12/10, perhaps?  And where is this dog’s fren?  Depicted in the adjacent floor mosaic, perhaps? https://t.co/SzkRT9LV4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sikh_coalition @valariekaur @SikhProf Signed! https://t.co/ySvAZKWLYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @indivisible410: Maryland's voter registration deadline is October 16th.

Check your registration or register at https://t.co/fHQ1G41j5V…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: He literally offered to pay the legal fees of supporters that beat the crap out of people. https://t.co/rW0P2fvqzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinWelby: If you are walking in darkness today, this is a reminder: you are loved. You are precious. You have value. Sometimes we ne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: https://t.co/t9EWEnyPKS is why you should always buy your name’s URL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: The Trump administration wants to pass new rules that would hamper peaceful protests in DC.

We have until Monday to make our voi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNBC @business Please follow @nytimes lead on this. https://t.co/C5puoNez6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: Sign this petition to @RepJohnKatko for debates in all 4 counties as soon as possible! The hallmark of democracy is fair,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jax came across this abandoned, ferocious-looking shoe on our evening walk and wondered if Max, from Maurice Sendak’s “Where the Wild Things Are,” had been in… https://t.co/hi6ggQtk8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: Great to participate in civic education today at the @LeadSyr class at the Onondaga County Justice Center. 

We had a grea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Maggie, an old tennis ball found on the trail today, plus a portion of the trail that is still muddy, equals: Total Bliss!  @WagWalking #wagwalker… https://t.co/3v1VI7RVm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: If you or someone you care about has health problems, they hate you, they really hate you https://t.co/gk6F4pD2on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this hot, humid mid-October afternoon, Jax covered well over a mile.  We even did some obedience training.  Such a good boy!  @WagWalking #wagwalker… https://t.co/10Isu59WD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSchumer: The deadline to register to vote in New York State is Friday, October 12. That’s in just THREE days. If you’re not register…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: 4 more days to register to vote! 

In order to vote on November 6 you need to be registered at your current address by Fri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: Today, October 9, is the final deadline to register to vote in this critical election if you live in one of these state…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dana_balter @SUforDana @IndivisibleNY24 Let’s get NY24 on the next updated list!  #FlipNY24 https://t.co/mKAS92Ddli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJDionne: Democracy is all that opponents of the GOP's Supreme Court coup have left. In November's elections, the party responsible for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndivisibleTeam: We're devastated. We're furious. And we're going to do something about it. Channel your outrage into action: find out…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: I want 7 debates across the district and 4 open access, joint, public town halls, one in each county. @RepJohnKatko has on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cmclymer: Married couple immigrated to Maine from Jamaica in the 1920s. One was a janitor and the other a maid. They worked hard and se…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RevDrBarber: GOP is using segregationist language of “mob rule” to fire up their white nationalist base. Lindsay Graham said he was “pi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenJeffMerkley: Don’t give up.

Don’t give up. 

Don’t give up.

Don’t give up.

Don’t give up.

Don’t give up.

Don’t give up.

Don’t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdKrassen: Here are Democratic Senators who need your help in the upcoming midterms. Please follow and VOTE!

@SenBillNelson - FL
@RepJ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillieJeanKing: Thank you, Dr. Christine Blasey Ford, for your courage in sharing your truth, which has given so many others the streng…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: These, on the other hand, are very fine people 2/ https://t.co/RikDGyxp0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: Just to be clear: this is a mob, probably paid by George Soros 1/ https://t.co/5swXPSJljJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mikel_Jollett: So the women with two Master’s degrees and a PhD is too dumb to know who ASSAULTED her but the drunk frat boy has a perf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CoryBooker: Amidst it all:

Let us not

Curl up,

Shut up, or 

Give up

Let us continue

To stand up

To speak up

To rise up

To neve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RBReich: If nothing else gets you to the polls to vote D: Checks and balances are gone. Rs now control all 3 branches of government, Rs…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDerk: @jaynordlinger @jaketapper From a middle of the road guy who’s voted both ways over40 years… I’ve already rented a 15 passen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: If the Saudi crown prince thought he could stifle criticism by murdering journalist Jamal Khashoggi, let's prove him wrong…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hankgreen: Retweet this if you are going to vote every single chance you get until you're dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mebudde: The definition of an accidental activist: “one catapulted into the work of changing the world by a life-changing experience of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMFlint: REMEMBER, REMEMBER THE 6TH OF NOVEMBER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @John_Barnitt: November 6th is exactly a MONTH AWAY, retweet this if you’re voting in the midterm elections!!! Most voter registration d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeteSouza: An embarrassment of a tweet from a US Senator https://t.co/9czsVehCJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: Older woman crying in photo: “How are we going to find the strength to keep fighting? Are we going to be out here for an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RanttMedia: When Franken was accused—he resigned

When Schneiderman was accused—he resigned

When Conyers was accused—he resigned

When…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisgeidner: VIDEO: The scene outside the Supreme Court when Kavanaugh’s confirmation was announced. https://t.co/5SF7Q27TeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @episcopalcafe: "President Trump and his supporters find community by rejoicing in the suffering of those they hate and fear." The Cruel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEllenShow: This tweet is for Dr. Ford. You put yourself through so much and I want you to know it wasn’t in vain. You started a move…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenDuckworth: Toughest day at my job so far. Scared and sad for my nation right now. Determined to fight harder now than ever before to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: Check out the latest ad from our campaign - @RepJohnKatko's voting record proves what we all know: he's a Trump yes-man. h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feaya is something of a canine introvert and was upstairs lying down at the back of the walk-in closet when I arrived.  However, she was fine with my putting… https://t.co/Uy02q97dm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackmjenkins And tragically, we now know that as Bishop @Mebudde was preaching her extraordinary sermon @WNCathedral on Christmas Eve, about love coming into the world wrapped in human flesh, a child was dying in @DHSgov detention in Texas.  Shame @SecNielsen shame. https://t.co/oWO8VzNU0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The child was held in a cell at a highway checkpoint” — Shame, @SecNielsen @DHSgov — Shame.  Your resignation is long overdue. https://t.co/Vh6Q0UJLGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickABC13: BRING SNIFFLES HOME: Born without a nose, the dog with the crooked teeth hopes a family will open their hearts to him this C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brava @Mebudde @WNCathedral @washdio @iamepiscopalian https://t.co/oEe0I1REHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RAICESTEXAS: A child is dead. https://t.co/sd46hmEDxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: Just a thought: Which should be considered more “marginal” - believing in Santa at age 7 or not believing in climate change…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t miss something quite special at historic St. Luke’s Episcopal Church — the Christmas star shining above the altar.  Blessed to have spent much of… https://t.co/AlGlJGW1EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @girlsreallyrule: So @HardballChris Matthews made some false statements at Bush's funeral that are clearly made up: “[@HillaryClinton] o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clairecmc: So sad that our dinner to say good bye to Senators that are leaving is not bipartisan. If we can’t be together to even recog…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On our walk in the woods this afternoon, Georgie could sense that deer were nearby, but she couldn’t see them and had to settle for chasing squirrels and crows!… https://t.co/GLfP7JMOGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tala adores playing in the leaves on the trail.  She also adores the frozen peanut butter Kong treats she receives upon returning home from her afternoon walk.… https://t.co/3YJMZRGIGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Give a dog a bone...” or a piece of a tree branch, as the case may be = a very happy dog.  @WagWalking #wagwalking #wagwalker #everwalk #everwalkusa… https://t.co/qzvXuKp8lI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Merrick.  Garland. https://t.co/HnOGVCpe0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dog_feelings: gooooob morning. i helped walk the small neighbor human. to the bus at the end of the street. i tried to get on with them…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidhogg111: Thank you to all the doctors standing up to the gun lobby the same way they did with the cigarette lobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Puck has a lot of pluck, and a lot of pluck has he... covering almost two and a half miles on his evening constitutional.  Hurrah for Puck!  @WagWalking… https://t.co/p7QtQYZqK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dana_balter: I am so proud to have the endorsement of UAW Region 9. Thank you to Mark Barbee and all of your members and leadership for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go, @dana_balter go!  4 Women Try to Unseat House Republicans in N.Y.; Donors and Celebrities Take Notice   via @NYTimes ⁦@IndivisibleNY24⁩ ⁦@SUforDana⁩ #FlipNY24 https://t.co/ZyYm5KnPt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bijanstephen: i've never seen a clearer explanation of plato's cave https://t.co/R8EIgpdLIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikiana_ph Thank you for what you’re doing in 2018... and you’ll be able to vote in 2020! https://t.co/eLbt8bmJMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@everwalkusa @diananyad https://t.co/1tr4a53i4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kashanacauley: When typos get Freudian: https://t.co/Xc9ET99OGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndivisibleNY24: “If anyone thinks I’m corrupted, throw me out of office right now.” There you have it people, from @RepJohnKatko himse…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>