<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/sq6EtP7Rxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/Au3dHRI0z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/5Ij29pZSwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/DKuzSEEcRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/SMQLVN4zVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/WSLRAu8fXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/iBK2ojZXFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/iKdybnQBtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/TeBKqYREjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/CFuyyxqUGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/3L1igA1pir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/5hn9Z6DOtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/E0rVRSr9fP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/mZh7WEbukZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/pjq1FPegna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/THnG6HLhQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/CSN4hRiLs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/4OXfEb6BJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/xprxzj3ziZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/A8lhIPB3IU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/9mvZ2MY0N8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BrvoC9kA4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/iolSNK6aQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/Vei62qP8wZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/9dH1Wfmjsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SE00bc5teo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/dNgiPmRdap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/84wnISUjEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/ioZozhL54Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/dNgiPmRdap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/L5gmOT5J4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/h1GqXvDVag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/XwDsL3oxEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/N261CbpPID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/6cng3n8z89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/OATSYwkEeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6DxFWL9zSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/U6EkfZWd5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/7sW7tLXVxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/0XigpxSgOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/r1dmkSEfEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/GOvZpdzt8E]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>