<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulu Hits 1 Million Subscribers As Facebook Integration Begins To Offer Social Viewing: This week has been a big... http://t.co/qeZODdhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Study Says the More Personalized, the Better: When you travel around the internet, you come across ads that ... http://t.co/ZAYXpJMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg Keynotes f8 Conference Live: Watch Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg reveal new updates to the social ... http://t.co/c94FvJlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Audit in 20 Minutes [Infographic]: InMotion Hosting has put together an infographic that tackles one of the ... http://t.co/gn07QwPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: f8 | Google defends itself in Washington | Salesforce.com buys Assisstly: Social Media:

Major changes... http://t.co/p6RAKleZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOL Adds E-Commerce to Project Devil: AOL’s Project Devil was supposed to be the key to the company’s future fin... http://t.co/ZjGSO237]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Transient Nature of Facebook's Like: The vast majority, 93%, of Facebook users click the “Like” button every... http://t.co/k5NiATTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google+: It’s A Matter of Trust: This post was written prior to yesterday’s announcement regarding Google+ being... http://t.co/QKo0VqWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Investors:  http://t.co/3bnNNizO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Thinking Now! Facebook Knows What Is Most Important To You!: Wow! What a relief! I have been having such a ... http://t.co/PEhBDisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Changes to Facebook | Deal valuations dropping | Windows Phone mindshare: Social Media:

Facebook ... http://t.co/SmSPwzqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Mentors Matter More Than Money: More public and private entities are supporting formal mentorship program... http://t.co/iKYzN9tP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WSJ Social: An End Run Around Those Pesky Pay Walls: Publications have been fiercely battling the erosion of the... http://t.co/DCLGyaZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I Did It: The TOMS Story: Blake Mycoskie explains why he jumped into the shoe business to Start Something Th... http://t.co/pIDKPRB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New New New Rules of Marketing and PR: The New New New Rules of Marketing and PRThis content from: Duct Tape... http://t.co/yhuD1QLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Profile of the Active Social Networker: Americans are spending more time on social networks and blogs, accordi... http://t.co/9xcdJ2vY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look! No Velcro! Google Wallet Arrives: Without getting all prognosticate-y about what this offering means to th... http://t.co/He6BuKrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonathan Fields Knows What's Killing Your Business Growth: Bold movers are often just as scared as you are. Here... http://t.co/bxhmzNoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix Apologizes Then Makes Matters Worse: “I messed up. I owe everyone an explanation.”
Two months ago, Netfl... http://t.co/M38hX9tm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iCircular Debuts - Just as Mobile Ad Fill Rates Start to Drop: The Associated Press and 40 newspapers have debut... http://t.co/hSrQk9LV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diageo Steps Up Facebook Presence with New Cross-border Deal: Diageo and Facebook have inked an advertising deal... http://t.co/NG3mItIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers Target the Unemployed as Money Mules:  http://t.co/sufmvbrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words that Work on Social Media: The keyword "dollars off" in a retail offer-related Facebook post provides the ... http://t.co/QvcKDCwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Update to online child privacy | Apple, Starbucks expands iTunes | MeLLmo raises $30M: Legal/Regulator... http://t.co/kfFnwmDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Look at PowerPoint Alternatives for Your Next Presentation: Not long ago, PowerPoint was the go-to tool for bu... http://t.co/SJIWGdx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Lesson in Growing Your Brand from the 'Pawn Stars': Here's a look at the many ways the stars of 'Pawn Stars' h... http://t.co/uZGfW1mD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Can Washington Help Business Create Jobs?: Washington's intrusion in business is polarizing—but most Ameri... http://t.co/riJAq3T7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Bidders eye Yahoo | Google+ launches first APIs | How to install Windows 8: Business Strategies:

... http://t.co/cTjcsDlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Closer to Design with Email Marketing Mobile Apps: For the last two years email marketers have been stea... http://t.co/AKpUUzBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News:  Facebook social ads | Sony tablet that doesn't look like an iPad | Xbox TV to launch soon: Online Ad ... http://t.co/RDAfPmTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share Maps Info Using Google+: Google continues to integrate more and more features into the web that is Google+... http://t.co/d1wKwT9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New YouTube Video Editor Goes Live | Image Stabilization, Color, Contrast, and Effects: YouTube now has a dedica... http://t.co/BoGPdTAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: 500,000 downloads for Windows 8 | Facebook subscribe | YouTube video editor: Mobile Computing:

Mi... http://t.co/SdrjGHIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blekko Now Searches HTML Coding, Other Hard-to-find Data: Blekko, which made a name for itself by implementing e... http://t.co/8hToAs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad Feld: Finding the Right Investors:  http://t.co/qBK5YKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payroll Tax Holiday: Bonus for Big Companies?:  http://t.co/9SsE4wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AdoTube's Acquisition Comes as Pre-roll Ads Surge: Exponential Interactive, Tribal Fusion’s parent company, has ... http://t.co/1mgSSTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World of Search Market Share Headlines: Every month we go through the same process. New data is released abo... http://t.co/GoLcdBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook’s Time Domination on the Web: Yesterday, we looked at some of the information that was given the latest... http://t.co/Ngm8dWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Tech 'Treps are Up in Arms over the PROTECT IP Act: Tech entrepreneurs have lambasted a new bill that they s... http://t.co/O76yFcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As GBTV Launches, Former Fox News Host Glenn Beck Claims Online TV Has Killed The Networks: GBTV is now on the a... http://t.co/a3m0FsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysts Predict a Happy Holiday Season for Retailers: It’s only been September for a couple of days now, but it... http://t.co/OpXLvB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aol and Yahoo: Please Merge Today!: Let me preface this post by saying that I have not done any (as in zero) res... http://t.co/WcDGwpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Branson on Why Biggest Doesn't Mean Best: The billionaire entrepreneur talks about how he carved a niche... http://t.co/NzZMTBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Will Never Forget: 
Join the Marketing Pilgrim Facebook Community

 http://t.co/wbgplGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Government Funding Source for Small Contractors: The Office of Naval Research funds research and developme... http://t.co/3o3JJAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. Postal Service Nears Collapse:  http://t.co/1DaObXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apps and Video Rise to the Top of Mobile Marketing Mix: Earlier this week, Frank took you through the Millennial... http://t.co/xEcsRJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brands May Have Better Toehold on Twitter Than They Think: Much ado has been made about the supposed distaste Tw... http://t.co/eACupDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bing Powered Search Continues to Chip Away at Google’s Search Dominance: It’s that time of the month again! It’s... http://t.co/GsNp64y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Offers a Step-by-Step Guide for Newbies: New guide is a big help for business owners new to the popular... http://t.co/EP9LNUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: More about Google-Zagat | Mozilla's guide to DNT | Smartphones outstrip feature devices: Google & ... http://t.co/8B5GILd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay Pushes into Social Retail With Gifts Projects Acquisition: eBay has acquired Gifts Projects - its first maj... http://t.co/8jdgxYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: More about Arrington | Who's next at Yahoo | Klout's 100M users | Nokia app downloads: Business Strate... http://t.co/8JJcLcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Klout Hits the 100 Million “Influencer” Mark: If nothing else, the social influence ranking service Klout ... http://t.co/qcFNdQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Add Former Classmates to Your Professional Network: If done right, reconnecting with old college fr... http://t.co/PasBjMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Ice Cream Sandwich coming this Fall | Tapjoy's new CMO | iPhone 5 first test photo: OS:

Goo... http://t.co/S6souuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IAB Takes Stab at Standardizing Rich Mobile Ads: The IAB Mobile Marketing Center of Excellence has released "Mob... http://t.co/TgFkZdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Big decisions at Groupon, Yahoo | .XXX begins | Twitter and Bing: Business Strategies:

Yahoo! dumps C... http://t.co/qBLlFl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carol Bartz Out As Yahoo CEO: For almost three years now Carol Bartz has been at the helm of Yahoo and it’s been... http://t.co/sbLb7fW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Bids High, Has Big Plans For Hulu, Maybe: There could be an interesting twist to the already-compelling t... http://t.co/ZABzLYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google's Hulu bid | AdMob v AdSense | iPad killer?: Ecommerce:

Google goes big with its Hulu bid.... http://t.co/11xR40x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Mobile Social Networkers Do it Every Day: Morning coffee? Check.
Review email? Check.
Twitter on mob... http://t.co/CiuWt6FM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gauging How Many Emails Your Customer Really Gets: Maybe email recipients aren't bombarded by as much email as o... http://t.co/89MZxyDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogs Seen As One of the Best Inbound Marketing Tools for Agencies: Inbound marketing encompasses a lot of Inter... http://t.co/K67wN7Vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take This Lollipop Demos the Horror of Cyberstalking: Facebook privacy is an oxymoron. The site is designed to r... http://t.co/6CvMoCGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Small Businesses Are Occupying Wall Street: Small business owners have long panned practices like baili... http://t.co/AVNEovnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Jobs Do Small Employers Create?:  http://t.co/cJawLAqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google encrypts search | Facebook power users migrate | Chime.in: Security:

Google encrypts searc... http://t.co/12Z6dMmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panda: Another Change; Plus It's A Job Killer: Google has made another tweak to Panda following the one on Oct. ... http://t.co/8zYx0Rev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google and Twitter Just Can’t Agree on Search Deal: In July, Google’s arrangement with Twitter to index all twee... http://t.co/L3WPSXhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond the Free Snacks: Spotlighting the Best Small Workplace Practices: A look at the innovative small-employer... http://t.co/YEgKZcVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sesame Street’s YouTube Channel Hacked To Show Hardcore Porn As The Muppets Go Bad: When a channel aimed entirel... http://t.co/UKz76NMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Weak ad industry hurts Yahoo talks | Wireless bill shock | Bill Gross' social network: Online Ad I... http://t.co/5pHk2KeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Questions to Answer Before You Write a Business Plan: Before you can map out a business plan, you have to ... http://t.co/o5ABkuLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Analytics Become Ever More Granular: Flurry recently unveiled version 3.1 of its suite of mobile analytic... http://t.co/nN3RXOf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Scullin, Power Recycler:  http://t.co/SFaYKpKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solar-Powered What?: Inventors and entrepreneurs are harnessing the sun's energy for everything from swimwear to... http://t.co/6SIf02Uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Things You Must Do To Sell To a Small Business Owner: 5 Things You Must Do To Sell To a Small Business OwnerTh... http://t.co/uV2fOVZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulu Is No Longer For Sale As Disney, News Corps., Comcast, and Providence Backtrack: Were you hoping to buy Hul... http://t.co/kn3dgOv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demet Mutlu, Fashion-Forward in Turkey: Her native Turkey had no decent online fashion outlet, so she bid Harv... http://t.co/ehSGjU2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Ad Spend Expected to Hit $500 Billion: Though the economy still has us all singing the blues here in the ... http://t.co/P3JtciFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email Marketers Should Also Consider Coordinating Mobile Screens with TV: It has become apparent that mobile adv... http://t.co/fthBbAkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry’s Latest Reputation Black Eye Could Be A Lethal Blow: In business there are times where you almost st... http://t.co/C3RYbHmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[foursquare’s Radar Tells You When You Are Near Cool: For a while now it seems like most reports about foursquare... http://t.co/HifqrKyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universal Cancels ‘Tower Heist’ Premium VOD Experiment After Boycott By Movie Theaters: Under pressure from exhi... http://t.co/4iPxmESS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franchise Group Resists Union Rules: A major franchise group is speaking out against efforts to update union ele... http://t.co/D4bq1Qb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry Outage Affects 'Millions' of Users: Major service interruption that hit other parts of the world earl... http://t.co/qDncLHGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brave New World of B2B Social Media: Citigroup is stepping up its use of social media. It is launching such ... http://t.co/w67dYdKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s Page Speed Online Tool Graduates From Labs!: Congratulations graduate!
Google’s Page Speed Online tool ... http://t.co/V0IAmi6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Food ad regulations | Mobile ad network for doctors | Questions about Google: Legal/Regulatory:

US FT... http://t.co/fdYmtj5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Take Your Business to the Next Level: Consider these three successful strategies to kick-start growth in ... http://t.co/fmhFc12k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Zynga | 18.8M iPhone users expected to upgrade | Privacy: Gaming:

Zynga launches new games, platf... http://t.co/AXUtxsyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If M-commerce is Going to Save the Holidays Retailers Need to Step Up Page Speed: There are high hopes among ret... http://t.co/IXi9tigT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iMessage Could Introduce a Change in the Way People Text: Apple plans to unveil its iMessage service on Wednesda... http://t.co/zDRxeWkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Gets High Marks for Social Responsibility: Google gets a lot of heat from a lot of people for a lot of re... http://t.co/OcBUr9nU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrfire 
"Self-reverence, self-knowledge, self-control - these three alone lead to power." -Alfred, Lord Tennyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Subsidize Big Boxes at Shops' Expense:  http://t.co/Hh24FDMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obtaining Business Loans From Neighbors: From crowdfunding sites to investment clubs, entrepreneurs are findin... http://t.co/zb3mULMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook’s New Partner Warns of Danger, Danger!: Facebook has partnered with Websense in order to make the web s... http://t.co/qSjZ6tOx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>