<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect nothing, live frugally on surprise. - Alice Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a sad day when you find out that it's not accident or time or fortune, but just yourself that kept things from you. - Hellman, Lillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To belittle is to be little. - Kalil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like any other luxury. You have no right to it unless you can afford it. - Anthony Trollope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our dreams are meant to come true, you know. What would be the purpose of dreaming if we could not fulfill our dreams? - Gautama Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is the settling of the soul into its most appropriate spot. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you knew it all it would not be creation but dictation. - Gertrude Stein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None are so old as those who have outlived enthusiasm. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be in your children's memories tomorrow, You have to be in their lives today. - Barbara Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing is not lying, nor is it theft. It is a journey and search for transparency between one's words and one's soul. - Richard Flanagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much has been said and sung of beautiful young girls, why don't somebody wake up to the beauty of old women? - Harriet Beecher Stowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand half-loves must be forsaken to take one whole heart home. - Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as we draw breath, we owe it to the ones we loved and lost to live out our lives without wasting them on regrets. - Sharon Sala]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every problem is a gift - without problems we would not grow. - Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather welcome change than cling to the past. - Robert T. Kiyosaki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts become things. If you see it in your mind, you will hold it in your hand. - Bob Proctor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First you jump off the cliff and build your wings on the way down. - Ray Bradbury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with being in the rat race is that even if you win, you're still a rat. - Lily Tomlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's the smallest decisions that can change your life forever. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be aware that, Great distances sometimes separate dreamland from reality. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capacity for love in its higher forms seems to be peculiarly human although even in humans it is still peculiar. - Jeanette Winterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man is a being in search of meaning. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brick walls are there for a reason. They let you know how badly you want things. - Randy Pausch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaven can be found in the most unlikely corners. - Mitch Albom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10 percent what happens to you and ninety percent how you respond to it. - Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What keeps life fascinating is the constant creativity of the soul. - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human spirit will not invest itself in a compromise. - Robert Fritz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivors can't always choose their methods. - Patricia Briggs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things That Happens When You Don’t Eat Meat - https://t.co/rlAUojHqz1 https://t.co/ANcMPU5TY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A love for tradition has never weakened a nation, indeed it has strengthened nations in their hour of peril. - Winston S. Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without discipline, there's no life at all. - Katharine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is the meaning and purpose of life, the whole aim and end of human existence. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple Exercises To Lose Fat - https://t.co/y6ECZCupZb https://t.co/mpMettK2IH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highest Paid Male Athletes - https://t.co/NfE3OqWfjv https://t.co/EvZDwoeFUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Impress a Girl - https://t.co/Mf8DWrb0sm https://t.co/DmbkZlmlgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power-lust is a weed that grows only in the vacant lots of an abandoned mind. - Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Protein Foods To Eat For Weight Loss - https://t.co/EnQtKjy3IM https://t.co/E9POwAc6kc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps one has to be very old before one learns to be amused rather than shocked. - Pearl S. Buck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how plain a woman may be, if truth and honesty are written across her face, she will be beautiful. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, goals are stars to steer by, not sticks with which to beat ourselves. - Barbara Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We mark some days as fair, some as foul, because we do not see that the character of every day as identical - Charles Frazier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how your heart is grieving, if you keep on believing, the dreams that you wish will come true. - Walt Disney Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you do not take an interest in politics doesn't mean politics won't take an interest in you. - Pericles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the load that breaks you down, it's the way you carry it. - Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To every problem, there is a most simple solution. - Agatha Christie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What keeps life fascinating is the constant creativity of the soul. - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love has no uttermost, as the stars have no number and the sea no rest. - Eleanor Farjeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who judge others should know how to judge themselves. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until you make peace with who you are, you'll never be content with what you have. - Doris Mortman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are my butterfly and I refuse to set you free. - Shannon Hale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do we live for, if it is not to make life less difficult for each other? - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age is something that doesn't matter, unless you are a cheese. - Billie Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It`s not how old you are, it`s how you are old. - Jules Renard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a knowledge of intimacy, localization in the spaces of our intimacy is more urgent than determination of dates. - Gaston Bachelard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not seek the because - in love there is no because, no reason, no explanation, no solutions. - Anaïs Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only one racing strategy that https://t.co/uNUqSnYEhq's the one I run by: Get in the lead and don't let anyone pass you. - Megan McCafferty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...And we pray, not for new earth or heaven, but to be quiet in heart, and in eye clear. What we need is here. - Wendell Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must take life the way it comes at you and make the best of it. - Yann Martel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never found beauty in longing for the impossible and never found the possible to be beyond my reach. - Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can change a person the way a parent can change a baby- awkwardly, and often with a great deal of mess. - Lemony Snicket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you teach a boy, you educate an individual; but if you teach a girl, you educate a community. - Greg Mortenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's harder to write in the third person but the advantage is you move around better. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is no moment more precious than the exact moment you are living now -geth - Obert Skye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blaze with the fire that is never extinguished. - Luisa Sigea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Croom: It is a defect of God's humour that he directs our hearts everywhere but to those who have a right to them. - Tom Stoppard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friendship improves happiness, and abates misery, by doubling our joys, and dividing our grief - Marcus Tullius Cicero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man cannot discover new oceans unless he has the courage to lose sight of the shore. - André Gide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't part with your illusions. When they are gone you may still exist, but you have ceased to live. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest thing about the road not taken is that you never know where it might have led. - Lisa Wingate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lord is my Shepherd, I shall not want. - David C. King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry is the rhythmical creation of beauty in words. - Edgar Allan Poe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of us come to this earth to gain our worth; we brought it with us. - Sheri L. Dew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The duty of youth is to challenge corruption. - Kurt Cobain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BB Cream VS Foundation - https://t.co/NNsChrSXLZ https://t.co/TY0T7Q7Mye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind has a thousand eyes, And the heart but one; Yet the light of a whole life dies, When the love is done. - Francis William Bourdillon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Films You Wish Disney Would Make - https://t.co/Wh0c2nnuSL https://t.co/O7op19EdMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind-blowing Landscapes - https://t.co/SajDWKz56Q https://t.co/rPHmQaqKUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The choice is ours to hear the echoes, to heed the call: when life isn't good, taste and see that the Lord is. - Matt Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that is necessary for evil to succeed is that good men do nothing. - Edmund Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would bring light must endure burning. - David Zindell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good life is inspired by love and guided by knowledge. - Bertrand Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..because the hardest boss a man can ever have is himself. - Stephen King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inexpensive Ways to Spend Time with Your Friends - https://t.co/y2ZaEHW9D1 https://t.co/QHpkndCmiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As beauty lies in eyes of beholder, struggling lies in reaching further. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never travel faster than your guardian angel can fly. - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest accomplishment is not in never falling, but in rising again after you fall. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is not a maybe thing, you know when you love someone. - Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is an irresistible desire to be irresistibly desired. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go for the moon. If you don't get it, you'll still be heading for a star - Willis Reed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who loves in the expectation of being loved in return is wasting their time. - Paulo Coelho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you re the only one to do something it always gets done. - Robert Newton Peck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love God and find him within - the only treasure worth finding. - Meher Baba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We loved with a love that was more than love. - Edgar Allan Poe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being busy is better than being bored. Bored left a long time ago. Busy is always around for me. - Tabitha Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all can be only who we are, no more, no less. - Terry Goodkind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One word frees us of all the weight and pain of life: That word is love. - Sophocles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We would rather be ruined than changed; We would rather die in our dread Than climb the cross of the moment And let our illusions die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts. - Marcus Aurelius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first step towards getting somewhere is to decide that you are not going to stay where you are. - J.P. Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not the men in your life that matters, its the life in your men. - Mae West]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>