<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Life does not give us chances...life is our chance to give! ~Ziggy via @iheartquotes #live #run #friends #give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree, it will live its whole #life believing that it is stupid." Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After all these years, about every week to 12 days my body just craves a long #run." -- Gary Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you can #imagine is real.- Pablo Picaso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will do #today what you won't, so #tomorrow I can do what you can't" -Unknown via @timagee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want something, go get it. Period. ~ Pursuit of #Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#You got a dream, you got to protect it. People can’t do something themselves, they want to tell you you can’t do it ~Pursuit of Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever let someone tell #you you can't do something. Not even me. All right? ~ Pursuit of Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This part of my #life... this little part.. is called "happiness" ~ Pursuit of Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laziness may appear attractive, but work gives #satisfaction.- Anne Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not because things are difficult that we do not #dare, it is because we do not dare that they are difficult.~ Seneca #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A little part of one dies when not living and feeling your #passion. Live it. Feel it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be not afraid of going slowly; be afraid only of standing still." -Chinese proverb #start #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those days when it's hard 2 put 1 foot in front of the other, but those R the days when #champions R created~ McNally via @McMillanRunning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For my part I know nothing with any certainty, but the sight of the #stars makes me dream."-Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human #spirit is indomitable." -Sir Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't stop playing because we grow old. We grow old because we stop playing." -George Bernard Shaw  #doit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you wait to #do everything until you're sure it's right, you'll probably never do much"-Borden via @Lotay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Never underestimate the power of #dreams and the influence of the human spirit.” Wilma Rudolph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most things which we think are impossible in life, is because we have never tried them. So go for every #dream"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you’re going to doubt something, doubt your own limits." ~Don Ward via @CharityIdeas #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know the more conservative you are, in #pace, from the beginning, the more you can push your wall back?” via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone is gifted - but some people never open their package" #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take risks, courage to try, dreams that come true, fall in love, discover the #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never #settle for mediocrity when you can have greatness"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Greatest danger for most of us is not that we aim too #high & we miss it, but we aim too low & reach it." Michelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Desire is the most important factor in the #success of any athlete." ~Willie Shoemaker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no telling how many miles you will have to #run while chasing a dream. ~Author Unknown via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody's got a laughin' place-
trouble is most folks won't take the time to go look for it" #find #laugh #love #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a #run---&gt;&gt;&gt;The greatest healing therapy is friendship and love - Hubert H. Humphrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you #sweat in practice, the less you bleed in battle. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Love #live #dream #chances #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really great people make you feel that you, too, can become great. ~Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decide that you want it more than you are afraid of it. ~ Bill Cosby via @iheartquotes #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is a #magic formula...It's just that the magic is different for everyone" Keith Dowling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man never made any material as resilient as the human spirit." - Bern Williams #quote via @SusanCosmos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why we love our coaches! "Tell everyone what you want to do & someone will want to #help you do it." - W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover your support system, Discover the people who step up with a helping hand, Discover what makes you smile, Discover your #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." - Babe Ruth #determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A good #friend is a connection 2life - a tie 2the past, a road 2the future, the key 2sanity in a totally insane world" Wyse via @coachprs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All great achievements require time." - Maya Angelou #train #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every person who ever achieved  #greatness crossed the bridge of self-doubt. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing limits achievement like small thinking; nothing expands possibilities like unleashed  #imagination.~William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The power of someone believing in you that you can do it, can mentally change your game" #coach #friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Training gives me proof" John Litei #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any #runner interested in maximizing potential must study the mind-body connection or their journey will not be complete" Ryan Hall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An overflowing lust for #life...the most attractive of all personality characteristics" Matt Fitzgerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t ask what the world needs. Ask what makes U come #alive & go do it. Because what the world needs is people who have come alive~Thurman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You've only got 3 choices in #life ➔ give up.. give in.. or give it all you've got." ~ Unknown via @livetorque]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have to ask us why we run, you'll never understand. #run via @successfulrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't imagine living and not #running ~Paula Radcliffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only passions, great #passions, can elevate the soul to great things. -Denis Diderot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your purpose in #life is to find your purpose & give your whole heart and soul to it. ~Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to do it because I want to do it.~ Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adventure is worthwhile in itself.~Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never interrupt someone doing what you said couldn't be done."-Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people have the will to #win, few have the will to prepare to win. -Bobby Knight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To get through the hardest #journey we need take only one step at a time, but we must keep on stepping"~Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Friends are the sunshine of life." - John Hay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Racing for me was about energy management." Frank Shorter #run #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This 26.2 is for all of the non-believers" RQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I can #getiton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got a #dream, you got to protect it. People can’t do something themselves, they want to tell you you can’t do it ~Pursuit of Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want something, go get it. Period. ~ Pursuit of Happiness #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." -Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I plan to break the rules #run #hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have #good when you can have #great ~~&gt; #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't follow your #dreams; chase them. ~ Richard Dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be pushed by your problems, be led by your #dreams ~Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running is a journey that whether we do alone or with others, we are always together"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think you got this, you got it! #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is just something about people who enjoy going long" #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hope is a #good thing, maybe the best thing, and no good thing ever dies” Shawshank Redemption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make room to receive your #desires ~ Rhonda Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All great achievements require time. ~ Maya Angelou #courage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Person born with a talent they are meant to use will find their greatest #happiness in using it." ~Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you know what you #want, & you want it bad enough, you'll find a way to get it. ~Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running reminds us that we are alive"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The next mile is the only one a person really has to make." Eric Sevareid #run #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live life fully while you're here. Experience everything. Take care of yourself and your #friends ~ Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let the barriers you see define what you do." Sonal Shah via @charityideas  #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great friend knows how to take you by the hand and lift you up when you are down and if you are really lucky for a #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Begin each day as if it were on purpose” Radmacher #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After a good #run, I feel like I am capable of anything"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world needs #dreamers & the world needs doers. But above all the world needs dreamers that do." Sarah Ban Breathnach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some men see things as they are & ask why. Others dream things that never were & ask why not.” Shaw  #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not a single path. Don't be afraid to #run on new roads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who has begun is half done - Horace #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who have abandoned their own dreams will try to convince you to abandon yours. Don't listen. #neverquit via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life. ~Charles Darwin #live #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life has no #limitations, except the ones you make." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we wait for the moment when everything, absolutely everything, is ready, we shall never #begin." - Ivan Turgenev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're pursuing a #dream & folks are saying, 'you can't do it, you're wasting your time' you're probably on the right track via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What #great thing would you attempt if you knew you could not fail? ~Robert H. Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We cannot waste time. We can only waste ourselves." - George M. Adams #quote via @SusanCosmos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still get wildly enthusiastic about little things. I play w/ leaves. I skip down the street & run against the wind~ Buscaglia via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put your #heart, #mind, and #soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success. ~Swami Sivananda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most powerful lesson you can learn in #running? You're capable of much more than you think." via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Racing teaches us to #challenge ourselves. It teaches us to push beyond where we though we could go." - Patti Sue Plummer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all #possible objections must first be overcome." ~ Samuel Johnson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>