<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead merry Christmas man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidbartlett1: Happy Christmas Eve. Time to share the best best vine ever again https://t.co/ykpY0U3fQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Staael2014 you too man, thanks for all the quality stuff! All the best for 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickyDVT90 @TVADDONS thanks for the help were back on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4th Jan start new job in Edinburgh.... It's all going on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 12 hour shift before Christmas! Trip to Edinburgh for the weekend tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dark_shark: "The problem with privatisation is that the profits are privatised and the costs are socialised." - Brian Eno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FREE_bets: When life actually starts to go your way... https://t.co/3kyWyPaVTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @timbolton1: If ever a picture summed this situation up 😂 https://t.co/U2vfeYU6U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAnfieldWrap: Know anyone who could do that job, Roy? #HodgsonForChelsea https://t.co/tsiwXL8xun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slug and lettuce 6/10 although they sold @AppletonRumUSA lovely stuff my Jamaican Friend was very pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Browns in Leeds 8/10 lovely place but rather expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got dragged to bierkeller last night it was the worst experience of my life. Really really Shit beer I couldn't drink 0/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas / leaving drinks in Leeds wish me luck....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On but s into town and its school kicking out time.. Mouthy fuckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmclark come wi di Meter reedin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meter reedin https://t.co/8tM9zy4e1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donkey https://t.co/z1C3ZJ3oOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jetfury looking good Geoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@premierinn @TravelodgeUK Was my parents 50th anniversary and couldn't leave them there. They've really enjoyed their stay now. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a restaurant just a reception with tables no ambience no style just woeful. Sorry going on but didn't know these places still existed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God awful rooms all that was missing was roaches climbing the walls. Restaurant was cheap tables red plastic chairs FFS. WTF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't think dark damp unwelcoming rooms at chain hotels were still around but @TravelodgeUK proved me wrong. Good staff crap rooms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booked them into @premierinn Edinburgh east last minute. Great rooms great beds clean warm and welcoming. @TravelodgeUK look and learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravelodgeUK your upgraded rooms are awful, your staff were great but we were not the only people who left. Not good at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My parents booked into a @TravelodgeUK in Edinburgh. When I saw the room I quickly sought a refund and moved them out. That's travelodgeical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njmsoccer you have some nice looking roast dinners, enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart this is our visit to longniddry last week near north Berwick. Lovely place https://t.co/3OL9psu3Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LothianLoop I'm still learning the area but groups like this give everyone a new idea or place to go. Loving it so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LothianLoop and you can enjoy both with just a 20 minute drive it's brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EastLothianHour we just moved to EDI from Leeds and there's so much to do but this weekend we went here, beautiful! https://t.co/39A8cz4zz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart beautiful!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a Nice place to take my visiting parents to eat in #Edinburgh #food #goodfood #50thweddinganiversary #restaurant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Breakfast I once saw Angela Bittis in the slug and lettuce in Edinburgh....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ofstednews can you tell me if I can find a FREE list of registered childminders in Edinburgh with out having to pay £20 month @childcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmarksteel just keep it buttoned during the men's game..... :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WHALES_org: 333 #whales inc. 200 pregnant ♀ slaughtered in Japan's latest #whaling mission. Petition: https://t.co/axOv2ZD1rj https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Longniddry #Edinburgh #coast #sea https://t.co/Hm6VO4mTo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #Weather watch suggests it don't know what the fxxk it's doing in #Edinburgh! #Rain #sunshine Rain sunshine repeat......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DietmarHamann: Barbaric  https://t.co/J1utsQHMWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im sure I've just seen Tim Burgess in Town #edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland hi it says you can buy family day tickets in the m ticket app on your website?? I only see weekly monthly and yearly???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Japan admits to killing more than 300 whales in Southern Ocean https://t.co/isRmiqV7DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NHSMillion: Pls RT if you feel lucky to have our incredible (and free) NHS #NHSMillion https://t.co/SuvGNaaoOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart such an honour to see these magnificent animals shame some countries think different. Enjoy your trip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart your showing off now :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart we happened to see Dolphins in the distance on a boat in Ibiza and it gave me chills....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart wow where's that Charles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a Johnny Cash / Richard Hawley kinda Sunday here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkBunnyTees you had Joker IPA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NHSMillion: As you put your lovely kids to bed tonight pls RT for all the incredible people who helped bring them into the world https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Valhallastreams hi I disabled acceleration but the video not smooth is there another setting? Thanks keep up the great work Love the newluk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5haneJ @maryannehobbs great memories of TG I remember getting my ears melted by speedy J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had 1 minute of Owen on BT sport ffs painful..... Setanta much better. #LFCvMUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart lighter nights more playtime!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitScotland great shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njmsoccer haha not just me then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye Bye #Leeds We had some good times we had some bad times. Hello #Edinburgh our new home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead need a change Dazzla working up there at mo and her in doors been offered job at EDI infirmary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead I am yes, house sold ready to rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Match4Z: I urgently need a bone marrow transplant. I have a very rare tissue type due to mixed ethnicity (Arabic/British). Pls help me …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NHSMillion: Pls help build an army of NHS supporters by following &amp; retweeting - together we can make a difference #NHSMillion https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rockcrusher01 @TVADDONS @TheBlazetamer @Javaman_sv thanks for your hard work, now rest and enjoy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still buzzin after last nights result and performance! Keep it rolling redmen #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbc5live absolutely woeful and miss selling products. Never going to use them again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumble bumble jog misplace a pass bumble some more #RealvCity #YayaToure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Yaya Toure bumble around would drive me nuts if I was a city fan #RealvCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bethnew: .@Honda, earlier today I gave birth to my daughter in the back of a Honda Fit. It is a mess. Can I have a free car? https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SlySporfs: RT Only If You Get Fellaini's Hair On His Head https://t.co/oBCsUHuYcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well in Benteke but Ibe has been awful today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveashy it's there to be won!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelDread always a great show Don.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking night again on @CCfunkandsoul. Another great live session.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Distinctboxes that's pretty impressive and lovely isn't it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Craig me and daughter Lyla (4) cooking pizza and stomping around the flat to the tunes. Any chance of a shout??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njmsoccer good to have you back though and looking good too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Breakfast pls can I sponsor the part of the show where U get annoyed at the length of the news jingle, don't know the technical term :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Breakfast @BSPOfficial storming start to the show it can only go downhill now......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice brisk morning in Edinburgh. Frost capped hills and a slight nip to the air, lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkBunnyTees after you checked boiler pressure.... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkBunnyTees turn all the valves off on hot radiators see if the lower ones heat up if they do part open the closed valves to "balance" it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrmarksteel: We should all now be allowed to say disgusting vile things about Kelvin Mackenzie, but it still wouldn't make things even…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well you don't often see deer run out in the road on the way to work do you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CCfunkandsoul absolutely loving this!! Bass line is driving me crazy....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess what song I've got in my head now??? https://t.co/k1GxzTk78M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ekRHP3BSu5                     Nice bit of Pre Summer vibes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrAliceRoberts Nutella and peanut butter mix worked for me!! Humane of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then a Stroll down Portobello beach. #Edinburgh lucky to have such beautiful places on my doorstep! https://t.co/zlAFfnYwPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely walk up the hills last night in #Edinburgh. 4 yr old daughter couldn't make it up Arthur's seat. https://t.co/WgV7w6YBuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uSwitchHelp I am told a BT broadband deal you offered £10 is wrong and I am being charged £20 @BTCare say I need to contact you??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH MY FUCKING GOD!!!! WHAT A GAME.... #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare vol012-120255]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare https://t.co/FMFYqNU5IZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare got this today. VOL012-120255 apparently Uswitch deals have nothing to do with you??? https://t.co/ZrhPGu9Zs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently according to your CS @uSwitchUK are misselling your products @BTCare just been told to wait a week for manager call back now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare still no call from a manager that was promised within 24 hours now into day 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadband Packages And Deals Online | BT @BTCare this £10 deal is costing me £20 miss selling your products??? https://t.co/MvbR3OAI2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreenpeaceUK: Wow! 251,654 have signed our petition to ban #microbeads! RT to spread the word. 

Sign here https://t.co/Kpsyo8EWua http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesevansart good lad!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare I have been in touch and promised a call back by manager in 24hours and now 48 later nothing.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>