<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Thundershirts Really Calm Dogs During Fireworks?: The anxiety vests were inspired by research into humans with severe anxiety or autism, but the veterinary science isn't quite up to par. https://t.co/rZfPp6429w https://t.co/gEnU8IbyRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why (and How) California Is Destroying Mountains of Weed: How exactly do you obliterate potentially tens of thousands of pounds of cannabis across the state? Not unlike how you get rid of yard trimmings. https://t.co/0l9dztH32m https://t.co/w9cVHsnQVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Cloud Software Engineer(s) (Job #461) &amp; Software Engineer(s) (#457): Dsgn, dvlp &amp; build sw for ntwk security firewall prods.… https://t.co/Xdog1Zmo84 https://t.co/zTMBjinWMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer – Web and Flash: Employment Opportunities – BrainTrain – Find A Therapist! – Follow us on Twitter! – Like us on Facebook! – Call us today: ************ – Home – Professionals – Clinical Decision Support Software – IVA-2 – MeSA Assist –… https://t.co/MzDrAxHhn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA tester: Java dveloper Ref No.: 18-26014 Location: long island city, New York 1. Good knowledge of SOA concepts, REST services. 2. Good knowledge of Java, J2EE and frameworks like Spring 3. Good to have knowledge of building micro-services on cloud… https://t.co/crfWqZq82S https://t.co/evIc8qnaqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/23/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/1JLu6XPpOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Mutation Math Shows How Life Keeps on Evolving: New results emerging from graph theory prove that the way a population is organized can guarantee the eventual triumph of natural selection—or permanently thwart it. https://t.co/fJaoF9fs0J https://t.co/iz2dj4F5eW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience Design Lead (New York, NY): Experience Design Lead (New York, NY) Apply now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Xing Start apply with Seek Apply Now Please wait… Apply now Apply for Job Enter your email to apply Date: Apr 15, 2017… https://t.co/YNAelSPw4n https://t.co/fkc1z30Qdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traveling Superintendent – Retail TI: Dallas, TX Full-time $0k – $0k Posted Today We are a commercial general contractor headquartered in Texas, doing business across the country. Our projects are both ground up and renovation and are mostly within the… https://t.co/Lr0aV3vsNz https://t.co/qD2t0nEYbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revit Integrator: Trimble is seeking a Revit Integrator to fill an opportunity in Los Angeles, CA.  Job Summary Trimble Professional Services is an AEC technology development and consulting company providing leading edge solutions to the industry's most… https://t.co/6Vrg8YNHn3 https://t.co/eUyZyMFDVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Developer – Careers – – Contact Us – – Blog – Client Login – REQUEST A DEMO – Search Toggle navigation – Unified Payer Platform – Medical/Rx Care – Pay for Quality – Member Engagement – Stakeholder Collaboration – Solutions – Medical –… https://t.co/kw7k0OnfpD https://t.co/XtIV3O31SR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP SD Functional – Vistex: DESCRIPTION: The SAP SD Functional Consultant is responsible for implementing and enhancing the SAP modules pertaining to the SAP solution. This includes implementation, upgrade, and/or extension of existing SAP applications… https://t.co/ht0ylLvmgL https://t.co/SzQo8Wkiia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Entire History of 'World of Warcraft' in One (Long) Video: The game’s designers talk through every expansion in the history of the legendary MMORPG. https://t.co/M8Lyupxmma https://t.co/VeyBgOG6SK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst #RT18: Amitech Solutions, Inc. a St. Louis, MO IT Consulting Firm, is looking for a Computer Systems Analyst with: “Master’s Degree in Applied Computing, Information Technology, Computer Science, Engineering, or Math; and “5… https://t.co/HAxjLSULVt https://t.co/xpyX2EXYlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wikimedia v. NSA Highlights the ACLU's Challenges in Fighting Mass Surveillance: The ACLU has been trying to challenge the NSA's bulk surveillance for years. A hearing in *Wikimedia v. NSA* Friday could mark a breakthrough. https://t.co/FTvxXOFV5s https://t.co/rJ7VhD5Tie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verification Engineer: Verification Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Work with specifications for memory controller, cache, and input/output designs in microprocessors. Develop test benches in software to emulate processor design stimulus. Check… https://t.co/9PGLQLwOWM https://t.co/3nffntbgHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Systems Software Manager: Job Title: Senior Embedded Systems Software Manager – ****** Primary Location United States-California-San Jose Job: Software Engineering Schedule: Full-time Description Xilinx seeks an innovative thought leader… https://t.co/FtIVMJ6JT5 https://t.co/w7MztBUqDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/M9FylSKMyf https://t.co/x848tOirox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Networks Engineer 3:   Job Description – Networks Engineer 3 (18007637) Networks Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18007637 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/BfSKpC7f8n https://t.co/ByVTBRQbq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-26848 Location: Plano, Texas Key skills required for the job are: Agile-Scrum-BFSI-Domain-L3 (Mandatory) Agile As a Senior Scrum Master, you are responsible for facilitating multiple Scrum teams. You are accountable… https://t.co/pQZ1N7kQzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Online Services: Software Developer, Online Services =================================== Have you ever thought about working with an amazing organization, surrounded by amazing, scary smart, people and making the world a better place?… https://t.co/GY6BCUUci6 https://t.co/q22CyS1lOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe System Administrator: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/23/2018 2:48 PM) Job ID 23641 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/mZaHR2Vn8a https://t.co/obfXbUq67R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Java 8 with React js exp: Java Developer with Java 8 with React js exp Ref No.: 18-28379 Location: Phoenix, Arizona Position: Java Developer with Java 8 with React js exp. Location: Phoenix, AZ Secondary SkillSet:Java, J2EE… https://t.co/F4BkMyprc6 https://t.co/38bsrpzkwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, IT Operations: Engineer, IT Operations Job Summary Engineer is responsible for a broad range of systems, administration, and operations in a Microsoft Windows physical and virtual environment. Other duties include assisting as part of the IT… https://t.co/HVq13PaFnq https://t.co/rm818t2nfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McLaren's Senna Ain't Pretty, but It Can Whip a Track: The $958,966 Senna, named for an F1 legend, won't win your heart with its looks. Who cares? https://t.co/AHu9hWJRLj https://t.co/Mgcc54tS4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: NET Developer – Greenville, Pennsylvania Potential candidates should submit their resumes to ********************** We invite you to join our team as a .NET Developer. We are focused on Digital Transformation and providing the best… https://t.co/WoXW250DOp https://t.co/HRcvKV4bgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Application Systems Analyst- Omaha, NE.: ETL Application Systems Analyst- Omaha, NE. Job no: ****** Work type: Full Time Regular Location: Nebraska Categories: Information Technnology Mutual of Omaha is a solid, family-oriented company that’s… https://t.co/q9A1kqKukh https://t.co/QgFUvUR0sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Associate Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides integrated services to the… https://t.co/bVXgoUqfao https://t.co/LiNesqwuIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Engineer 2 – Embedded SW Development (SW Tech Lead): Location: Grand Rapids, Michigan Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Office About Us: To stay connected with exciting news and the latest job opportunities from GE businesses,… https://t.co/TWVirkYGNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Scientist/Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides integrated services to… https://t.co/2yLYtwSpFa https://t.co/bZOluyItf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Concur Implementation Project Manager: SAP Concur – Implementation Project Manager Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community… https://t.co/n4N1U1YFFm https://t.co/oXBzceJVER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical QA Tester: Technical QA Tester Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Looking for a seasoned professional to support international payments applications… https://t.co/XxIw9HBKrg https://t.co/fBt0pZ8wmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product UX/UI Designer – Avon, CT: Location: Connecticut, US Company: Hubbell Incorporated Division: iDevices iDevices is a preeminent manufacturer of smart home solutions and a proud member of the Hubbell Incorporated family of brands. As partners in… https://t.co/T9uSEDbhfh https://t.co/E6vSMBz3Uy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java 8 Microservice Application Architect: JAVA 8 MICROSERVICE APPLICATION ARCHITECT GlobalConsulting Company _**Green Card holders or US Citizens ONLY ** **DO NOT APPLY UNLESS YOU ARE A GREEN CARD HOLDER OR A US CITIZEN**_ LOCATION East Coast MUST HAVE:… https://t.co/Xh0agaYKBH https://t.co/qJbgqfbfDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer with Azure AI: Project Description Our program was started as the migration of the financial instruments trading legacy mainframe system to a new technical, highly-scalable platform. The success of the program in both the migration… https://t.co/fh23MWLBPp https://t.co/VxSUCPOOSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Internship Data Analyst: 2018 Summer Internship – Data Analyst Company Description: Atlas Copco Compressors LLC is part of the Compressor Technique Business Area, and its headquarters are located in Rock Hill, S.C. The company manufactures,… https://t.co/SJkMJPcVF6 https://t.co/Xey215QAvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Curriculum Developer: Associate Curriculum Developer | Pega Skip to main content – Training – Support – Knowledgebase – PegaWorld – PDN – Pega Academy – Product Design – Pega Blog – Partners – Consulting – English – English – Franais – Deutsch… https://t.co/FoAYXbD7eO https://t.co/SkG6676ytA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crash-Happy RC Cars Make Self-Driving Tech Smarter: Short on time, money, and space, Georgia Tech researchers created a 1:5 scale platform that lets them test autonomous tech without fear of crashing. https://t.co/HExMIh8JTE https://t.co/xLG9yimISO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Lead: Salesforce Technical Lead in Phoenix, Arizona, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students –… https://t.co/bj0NBefYsX https://t.co/hfwmrcKmCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software DevOps Solutions Engineer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Software &amp; DevOps Solutions Engineer to join our team in Alexandria, VA, to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems.… https://t.co/ckXeLqe6LA https://t.co/hp8XMvBDLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Supplier: Req ID : 437922BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : The GIMS (GEOINT Information Management Services) Next Program provides critical capabilities to help enable efficient and timely GEOINT… https://t.co/aNb6bYTntl https://t.co/L9pJjcMywR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Education Construction – North LA: A mid sized General Contractor in North Los Angeles is looking for a Project Manager to join their team. The General Contractor specializes in delivering construction projects in the educational sector… https://t.co/LYUaSymzdF https://t.co/AzAZtiGFo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Salesforce Developer: JOB SUMMARY _Looking to put your years of technical computing and coding experience to the test? We need a skilled and competent SENIOR SALESFORCEDEVELOPER to develop innovative computing solutions and integrate a… https://t.co/9vZZ1iBFxM https://t.co/EKxY9lesCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Sentence With 7 Meanings Unlocks a Mystery of Human Speech: Neuroscientists turned to an internet-famous phrase to identify the region of the brain that controls pitch and emphasis in human speech. https://t.co/fZQWU3drw8 https://t.co/AWPAFHFzxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Software Developer: Atlassian, Inc. seeks to work in Mountain View, CA: 1) Software Developer, Mobile to develop reusable software components and libraries as well as consumer facing network based mobile applications using latest Android mobile… https://t.co/oyw1X1m7zH https://t.co/XVCAHcCRTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance: Medical Devices: Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance (#PS-1005) in Santa Ana, CA, requires 40% domestic &amp; 10% international travel; expenses paid by employer. Principal Engineer, R&amp;D – Advanced Technology (#ST-0420) in… https://t.co/BSQtDY5flK https://t.co/KhQLrERgAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony Kennedy’s Retirement May Have Huge Consequences for Privacy: Kennedy’s record is mixed, but he was a thoughtful voice on how to interpret constitutional rights for the internet era. https://t.co/t3X1WeVrYQ https://t.co/EuBWhD1wuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: RM &amp; CM Technical Lead Elevate Credit Service, LLC Addison, TX Position requires related degree, experience, and skills. The position will supervise and lead 3 RM &amp; CM Engineers. Requires travel to Fort Worth, TX 1-2 times per month for… https://t.co/SMjJ9CFnPf https://t.co/Xu9AvR1Ab0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Senior Consultant #XSFH18FA0518AUS1: Advisory Senior Consultant for Deloitte &amp; Touche LLP in Austin, TX to identify and evaluate complex business and technology risks, internal controls that mitigate risks, and related opportunities for internal… https://t.co/jT7NWAmxKg https://t.co/JAhMCIouJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA's Astro-Mice Will Test What Space Does to Your Gut: A new study will help the space agency understand how to keep its astronauts—and their resident microbes—healthy on future missions to Mars. https://t.co/z56qSLRVw2 https://t.co/Awus9tdwrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Lead: SR Number APPS/APPS/2018/****** Designation Senior Technical Lead Location Iowa Job Family Development (Development) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for managing technology in projects and providing technical guidance… https://t.co/mTN1ZK5zdN https://t.co/MnQUSDRRc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Expecting Games to Build Empathy: Games, the thinking goes, can make you a better person. But can they? Do they? https://t.co/synCF60v8T https://t.co/UiFbgygfDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Your user session will timeout in 5 minutes. Please click OK to continue with your application. Data Scientist Tracking Code 120-****** Job Description Position Highlights: – Recognized leader: Rated #1 Prepaid Wireless Provider in the… https://t.co/QuH5P3F6vT https://t.co/bxoY6r4jxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Analyst Specialist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Colorado Springs, CO Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/uvLQbeLqhi https://t.co/m33xL4skrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Senior Project Manager-0041O3 Description Schneider Electric creates connected technologies that reshape industries, transform cities and enrich lives. Our 144,000 employees thrive in more than 100 countries. From the simplest of… https://t.co/Bv8VkYFmeM https://t.co/iNogpOVZ8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco's Climate Case Against Big Oil Gets Dismissed: “Our litigation forced a public court proceeding on climate science, and now these companies can no longer deny it is real and valid.” https://t.co/UtQYZz97MG https://t.co/rFJSyd0YrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Yer Bread and Milk From Kroger's Cute New Delivery Robot: Built by Nuro, the little autonomous R1 can carry 12 bags of groceries to your door—but the other logistics are still up in the air. https://t.co/PtUopzbNoX https://t.co/wCyGvQMWIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Softw Dvlpr, IBM Corporation, San Jose, CA: Write productn quality code, unit tests, test plans, QA, &amp; documentatn. Prep technl proposals &amp; proof of concepts for various networking use cases. Dvlp web UI for cloud based Load Balancer… https://t.co/Mnn0iFb7HQ https://t.co/A9KHKVqZy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Senior Software Engineer: Lead Senior Software Engineer job in Panama City Beach, Florida, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion… https://t.co/FkWEVqkbFh https://t.co/KFIqsekGPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead, IT Applications – DevOps Coach: Technical Lead, IT Applications – DevOps Coach View Profile – Join Our Talent Community – Featured Jobs – Jobs at the Airport – Professional – Technical Operations &amp; Maintenance – Customer Service – Pilots… https://t.co/R8Dm6O6RFc https://t.co/vybHqVWCBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maintenance Senior Software Engineer: Maintenance Senior Software Engineer ==================================== This is a programming position that is dedicated to providing post-release software troubleshooting and defect remediation. The Maintenance… https://t.co/9E2gVo4fs4 https://t.co/miBzJsDPVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Engineer: Austin, TX Full-time $80k – $130k Posted Today We are located in tech- loving Austin, TX and are a small team in big growth mode. We are in the Music industry and have developed a pretty awesome enterprise application that… https://t.co/JRZl5R4gj7 https://t.co/0zneq9aLH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIV Diagnostics Project Manager: Job ID 11280 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Clinical Research Support Services Overview Cures Start Here. At Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center,… https://t.co/8lVHDkbHsU https://t.co/kxgphoHZex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Help build a critical system relied-upon by virtually all aspects of our domains infrastructure in a globally-deployed, containerized cloud infrastructure. GoDaddy’s (NYSE: GDDY) mission is to radically shift the global economy… https://t.co/HfFVT0yu97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Web Development: Hello Professional, Hope you are doing great !! Please respond with your updated resume if you are interested in below job position. SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WEB DEVELOPMENT * NEED ENGINEERING OR SCIENCE DEGREE… https://t.co/hYsorMI9IQ https://t.co/08L3OBQbkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst,JAVA , Richmond Virginia: May 22 2018 Programmer Analyst,JAVA , Richmond Virginia YSI Jobs – YSI HR Programmer Analyst, JAVA – We are seeking an experienced Senior Software Engineer to technically lead web-based development projects… https://t.co/aNeDGnlXwe https://t.co/KSiv7BCv3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R48399: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R48399 Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/9BVehClAt0 https://t.co/DrZpSGwkXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New Satellite Arms Race Threatening to Explode in Space: Trump’s call for a “Space Force” escalates a quiet, dangerous contest between the US, China, and Russia—one whose consequences no one really understands. https://t.co/8w2DzfbAKS https://t.co/W7il7yp2pA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise of DNA Data Storage: Could DNA as an archival medium be the solution to our information overload? https://t.co/Hk7QuYI7VB https://t.co/frwtrr32bQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: 17103BR Job Description and Requirements Position Name: Tech Support Engineer Position Location: Burlington, MA Position Type: Full Time About Black Duck Software, Synopsys Did you know the Synopsys acquired Black Duck… https://t.co/MuKaEH3uv9 https://t.co/EjfNIBeEfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site Reliability Engineer: 100252BR Site Reliability Engineer CO – Aurora, TX – Richardson, VA – Dulles, VA – Sterling 100252BR Raytheon Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) has immediate openings for Sr. DevOps Engineers and Site Reliability… https://t.co/MSnLAGN0M1 https://t.co/qJ2jjiqfgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Engineer (MM): Job Summary DataRobot accelerates the process of building predictive models to get the most out of valuable data. We work hard to create tools that nascent data scientists can use effectively while also exposing the rich detail and… https://t.co/NfmXeSEBU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search Developer/Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Silver Spring, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/20/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/guIzYXsU54 https://t.co/1BTAnbmeQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Senior Consultant #XSFH18FA0518AUS1: Advisory Senior Consultant for Deloitte &amp; Touche LLP in Austin, TX to identify and evaluate complex business and technology risks, internal controls that mitigate risks, and related opportunities for internal… https://t.co/bPQyUJatbc https://t.co/WoFmVaW0DJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VR Pilot Training Now Comes With a Sense of Touch: Finger-mounted actuators give pilots training with virtual reality the sensation of touching the switches and controls, so they’re better prepared when the move into the real cockpit. https://t.co/2NXx1Vcouj https://t.co/GoxQrzbePX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst: Business System Analyst Midlothian, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 06/05/18, Posted Date – 06/05/18 Primary SkillsBATax TermsC2COverview Phone and Inperson. Duration- 6months. Rate- 50. Location- Richmond, VA. Client-… https://t.co/OeJxjqDmfh https://t.co/jo49kQJbTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator: Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the largest and most diversified television… https://t.co/lEA9y0BgLO https://t.co/qXeB749GiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Westworld' Recap, Season 2 Episode 10: What *Is* Real?: All of Season 2 has toyed with perceptions of reality—and the finale took that to the extreme. https://t.co/wKKkcj1ykz https://t.co/snrMIjI2Y8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular Developer: Angular Developer Ref No.: 18-26084 Location: Buffalo Grove, Illinois Role: Angular 4 Position: Contract // W2 Duration: 12 months Location: Buffalo Grove, IL Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills: 1) Hands on experience in in… https://t.co/FAKZhi0qi4 https://t.co/mcLyN1F17F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: About Essence Essence, part of GroupM, is a global data and measurement-driven agency that blends data science, objective media and captivating experiences to build valuable connections between brands and consumers. Clients include… https://t.co/xbOoRF5Pvu https://t.co/x6tnLRoYcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J2EE Agile Programmer Developer: J2EE AGILE PROGRAMMER DEVELOPER Global Consulting Company _**Green Card holders or US Citizens ONLY**_ _**DO NOT APPLY UNLESS YOU ARE A GREEN CARD HOLDER OR A US CITIZEN**_ LOCATION Cincinnati, OH _**CANDIDATE MUST BE… https://t.co/vKJYQQRquq https://t.co/VAkmr4tZeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Quest to Make Super-cold Quantum Blobs in Space: Physicists launched a custom-made freezer and then let it plummet back to Earth—for science! https://t.co/NRJdTjogiV https://t.co/bUzRGBeCHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Research, design, plan, develop and/or evaluate new, advanced network technologies. Apply at https://t.co/aAz73rZJdX, Req # 243924BR. Sprint is a background screening,… https://t.co/pZQyUtCpmD https://t.co/FuSFrCS0H0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Resources Analyst / Admin Asst.: OVERVIEW RSDCGROUP, LLC (RSDC) is a Veteran Owned Small Business (VOSB) with a presence in the Washington, DC Metropolitan area headquartered in Arlington, Virginia with offices nationwide. We deliver results for… https://t.co/yGdolq6ura https://t.co/yBgdP8Il2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westworld’s Real Villain Has Always Been Its Privacy Policy: Those rich people really should have read the Delos terms of service. https://t.co/KvZeGKCevG https://t.co/2WxN0zXq9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Water/Wastewater Project Manager: Discipline Water/Wastewater Engineering Job Location(s) US-NJ-Red Bank Type Regular Full-Time Use your browser ‘Back’ button to return to job listings Overview Maser Consulting is seeking a Senior Project Manager… https://t.co/MPvSRmWrZY https://t.co/8bLTEEwwe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Digital Network Analyst 3: Company Overview For 29 years, clients in the private and public sectors have relied upon SOS International LLC (SOSi) for critical operations in the world’s most challenging environments. SOSi is privately held, was… https://t.co/nWcq8KU7gb https://t.co/I9qVKWhMRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/HKAnroRMY7 https://t.co/VXSFr1K7p7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-end Developer: This fast-growing company is adding to their staff. The technology is a scalable platform that has both mobile and web applications. They use some of the most modern and robust technologies in their stack including: Docker, RESTful… https://t.co/lvqagwKjdB https://t.co/EBX5P0npXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager: Req ID 96416BR Business Title Program Manager Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Programs &amp; Operations Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is seeking a motivated, career and… https://t.co/UT9bhIDyra https://t.co/2ba8oboS0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Erwin, TN Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/12UxHcrSgt https://t.co/Mg28zmLBbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a Problem Only Quantum Computers Will Ever Be Able to Solve: Computer scientists have been searching for years for a type of problem that a quantum computer can solve but that any possible future classical computer cannot. Now they’ve found one. https://t.co/7tZ7bYuvoH https://t.co/gLOhGTZACf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Data Warehouse): Are you passionate about software development, data and analytics? Are you innovative with broad development skills that you keep current? Are you a committed team player able to work with and support others as they… https://t.co/D03gc5m7hp https://t.co/L7ZUhhwAaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate IT Support Engineer: JOB SUMMARY: This Corporate IT Support Engineer serves as the primary point of contact in our Chicago corporate office for all level 1 and 2 technology issues. Responsible for aligning business objectives with pack members… https://t.co/zjur4DQgzV https://t.co/USr15A4rDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Business Time for Rocket Lab, Launcher of Small Satellites: The question now is: Can it loft its rockets inside the newly opened launch window, or will it stay on the launch pad for ever and ever and ever? https://t.co/cABSQuqah5 https://t.co/IVL341VO5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Job Description Today’s warfighters and intelligence analysts are overwhelmed with data and tasks from a variety of unmanned vehicle systems. Our software helps the warfighter become more effective and efficient in operating groups… https://t.co/3My96f1oDE https://t.co/6CYhdsnE6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect Cloud and Systems Architecture: Solution Architect – Cloud and Systems Architecture Ref No.: 18-23718 Location: Los Angeles, California Job Title: Solution Architect – Cloud and Systems Architecture Location: Los Angeles, CA Salary:… https://t.co/hP4ghNFlJS https://t.co/vEJw5Kzntf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: L2 Support Analyst Ref No.: 18-27403 Location: Edison, Texas Mandatory Technical Skills: Strong knowledge of Windows 2012 and 2008 server. Strong knowledge of IIS6 and IIS7 including virtual directory and app pool configuration and… https://t.co/ACsqBROMF3 https://t.co/vdaiazcUPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carpenter v. United States Decision Strengthens Digital Privacy: Thanks to Carpenter v. United States, the government will now generally need a warrant to obtain your cell site location information. https://t.co/0K36NTWZFJ https://t.co/L7KyqdGznU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager with SAP HR SUCCESSFACTOR Implementation experience: Minimum 10 + years of experience as Project Manager handling multiple projects. Experience handling/management of HR Successfactors Projects. Manages the entire project lifecycle from… https://t.co/ZvLwfITNOS https://t.co/o5uH2MNJGv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>