<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard my Capital Kings remix of All The Way yet? Check it out! http://t.co/zjtTWynQF7 #Soundcloud #remix @CapitalKingsUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Dark Into Light’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/rP6fxdR36Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's work comes to an end in the studio but once dawn comes, I'll be finishing up and mastering the… http://t.co/MKYRX3zwJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like Ive uploaded a song a month ago but in reality its only been 2 weeks...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im no good with people. Thats it :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its time for me to get a new USB port... I need more slots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ArmorOGod: God will never turn anyone away that truly desires to come to him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristnDubstep: And because you belong to him, the power of the life-giving Spirit has freed you from the power of sin that leads to de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I up so early?! This is not normal I should still have 5 more hours of sleep!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'm off to bed early tonight for no reason at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its time for me to start doing worship covers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Filipino_probs: If you're ever late to class, just use the "But I'm Filipino" card... Maybe it'll work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think "Ayo" is my new catch phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brandon747: Stay safe my Filipino people! 

Praying for you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: Whoever has the Son has life; whoever does not have the Son of God does not have life. 1 John 5:12 NIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weakest can be the strongest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying @SwedRevolution 's latest track. Love how its electronic and jazz. Checks it out --&gt; http://t.co/Iqc8CXFNR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: New album coming soon!!!!! #worship #praise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is one of those days when I actually want to go outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let my life be the proof, the proof of Your love"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JosephPrince: What we need is not more "self-help." What we need is the Lord's help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thunder woke me up -_____________-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are some of your favourite plugins for producing music? #music #producers #electronic #hiphop #plugins #fav #vst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having too much fun with the vocoder on Ableton Live =))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traktor vs Serato? #DJ #Help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I spent an hour with my dad taking the old laptop apart just to make a usb fan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Calvary__Tweets: Faith births a Christian.
Trials strengthen a Christian.
Life proves a Christian.
Death crowns a Christian.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should make a DJ video tomorrow.... I should post it on my YouTube channel too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snowylm That happens to me when I use the camera... I hate it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snowylm Sad isnt it bro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a new phone. After a 30 second phone call, my phone dies....  The battery was at 80% and just drops to nothin'. #BlackBerryProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made it to Senior Vocal Jazz! #MadeItByDefault #Only4basses #NoCompetition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: When doubts start to creep in, take a moment to pray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I actually made some for dinner last night xD my family looooved it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and onions don't work well together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day tomorrow... I should sleep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipChbeeb you should do a meet and greet ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai So true.... #SadLifeSoSad #Truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai you just wait.. One day ill cook a taco bowl thing and bring it to school. and... i... wont... share....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I hate you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai *still walking* http://t.co/nfyXT3Ihiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai -____________- *walks away*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Actually its my job. Been doing it since grade 5. ;) #Veteran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Fine but if you have taco bowls again, im getting some!  #TacoBowlForDays http://t.co/JDYEhQ6qfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Still taking photos. My point is still proven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai you proved it when you had my hat during 4th block today. #PointProven]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time to restring my electric guitar....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Well when that day comes... Im assuming that there will be more selfies because of that hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raised eyebrow and fedoras w/ @TheManlySamurai #HighlightOfTheDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: My remix of Bigger Picture by Matthew Parker http://t.co/3FRgTLhb3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: My remix of Can You See Me by Matthew Parker http://t.co/mdxr5EGfBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I have 1 more remix contest for this month. And then another one due the 2nd week of October... BUSY BUSY BUSY!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Matthew Parker - Bigger Picture (12th Son Of Jacob Remix) http://t.co/p3KUn4dElU on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning to wake up early tomorrow to work on the @CapitalKingsUSA remix. I need to get back on my music grind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone teach me the quadratic formula? I kinda need it for physics 12... #ConsOfBeingTheOnlyGrade11InTheClass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more hour 'til call time for tonight's performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai no wonder youre always lonely. You DON'T spend ENOUGH time with the things you love... #sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai stop spending time watching shows and get back on your skateboard.. You need more quality time with your skateboard....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you havent heard my remix of Can You See Me from @MatthewParker2 , Check it out here! http://t.co/p4gMBz4Ibe #SoundCloud #remix #house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some reason, I cant make a remix in the key of B Minor... Its been so long that ive been trying to remix this song.... Whats the secret?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will seek me and find me, when you seek me with all your heart. (Jeremiah 29:13)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristnDubstep: Let my mouth be filled with Your praise And with Your glory all the day. (Psalms 71:8 NKJV)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my remix of @MatthewParker2 's song, Can You See Me? http://t.co/p4gMBz4Ibe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Matthew Parker - Can You See Me? (12th Son Of Jacob Remix) http://t.co/wFX0bJ3UDO on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will upload the remix anytime from tomorrow to next Friday. So stay tuned to my twitter, soundcloud or facebook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished a new remix! Uploading it to Soundcloud in a few days! Stay tuned ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My physics teacher has a twitter account... That's pretty awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I decide to work on a remix at night... I dont wanna stop working but I need to wake up early tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually like my classes this semester. Really like how its all balanced and so chill. Too bad I dont have a lunch though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewParker2 They sound so clean! What effects did you use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @manwellreyes: You're not defined by your past you're prepared by your past. Things you've gone through in the past got u ready for your…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewParker2 How'd you get the vocals like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @manwellreyes: Our faith isn't a to-do list, its a living breathing relationship! God is real.love u guys #mindofmanny http://t.co/KEYSN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reached 500 soundcloud follwers! Thanks guuuys &lt;3 https://t.co/G1cyAUyulP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VincentAraujo Ohhh Yeeeeeeaaaaaaaaah!! #OnTwitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LivingForGod0: Jeremiah 29:11 'I know the plans I have for you. Plans to prosper you and not to harm you. Plans to give you hope and a …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikedonehey: If your church understands the gospel, you will see people breaking free from the world's social economy. 
We give as we w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karina and Lisa are trying to get me to listen to country music...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EM_Magazine: #ADE "Future of DJ technology" panel asks: Are iOS apps replacing specialized equipment for DJs? What do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Got yo back. #MostSupportiveFriendEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever claims to be in the light but hates others is still in the dark - 1 John 2:9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First attempt to make Pandesal today... Should be ready in about 5 min...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got an audio interface and a mic stand. Was able to do some recording with Ate Mayang and the… http://t.co/l8Vspq5FOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeannePineda #LifeOfThePinedas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got an audio interface and a mic stand! I can finally use my condenser mics!! Time to record.. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: If you had faith even as small as a mustard seed, you could say to this mountain, "Move from here to there," &amp; it woul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealYoungNoah: Dear Christian the world is not supposed to accept you. Acceptance by the world equals distance from God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a phone... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai highlight of the day: The grapes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haaas a skateboard noaaaw!! #SoHappy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Thats probs the best place to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Where we gunna go skateboarding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewParker2 needs to show me some producing tips.... Congrats on winning the Capital Kings remix contest, AGAIN!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So whats our plan for tutorials tomorrow? @TheManlySamurai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DJin' this whole weekend. Its been so long since Ive been on the turntables. It was a fun time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im kinda late, but I finally watched Tron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That dance battle thoooooo!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment in my music comp class when my teacher plays my song &amp; turns the volume up to the point where everyone can feel the bass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai we shall do this again sooooooooon.... And go ahead and take them =P AND WHERE'S MY $1.50!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>