<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/mk1y2gwKE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/8GH7dyP1gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/Dk6wvxRWfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/4ZgGhGboxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/ahASpMwV7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/fmwSkCR5ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/453JdZiWc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/YVsNprGXwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/uleST7YGx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/NDW2tbKxNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/CrdxNuRwsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/ULeqnHUmBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/4LLAs69Qxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/efGkWMhFL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/Cl83vrw6gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/weUPI6THE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/SJnKzhPaRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/uWhovyyp9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/KejO9z1p3t  http://t.co/g5JrwNJxeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/inT1kTVhjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/N4oJbwb6Qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/mGKgRSTq0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/J0jN28OTry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/NNERquotge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/q7el13093Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/aEElwzWfLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/uDjTxio0oL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/rkRZEbVfOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/q7el13093Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/0EZDAwrCGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/YR4yzmfSAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/OmwqoyxVbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/7shC6DIaaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/W2LdJethUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/YAsoIi17zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/inT1kTVhjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/YMkbszIakA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/UgwfFLz9yC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/6dADOAx0tI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/HzY6yi6LGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/LCoXyGqRJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/ofSedTUyGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/N6WLZnFaff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/FVzwyVWHr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/tOyCx7z53U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/NLZhCHsWcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/LARFtt2W0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Autism  http://t.co/9r8oX47V3n]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>