<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/5dqqb2YMcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/i9rEoFtQBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/HvUqT11IhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/gxc4eDzsMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/X04v4klpWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/MLIOCMxbEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/6DX5jGWgld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/TwrfZK5Wzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/5jfUJsM22Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/3OX37l1RIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/W3aj51isyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/4puYXj9e2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/uVelgsQtQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/738MHaukIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/rLlz9L7S1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/NF8RvIiu8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/b41D6fz6by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/5BmoCf8cth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/dZm5bWLARt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/XbEWqgA7Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/W1xNAZ7PHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/wFgAoN5ru4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/uAEbEEg5sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/dPCmqxkG25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/p46BfkpVxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/9ouxYFBKDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/ZHr8LJwOBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/sTLxgeq5Sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/0fUqLgGlOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/B0NYyDCeZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/82ZUR3DajG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/zJ2fZeYfaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/cPXokRYWyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/FJz0SOhFUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/jXyEzixUeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/gc7fqMxQ9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/nAdUGqkZL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/5vs55eGl4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/6vvrIFFuBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/QF8pvvHoye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/aPll1HEQ2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Kss85CYjQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/yHyWzZuFkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/cRALhCGxmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/KU0nS8Z30Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/HPXMFzbO0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/bU3fDzCfX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/GdKaljh9Mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/wy9Bx3ujyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/fhsvP6VXJF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>