<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists call discovery 'a game changer': As if their deadly venom and spiny exteriors weren't enough, scientists at the University of Kansas have found that stonefish also have a hidden switchblade on their face that they can flick out whenever they… https://t.co/AtTfDHRedS https://t.co/kari2skdsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weapons the US, UK and France used to target Syria: The United States combined with the armed forces of the United Kingdom and France early Saturday to carry out airstrikes against the chemical weapons facilities maintained by the regime of Syria. Here… https://t.co/RKiv1Al2Wb https://t.co/YXKRIXmkqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's message to Iran and Russia: President Donald Trump had a message for Iran and Russia during an address to the nation, asking "what kind of nation wants to be associated with the mass murder" of innocent people. https://t.co/OhHQ3ZNtD6 https://t.co/xsrBp3SEHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing with the Stars to feature athletes-only cast https://t.co/BDzPEKIgvu https://t.co/mgljhmeKjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic congressman: 'People will rot' for besmirching' Comey, Mueller: Rep. Jim Himes blasted detractors of former FBI Director James Comey and special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday, saying they "will rot in hell." https://t.co/HOi9ltOZ2T https://t.co/RMWdPYjuC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week in 26 photos: Take a look at 26 photos of the week from April 6 through April 12. https://t.co/suWmtTax52 https://t.co/Rm4lxS1ztk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot more to the Michael Cohen probe https://t.co/bUg8NVhrTn https://t.co/aXOV1sFtCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona governor offers teachers 20% pay raise: Faced with growing pressure from educators, Arizona Governor Doug Ducey announced Thursday his plan to give teachers 20% pay raises by the beginning of the 2020 school year. https://t.co/BHlqQ9vHEA https://t.co/FMQNfcy6sT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican voters are turning against the Mueller probe: Six months ago, Republican voters were almost evenly split on whether special counsel Robert Mueller was conducting a fair investigation into potential links between President Donald Trump's… https://t.co/bXdOA1BWZR https://t.co/vs80lhmrkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian 'genital-breathing' turtle faces extinction, group says: An Australian river turtle with a distinctive green punk-rock hairstyle, two spikes under its chin and the ability to breathe through its genitals is on a new list of endangered reptiles. https://t.co/XVTMlNq8OM https://t.co/LL31741iTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV shoot with Katie Holmes angers parents: A Chicago location shoot for a FOX television pilot starring Katie Holmes raised concerns for parents of students at an adjacent school. WBBM has more. https://t.co/x25YtSHJxn https://t.co/UwxPsaoNHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late-night hosts say goodbye to Paul Ryan: Late-night hosts Stephen Colbert, Jimmy Kimmel and Jimmy Fallon roasted House Speaker Paul Ryan after he announced he is not seeking re-election and will retire from Congress after this year. https://t.co/VCNDzMd3yA https://t.co/bb5hWbFOFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Meyers' son born in apartment lobby: Seth Meyers told his "Late Night" audience Monday that when his son, Ashe Olsen, was born two years ago, they worried he might arrive in an Uber. https://t.co/0NYh2tN04B https://t.co/KdbXUk4gHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lynching memorial rewrites American history https://t.co/yKdCZ0K16h https://t.co/1AEuwPjAqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police are reviewing 15 cold cases in Toronto serial killer investigation: Accused serial killer Bruce McArthur was charged with murder in the death of a seventh man Wednesday as police said they are reviewing cold cases for possible connections to him. https://t.co/d6r8r46z5E https://t.co/sFyBSfqhA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilary Swank snaps selfie with fan as doppelganger: Actress Hilary Swank talks to Conan O'Brien about often being mistaken for fellow actress Jennifer Garner. https://t.co/Fcos80un8N https://t.co/wFAZpRqdyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will be the next House Speaker?: Sources close to House Speaker Paul Ryan have said he won't seek re-election in 2018. CNN's David Chalian provides analysis on Ryan's decision. https://t.co/WsjjguP3cl https://t.co/Vdjgio4hAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's 10 most scenic airport approaches for 2018: The rocky coast of Donegal, Ireland played a starring role in the "Star Wars: The Force Awakens" when none other than the Millennium Falcon landed on the county's rocky Malin Head -- Ireland's most… https://t.co/xfRJ1GYIRh https://t.co/pE7hGOR7Mp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/ar9w75YviS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington is on edge watching a president who feels besieged by ever-widening legal probes around him: Donald Trump is acting like he feels the walls are closing in. https://t.co/tuHnNFPWta https://t.co/X41a5IInwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Senate fails its Facebook test https://t.co/2QO22DQY2U https://t.co/UGpp5pUmZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The proven health benefits of honey: Move over, prehistoric bears. Humans have loved honey since the Stone Age. https://t.co/4bzywckgZX https://t.co/kuDpA4qaHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Raid is about leverage: The FBI raids on the home, office and hotel room of President Donald Trump's lawyer Michael Cohen were shocking, but in some ways not surprising. I've been saying for a while now that the President's alleged affair with… https://t.co/2FmAzHDdla https://t.co/ul5Ou9KaJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt is the face of America's big problem: The federal government's top ethics official has asked the Environmental Protection Agency to take "appropriate actions to address any violations" rising from the behavior of the agency's administrator,… https://t.co/erdhx5y2HQ https://t.co/kN0uhlPUqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 10 years, he finally makes the NBA https://t.co/bxTcRIbqxg https://t.co/k9nvrGw2pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Four questions Congress must ask: Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg is headed to Capitol Hill to answer questions from lawmakers, after the company admitted the personal information of millions of users was shared with Cambridge Analytica, a firm… https://t.co/cSMYYn5luL https://t.co/PWG8JwAKcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A Quiet Place' leads box office, as horror keeps making noise: Another weekend, another No. 1 finish by a horror movie at the box office -- in this case, "A Quiet Place," a taut, niftily constructed exercise in tension starring and directed by John… https://t.co/o2G5sm9aZP https://t.co/SNQ3QZRNg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diabetes skin patch could abolish finger-prick tests: Researchers have created a skin patch that can measure glucose levels from hair follicles, bringing us one step closer to needle-less glucose monitoring. https://t.co/jQ6NSUblcz https://t.co/1e0V5yO9tQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/4gkzP0PCEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loretta Lynch counters 2017 Comey testimony: Former attorney general Loretta Lynch reacted to James Comey's 2017 Capitol Hill testimony when he said he was uneasy with her characterization of the Clinton email investigation as "a matter." https://t.co/9krWY3HpYw https://t.co/F26tpsRQ8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fleetwood Mac splits with longtime band mate: Fleetwood Mac and Lindsey Buckingham are cutting ties. https://t.co/fh6DTHkD83 https://t.co/wUDAMONc73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump said 'they broke into the office of one of my personal attorneys' and said 'it's a disgraceful situation' and 'a total witch hunt': President Donald Trump slammed the FBI raid on his personal attorney Michael Cohen's office and hotel room as a… https://t.co/WznO5jS9lW https://t.co/1SSJm8LQDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former intel heavyweights endorse Trump's CIA pick: More than 50 former US national security officials and lawmakers endorsed Gina Haspel, President Donald Trump's controversial pick to head the CIA, in a letter sent Monday to the Senate Intelligence… https://t.co/YnAs8mnqJ5 https://t.co/hqfYSwFcCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 cards charging 0% interest until nearly 2020 https://t.co/AoiIvDPDhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Bolton: I'm 'not much of a carrot man' https://t.co/5m18WHtPlh https://t.co/H9NoJQgclM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/GAaRHWaTEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump lost Ann Coulter https://t.co/LO1VNAvxmw https://t.co/QMyAJtIyYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your China-US trade fight questions, answered https://t.co/Q7IhGyCElb https://t.co/cTK3H2ykE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Robbins apologizes for #MeToo remark: Life coach Tony Robbins apologized Sunday for his comments about the #MeToo movement after suggesting during a March event that some women use it to gain significance by playing the victim. https://t.co/8mQ0ShkqJ0 https://t.co/ZC1KogZz5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Hannity, who mocked Michelle Obama, says it's wrong to mock Melania: This entire incident began simply enough on Monday night when ABC's Jimmy Kimmel did what late-night comedy hosts do: He told a joke. But now that one joke has given way to an… https://t.co/JUGvzcojkG https://t.co/JGhI2emsIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stelter: Trump's Fox News addiction has consequences: CNN's Brian Stelter explains how President Trump's "addiction to Fox" leads to impulsive actions. https://t.co/FBjGJ6JANA https://t.co/xEFrFpGHWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican President to Trump: 'No one stands above the dignity of Mexico': After days of President Donald Trump's aggressive rhetoric against immigration via Mexico, Mexican President Enrique Peña Nieto delivered a stern response to his US counterpart,… https://t.co/VCFXBeFmX4 https://t.co/wIYC1PXMcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality check on Trump's border war: The way President Donald Trump describes it, he's sending in troops to meet hordes of immigrants amassing at the southern border. https://t.co/n2ZrWCtGSu https://t.co/G4iJfyV4sW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/grU1bsRbO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN goes inside formerly besieged Eastern Ghouta: CNN's Frederik Pleitgen goes inside Eastern Ghouta -- the formerly besieged suburb of Damascus. Years of siege and fighting have laid waste to what used to be a thriving business district, leaving tens of… https://t.co/ohnr83TPtR https://t.co/xX6eR4tf7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Nugent likens Democrats, media and academics to rabid coyotes: 'Every time you see one, shoot one': Ted Nugent compared multiple groups he opposes to "rabid coyotes" on Friday, adding that you "keep your gun handy" to shoot them on sight. https://t.co/8WDzbuniGh https://t.co/UiE7rIzcee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Is Putin Trump's top adviser on Syria?: Why is President Trump suddenly in a rush to get out of Syria? https://t.co/YRQbIg0voa https://t.co/xkiUImDXqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several Syrian activist groups reported a brutal attack on the city of Douma, but the Syrian regime denies it: on Saturday reported that a brutal attack on the remnants of the rebel-held city of Douma in Eastern Ghouta left dozens of civilians killed and… https://t.co/aiQKF6sJLz https://t.co/Hnjgj7A6nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WSJ: Special counsel looking into Roger Stone's ties to WikiLeaks: Roger Stone's potential ties to WikiLeaks and its founder, Julian Assange, are being investigated by special counsel Robert Mueller, The Wall Street Journal reported Monday, citing a… https://t.co/Ex3wduLR23 https://t.co/KEB38dxNr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teens who dropped sandbag on car, killing man, are sentenced: Four Toledo, Ohio, teenagers accused of killing a man when they dropped a sandbag from a highway overpass have been ordered to a youth treatment facility, a court official said. https://t.co/9Kyvqy9fL5 https://t.co/ilFXhdz6Lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steph Curry names the worst popcorn in the NBA https://t.co/5ya1zOg7FR https://t.co/BD8EovBNdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia's oligarchs are different from other billionaires: Oligarch. It sounds nefarious, to be sure. CNN reported Wednesday that special counsel Robert Mueller, who is charged with investigating Russian election meddling, had questioned three Russian… https://t.co/k8XB4WyPt8 https://t.co/QMAUB5rJ3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/JQkDJKC7dl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: How Robert Mueller could finesse his endgame: If you want everyone to like you, don't become a prosecutor. The job ensures that, in almost every case, at least one person will be unhappy with you, regardless of your choices. The best prosecutors… https://t.co/YtG5N0vPbF https://t.co/9FUx1WJ13Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where disabled women are gang-raped and left: In 2014, a 23-year-old woman with cerebral palsy was allegedly gang-raped and thrown from the rooftop in the eastern Indian state of West Bengal. https://t.co/qecVKYEXkC https://t.co/a2zFc02Wvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN host spars with evangelical leader: You're cherry-picking: Tony Perkins, the president of the conservative Family Research Council, tells CNN's Erin Burnett that Scott Pruitt is only trying to protect himself. https://t.co/4rE9GSlC4n https://t.co/cJA2Ao8zNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlords changed locks to keep Pruitt out, source says: The couple that rented out a room to Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt forced him out by changing the code on their locks after becoming increasingly frustrated with him as… https://t.co/isWNWpO43u https://t.co/jGoBLdJzWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Airlines cancels deal with Airbus to buy 47 jets from Boeing https://t.co/OQGZCmHbt4 https://t.co/tMQNdQmFFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaping now an epidemic among US high schoolers: A sharp spike in vaping and the use of e-cigarettes by students has grabbed the attention of the US Food and Drug Administration. https://t.co/7JIRJOJtz7 https://t.co/sfVQBIbjMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JFK's 'secret' doomsday map revealed: An old map of Cuba is up for auction in Boston -- but it's much more than a map. https://t.co/0hbrcBHPzI https://t.co/v3XoXcqkUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven-foot-tall player drives tiny go-kart: He's more than seven feet tall. He has incredibly huge hands. And he 's an NBA record holder. https://t.co/WKeS9IlrpM https://t.co/xrkIyAGH3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why didn't I kill him? https://t.co/cVDPK39rg9 https://t.co/0lWvXzfpBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sports guy proving Trump wrong https://t.co/iANJVU3s2z https://t.co/jVBaTckdAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/pd1zrJyUmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border sheriff: Guard deployment unnecessary: CNN's Gary Tuchman travels to the Texas border where Sheriff Tom Schmerber tells him that he thinks President Donald Trump doesn't need to send National Guard troops for extra support. https://t.co/EO4dgMO75m https://t.co/Nl38AZa93K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFC star is wanted for questioning by NYPD: The New York Police Department wants to question Ultimate Fighting Championship star Conor McGregor in connection with an incident Thursday at the Barclays Center in Brooklyn, according to an NYPD source with… https://t.co/PXUgUKo3PC https://t.co/i0Tpaz4Pug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Paterno' tackles Penn St. scandal: "Paterno" bears the name of the legendary Penn St. football coach, but in ways he's a second-string player in this HBO movie, a look at his frantic final days that bears a striking resemblance to -- and includes the… https://t.co/Ek9MTnoWLU https://t.co/lvpzPZh3xV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Hall of Famer hit by truck and killed https://t.co/z3NtkbumS8 https://t.co/d5OVwJjaHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Nazi resolution fails again in Tennessee: A resolution condemning neo-Nazis and white nationalists died once again in the Tennessee legislature this week, the second time such a bill failed to pass the state house in the past few weeks. https://t.co/z6O9qc9GBB https://t.co/d2YpqX2T7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dwayne Johnson explains Vin Diesel feud: What we would have given to be a fly on the wall in the trailer with Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson and Vin Diesel. https://t.co/SeOXSC3iwO https://t.co/TyOUh2ppUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans' caregivers are subjects of immigration moves: After back-to-back, eight-hour shifts at a chiropractor's office and a rehab center, Nirva arrived outside an elderly woman's house just in time to help her up the front steps. https://t.co/eJJAv0ZtqP https://t.co/VVfajjFf80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-rival slams Trump as an 'ignoramus' on national security: Former presidential candidate Evan McMullin criticizes a reported directive issued by President Donald Trump to his military advisers to finish the mission in Syria within six months. https://t.co/RCFaT4kROW https://t.co/sy5Twi6Cek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/lEwXB1kqSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazingly simple way to pay off your mortgage fast https://t.co/P2GOwYzMvp https://t.co/fHkCyVP4Hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President got irritated when advisers warned that pulling out of Syria would be unwise, sources say: President Donald Trump grew irritated with his top military brass and national security team on Tuesday when they advised him an immediate withdrawal… https://t.co/0xnLDaKTpL https://t.co/bF19d3WyBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US expected to sanction Russian oligarchs: President Donald Trump's administration is expected to sanction "several" Russian oligarchs with ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin over 2016 election interference, according to two senior administration… https://t.co/EV7S8TKB6k https://t.co/c0FqqCKjI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks a lot like snow, but it's not: A home security camera in Apex, North Carolina, caught footage of pollen so large it looked like snow. https://t.co/i60uV6j7Iq https://t.co/NRdhwhzhpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kasich to CNN: Independent presidential run 'unlikely': Ohio Republican Gov. John Kasich says he is "unlikely" to challenge President Donald Trump in 2020 as an independent, but also spent Tuesday in this first-in-the-nation primary state, insisting… https://t.co/h7yeDLr22M https://t.co/gVfqIREl0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question that haunts MLK's final day: It's April 4, 1968, and the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. steps outside his room at the Lorraine Motel in Memphis, Tennessee, and leans over the balcony. https://t.co/xvAwt1hOtW https://t.co/mUVJbBCJnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/jdpou6tY2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McMaster: 'We have failed to impose sufficient costs' on Russia: In his last public remarks as national security adviser, Lt. Gen. HR McMaster offered harsh words for Russia Tuesday during a speech at the Atlantic Council in Washington DC. https://t.co/lMhTxJTlmz https://t.co/E2DikJ9NLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFCer has to cut scary amount of weight by Friday https://t.co/brTdrMN8na https://t.co/XA74y1VLfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: What to do when your boss forces you to read propaganda on air: The Sinclair Broadcast Group has come under heavy fire for giving its local TV anchors an unusual order -- they were required to read statements that appear to echo President Donald… https://t.co/EC0iV3oOBO https://t.co/BxKNRTngks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why nice people become mean online: Late in the evening of February 16, Professor Mary Beard posted on Twitter a photograph of herself crying. https://t.co/s4fKHsSAmA https://t.co/7zUiyHKmaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This satellite will find thousands of planets: TESS the planet hunter is getting ready to launch next month. The Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite is NASA's next mission in the search for exoplanets, or planets that are outside our solar system. https://t.co/1A6qUyMnvU https://t.co/R95IDGotX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bed, Bath &amp; Beyond will take your Toys 'R' Us gift cards https://t.co/rl6coNhlVe https://t.co/QPHKYIgbE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$1097: 8-night Rome, Tuscany &amp; Venice escape https://t.co/LpqSLH4L2K https://t.co/xnm3OJwKbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows violent arrest in Texas: Cellphone footage shows police forcibly detaining and hitting a man who was allegedly resisting arrest, according to Ft. Worth police in Texas. https://t.co/lmbAACeAW5 https://t.co/QNGRVSxJLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From teens to teachers, activism stirs the electorate: It's too early to declare a season of American revolt, but forces of activism and protest are stirring across the country that may yet nurture a genuine political pivot point. https://t.co/eHJI284rSg https://t.co/gm90FYGwas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Weeknd's new album and Selena Gomez: Was The Weeknd's new album inspired by the singer's breakup with Selena Gomez? https://t.co/DEbq6ukyo9 https://t.co/1SLI0Upd6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/6PByZx8Gqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgotten painting is worth millions: Robert Warren was poking through his art gallery's closet when he stumbled on an old painting hidden behind a table. https://t.co/n7upUzDPpz https://t.co/HhJ8D65yrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin unleashes Satan in a blaze of glory: Every week, I offer a glimpse of the kind of intelligence assessments that are likely to come across the desk of the President of the United States. Modeled on the President's Daily Briefing, or PDB, which the… https://t.co/j71i10dhFA https://t.co/k0xshQsApy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg reveals why he loves hoops https://t.co/IzEjiy3oNO https://t.co/PdurrWt5kI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House intern photo raises questions: Lynn Sweet, the Chicago Sun-Times' Washington Bureau Chief, told CNN's Victor Blackwell the lack of diversity in the White House's spring 2018 program signals the lack of commitment in Trump's White House to put… https://t.co/OPCC44sTnW https://t.co/MRWGHirj7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-apartheid activist Winnie Mandela dies: Winnie Mandela, the South African anti-apartheid activist and former wife of the late President Nelson Mandela, has died at the age of 81, a family member told CNN Monday. https://t.co/roBSBhPnPY https://t.co/rG1iscXC9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump and the GOP are gaining: New polling from CNN and other outlets indicates that President Donald Trump's job approval has improved since mid-December, and that the Democrats' advantage over Republicans in the upcoming midterm elections has shrunk. https://t.co/qdenEbyuu4 https://t.co/wKT8i3OeuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/u6vbzdia2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can 'Roseanne' reboot help Trump?: President Trump has a new favorite TV show but can Roseanne's support - and the monster ratings - perhaps also give the president a boost? https://t.co/NJgg2kaXWI https://t.co/rT9cXNu2aK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where fat goes when you lose weight: The world is obsessed with fad diets and weight loss, yet few of us know how a kilogram of fat actually vanishes off the scales. https://t.co/UWVFC2skyA https://t.co/Iph5XlnNYR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>