<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/MBGTyOPq5v https://t.co/1usIH8rwwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Strategy Consultant: SENIOR BUSINESS STRATEGY CONSULTANT w/ Red Hat, Inc. in Raleigh, NC. Business Strategy Consultant on Global Sales Operations team. Guide multi efforts to develop &amp; rationalize strategic initiatives for the Sales &amp;… https://t.co/7KJPH3yf1F https://t.co/yMyWmseDsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Senior Business Analyst Photon Infotech, Inc., Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Senior Business Analyst To gather, analyze &amp; document business, system &amp; functional requirements from clients and business users.… https://t.co/HPtCfdgrAu https://t.co/wa6fv8LXVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Architect: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Senior Software Engineer/Architect IT Engineering Suitland, Maryland MetroStar Systems is looking for a Senior Software Engineer/Architect that likes to lead and… https://t.co/j6ycSHTrOo https://t.co/5jjMprLZPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Manager Supply Chain: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Summary: Verizon Fios Supply Chain is looking for a Business Intelligence Manager who will be responsible for organizing and reporting data from our business intelligence… https://t.co/Ba2preH5r5 https://t.co/MbHbp6ukgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecommunications Network Research Analyst Job: Telecommunications Network Research Analyst (Job Number:420421) Description: Introduction We are looking for a self-starting, inquisitive Research Analyst to support collection of information and… https://t.co/64mZbOyOLW https://t.co/4XfdZSvi2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Trimbleis recruiting for a Software Engineer to fill an opportunity in Westminster, CO. The Agriculture division at Trimble is looking for an Enterprise Application Engineer to lead and collaborate on the design and development of an… https://t.co/2VUg4rGR5y https://t.co/cy5jQxCYba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Embedded Software 4:   Job Description – Engineer Embedded Software 4 (18012003) Engineer Embedded Software 4 Requisition ID : 18012003 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/5KHNwzeWHc https://t.co/q9YnlOtesI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: 5 + years experience object oriented application development in Python (Version 3.x desired) Results oriented with the ability to work independently and self-manage. Strong OOP, analytical, and troubleshooting skills. Experience… https://t.co/znNdrvFVAM https://t.co/Jbgjpuj1G6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Honolulu, HI Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/28/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/vkMdzDm22Y https://t.co/bC4Pk8bXH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator II: Database Administrator II needed in Tulsa, Oklahoma to provide database services including design, creation, and maintenance of database systems. Applicants must have the minimum of a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science,… https://t.co/9tRdwdpSVZ https://t.co/mO8NODfph8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance, Principal Engineer, R&amp;D – Advanced Technology: Medical Devices: Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance (#PS-1005) in Santa Ana, CA, requires 40% domestic &amp; 10% international travel; expenses paid by employer. Principal Engineer,… https://t.co/clQBNwoKeM https://t.co/hwrBQICncD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #IR1017PB: Senior Software Engineer sought by Crowdstrike, Inc., Irvine, CA: Lead backend engineering efforts from rapid prototypes to large-scale applications across CrowdStrike products.   recblid b7oxh9qlvlvglbdiil6yy6fgl4aghk https://t.co/uGE1BIhFSG https://t.co/MiBVk2Lkld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Research Analyst: Market Research Analyst to research market conditions/determine potential sales. Mon-Fri. 40 hrs/wk. 12 months exp. req’d. Mail Resume to Balloonzilla, LLC 18021 Sky Park Circle Suite K Irvine, CA 92614 recblid… https://t.co/wzlyQjiXjX https://t.co/PnR1xZGqWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Software Engineer: .Net Software Engineer: 6 month contract to hire Client offers 2 remote days each week after one is settled in. The key skills that will be used daily are – high level of techno-functional skills, solid understanding of .Net &amp;… https://t.co/E3kAHNAaOS https://t.co/raYqvt6LA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS DevOps Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-40957 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Job Description: SysOps or Cloud Systems Administration Position Summary… https://t.co/N9co8kom1t https://t.co/huJRgZGpcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrate/DevOps Engineer: General Dynamics IT has an opening for a Migrate/DevOps Engineer with strong communication and technical skills that will support the Department of Commerce 2020 Decennial Census Systems of Systems hybrid cloud infrastructure and… https://t.co/HFReGdw2g2 https://t.co/wWTlVsOVJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Company Summary =============== First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) operates through its family of companies to help people achieve and protect their dream of homeownership. First American was named one of FORTUNE’s 100… https://t.co/ECubMQKhMh https://t.co/XjvDGJSDf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-26510 Location: Montvale, New Jersey Role : Java Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Montvale, NJ Job Description : Java, Hibernate, Spring, REST Webservices, Oracle DB, JMS, NoSQL https://t.co/XpQJ1pd6Bg https://t.co/ycdjYwhsBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Systems Developer: Youngs Market Company – Careers -Salesforce Systems Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/Xcip2sr2Ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Asc Manager – Moorestown, NJ: Req ID : 433066BR Job Code/Title : L4504:Mult Func HR Asc Mgr Job Description : Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS) provides systems engineering, software development, training solutions and complex program… https://t.co/gaQcpKZYJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Job Description PSI Title: Systems Administrator Work Location: South Korea Description Essential Functions and Job Responsibilities: The successful candidate’s core responsibilities will include, but not to be limited to: –… https://t.co/7fDSH5dzd7 https://t.co/sGkA2anhSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description What is the opportunity? As a Software Engineer with RBC Wealth Management you will, be focused on Mainframe programming you partner across IT and with assigned business lines to assess, research, and analyze business,… https://t.co/sqducs4V5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Full Stack Developer Web Development Arlington, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Full Stack Developer that is passionate about designing and building some of the… https://t.co/KPQuwwWdqL https://t.co/cL1ZJV8KzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Careers Center | Java Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/hkamkPhwR5 https://t.co/xPU83Nvb9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer Net: Job Description Job Title: Senior Developer – .Net Requisition Number: 23442 Position Type: Full Time City: Brentwood Campus: Corporate OH State/Province: Tennessee Job Description: The Senior Developer – .NET is responsible for the… https://t.co/mYRhMJjMIZ https://t.co/OPgjaBlfXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer/SharePoint Architect: Job Description BAE Systems is seeking a skilled Front End Developer/Point Architect to act as the Point Subject Matter Expert for the directorate of a large government agency. Personnel will create customized… https://t.co/JvrWQYk6DP https://t.co/27KSD2LoXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Research Data Scientist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Norfolk, VA Job Type: Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/fsRZfMdzuN https://t.co/5fUYUJx7fl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/Visual Designer: THE ROLE: SENIOR UX/VISUAL DESIGNER – BEHAVIOR CHANGE PLATFORM We engages individuals in behavior changes that positively and measurably impact their well-being and performance. We focus upstream before stress and burnout lead to… https://t.co/8Qwh9HTshe https://t.co/dMU7VkdPmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. As a Senior Network Engineer, you will lead expansion of Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) which is being deployed throughout Verizon both In Franchise and Out of Franchise. You will provide… https://t.co/DSlf9Ol4Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Application Architect Burlington, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/04/18, Posted Date – 06/06/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview 6 month to 2 year in duration Corporate IT is actively searching for… https://t.co/cDZ3adP3mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer, Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/8/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/0ZjikOIhXf https://t.co/olU8efWd4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Application Developer/Configurator Duluth, GA: IT Application Developer/Configurator – Duluth, GA 3950 Shackleford Rd, Hampton Green Duluth, Georgia, 30096 United States IT Application Developer/Configurator – Duluth, GA The opportunity: – Support,… https://t.co/I6DcMJqIgB https://t.co/xu3FH87505]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager, Senior (Program Manager) – Secret Clearance Required: Organizes, directs, and manages contract operation support functions, involving multiple, complex and inter-related project tasks. Manages teams of contract support personnel at… https://t.co/yl1AdRITtW https://t.co/lK6aNvOxiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Project Manager: Job ID #: 13572 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Technology Services Group – Department: Technology Services – Operations – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location:… https://t.co/7nTm4vAR0B https://t.co/0N62z9d9nN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Support Analyst Internship: Summary: The Associate Support Analyst Intern will be responsible for providing customer service and frontline support for clients subscribing to Charles River’s suite of Managed Services including Application… https://t.co/4wjgLFcV5u https://t.co/chuQw2gXwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Senior Elastic Compute Platform Software Engineer with Clearance: Job Description BAE Systems is looking for System Programmer candidates that are interested in working an Elastic Compute Platform development and Utility Cloud… https://t.co/opteoQRGz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer: Project Engineer 1 sought by C&amp;D Zodiac, Inc. in Huntington Beach, CA. Engineering for systems and products. Monitor progress, manage, design. Create KPIs. Requires: BS + 2. recblid gzqjr1b5xbiloc69mntpakol5902nq https://t.co/muOdJra84G https://t.co/mXXND4eWIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/GYsJAr3BCt https://t.co/CLUcYBZSVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software and Controls Applications Engineer #10756TO: Software and Controls Applications Engineer – Englewood, CO. Design and optimize from concept to completion software, hardware, applications and control systems for new and existing products.… https://t.co/6QZNNrMRe2 https://t.co/Ehfyy4NRqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OEM Software Engineer: OEM Software Engineer sought by Masimo Corporation, Irvine, CA: Design, develop, and implement medical device firmware and software applications. recblid regtk2kzbd5y0ylggq0oxslpk425y9 https://t.co/1ipByQGn4e https://t.co/7WTQa55uG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II – Web Developer: The Scientific Informatics group at ABC supports R &amp; D activities at the Abbvie Bioresearch Center which focuses on immunology and biologics therapeutic development. We are looking for an exceptional candidate for a… https://t.co/PEQKBy5XFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Application Lifecycle Management (ALM) – West Coast USA (Remote): **Solution Architect – Application Lifecycle Management (ALM) – West Coast USA (Remote)** Locations:Foster City, California Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply… https://t.co/a0mJbA6h3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Solutions Architect – Networking: Job Title Inside Solutions Architect – Networking State Pennsylvania Description The Inside Solutions Architect (inside SA) provides pre-sale technical consutling to advise and recommend technology solutions of… https://t.co/37bXVJaC0q https://t.co/pmrkTwc6Ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management 2:   Job Description – Project Management 2 (18011060) Project Management 2 Requisition ID : 18011060 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/nKiHiyw9cC https://t.co/iluzaBuVQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Developer: JOB SUMMARY: Join our winning team with a 100-year track record of success. We’ve just completed our most successful year ever! Midmark has a corporate culture like no other in the markets we serve. As we continue to grow each… https://t.co/dVfqZWAFHg https://t.co/1q8P5xH8cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer: OVERVIEW We are looking to grow our team and are seeking a Software Engineer to work on a range of projects, from web applications to business apps to add-on tools for 3rd party software. We value creative, strategic… https://t.co/ZL0Zm36oi8 https://t.co/60Wx8yLOmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversion EE Project Manager: Location San Jose – CA, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 5/2/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2501 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to… https://t.co/xAlaoqhrAV https://t.co/n7e0sm5aJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plc Programmer / Industrial Electrician: PLC Programmer / Industrial Electrician Unilock, a family-owned and operated business, originally introduced the paving stone to North America in 1972. Backed by family values and a commitment to quality, Unilock… https://t.co/Nce0V7Rwk3 https://t.co/8nRAwYQN7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multifamily Project Manager – Ground-Up Podium Builds: Oakland, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based out of Oakland, CA, we are Builders. With over thirty years of experience, we are Northern and Central California’s premier commercial,… https://t.co/K1gn7u6Zq1 https://t.co/KbzA4bakAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Automation Developer: Company Summary =============== First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) operates through its family of companies to help people achieve and protect their dream of homeownership. First American was named one… https://t.co/hmuud7tNh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer, Apple Media Products Infrastructure: Changing the world is all in a day’s work at Apple. If you love innovation, here’s your chance to make a career of it. You’ll work hard. But the job comes with more than a few perks. Hands-on… https://t.co/arQauFoFrr https://t.co/IQLd6o81cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description Engineering Project Manager (WD***********) What you will do: Join the Johnson Controls Valve &amp; Actuator Product Engineering team as a Senior Project Manager. Plan and manage hardware projects that define,… https://t.co/EBSwVgX5x0 https://t.co/GZacaeKEgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Engineer: SOLUTION (ELECTRICAL) ENGINEER (multiple positions) for Siemens Industry, Inc. (Raleigh, NC) anlyze cstmr’s tech specs rgrdng app of Siemens swtchgr prdcts alng w/ assctd prtctn &amp; cntrl systms. Req Mast in Elec Eng or rel + 2 yrs exp… https://t.co/aXnSqfuBmu https://t.co/cQ7ibZuej3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Aberdeen, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/F6HnSt1dej https://t.co/J5E6zwW8g8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect Enterprise Integration Services: Solution Architect – Enterprise Integration Services Date: Apr 21, 2018 Location: Clinton, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now… https://t.co/wKHIiQOeuf https://t.co/dXGyQR7gab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Engineering Lead: Job ID: ********-11804-SH Company Name: Verisk 3E Description: Do you have an entrepreneurial spirit and know how to get things done? Are you looking to join a company where creativity and innovation is encouraged? If… https://t.co/TVQfFZeD4n https://t.co/Atf3hHek7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire Alarm Designer Project Systems Specialist II: Job Description Fire Alarm Designer – Project Systems Specialist II (WD***********) What you will do Johnson Controls l is a global leader in the design, manufacture, installation, and service of a… https://t.co/F5oKGQU0E4 https://t.co/LogqsGB7bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Administrator (Windows or Linux ) 4:   Job Description – Sr. Systems Administrator (Windows or Linux ) 4 (18008602) Sr. Systems Administrator (Windows or Linux ) 4 Requisition ID : 18008602 Location : United States-Virginia-McLean US… https://t.co/faAskNppqm https://t.co/sGMJzKeATe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr DevOps Engineer: Design, development, and deployment of software, databases, and script-based tools for a wide range of needs, with a primary overall purpose of automation/streamlining of operational processes and providing insights into business… https://t.co/xMzf9EPJID https://t.co/oigKIC3E0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer: MaxLinear, Inc., a leader in highly integrated RF analog and mixed-signal semiconductor solutions, has the following degreed/experienced position available in Irvine, CA: Systems Applications Engineer. To apply, mail resume to:… https://t.co/oTcS314NJT https://t.co/aKwDpIaBwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Development Expert for SuccessFactors, Inc. (South San Francisco, CA) to be responsible for development focusing on concept, design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team or responsible for complex… https://t.co/OY0LlCFKSc https://t.co/UMhg3iCAct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Project Manager, Catalog Mastering: Brand Paramount Pictures iCIMS ID 2018-8876 Overview and Responsibilities This position is responsible for overseeing and managing the transfer of Catalog titles and the delivery of all Archival and… https://t.co/eTSgdhKS28 https://t.co/ZZzHeGYV7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineer, Robot Programmer: Manufacturing Engineer, Robot Programmer Job Description: There are 7 billion people on this planet. And by 2050, there will be 2 billion more many moving into urban centers at an unprecedented rate. Making sure… https://t.co/YD2kjYqFYy https://t.co/ny73zazXAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Security Consultant: Sr. Network Security Consultant Ref No.:18-00098 Location: Sacramento, California Skill Type:Service Delivery Job Type:Contract Career Level:Mid to Senior Level NWN is recognized as one of the top 16 Cisco partners in the… https://t.co/iNoXgkAIMD https://t.co/JsuubXCVCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer: Java Fullstack Developer Ref No.: 18-26112 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey Role : Java Fullstack Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Secaucus, NJ Job Description : Full-Stack Software Engineer- Frontend experience Backend… https://t.co/1t1bdBuDjk https://t.co/P5te0P8f20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Business Analyst: Sr. Systems Business Analyst – Requisition ID: WD****** – Position: Full time – Open date: Jun 5, 2018 9:20 AM – Functional area: IT – Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania – Required degrees: Bachelors – Experience required:… https://t.co/Yrk9fWFLNY https://t.co/s4qDb29NT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Financials Developer: Prestigious Enterprise company is currently seeking a Senior Financials Developer with C++ and preferably Python experience. Candidate will join a team responsible for the C++ Library that implements major market and credit risk… https://t.co/55XwoHDoss https://t.co/DY6Resl7gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Technical Program Manager: IT Strategy and Operations: Description Infoblox is seeking a Sr. IT Technical Program Manager: Infrastructure, Operations, and Security. The Senior IT Technical Program Manager will join our Information Technology team… https://t.co/uATHu6gGpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Quality Assurance Analyst: Great opportunity for senior QA analysts to join a fortune 500 company located in the Cleveland, OH area. All levels are needed, from intermediate analysts all the way up to QA Lead, with and without automated testing… https://t.co/QeRmrYz51b https://t.co/eZ9RXYcnaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Marketing: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the world?… https://t.co/1RvgzMWqU7 https://t.co/AeyLgWsFbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-26356 Location: Troy, Michigan Position: Salesforce Developer Location: Troy ,MI Duration: Fulltime Permanent Role – Candidate must have strong experience with Visualforce, Apex, Triggers, Eclipse… https://t.co/Ohj3gatezO https://t.co/9Bcb5Z4iCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack/Java: at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Waltham, MA Senior Software Engineer, Front End Constant Contact, Inc. helps small businesses and nonprofits connect with their customers, clients, and members.… https://t.co/m7Hz8i2eE3 https://t.co/Z6eI97CRLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OR Systems Administrator: Job Description Adventist Healthcare – A premier healthcare system – A compassionate mission of healing – Dynamic Maryland/Washington D.C. market We are a non-profit network of healthcare providers based in Rockville, Maryland.… https://t.co/YYEmUEfgTx https://t.co/xJBPiAKxKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS Systems Administrator: Job TitleSAS Systems Administrator – ID:31805 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSAS GRID Manager/SAS Platform, Linux OS LocationPlano, TX Date Posted05/25/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of… https://t.co/RbfsywHnA4 https://t.co/EdJMvTSELx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Time Oracle Cloud Procurement Functional SME (75-100%, travel): Position: Oracle Cloud Procurement Functional SME (75-100% travel) Location: Sterling, VA Duration: Full Time Consulting Oracle Cloud Procurement Functional SME – primarily with strong… https://t.co/HrOoIlvF6Q https://t.co/TmlFJNHz8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal-Consulting-Technology-System Integration-Specialist Senior: Federal-Consulting-Technology-System Integration-Specialist Senior in Los Angeles, California, United States | Information Technology at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About… https://t.co/tbqtdl1QPE https://t.co/VRNh65JeMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Data Architect ============== Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is currently looking for outstanding IT… https://t.co/YtQrIE2EjP https://t.co/NwMqnQrQWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager II: Job Title: IT Project Manager II Requisition Number: 23941 Position Type: Full Time City: Brentwood Campus: Corporate OH State/Province: Tennessee Job Description: The IT Project Manager II is responsible for developing,… https://t.co/aybuj20ZU6 https://t.co/v9AD7MsfPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2 (Java): The Asurion’s Back Office Gateway IT team has created critical enterprise applications to support Asurion global billing, tax calculations and other functions, which are essential for business innovations and customer… https://t.co/uM5GOig1c5 https://t.co/zfix0YZyJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apex Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/14eNR2n9cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing… As the End to End Architect you will handle the marketing initiatives that drive the annual revenue growth and margin improvement for Verizon Consumer Markets. You will lead a variety… https://t.co/J93b21nK4Y https://t.co/KRjjjCZzml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Engineer: La Jolla, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today We are making a game changing impact on both small and large companies. Helping them with putting their best foot forward. With UI/UX approach we are helping companies succeed with… https://t.co/nwe4aBN6wu https://t.co/5qDAH2NpjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Query Broker: Req ID : 437928BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : The GIMS (GEOINT Information Management Services) Next Program provides critical capabilities to help enable efficient and timely GEOINT… https://t.co/5UwSllClYo https://t.co/6cPQrivBSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Demand Generation: Help Drive Demand For The System Of Record For Data Teams: Periscope Data is looking for a Director of Marketing to drive our GTM, customer acquisition and demand generation strategies and tactics. You’ll drive our… https://t.co/f8goXeTsUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer(US Citizens and Green Card Holders Only): Job Summary Direct hire opportunity for a .NET Developer to join the team. We are looking for someone with development knowledge and experience in Microsoft development technologies. *******… https://t.co/0U0yHydL5h https://t.co/JWqdWSgvoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Ariba Software Engineer in Test Job: Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Software-Quality Assurance Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Regular Full Time COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP started in 1972 as a team of five… https://t.co/KJbSce1Hc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commmunications Systems Engineer 4:   Job Description – Commmunications Systems Engineer 4 (18011169) Commmunications Systems Engineer 4 Requisition ID : 18011169 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/RCjSePlRk8 https://t.co/KzgEOejk4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Analyst: Financial Analyst (Multiple Positions); Mountain View, CA; Develop financial and data models and tools that provide a platform for Google decision making. #JUN2018MV FA Exp Incl: financial analysis, financial modeling, or financial… https://t.co/0H4yXgKm1v https://t.co/MY1fhPEVWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Denver, CO Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/z6PlLhFFXm https://t.co/hiUeVlD3HK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator ===================== Req #: ******Location: Herndon, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description What You ll Get to Do:… https://t.co/drSxOrOzVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer (EDA): Job Title: Senior Staff Software Engineer (EDA) – ****** Primary Location United States-California-San Jose Job: Software Engineering Schedule: Full-time Description Xilinx is industry leader in providing FPGA… https://t.co/C45Mff8G2A https://t.co/HW64NBdXR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Support Specialist/Help Desk: Systems Support Specialist/Help Desk Job Description CoStar provides industry professionals and consumers of commercial real estate and apartments with critical knowledge to explore and complete transactions by… https://t.co/fpN3fVtihc https://t.co/ksYYy98Ahj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Valuation Manager – Greensboro or Raleigh Office!: Raleigh, NC Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Business Valuation Manager with minimum 5 years of experience overseeing complex Business valuation projects and… https://t.co/sUGV2ayweY https://t.co/ovHUxQdzcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 3-4:   Job Description – Engineer Software 3-4 (18010694) Engineer Software 3-4 Requisition ID : 18010694 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/EshTFp39zl https://t.co/j2Zgp3cqRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: MUST BE A US CITIZEN WITH A U.S. GOVERNMENT CLEARANCE – TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH NOTE:Must have an active TS-SCI with poly. No sponsorships or upgrades are available. Submissions without this requirement will not be considered. H1-B… https://t.co/QbdA9RI0Lg https://t.co/WM147UYDMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Software Engineer II with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media… https://t.co/7YVDbdvCUb https://t.co/zA6c5n5Bfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer – Requisition ID: WD****** – Position: Full time – Open date: May 16, 2018 7:13 PM – Functional area: Engineering – Location: Upper Merion, Pennsylvania – Required degrees: Bachelors – Experience required: 2 years… https://t.co/HOOSYk7bSH https://t.co/EGYaHaQHMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator – Linthicum: Hi: My name is Criss Brient with ALTA. We are looking to fill the following positions in Linthicum, MD. Salary / Terms negotiable. Please call to discuss more details. CRISS BRIENT ALTA[Click Here to Email Your Resum]… https://t.co/iWxuMERsVH https://t.co/nKHEjxN4O0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Engineer: San Jose, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Machine Learning Engineer with 3+ years of experience, please read on! **Your application will be considered incomplete unless the screening questions… https://t.co/VMp6IsBThm https://t.co/hYvQnYfTtY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>