<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret Service responds to reports of shots fired at White House - https://t.co/zNKfks1GdH https://t.co/SDw9KW2n13 https://t.co/sVhMBqFjkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret Service: Man shoots himself near WH https://t.co/01f0BnotQ8 https://t.co/J6pNqIbJfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: White House on LOCKDOWN as 'shots fired' - Daily Star https://t.co/4556GLqIvh https://t.co/AsYwNV7Tjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active search for missing Hickman Police Officer - WPSD Local 6 https://t.co/PdZEXyVP1y https://t.co/uTUcZBI3GG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe's icy blast claims more lives https://t.co/cPKu5Diydw https://t.co/nOHCyjnStU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student suspected of killing his parents on campus arrested - CBS News https://t.co/3srItfsRjr https://t.co/RiiibbwGYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Get Your Hopes Up on Gun Reform - The Atlantic https://t.co/wIATlRCqpV https://t.co/H3aSQei8pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See waves taller than homes lash coast https://t.co/h0ayGx4CT2 https://t.co/FiiIKcGTou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain Las Vegas shooting victims' families to receive $275G each, donation fund says - Fox News https://t.co/DSQhfvQUzv https://t.co/3dqOogoBdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow-moving nor'easter brings coastal flooding and hurricane-force winds. Five people have died. https://t.co/7htUb8FUIp https://t.co/Ohh2Q6YN6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why social media surveillance isn't the answer to our gun crisis - Mashable https://t.co/DguVX1VhMR https://t.co/AU33d8V6do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowdfunding for Marjory Stoneman Douglas student newspaper hits halfway mark - CNNMoney https://t.co/ZBqVAsAueA https://t.co/EuHKKzk9Yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Winter Storm, Avalanche Leave 1 Dead, 2 Injured - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/SKRztlLByw https://t.co/QoIEr6Wlog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump risks more than a trade war by targeting China https://t.co/zTdYaRvLDw https://t.co/Ki1igN4Ec3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain Las Vegas shooting victims' families to receive $275G each, donation fund says - Fox News https://t.co/AhWG9O1aLi https://t.co/xK9F1RO0cL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston's streets are flooding https://t.co/4d8XGlksWB https://t.co/zVh14Clx0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scaramucci says he's banned from the WH https://t.co/dtALXY3VJX https://t.co/Ph5KMW7Nlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days before the election, Stormy Daniels threatened to cancel deal to keep alleged affair with Trump secret - Washington Post https://t.co/SVpZGcjVSv https://t.co/oU30Fjcuhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Ross hospitalized in Florida after becoming ill at home - USA TODAY https://t.co/HPtIA1PQt3 https://t.co/WUQCaDpuwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flake: Trump will have 2020 challenge https://t.co/LEfb7G8N1y https://t.co/0jck6iztW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sours flagging NAFTA talks with steel trade war threats - Reuters https://t.co/ZVKm2KxaMu https://t.co/w8hD9qfrC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapper: If this isn't a tailspin, what is it? https://t.co/2Pt0aajsPA https://t.co/9mIzRPuvBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orrin Hatch apologizes for saying Obamacare supporters 'stupidest, dumbass people I've ever met' - USA TODAY https://t.co/MoX0j8aBR2 https://t.co/b2U7KHdsq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defiant Kelly continues to misrepresent his handling of scandal https://t.co/ks7ngNxdnC https://t.co/KBTidbzI2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump thinks a trade war would be good https://t.co/4FxcaB5P4J https://t.co/R7DDJ9K7Qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one knows where Trump is on guns -- perhaps including Trump https://t.co/dxwfbNFgVG https://t.co/TKVbjWpNP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boone County deputy will not survive shooting; his organs are being donated - https://t.co/Yl5UP75Zrs https://t.co/iKOukJFO9S https://t.co/oAHtMy1Vow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly says sorry not sorry https://t.co/Uscvdps3YJ https://t.co/hMD3iNFK65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Attacks Alec Baldwin In Early Morning Twitter Rant Amid Week Of Chaos - HuffPost https://t.co/8ZhEmwQn2P https://t.co/Ybb4ZdqhAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only strategy is that there is no strategy https://t.co/o8UlNioJwC https://t.co/ZBcug919WN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Says He Was Aware of White House Clearance Problems Last Year - Bloomberg https://t.co/7zceT4qgLV https://t.co/D5DNSevwmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparent explosive device found on Mexican ferry off Cozumel - ABC News https://t.co/HgLXdh5a3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Are Academy Voters So Pissed Off About Netflix's Oscars Prospects? - Vulture https://t.co/MhqMg9BMn1 https://t.co/k4Lqezk8Em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump's tariff move shows his ignorance https://t.co/ghDgmnhw1y https://t.co/wfNatHwQ8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hard facts' for both sides in Brexit talks - Theresa May - BBC News https://t.co/k946IyEVVo https://t.co/bOSXTb9yl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The last American 'trade war' didn't work out so great https://t.co/Ew3iLd4C5K https://t.co/ZbLHw63jcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Michigan shooting: University responds to report of shots fired, says suspect at large - live updates - CBS News https://t.co/wklWE9r0vR https://t.co/fExATsmElU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['LIFE &amp; DEATH' warning issued as nor'easter poses 'bomb cyclone' threat https://t.co/HJXS5gNaVW https://t.co/YQZGDtpvsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump trashes Baldwin's 'terrible impersonation' https://t.co/gnsz2MMvsy https://t.co/Hq3iXjFqkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon looks to adjust missile defense policy to include threats from Russia, China - Washington Post https://t.co/BqXMb3jkb9 https://t.co/8SNZqphLCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT: Trump using Kelly to push out Ivanka https://t.co/WxueBljouF https://t.co/NNeNOFPYXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Borger: The great unraveling of Trump https://t.co/HgKXLKFdDP https://t.co/elMchovNr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burkina Faso attack: Ouagadougou sees gunfire and explosion - BBC News https://t.co/668iM7zoOs https://t.co/PsBJY2fKa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump defends tariffs, says 'trade wars are good' https://t.co/vMgG31jqii https://t.co/89GapwZVfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper presses Dana Loesch on Trump's gun comments https://t.co/yPeOQd1tnL https://t.co/lKYyI7wSqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montecito is warned to evacuate ahead of storm, and jittery residents are ready to go - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/0edo7mCUnn https://t.co/lkcpr6i2hG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do gun policies save lives? Lack of research means we just don't know - USA TODAY https://t.co/ZVdTH9rA5s https://t.co/t9noZX1Es1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother Details Day She Found Her Children Slain in Bathroom - New York Times https://t.co/yCMcvvVVAq https://t.co/N5iPo69iVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper: Setbacks contradict past Trump claims https://t.co/Goi4J2Tl7b https://t.co/WZvl5WJ6HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: You don't have a country without steel https://t.co/BFOFwQ7l3h https://t.co/chw5uwmQjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Orrin Hatch calls Obamacare supporters 'stupidest, dumbass people' https://t.co/U3kjjthekr https://t.co/Cddrzhoaei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and NRA meet, tweet mutual support https://t.co/YRKIxpKjbz https://t.co/zVnNLuPH0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department reviewing Oakland mayor's tipoff of immigration raids, which led to 232 arrests - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/UHv3PlO2Hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Shoot A School Kid Only $29': Vegas Gun Range Billboard Vandalized - CBS Los Angeles https://t.co/BLY1oCpOFr https://t.co/DoZCYEJLKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator says Kushner has no business being in White House https://t.co/CUupzfoKht https://t.co/SffNxj1Rck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California family found living in box for 4 years, officials say - Fox News https://t.co/Arb2XDhx9o https://t.co/3TQ9LLr5lG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McMaster could leave the White House by the end of the month https://t.co/CNQ39UcQVg https://t.co/k3Hp9ZSs3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH promised firearms policy plan by Friday. Then Trump had his 'surreal' guns meeting. https://t.co/FhkxWkZESw https://t.co/LTUaxyqWPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple people found dead in Massachusetts home, police say - Fox News https://t.co/pnF29zIOOr https://t.co/RQ6zWaZiNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: 57% think Trump is a racist. Or do they just not like him? https://t.co/amQLU71GJo https://t.co/bY5qlnguG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: FBI counterintel investigating Ivanka Trump business deal - CNN https://t.co/RLTN0XC3Qq https://t.co/2fxK48rQms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Jeff Sessions finally called Trump's bluff https://t.co/h3NvCGECJ7 https://t.co/XHrXEaSg1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: 'Javanka' should follow Hope Hicks out the door https://t.co/Fgs3qSrxci https://t.co/ksyaonj1ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The feuds and frustrations splitting the Trump White House https://t.co/r0m35WVtm9 https://t.co/VMzmLVtPHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bodies of woman, three children discovered inside Massachusetts home: police - Fox News https://t.co/Dr14wDxzy9 https://t.co/BG6jNoxlku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia Senate approves tax bill, snubbing Delta in NRA feud - ABC News https://t.co/cQZppsMvMl https://t.co/mw7A1Rswrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Think the White House is in chaos now? Just wait. https://t.co/LR1GYBKlJs https://t.co/PU3ewURlXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump hails drug death penalty nations https://t.co/qKiZsz8BtZ https://t.co/Ed3GmLk7yF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Intelligence Leaders Say House GOP Leaked a Senator's Texts - New York Times https://t.co/rEuwiv8KkQ https://t.co/sjEUpJUTb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate dashes hopes for swift gun legislation https://t.co/uQtWRjXl7C https://t.co/O0XbSXweex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US ambassador to Mexico resigning in another big loss for State Department - ABC News https://t.co/DL4GE1mRzW https://t.co/Uw5AakqDpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Republicans are angry about the tariffs https://t.co/xyhqRLcExd https://t.co/gDn908N3pW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two powerful GOP senators unhappy with tariffs https://t.co/eD5LNIn6Uz https://t.co/vQHLvnKt2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Ambassador to Mexico to Quit Amid Tense Relations Under Trump - New York Times https://t.co/jlOjv6mWjo https://t.co/ALGQ1qZQEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kelly jokes about his job: God punished me https://t.co/JDsmwKWNPU https://t.co/ihKNyxVFD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House pulls back from expected announcement on imported steel tariffs - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/XrYImYE5qF https://t.co/qV4xE8BOx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US to impose steel and aluminum tariffs next week https://t.co/z9whmotc1P https://t.co/ihkr7Q570f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Oversight Committee wants info on office redecoration https://t.co/PMVnZpVOu5 https://t.co/x90MOG8Z2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Arrested in White Powder Mailings to Donald Trump Jr., Antonio Sabato Jr., Other Public Figures: Feds - NBC New York https://t.co/JVTsYSYrlw https://t.co/Bv9GHBzF0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the dining set HUD wanted to buy https://t.co/y38B2ilIHU https://t.co/vUNzvzTurH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Meetings With Jared Kushner, and $509 Million in Loans: DealBook Briefing - New York Times https://t.co/CYI7JiJWGN https://t.co/JLFeq2I1zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: The 43 standout lines from Trump's gathering on guns https://t.co/tMGXKSZaAo https://t.co/BGv6pK44Qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives Are Losing the Culture War Over Guns - The Atlantic https://t.co/piUXrh5nLq https://t.co/rxpXWvbuWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scaramucci: Culture of fear inside White House https://t.co/m5zORRa6Ni https://t.co/ozEYkTntPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A diverse community of believers thrives in Billy Graham's Charlotte - https://t.co/zNKfks1GdH https://t.co/TAWnYOIhrp https://t.co/zPjRxpxYyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pennsylvania couples clutching AR-15 rifles renew wedding vows - CNN https://t.co/rLZ8xLwdZu https://t.co/SXqZv2YKQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill to allow red light running passes committee in Utah House - https://t.co/NWslIKs3n6 https://t.co/uMpggu0tIu https://t.co/vfLk1vTPcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at odds with Republican lawmakers over gun reforms - BBC News https://t.co/ACVQySv4jl https://t.co/XzsYLXJMT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Governor reacts to Delta, NRA fallout: We didn't start this https://t.co/QtG2SBWjSU https://t.co/vwNNoIn06v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at odds with Republican lawmakers over gun reforms - BBC News https://t.co/cdiaWJXVHO https://t.co/mVHEiSZBqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Stuns Lawmakers With Seeming Embrace of Gun Control - New York Times https://t.co/iE9uAUONrM https://t.co/3U12NTyGPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hicks' departure leaves the inner circle of the President, for whom loyalty is an obsession, in tatters https://t.co/d7FxzLwcF9 https://t.co/tckfqmkUFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman accused of poisoning look-alike with cheesecake - CBS News https://t.co/Xe4xZhpZzi https://t.co/Wa4hCnpkXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St. Lucie deputies investigate connection in three bodies found in Port St. Lucie - TCPalm https://t.co/RoD8D0d6Ro https://t.co/LCaGoAvHSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians hand in 57000 firearms during gun amnesty - CNN https://t.co/axeGLBebBT https://t.co/Q3ZTUCe2MO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernstein and Woodward compare Trump, Nixon responses https://t.co/yctt74XwnD https://t.co/vu02udZsPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NRA: Trump's meeting on guns 'great TV' but 'bad policy' https://t.co/KxWkuRjr4c https://t.co/P1fiUXZJcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio: Gun control debate reminds us we 'don't like each other very much' - The Hill https://t.co/ahbIIm1aAo https://t.co/MXVtnC3wrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker: More Jews would have survived Holocaust if they were armed https://t.co/qeZqloZjJ6 https://t.co/bchxZ0QeHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Things to Know About the Big, Snowy Storm Approaching California - KQED https://t.co/0oqIqm5DNC https://t.co/VlAB5dHMJv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>