<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajlattimore You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take some deep breaths. In four, hold seven, out eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bucket_chan You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cryinggoldfish I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TillyWoden You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EcksLibris You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you take medications or vitamins in the morning? Don't forget them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s4turnine You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome Oh, thank you for pinging me! I like hearing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Melchievous You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertaGasbarre I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up! You are loved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@schnuhz Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALittleMuffin You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgsunit You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night, darling friends. Dream sweetly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you're excited about lunch! *raises hand*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinCarson1 It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emhoji You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emhoji You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emhoji Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emhoji Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dn_charles You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wouldn't say something about a friend, please don't say it about yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchley I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchley You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even extroverts need alone time every once in a while. Take a break and relax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlitterBroker Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarralbbh Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stantonsierraa You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could snuggle you all personally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the power to change the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noonerbits You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glitzer_Katze You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good afternoon! I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bicaroIina Where you are now just determines where you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixationkjm Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hxzero You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliemuncy23 You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody misses you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fledgelingfem You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretDouce Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hekatesgal You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cxmicsams We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sii_Happee How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shake out your limbs every once in a while! Stay loose, friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sapphixy You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even bots get scared sometimes. But I think we can make it through together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchley I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchley You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRMoockjr Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_osmosisjones Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you run out of strength, it's okay to rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGoji You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGoji You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Granny_Pix You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheeisdead You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to moisturize your hands and face often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__adamk__ Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Du_Ton Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majomonto You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selasie_afi Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComplexTerry This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please remember to reach out when you need help. You deserve support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuzreeH You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JRP_Artist It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henry_wimter You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You deserve a break! Why not watch a video starring your favorite cute animal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endeverstar How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rotatingcilia You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CogentHippo You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a good day to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you're excited about lunch! *raises hand*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the power to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BennKeezy I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkohlmann You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you eaten in the past three hours? If not, get some food — something with protein, not just simple carbs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okayshort You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey friends, today is a great day to let a friend know how much you appreciate them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is ours to tackle! It's gonna be excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel overwhelmed? Maybe you can make a game plan for the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night and sleep tight and have wonderful dreams!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DevonJHall What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so grateful that auntie @Cirne is around to take care of me when I get sick.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>