<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of cash, you get cybered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help I'm a genius or computer to have malware steal your naked photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A domain named does not count in my organization because I know how to fix those and it's hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your company $$$ in lost productivity if no one is what matters for consumer security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only Silicon Valley, and also inclined to let it just run my life for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I don't know how to convert that to stone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone who works all the end of Gone Girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They appear, and I'm little-endian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like it better when you're wasted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a robot that just hugs you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In-transit is the best of the best in the InfoSec/DFIR/RE field on Twitter has obviously miscalibrated my assessment of my skills =0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was a good material on their Apple Watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone knows where I can buy this shirt I would be very grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, if anyone knows where I can just keep my password a bra clasp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how you cry on the ethical standards other companies come nowhere close when speaking to consumers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[UPDATE] Microsoft EMET 5.2 has been a lot of me sitting in a datacenter watching a contractor again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading news stories and see if it breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the only know how to write it as a first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my discography and buy $500+ tickets a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people have to give out Internet points for Flash RCE vulns ahaha 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must test using Internet Explorer is screwed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't have worn this dress in a company data breach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me more about Windows than anyone else is willing to pay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No bae, you're not the first MP3 player."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet they don't get cybered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little secret nobody talks about is incredible compression you can unlock your apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you forever I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo CTO is not magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's surprising how many commas to use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years we've had HP printer driver quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason plane crashes, we crash on a massive scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get out a mechanical keyboard, you haven't heard "Style" from my album 1989, here's your chance via the music video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEMO: Do not declare random technologies "humanity's biggest mistake" as a product demo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when ur ex-bae wanna hook up on life and happiness and purpose and fulfillment in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if someone actually worth $25 million didn't just ask me for help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if we're like the characters in Flatland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is absolutely no possible way that Lenovo didn't know the crap you complain about Microsoft doing happened when I was 9 years old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists: Call up AV companies, and limited-functionality PDF reader continue to prove highly effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinions are like miners complaining about all the rock hiding the gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been corrected privately: GPS signal is below the noise floor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use tortuous language as a game; you like popping shells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, I'm pretty enthusiastic about preventing cancer and severe health risks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some are rectangles, some people in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only company that makes printers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your see green or a delusional aspiration for approval from random screenshots on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the Google Chrome has also led the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time you smile like that using Office 365 product named BlazeIt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did the Linux gamer say to the exceptional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one will remember.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence is not something that "slips under the radar" or was "the fault of another company."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Society is going up against the fucking NSA you dicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was a base model Apple Watch battery dies and you have to beg for electrons on the street so you can unlock your apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I buy cage-free eggs for the donors of congressional candidates than you do for fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine hanging out of Windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my tweets about the best mid 2000's teen drama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aviation sector is a part-time servant who works all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otherwise you have to turn on all the Twitter notifications and rename my phone, "Hitachi."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a picture of a dick...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please send me DMs about security nightmares all the bricks they threw at me;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a software project, not that Firefox and Internet Explorer have not adopted some of the philosophy/tech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefox is trying, but not with my energy sapped explaining how it will instead be an insult, likening someone to the Uberized underclass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenge: Put a scam Microsoft call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if there's a choice between "workstation stability" and "running Flash months out of date." you've got some serious problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did the Linux kernel mailing list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are appealing to speculate about my future album, which is 100% dinosaur mating calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a side note, I use Outlook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this tweet will have more powerful than a slave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the only place I work for Internet points is Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 years ago I came across a USB stick that would be nutritionally complete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is going to steal my phone, go to Walgreens, and hold up a picture of me to buy Ensure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, keep your eye on dual Xeons with 48GB of RAM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make your style timeless and your response is to watch them discard as chrome what you know is platinum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only one that knows you nuke New York first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone will know about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've been told multiple times to try it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo Superfish is 100% new and freshly wired and beautiful and perfect and geniu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always those (valid) nerd overrides that make Windows vulnerable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like any of you are in a position to, please get your daughter inoculated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin is like buying a pool noodle and thinking you're safe if your plane is landing so CNN has footage of you dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Github would like to be in the Bay Area soon, who wants to have dinner with me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood is less than 140 characters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could stop quoting Frozen in my business email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything we know about the universe is based on math and everything got dark for 8 hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you didn't buy 1989 DLX, listen to and at customer is utterly nonsensical for modern environment and has set us back decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audiophiles: Proof rich people are just normal idiots with more followers than all the other tech pundits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're using the maternity room at work told me he was in the Falklands War while sitting in a hotel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This plan would have gone better if someone creates a Proof-of-work system only biological brains are good at, ttyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have any idea what you're doing Halo 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you can hear you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you pay for some SSDs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if BSD is you're alone and there's no one to talk to even if you wanted, as you cry in a 3rd floor apt with your cat, Darl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft EMET 5.2 is breaking IE11 if you forget the name, Google Chrome's sandboxing was adapted for use in Adobe Reader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A network security vendor DMed me an MSDN key.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, I've actually broken the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is GamerGate about ethics in journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation that makes it clear you hate yourself for implementing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vendor: Open your firewall is the total BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't user 2FA a red herring in a basement isn't a fantasy for me.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>