<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/lTE5tnBIXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/NcNN81W56y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/KsOE8eJBHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/iLYMSSLk1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/YEV6bm1843]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SELagsr6hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/nPAvePSCU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/8kmRI6jzYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/ojRX64wDne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/upgs58LBTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/U6iJ2Jr1cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/a4eeDzhSDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/DINRChpVfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/JnvWK6Tm6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/jlTQdQxxif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/BUFHnIqzH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else. - James M. Barrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/VdST04lbK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/l4p4PHwhyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/nL7BSfLTpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/kiWJB1koGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/czBXpQHQkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/sXhBwfIM3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/KEworhCi7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/MoPZLa6XBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/tZZOUEbW3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/IMHAZ04h8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/2Ii3DkTsR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/oPxuCwUrbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/tt335YCS1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/Ao5dzqI972]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/RiT3TX6SEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/Lk2ZT2JMQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/6xQKfZy3Yh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/ziL63TkCFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/b9r9FwKjVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/qOMaa1HCeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/NibViItZ3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird of paradise alights only upon the hand that does not grasp. - John Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/X3xcnj3Qql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/md3EP06rWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/42Pv0PZeGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/haHhc8K0tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/RyZaZFrhJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/yjPiCeC9tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/SFy7VjPcUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>