<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatbot developer: Chatbot developer Ref No.: 18-21196 Location: Dublin, Ohio Position Chatbot developer Location: Dublin, OH Duration: Contract Competencies: Digital : AngularJS, Digital : Node.js Experience (Years): 6-8 Essential Skills: Angular 4/5… https://t.co/XMzWJbgPQK https://t.co/p2qZPMQVXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump weighs in on 'Yanny' vs. 'Laurel' debate: 'It's covfefe' - Business Insider: Business Insider Trump weighs in on 'Yanny' vs. 'Laurel' debate: 'It's covfefe' Business Insider The White House released a lighthearted video of various officials… https://t.co/P9QDmcWIsr https://t.co/HslzVC8qtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCarthy to GOP: DACA vote could cost us the House - Politico: Politico McCarthy to GOP: DACA vote could cost us the House Politico House Republicans are flailing to get on the same page on immigration, as rebellious moderates inch closer toward forcing… https://t.co/tQEMbU0QWy https://t.co/FI8CH3BOuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pack of vicious dogs running wild attacks, kills woman - WSB Radio: WSB Radio Pack of vicious dogs running wild attacks, kills woman WSB Radio ARDMORE, Okla. - A vicious attack by seven small dogs has left an Oklahoma woman dead. Tracie Garcia was… https://t.co/ctARGjgyvJ https://t.co/kLRUoTS5EA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: California blast victim's family expresses shock - ABC News: ABC News The Latest: California blast victim's family expresses shock ABC News The Latest on a deadly explosion at a Southern California office building (all times local):. 5:30… https://t.co/pQZtBUP6Em https://t.co/oUvauQ3VWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just fessed up to reimbursing Michael Cohen. Still no mention of Stormy Daniels though - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Trump just fessed up to reimbursing Michael Cohen. Still no mention of Stormy Daniels though Los Angeles Times Michael… https://t.co/53R2SNB75P https://t.co/RekH7obj8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump ponders North Korean threat to cancel Singapore summit with Kim Jong Un - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Donald Trump ponders North Korean threat to cancel Singapore summit with Kim Jong Un USA TODAY WASHINGTON — The Trump administration declared… https://t.co/2h7HntP8E9 https://t.co/GQpWOPrKsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team ready to 'pressure' Mueller at probe's one-year mark - Politico: Politico Trump team ready to 'pressure' Mueller at probe's one-year mark Politico President Donald Trump's attorney has an unlikely new role model for special counsel Robert… https://t.co/rOXsH1pLII https://t.co/7acsB0NPts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT System Test Engineer: Our direct client is looking to hire a Senior IT System Test Engineer in Cleveland, OH or Colorado Springs, CO. We are looking for experienced systems test engineers/software engineers with 3+ years of C#.NET development… https://t.co/tCUIgwNLPq https://t.co/HXbvBXBwFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: DESCRIPTION: Make your move to Employer!! The Advanced Solution Group (ASG) of Employer is currently seeking a SOFTWARE ENGINEER for our Beavercreek / Dayton, OH location. We are charted by AFRL to work on open architecture research,… https://t.co/pgcy1L9IFa https://t.co/Qr1B8NkGAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 31 most important, insightful and just plain odd lines from Donald Trump Jr.'s Russia testimony - CNN: CNN The 31 most important, insightful and just plain odd lines from Donald Trump Jr.'s Russia testimony CNN (CNN) On Wednesday morning, the Senate… https://t.co/DtFIf0kNXd https://t.co/pRmoTnsZ0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: DESCRIPTION: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Employer currently has an opening for a COMPUTER SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR to support contracts on Wright-Patterson AFB in Dayton, OH. The successful candidate will work with a… https://t.co/7DmpqWrd1U https://t.co/JnDa7bauLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows teacher drowning animals in front of class - New York Post: New York Post Video shows teacher drowning animals in front of class New York Post An agriculture teacher in Florida allegedly drowned two raccoons and an opossum with help from… https://t.co/R9NZpV7t0U https://t.co/PGYFAbttI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Search Of CIA Leak Suspect Turned Up Photos Of Sex Assault On Unconscious Friend - HuffPost: HuffPost FBI Search Of CIA Leak Suspect Turned Up Photos Of Sex Assault On Unconscious Friend HuffPost WASHINGTON ― A 30-year-old former CIA employee the… https://t.co/826WT2kxar https://t.co/U6UfVffD3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Overturns Assisted Suicide Law In California - NPR: NPR Judge Overturns Assisted Suicide Law In California NPR A California law permitting physicians to prescribe life-ending drugs to terminally ill patients has been overturned by a judge who says… https://t.co/7gvaSfymiU https://t.co/nINDAV2qXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Primary elections: Buehler wins GOP nomination to challenge Oregon Gov. Kate Brown - Washington Post: Washington Post Primary elections: Buehler wins GOP nomination to challenge Oregon Gov. Kate Brown Washington Post Recent developments. ○ Nebraska… https://t.co/k4RpqMCWCJ https://t.co/tGSX3a15dL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump provides updates on first lady Melania Trump after medical procedure - CBS News: CBS News Trump provides updates on first lady Melania Trump after medical procedure CBS News Last Updated May 15, 2018 6:16 PM EDT. President Donald Trump said Tuesday… https://t.co/Ni7NXSosRO https://t.co/CChOdLh0gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intense storm passing through Beltway and District; Flash flood emergency in Frederick, Md. - Washington Post: Boston Herald Intense storm passing through Beltway and District; Flash flood emergency in Frederick, Md. Washington Post ... * Severe… https://t.co/u5Eiy7imXg https://t.co/YgRelFNGp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data analyst: Job TitleData analyst – ID:31412 Duration3 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSAS, SQL, PL/SQL LocationHilliard, OH Date Posted04/05/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for Data analyst to join their… https://t.co/UbjvTKFFAA https://t.co/nFO08JczKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penn. Teacher Is Fatally Shot in Her Mom's Driveway on Mother's Day - https://t.co/wguBczZhC3: https://t.co/wguBczZhC3 Penn. Teacher Is Fatally Shot in Her Mom's Driveway on Mother's Day https://t.co/wguBczZhC3 A teacher in Aliquippa, Pennsylvania, was… https://t.co/zd9BzBXdCh https://t.co/n6gc4dCeFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Democrat backs Haspel for CIA director after she says interrogation program should not have been started - Washington Post: Washington Post Key Democrat backs Haspel for CIA director after she says interrogation program should not have been started… https://t.co/u5oVpHxLoK https://t.co/YbPxaxSatO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top intelligence official says Chinese ZTE cellphones pose security risk to US - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Top intelligence official says Chinese ZTE cellphones pose security risk to US https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC WASHINGTON — The… https://t.co/EJrq0IiEln https://t.co/CFQVVBcSDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber will no longer force victims of sexual assault into arbitration - CNNMoney: CNNMoney Uber will no longer force victims of sexual assault into arbitration CNNMoney Uber says it is taking steps to help reduce the culture of silence around sexual… https://t.co/KB1OYgIGfo https://t.co/OvSJFLMYI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Level Software Developer: Key Responsibilities &amp; Expectations Write well designed and efficient code by using modern software development practices. Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS practices. Integrate data from… https://t.co/nA2IXDwczX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sichuan Airlines co-pilot "sucked halfway" out of cockpit, captain says - Reuters: Hindustan Times Sichuan Airlines co-pilot "sucked halfway" out of cockpit, captain says Reuters SHANGHAI (Reuters) - The co-pilot of a Sichuan Airlines flight that was… https://t.co/s7LIBCyh7R https://t.co/ZVcThgAud5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Torture occurred in this house': Parents charged after police find 10 children living amid feces, garbage - Washington Post: Washington Post 'Torture occurred in this house': Parents charged after police find 10 children living amid feces, garbage… https://t.co/5ARLy3A0yr https://t.co/Ttf6t5ZzUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/pMfuir3s4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidney Condition Puts Melania Trump in the Hospital - New York Times: New York Times Kidney Condition Puts Melania Trump in the Hospital New York Times WASHINGTON — Melania Trump underwent a medical procedure on Monday morning to treat what the White… https://t.co/2Ta3CYpCBr https://t.co/UtP70ypVY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer I: The DevOps Engineer is focused on automation and optimization of the CI/CD and release management pipeline supporting both Commercial Off The Shelf (COTS) solutions as well as custom, in-house built applications. The ideal candidate… https://t.co/KustcgOUEG https://t.co/J1que2Qx0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii volcano eruptions: "Lava chaser" records Kilauea "lava bombs" - CBS News: CBS News Hawaii volcano eruptions: "Lava chaser" records Kilauea "lava bombs" CBS News A self-described "lava chaser" documented the jaw-dropping fury of the Kilauea volcano… https://t.co/dXCYfilU45 https://t.co/FwnnztgU4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Desktop Support Analyst: Job Description Job Description As an IT Desktop Support Analyst, you will be supporting CVS Health’s Solon, OH Specialty Pharmacy by providing desktop support to include technical advice, guidance, and informal training to… https://t.co/ttjbrKWvkt https://t.co/evOu2snLE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corey Lewandowski joining Pence team, will focus on midterms and then 2020 - Fox News: Fox News Corey Lewandowski joining Pence team, will focus on midterms and then 2020 Fox News EXCLUSIVE: Corey Lewandowski, who helped Donald Trump win the Republican… https://t.co/pAwUOagurK https://t.co/gpyjifNwVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caged Tiger at Florida high school prom causes uproar - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Caged Tiger at Florida high school prom causes uproar USA TODAY A Florida high school principal said he regrets using live animals including a caged tiger as part of a… https://t.co/ereLNbDeEI https://t.co/oweqBid1eR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand Junction, Colorado Officials hunt for bear that dragged girl outside her home - CBS News: CBS News Grand Junction, Colorado Officials hunt for bear that dragged girl outside her home CBS News MESA COUNTY, Colo. – Authorities in Grand Junction have… https://t.co/gFpf4s5EGi https://t.co/X9GxQm4Jwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Angular Developer: UI Angular Developer Ref No.:18-07580 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 04/24/2018 Job Title – UI Angular Developer Job Location – Cincinnati, OH Duration- Fulltime Required Skills – – Develop… https://t.co/IvtsSDe9wz https://t.co/TrevGxKwY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Toensing: Senate should defend constitutional powers of Trump -- not Mueller - Fox News: Fox News Victoria Toensing: Senate should defend constitutional powers of Trump -- not Mueller Fox News Before the Senate debates a bill to protect Special… https://t.co/1Rd7j2JC03 https://t.co/Bji1fbCoSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Refuses to Apologize for Kelly Sadler's Joke About McCain - New York Times: New York Times White House Refuses to Apologize for Kelly Sadler's Joke About McCain New York Times Senator John McCain of Arizona at the Capitol in November. He… https://t.co/o3SpHKDuLw https://t.co/mRA1mxQ3MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FIORI: SAP FIORI Ref No.: 18-20522 Location: Dublin, Ohio SAP FIORI Consultant Dublin, OH Required Experience and skills: A minimum of 8-10 years of progressively responsible experience in a full life cycle implementation of a SAP ERP [planning,… https://t.co/KTilX2OPa1 https://t.co/WlkuaLaBFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Nuclear Manufacturing: Seeking a highly experienced Project/Program Manager to plan and manage confidential business projects in our Nuclear Pharmacy Service business. Projects consist of a combination of some or all of: contracts… https://t.co/BKkuABLEWw https://t.co/ADFx56FeqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team sends mixed signals to Europe - Politico: Politico Trump team sends mixed signals to Europe Politico National security adviser John Bolton on Sunday carefully doubled down on President Donald Trump's threat that European countries could be… https://t.co/81FH0j8u3T https://t.co/3CXz8NVqZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Ivanka and Jared join embassy party in Jerusalem, Gaza braces for violence - Washington Post: Washington Post As Ivanka and Jared join embassy party in Jerusalem, Gaza braces for violence Washington Post MEFALSIM, Israel — As Jared Kushner and Ivanka… https://t.co/oI7pwiUz4u https://t.co/9IffvImtQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pledges to help Chinese phonemaker ZTE 'get back into business' - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump pledges to help Chinese phonemaker ZTE 'get back into business' Washington Post President Trump pledged on Sunday to help Chinese telecom giant… https://t.co/dUppqklA7T https://t.co/b5fu5xU00t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team sends mixed signals to Europe - Politico: Politico Trump team sends mixed signals to Europe Politico National security adviser John Bolton on Sunday carefully doubled down on President Donald Trump's threat that European countries could be… https://t.co/Jq94ArbnxU https://t.co/7xtJj07gec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cognos IT Data Warehouse Developer: Hi, Please go thru the requirement given below and send me your matching profiles with minimum expected rate/salary, visa status, current location and availability. Please let us know if you would like to work on our… https://t.co/3CymxBhf0u https://t.co/opmkqebjKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsey O. Graham blasts White House aide's McCain remark as 'pretty disgusting thing to say' - Washington Post: Washington Post Lindsey O. Graham blasts White House aide's McCain remark as 'pretty disgusting thing to say' Washington Post Sen. Lindsey O.… https://t.co/kqcAyS0Vrq https://t.co/SmZ50bHAvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not the way I would deal with people," former Defense Secretary Gates says of Trump - CBS News: CBS News "Not the way I would deal with people," former Defense Secretary Gates says of Trump CBS News Asked about reports that Homeland Security Secretary… https://t.co/HnDIJMkD8l https://t.co/tWc6q3yMO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqis vote in first national election since toppling of ISIS, but turnout was low - Washington Post: Washington Post Iraqis vote in first national election since toppling of ISIS, but turnout was low Washington Post NAJAF, Iraq — Iraqis on Saturday… https://t.co/FJsDCNimOT https://t.co/sXRyzD9sDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 76210BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position Summary Position Summary In… https://t.co/5cBthMjwry https://t.co/ylcIPqAxGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 2 killed in 3 church explosions in Indonesia - CNN: CNN At least 2 killed in 3 church explosions in Indonesia CNN (CNN) Explosions rocked three different churches in Indonesia on Sunday morning, killing at least two people and injuring 13, Frans… https://t.co/jiUWOheyxX https://t.co/ZcgQCVwjuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Our city has been bruised': Islamic State claims responsibility for Paris stabbing that killed 1 , injured 4 - USA TODAY: USA TODAY 'Our city has been bruised': Islamic State claims responsibility for Paris stabbing that killed 1 , injured 4 USA TODAY… https://t.co/hIvCxd8B2r https://t.co/3AJL2IpyDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US jets intercept pair of Russian bombers off Alaskan coast - Washington Post: Washington Post US jets intercept pair of Russian bombers off Alaskan coast Washington Post Two Russian long-range bombers were intercepted off the coast of Alaska by a pair… https://t.co/S883emEGeK https://t.co/H65MdfLAkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer $140k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Android Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily in our… https://t.co/vbbpD3CBBT https://t.co/n4I4UhrLnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii braces for major volcano eruption, prepares for possible evacuation of 2000 - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Hawaii braces for major volcano eruption, prepares for possible evacuation of 2000 USA TODAY With scientists warning that a steam-driven volcanic… https://t.co/arv7jcMXaO https://t.co/YRjyfh0nIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump White House crossed a new threshold for political debasement this week - Washington Post: Washington Post The Trump White House crossed a new threshold for political debasement this week Washington Post The White House probably thinks it cannot… https://t.co/Xt8cpDP4pU https://t.co/DLZzjkOScj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected shooter at a Palmdale high school is a former student who recently transferred - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Suspected shooter at a Palmdale high school is a former student who recently transferred Los Angeles Times The 911 calls… https://t.co/gxQI6sjLUE https://t.co/2N5Z8kRJWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyer for 2 Schneiderman Accusers Brought Their Claims to Michael Cohen - New York Times: New York Times Lawyer for 2 Schneiderman Accusers Brought Their Claims to Michael Cohen New York Times A lawyer who says he once represented two women who claimed… https://t.co/sfWfaHW5Ej https://t.co/98aZcChtJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Russian Troll Facebook Ads Barely Targeted Swing States - HuffPost: HuffPost The Russian Troll Facebook Ads Barely Targeted Swing States HuffPost WASHINGTON ― Did Russians target the key swing states with their social media advertising push, and did… https://t.co/k8DN0Lkjsu https://t.co/QmsbUeQ2Qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T CEO Says Hiring Michael Cohen Was a "Big Mistake." But Its Merger With Time Warner Isn't in Any Worse Shape. - Fortune: Fortune AT&amp;T CEO Says Hiring Michael Cohen Was a "Big Mistake." But Its Merger With Time Warner Isn't in Any Worse Shape. Fortune… https://t.co/wKlDDbDTUa https://t.co/yddkgHk7Rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer / Cincinnati , OH Overview: We are seeking a Full Stack Developer to help develop and maintain our current business applications and web services. You will use your web development skills to develop applications and… https://t.co/P1dJ96a2c3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Engineering Test Analyst: The QE Analyst is actively working on multiple, critical testing, compliance and automation initiatives while working closely together with the software developers, project managers and other participants of a given… https://t.co/pyPPoediLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Plan On Prescription Drug Prices Looks Nothing Like What He Promised - HuffPost: HuffPost Trump's Plan On Prescription Drug Prices Looks Nothing Like What He Promised HuffPost Candidate Donald Trump promised Americans a war on the pharmaceutical… https://t.co/5YtBKeMu3K https://t.co/5hcnON65bH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst | Master Data (metadata mining): Data Analyst | Master Data (metadata mining) Columbus, OH 04-11-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your… https://t.co/ow7E6CwuYQ https://t.co/PzrCe9poqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina officer chokes, slams man at a Waffle House after prom - CNN: CNN North Carolina officer chokes, slams man at a Waffle House after prom CNN (CNN) Anthony Wall's night started at the prom with his sister, followed by a stop at a Waffle… https://t.co/P868jCQnao https://t.co/iZCIJ6LKmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Data Scientist, AES: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and… https://t.co/hOtERwX6UK https://t.co/oXQUTDULPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer (IntelliCorp- Beachwood,OH): Job ID: ********-10280-JSV Company Name: Intellicorp Records Description: Summary We are seeking a highly skilled Business Intelligence Developer to join us in our work here at IntelliCorp. If… https://t.co/gg76xWW8l5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Dead in Australia's Worst Mass Shooting Since 1996 - New York Times: New York Times 7 Dead in Australia's Worst Mass Shooting Since 1996 New York Times PERTH, Australia — Seven people, including four children, were found dead from gunshot wounds at a… https://t.co/AfouKiiLTv https://t.co/61WvPSQy94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Android Developer: Senior Android Developer – Halcyon – Cleveland, OH | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Senior… https://t.co/wcgLqor2eG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump unloads on Homeland Security secretary in lengthy immigration tirade - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump unloads on Homeland Security secretary in lengthy immigration tirade Washington Post President Trump berated Homeland Security Secretary… https://t.co/XfvkFl7aa0 https://t.co/SB915yTBQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Software Engineer: Are you an ops person with a penchant for software development? Then we might be looking for you. If you have experience with Hadoop, public or private cloud, we might be in love. This position is with one of our clients in… https://t.co/0FnWPUfdc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven found dead at Australia rural property: police - Yahoo News: Seven found dead at Australia rural property: police Yahoo News Four children and three adults were found dead Friday at a rural property near the Margaret River wine region in western… https://t.co/S9ultMdhwX https://t.co/i3Y9f46y3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran launched an attack on Israel — and it got badly beaten and internationally abandoned - Business Insider: Business Insider Iran launched an attack on Israel — and it got badly beaten and internationally abandoned Business Insider Iran launched a… https://t.co/1eM08uIBiX https://t.co/98Uv1xalpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Grc consultant: Who are we looking for? A mid-senior level SAP consultant to manage a critical activities in project. The Individual should be passionate about technology, experienced in managing cutting edge technology applications.… https://t.co/1LFAfVGj4f https://t.co/92NvzixqxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsey Baum case: Remains found by hunters in 2017 ID'd as long-missing Wash. girl - CBS News: CBS News Lindsey Baum case: Remains found by hunters in 2017 ID'd as long-missing Wash. girl CBS News GRAYS HARBOR COUNTY, Wash. -- Remains found in September… https://t.co/lFIQ48ELjN https://t.co/vjYX4hUeC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: The Data Scientist reports to the SVP, Retail Analytics Utilize a blended approach of statistical, computer science and business knowledge to develop new approaches to lead analysis and interpretation of large data sets to develop data… https://t.co/5XUx1kwslU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump Came to Enforce a Practice of Separating Migrant Families - New York Times: New York Times How Trump Came to Enforce a Practice of Separating Migrant Families New York Times WASHINGTON — Almost immediately after President Trump took office, his… https://t.co/ErqK8t3DWl https://t.co/ym1qaV8HIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dba: db2/dba Ref No.: 18-23225 Location: columbs, Ohio – 8+ years experience with excellent verbal and written communication skills. – 4+ years of lead experience in handling teams – 8+ years of experience in supporting DB2 server ,concerning database,… https://t.co/EuDYRflPvO https://t.co/iHl5AfIjxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dangerous mass of hot, humid air triggers heat advisories in Midwest, targets East - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Dangerous mass of hot, humid air triggers heat advisories in Midwest, targets East USA TODAY Chicago set for heat wave as forecasts call for three… https://t.co/jYhi8GSVwR https://t.co/AACx11KKCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dangerous mass of hot, humid air triggers heat advisories in Midwest, targets East - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Dangerous mass of hot, humid air triggers heat advisories in Midwest, targets East USA TODAY Chicago set for heat wave as forecasts call for three… https://t.co/viaAFBM78W https://t.co/Ex9NT6dJdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Former Walmart That Is Now a Shelter for Almost 1500 Migrant Children - New York Times: New York Times Inside the Former Walmart That Is Now a Shelter for Almost 1500 Migrant Children New York Times BROWNSVILLE, Tex. — In the loading docks,… https://t.co/4GXhvzQz2f https://t.co/ABLJbr3LIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA developer: JAVA developer (Edge API &amp; Azure API) Ref No.: 18-20737 Location: Amelia, Ohio Position: JAVA developer (Edge API &amp; Azure API) Location: Amelia, OH Duration : Full-time/Perm Job Description: – 5-7 years of hands on work experience using… https://t.co/UtGbGlufzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort ordered to jail after witness-tampering charges - Washington Post: Washington Post Paul Manafort ordered to jail after witness-tampering charges Washington Post A federal judge ordered Paul Manafort to jail Friday over charges he tampered… https://t.co/uufNH0xbWS https://t.co/A7yPa0KBTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Credit Card: Developer Credit Card (Acquirer) + Mainframe / COBOL and CICS Columbus, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsDB2,COBOL,VSAM,CICSTax TermsC2COverview Developer Credit Card (Acquirer) +… https://t.co/CKAcrzR0Yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats pounce on Trump trade war in midterms - Politico: Politico Democrats pounce on Trump trade war in midterms Politico President Donald Trump's “America first” trade crackdown increasingly has the look of a first-rate campaign issue for Democrats… https://t.co/O3ZAtYpcsf https://t.co/xedRzWB3GX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump cites as a negotiating tool his policy of separating immigrant children from their parents - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump cites as a negotiating tool his policy of separating immigrant children from their parents Washington Post President… https://t.co/hn9PN5pNpC https://t.co/UZzyCHJNBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York handed President Trump a big fat lawsuit for his birthday - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times New York handed President Trump a big fat lawsuit for his birthday Los Angeles Times President Trump blows out a birthday candle earlier this week… https://t.co/GY11lfcIpX https://t.co/r0OevAPo5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Asks Judge to Muzzle Michael Avenatti, Stormy Daniels's Lawyer - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Michael Cohen Asks Judge to Muzzle Michael Avenatti, Stormy Daniels's Lawyer Wall Street Journal LOS ANGELES— Donald Trump's former… https://t.co/xD4dNUr06z https://t.co/iZ5yQ7f1U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API Developer: For Siemens Java API Developer job – Information Technology – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers Job Java API… https://t.co/UE95WFjTBK https://t.co/RBoClRTALz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHOTOS: Two adults, two children shot in Westminster - The Denver Post: The Denver Post PHOTOS: Two adults, two children shot in Westminster The Denver Post Some people were locked inside nearby businesses for hours as they waited for an all-clear sign… https://t.co/g8tjThTIiF https://t.co/FNy91Wa221]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan claims US drone strike kills Pakistan Taliban leader - CNN: CNN Afghanistan claims US drone strike kills Pakistan Taliban leader CNN (CNN) A US drone strike in Afghanistan's northeastern Kunar province has killed a leading militant, who was… https://t.co/RaT1CgYb1l https://t.co/kTaFRSuORo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester | design and create automated test conditions and scripts to address business and technical use cases: Software Tester | design and create automated test conditions and scripts to address business and technical use cases – CareWorks… https://t.co/m937DSdDYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In defense of separating immigrant families, Sessions cites same Bible passage used to defend slavery - Washington Post: Washington Post In defense of separating immigrant families, Sessions cites same Bible passage used to defend slavery Washington Post… https://t.co/72mUSjxxUO https://t.co/0UHCgZbo99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/l7DAF8O1pT https://t.co/PtQnSu5PVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two adults, two children shot in Westminster; suspect in custody - The Denver Post: The Denver Post Two adults, two children shot in Westminster; suspect in custody The Denver Post Two adults and two children were shot Thursday afternoon in a parking lot… https://t.co/ScQn5OQzoz https://t.co/kWVoAEF8VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York files civil suit against President Trump, alleging his charity engaged in 'illegal conduct' - Washington Post: Washington Post New York files civil suit against President Trump, alleging his charity engaged in 'illegal conduct' Washington Post… https://t.co/EwjxRXAKnD https://t.co/5M5MRqtUPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen makes Trump's birthday great by donating to ACLU in installments of $72K - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Chrissy Teigen makes Trump's birthday great by donating to ACLU in installments of $72K USA TODAY "I've come to wish you an unhappy birthday."… https://t.co/e3LnVFCLDi https://t.co/sfpuRhhlH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NX Software Engineer: Division: Digital Factory Business Unit: Product Lifecycle Management-PLM Requisition Number: ****** Primary Location: United States-Ohio-Milford Assignment Category: Full-time regular Experience Level: Entry level Education… https://t.co/xlqnJ57970 https://t.co/6ORzcQCtxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspector general blasts Comey and also says others at FBI showed 'willingness to take official action' to hurt Trump - Washington Post: Washington Post Inspector general blasts Comey and also says others at FBI showed 'willingness to take official… https://t.co/wOJiK24Yy8 https://t.co/osMoUIETj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: * Perform analysis of all data into, out of and within client in support of Data Warehousing efforts * Identify and quantify data issues within the organization and assist in the development plans to resolve data issues * Support regular… https://t.co/j95aSPlao1 https://t.co/2aEBpfAHJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court says Minnesota ban on political apparel in polling places too broad - Washington Post: Washington Post Supreme Court says Minnesota ban on political apparel in polling places too broad Washington Post The Supreme Court on Thursday struck… https://t.co/B9E8TtVXpY https://t.co/FUDX6JshO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Shelter Greets Migrant Kids With Big Trump Mural - Daily Beast: Daily Beast Texas Shelter Greets Migrant Kids With Big Trump Mural Daily Beast A Texas shelter housing child immigrants who have been separated from their parents at the U.S.-Mexico… https://t.co/RTtijjgDaC https://t.co/vR71OUy0g8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>