<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamptonCtHalf Go Josie! Go Josie! good luck tomorrow Karen x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sesame Street puppeteer squares up to his ego in Big Birdman spoof http://t.co/COBnXQZAaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FreeseChristian: This is what the "internet of things" endgame looks like http://t.co/DllqzZOMBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @suttonnick: With 638 seats in
How many votes on average to elect an MP?
SNP 25,972
CON34,242
LAB40,347
LD290,520
GRN1,127,952
UKIP3,805…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking to Farage's loss at Heathrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FactCheck: How would proportional representation change the #GE2015
balance of power, asks @FactCheck: http://t.co/d7QFEKqVzz http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidwearing: What's to come:
&gt; Abolition of maternity pay
&gt; No incapacity benefit for under-25s 
&gt; Increase in bedroom tax 
http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeMonbiot: South of the border, a once-progressive party tacks and triangulates, offering a dilute version of business as usual. Th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up to see if Father Christmas came only to find your house done got robbed #ukelection2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when you fact-check claims in the General Election manifestos? | Nesta https://t.co/YyT30hJh0h via @nesta_uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still disappointed that Labour let themselves be bullied by small c conservative press into ruling out ANY collab w SNP #marrshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VSOUK: Congrats Kate &amp; William on the birth of your baby girl. Every safe birth is worth celebrating! #RoyalBaby #IDM2015 http://t.co/f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the front page of The Sun. Think my brain did a little sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quendergeer spot on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @quendergeer: danny alexander looks like a tomato ketchup crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two #jobs going with the ETA - a lovely little ethical company based in Weybridge, Surrey (biased, me?) https://t.co/sXTmpks3ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimwaterson: @DJSkelton If the baby only popped out on 7 May there'd be a full blown constitutional crisis due to the lack of satellite…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darranjmartin: @lucyreckons Could we get a re-tweet please for #DineWithEmerge and vote for your star dish! #LiveBelowTheLine https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, THIS is my worst way to die &gt; Man cooked alive with 12,000 pounds of tuna http://t.co/z8uORaufY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On June 17 I'll join @TheCCoalition to Speak Up #fortheloveof all we could lose to climate change. Join me? http://t.co/JmJ6e1Pdqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am seriously considering buying a teasmade - do they still make those? Later on, I'll be researching retirement homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicholasPegg: "I haven't got time to hang out with Russell Brand," sniffs busy Prime Minister David Cameron. http://t.co/YIV5ItKXJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nepal Earthquake: Sending Shockwaves Through My Family http://t.co/4XcB0m5G23 via @HuffPostUKPol @VSO_Intl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce Forsyth makes an emotional plea for assisted dying after his wife's tragic death http://t.co/Nuo8znXXhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Need You Now” by @Hot_Chip is my new jam. Listen: http://t.co/nCwLtRcpL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Novembervivi: MY LITTLE BROTHER HIT ME OVER THE HEAD WITH A STOOL WHEN WE WERE SMALL AND NOW HE'S A HEADTEACHER WILL YOU THINK OF THE C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank heck we're not judged on childhoods RT @AngusMacNeilSNP: UK media desperation against SNP #DollGate http://t.co/GFBURy9mb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fourth emergency service is…your local bike courier https://t.co/iJVxvcJbfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadio2 *whose :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brainmage: I am a HUMAN TEENAGE GIRL. I enjoy the FACE AND NECK of the NOT REPTILLIAN David Cameron. I ACHE FOR HIS TOUCH #cameronettes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffPostUKPol So painfully lame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Heidi37070845: Literally the best thing I've ever made #milibae #milifandom http://t.co/NRiHVskovo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Independent: Here's your pre-emptive 'royal baby is born' story http://t.co/xj5XCDES0t http://t.co/d793fcZGse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK political party that voters would feel most proud to vote for http://t.co/aB6EYXcj5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cyclingalong: Stick a toaster in the bath. What happens next will shock you. 230V will blow your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @garwboy: A guaranteed 100% effective guide for avoiding criticism on Twitter http://t.co/KIzyAVQj2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adored @VariousGuises at After The Goldrush last night. Love! https://t.co/hWPyMvJZAH @iamdanduke was pretty OK too I guess :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealBobMortimer: If I had 11,000 pounds I would buy a nearly new Ford Focus and anything left over I would put towards repairing my mam…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Disney @thefoxisblack @AmyLouiseHanna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was germ of #milifandom Right-On Student Activist Crush Miliband? Remember http://t.co/blfKXGbS74?  https://t.co/wH6J0MtC1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saucy monks in love! ...remaining 95% of 'Sex and the Church' more depressing http://t.co/B6kpaTNPRw http://t.co/6Tgn0hXC3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious! &gt; Britain’s criminally stupid attitudes to race and immigration beyond parody | Frankie Boyle http://t.co/Gn3YiRoivP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jasongorman: One person told that Wonga joke early this morning. Thanks to massive compound interest, that joke has now been told by 1.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Doncaster Rovers admit they had one of the most boring games ever http://t.co/pZ63kE3TBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartless&gt; "@chris_coltrane Reasons people's benefits sanctioned &amp; turned to foodbanks. http://t.co/hM8nljmqbT https://t.co/YYMrF3jf2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BJTC_UK: Interesting piece on how social media is changing journalism ethics by @Ashoka http://t.co/ff9WFVHGHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE the new #shedthemonster cycling campaign by @peopleforbikes https://t.co/ScHfLX1rRq. Pure fun. Cc @ETATheTwig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jonathan_Rowson: #BBCDebate 6. The repeated and wilful conflation of renewing trident with 'protecting the country' needs to be called …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JudithFlanders: @zoesqwilliams Have you noticed that the word for spending on roads is 'investment', and for public transport it's 'sub…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Poor internet for poor people" @qzindia asks: is Facebook engaged in economic racism w its Zero service? http://t.co/kbLc0xE30j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched a snippet of #BBCDebate. Dimbleby wearing a tie in UKIP colours?! Guess not many non-partisan colours left...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Extinction_OPS: Victory: Chile becomes first nation to protect all seamounts from bottom trawling http://t.co/r4Gz7GjJwe http://t.co/Y1…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astonishingly frank 1960s oil company advertisement (via @fp2p) #copywriting http://t.co/qPfWjxh19I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garwboy Wrong colour, go red. Or hot cider brandy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched trailer for @uncertainfilm #documentary. V excited to see this! https://t.co/pnuZ2Pxsn1 #tribeca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God saw the pun that He had made, and He saw that it was good. http://t.co/tx0y4Q9UpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School disco over the road. Flashback to horror and hormones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring back Fun House! http://t.co/IUerp50Q0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you tackle poverty through hairdressing? Insightful blog by @VSO_Intl volunteers Mark &amp; Mary https://t.co/4pA4J0q7as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YanniKouts: Ι've been tweeting these past few days on the generational divide in the #Greferendum.
Younger voters: 67% No
Elder: 37% No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @docky: Women just don't understand the rules of professional sports. http://t.co/oC5d6aQphO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the smartest short films I've ever seen: https://t.co/upaAk8PBPM *tips hat at @BlueSeatStudios*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Global_Witness: Check out our latest undercover sting, which puts #Australia at the heart of regional money laundering. VIDEO http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally irresponsible of @MailOnline  to show photos of ISIS torture and sadism on homepage. Bolstering cowardly propaganda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bimadew: one of these goats is not like the others. she is actually the GOAT. http://t.co/t4DV35NfAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @suicideresearch: Great to see Irish Prime Minister directly involved in launch of Irish Suicide Prevention Strategy  https://t.co/4AXgK…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseyTan @AmyLouiseHanna @BlandAlice @BrownKnows1 @JimGooch @minneyju @JamesOliverWest Lovebox prize draw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HTCLoveLineUp @AmyLouiseHanna  @RoseyTan  @BlandAlice  @BrownKnows1 @JimGooch @minneyju @JamesOliverWest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just pledged my support for #AssistedDying. Will you? | #mydeathmychoice https://t.co/hgVdRk1HPh via @dignityindying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF govts want to increase pace of growth, concentrate on helping the poorest 20% of citizens, says IMF http://t.co/OI23Nfi6vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robertlenne: If you donate blood in Sweden the county council will text you when your blood is used. http://t.co/4Ycf5O6m3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fabianmohr: What @nytimes journalists see this week when using a desktop browser. http://t.co/H1DgzmAI3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ollywainwright: Favourite story of the week: the Crystal Maze to return as an immersive public attraction http://t.co/nHhgl1J0lI http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Guardian it hurts: "Scythe like Poldark" "Advantages for yr lawn" "A basic set will cost around £100" http://t.co/0So8QHTBS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely letterpress and printy bits from Pop Press at #Manmade fair! http://t.co/UV1oV0oXgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reptile Dysfunction" is just the best headline ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: Vanuatu to sue major carbon polluters for climate damage https://t.co/NV51MGz1XK via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesco trials ‘FareShare FoodCloud’ app to redistribute leftover food to charity http://t.co/UbsTLHEkq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like something out of a dystopian sci-fi with bet-along news. https://t.co/ZzAi641bJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC One of the Family - v affecting. If I ever grow up/earn money, I'd like to try and foster http://t.co/C20wLxtf2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonsnowC4: HSBC TO BIG TO JAIL? See my Snowblog as HSBC's boss prepares to sack 25,000 of his workers: http://t.co/LZZpPe0U7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphic design friends -&gt; amazing (and rare) volunteer #job opportunity in Papua New Guinea w @VSO_Intl http://t.co/kV5wGiGB8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap textiles come at a high price - Rana Plaza &amp; @vso_intl projects offering humane alternatives via @rubywright99 @HuffPostUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politicshome: Cameron 'instructed Cabinet not to pledge to donate pay rises to charity’ http://t.co/6zRi478yza http://t.co/xkYmjIq7Fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonsnowC4: How about a massive re-Tweet between now and midnight demanding:
http://t.co/gH7BENB7DH http://t.co/MwHoPQtAHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CertifiablyMod it was super great thanks!     Amazing people food weather and nature! How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft turns to gamification to tackle water crisis: http://t.co/Oa40emBJtP via @edie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get left home alone one night and I am downloading Sims 2. Lord have mercy on my soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you need to earn to live in these London boroughs? http://t.co/wKqWFIMKOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant article about how Germany is benefitting from migrants. Refugee-phobic UK media makes me sick http://t.co/aDUXDlDvip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jodikantor: Inside Amazon: Bezos' quiet experiment in pushing employees as far as they can go. Our story: http://t.co/056XdY91l3 http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregnant housemate cannot lick the bowl. Aside from discomfort, vomiting &amp; prolapse threat, is this worst thing abt expecting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Corbyn4Leader: Important restatement of Jeremy Corbyn's position regarding personal abuse. It's a credo for our campaign #respect http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe HMRC helpline just tried to bully me into paying off an unexpected tax bill by getting out a credit card!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm inexplicably really, really in the mood to ride a horse. But explicably broke. How can I ride a horse for free in London?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rights_info: How cool is this? Graphics showing what human rights do for children, free speech, equality... http://t.co/0W1Yl687Oo http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC remains unafraid of asking the big questions: Who, What, Why: Is it wrong to exercise in a graveyard? http://t.co/8cLe3nt0DA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry what?! Weird copywriting, plus tips most certainly not neccessary DM I can assure you. http://t.co/O3qonDJ9WA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That tech to "block" a person from Black Mirror would be great to use against Tony Blair right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jackieschneider: The fact that @BBCr4today says "labour election not going smoothly" makes me suspect their impartiality]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>