<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@glamourgirlca @MarkShapiro People talking playoffs..let's finally get to .500 and stay there first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: Surveillance video captures the moment an ground crew worker at a Florida airport was struck by lightning https://t.co/2SxErg8fZE因]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 How the hell did isn't get autocorrected to insight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Being put on waivers insight a sign of disrespect to a player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @JaysFromCouch @DocReihl @JasonAtTheGame @Panikkar37 Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @JaysFromCouch @DocReihl @JasonAtTheGame @Panikkar37 Solid episode.  Recently started reading Shaun's work.  Love what they are doing over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ari_shapiro: Jays Journal Podcast - "A Glimmer of Hope." Link: https://t.co/93amnWOWm7. @JaysFromCouch, @DocReihl, @JasonAtTheGame, @Pa因]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kskroob @aigkenham An Old book that basically plagiarized countless religious/cultural stories before it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aigkenham  https://t.co/GvNwslwEhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aigkenham Lmao at Ham talking about others wasting millions of $]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucasCasaletto @Jsumadchat @MStrooo6 Only if you've got small man syndrome.  You think Scherzer or Kershaw cares if someone is pissed after striking out.  They'd laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redditsportsbot Buck is right.  Stroman can show emotion it's just how he is expressing it is in question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rozodru @ari_shapiro Original coffee blend from a few years back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rozodru @ari_shapiro Didn't McDonalds pay for the Tim Horton's coffee blend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Well they said they are looking to stay competitive next season despite the same donut and timbit selections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Goins is a bench player thrust into a starting position because of injuries.  Get over it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonAtTheGame @JaysJournal Got the talent.  Just needs to put it together between the ears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @ColeShelton91 @big_nate5 At the very least I could see him being a big arm out of the pen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeShelton91 @ari_shapiro @big_nate5 Big kid who can throw heat when needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@titaniumtori @BarryDavis_ That's the funny thing about baseball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Trying harder never works in baseball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Chirping Stromen needs to tone it down as he's been in the league a minute,hasn't accomplished anything yet and his team sits in last place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Hopefully AAA when Alford is called up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAiden @JaysFromCouch So just about everyone who comments on sportsnet Facebook articles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAiden @JaysFromCouch Only fans that have no clue will be disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAiden @JaysFromCouch You can't be serious with that expectation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I declined to vote lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @LeafsJaysFan Sorry I meant to say second wild card race.  Those teams that sit 4-6 games back for the better part of the season..see Jays this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @LeafsJaysFan Doesn't take much because the second wildcard is designed to give false hope to fans for a long stretch of the season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch I wonder what percentage of those fan think Zaun should be his replacement?.. smh indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertGibsonIII Why do I need a baseball jersey to feel proud to be Canadian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch Bland due to the poor performances of our pending free agents...but if they had performed maybe we wouldn't be sellers..hmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch I think most of the heavily lifting comes next month and at the winter meetings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SInow You can see Christie's abs and back are ready to explode under the pressure in this picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Drafting and acquiring prospects should focus up the middle (c, p, SS &amp; cf)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro All 3 will happen..just not sure how long they'll stay competitive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baseball_Jenn I don't understand the mound visit in 0-2.  Especially after striking out the last batter.  Broke up his groove.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Unconditional love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT Who allows a pregnancy that late to be aborted if the baby is healthy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Yeah, signature food for all ballparks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MannyTV_ For 2018..also could bring back better value next deadline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesZenon @ari_shapiro If Smith's defence drastically improves, let's do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro #cluboption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Ok, thanks.  Honestly it's not surprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Are these increases legit?  I'm trying to find other postings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HughCook_ca Well that means eating 60% of Tulo's remaining contract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Love the optimism after sweeping one of the worst teams in baseball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Glad I picked him up in my pool.  3 HR in 2 games :0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @timandsid: Umpire Will Little's Wikipedia bio has been updated... (H/T @MarcusRozsa) https://t.co/zT7nAgJiWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Umps aren't available to the media after the game, correct?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolewiii Did they just hit 6 home runs in the 4th inning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro In both ABs he missed balls right down the middle after the "bad" calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Worshiping either is a bad idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal Toronto is on everyone's no list lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewStoeten: ICYMI: Eight current Blue Jays who combined for 25 WAR last year have produced just 4 WAR so far in 2017. Fun! https://t因]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Needs to throw some water coolers like in the movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SatbirSingh_ @BrianSwane Late 2015 was a historic run to a division, but that kind of ball doesn't happen very often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SatbirSingh_ @BrianSwane A lot of things need to click for this team to go on that kind of run..not to mention 6-7 teams ahead of them need to collapse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SatbirSingh_ It's the number of teams we need to stay pace with concerns me more then games back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSScottWhite Kershaw can retire tomorrow and be in the HOF imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysJournal @Jasons_JaysHub Clickbait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He probably doesn't know what he's voting on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioVendetta radio show is 1/3rd better this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro It's a shame his season is wasted in last place.  Here's hoping for next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baseball_Jenn I remember reading somewhere most of the tickets are sold before the season.  To get a real sense is tickets resold on the secondary market]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baseball_Jenn It means most of these tickets were sold before April]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jays_troll @Wilnerness590 I agree.  Lots of needs and not enough options to make it happen.I don't see how that makes a contender in a tough AL east and wildcard race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fleming_clan @eephusasher Hmm thought I read it was a substantial renovation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Notatrainer @SNETCampbell What?  So the team AA constructed in 2015 that took them to back 2 back ALCS and scored a gazillion runs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaticLineSal @BarryDavis_ So, what would his logic be?  Have you ever thought about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Shake it up.  Gibby put out 70-80 different lineups already this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eephusasher The current proposed renovation for the dome is sitting at 500+ mil and that doesn't include grass.  How much would grass cost? Yikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 LF, RF, backup catcher, bullpen, bench depth, AAA depth, 4th &amp; 5th spot in the rotation.. and that's hoping Travis is healthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGarfoose Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Take 50% off the price]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks Moving Osuna and Donaldson make the most sense.  Replenish farm, get MLB prospects and can fill both positions in free agency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks Jays need bench depth, AAA depth as well as roster spots at the MLB level. Contending is a fantasy #IntendToContend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks Jays need to over spend in free agency if they don't plan on trading one of their assets #IntendToContend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolewiii @JaysFromCouch Epically botched 7th innings don't help either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolewiii @JaysFromCouch Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolewiii @JaysFromCouch Lots of fans want the problems fixed but there are important factors at play that have closed the Jays options]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @rolewiii Sorry don't mean to spam,  what number of players and positions actually constitutes a "core" to build around?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @rolewiii (2). If the answer is trades,  then who is exactly can the Jays trade to accomplish this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @rolewiii We often hear the Jays need to get younger and more athletic.  How are the Jays able to do this minus the draft and international signings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Every5thDay Depth move for the minors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch Time well spent.  Our second is still young enough to have naps on me.  Cherish these moments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noles506 @bnicholsonsmith Bandwagon fans first taste of baseball was late 2015z. Historic offence and MVP caliber baseball..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonsmith They aren't as bad as those numbers suggest, I feel they are middle of the pack...that said.. changes need to be made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal @JRSox305 I could only think of 4 teams able to take on that contract..2 in the AL east]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonHeyman: kyrie irving said the earth was flat &amp; we wondered about him. then he wanted to leave lebron &amp; join the knicks so now we kno因]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BluejaysAlways Was there any deals with the twins in the last hour or two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro It's only bleak for those who live and die with every game.  Long terms views people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg How hurt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heathcummingssr listen to podcast religiously... just wanted to say stage safe over the next 3-4 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZAN_4PM Patriots D made the Chiefs look better then they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg Amendola hurt..in other news, water is wet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg I've got KC DST but thinking of starting Bills against the Jets week 1.  Thoughts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Travis.  When he's healthy he carries the team...also that kinda says a lot about the current club tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg Filler episode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiltonHydro power out for 741 Woodward.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>