<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dalymount is in some state in fairness #giles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ftztipp It'll be a very small percentage of women who need this service, unfortunately there'll be women and girls who'll need this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ftztipp Look dude, this is about choice it's not about 'killing' babies. It's about that service been there for a woman who needs it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ftztipp what if the girl was a 12 yo and she got raped do you think she should carry a child that was conceived without her consent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ftztipp No you don't if it's your child then you can talk to her and figure out what is best for everyone apart from that no you dont]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ftztipp But I'm right, as a man I shouldn't be allowed dictate what a woman does with her body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Footage from today's Rally for Life #RallyForLife https://t.co/gMczjRLkiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only people who should have a say on abortion is women of childbearing age.  #RallyForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJOE_UK Yeah https://t.co/BnIk7zhDxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graeme waiting to meet Daniela in Swindon on their 2nd date #FirstDates https://t.co/Ma98K5pJhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blunders1985  https://t.co/3xZyU1tOfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't Nobody better looking than Chaka on #FirstDates tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly is just a hipster non deadly version of Begbie from Trainspotting #FirstDates https://t.co/IjHbNkCScE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white middle class Wu Tang Clan? Fuck off Deadly  #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's name Deadly in Ireland means 'good' my brain is fucking wrecked #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esme is so far out of my league if we were football teams we'd play each other once every 20 years in the FA Cup #pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your team loses 5-0 but you're a full on psycho. #MCILIV https://t.co/j5GKs00jkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sad to think there's still ignorant fucks like Combo roaming the streets spreading their bullshit #ThisIsEngland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Milky/Combo bit in  #ThisIsEngland is so fucking hard to watch but kudos to Stephen Graham a seriously good actor to pull that off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That girl drew that painting with her mouth, this is the best I can manage with my hands. Good on her #LateLateShow https://t.co/eGDagEn8Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can always get this lad to ask can we be team number 33 it might just work.  #COYBIG https://t.co/CMO5ZDFqdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitrovic's score for that dive #IRESRB #COYBIG https://t.co/CARL00vmRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a man woman or child in this country, Marty Morrissey doesn't know anything about. He knows the refs route at work #GalvWat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Joey Barton getting through #XFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Martin 3 points are hard to get when you send a side to play absolutely atrocious football. #GEOIRE #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Keane waiting in the dressing room for the team so he can kick some heads in #COYBIG #GEOIRL https://t.co/R3R11gY3In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland will start playing ball in the 80th minute and get the winner, just like they do every fucking game  #GEOIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunphy when he hears Hoolahan is coming on at half time #GEOIRL #COYBIG https://t.co/rX1ToqlpxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Eva after getting home from the  #LateLateShow https://t.co/lqgsByboKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananthmdna1 The one which only sells organic gluten free vegan food. So Dr Ava is satisfied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine going for a drink with her, do ya fancy a taco chips from abrakebabra? No that sounds like fun we'll have some lettuce #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be honest I can't wait till this lad is on the #LateLateShow to tell us all how much of a shithole Ireland has become https://t.co/gxldSMoyB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NialOFarrell I'm sure he's a very good coach, anyway man it's a joke probably a crap joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next week Ryan interviews Bernie from Crumlin Credit Union who once gave Conor's mother a loan #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things turn nasty when the sheep gets his own back on Tubridy for making a show of him #LateLateShow https://t.co/fxcSxIOJ9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RTE canteen and Car Park till next May now that the #LateLateShow is back https://t.co/YLkVupYdrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She said Paris is a country that ends in two consonants. #pointless https://t.co/MdACPOUnJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamienolan3 Ok https://t.co/KTIqiV3BP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huddersfield v Newcastle last week West Brom v Stoke this week, it's just so painful to watch #WBASTK https://t.co/qTdYfaCi3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United Fans watching the Champions League draw #MUFC #UCLdraw https://t.co/mcLDu5Yqyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next up the Hunzo Rose her interests are cans of Kopparberg, posting pics of her girlos and her little angles on Facebook #Roseoftralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Western Canada Rose is dating Beck, what a loser #Roseoftralee https://t.co/PjILcOMjiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Roseoftralee nowadays is basically just a middle aged man talking to girls who are too young for him shifting wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland Why is the broadband in Naas still not fixed? And why have you not replied to the tweet I sent last night? Very poor service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the Rose who studied at the University of Life and attended the School of Hard Knocks works as a full time mad bastard #Roseoftralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like every programme on RTÉ no one is watching the  #Roseoftralee just ripping the piss out of it on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hong Kong rose has educated good auld Daithi on a few things #Roseoftralee https://t.co/2ibrjkU2Vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally think the Chinese immigrants are the best, a great bunch of lads #Roseoftralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Melbourne Rose a lot of people have had 'Escort experiences' but they choose to keep that stuff a secret #Roseoftralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see your man Derek Ryan keeping the 2004 classic hairdo of bleached blonde spiky hair alive #Roseoftralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@139Wolfhound @SkyHelpIreland I've turned it off it's that bad, Sky don't seem to care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requirements to go on the  #RoseOfTralee

1. Be a teacher
2. Be involved in GAA
3. Want road frontage
4. Be a lovely girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's basically every song on a DJ's 21st set #RoseOfTralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland what's the craic with broadband speeds gone so slow in Naas, I have to turn my wifi off to get anything done on my phone. https://t.co/WteLL9RNmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits This came on the other day on some 00s mix I have on Apple Music my first urge was to skip but then I thought nah fuck it, it's a banger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to admire Donaghy and Moran's dedication to wearing their socks knee high in the face of such adversity  #KerryvMayo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayo fan at the Huddersfield v Newcastle match. There's truth in the saying you're never more than 6 feet away from a Mayo fan #KerryVMayo https://t.co/eUVtIYyrkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louis Walsh talking about his life in music on RTÉ again #miriam https://t.co/iAqT4bP6Go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WelBeast You until 4:33pm today https://t.co/HOVZY3VVkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Miriam O'Callaghan horses the hash out of it #miriam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visual representation of Roscommon's play today #MAYOvRos https://t.co/bgN40ROtuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD  https://t.co/q1BKAIJgnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Keane walking down the tunnel after game #COYBIG #WALIRL https://t.co/48m2mmm3KP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Darren Randolph there #COYBIG #WALIRL https://t.co/krsBSg2fZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swinklestar Don’t be silly we might actually win if we play the ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland have 45 minutes to get a play off place enough of the long ball shite and just fucking go for it #WALIRL #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You break our legs we break your heads seems fair enough #WALIRL #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Meyler got the captaincy tonight purely because of his fantastic well groomed beard #WALIRL #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve had more fun at mass with the extra long gospel than I’ve had watching this match #IRLMOL #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eamon Dunphy is no where to be seen tonight, RTÉ obviously put him away for his own good, in case he cums over Hoolahan #COYBIG #IRLMOL https://t.co/HaNlxznILz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Hogan has one of the most Manc accents I’ve ever heard. Good on em. #COYBIG #IRLMOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the rain falls at Jordan Henderson house #ENGSLO https://t.co/Kq1xEZrbeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a neutral watching this England game, it’s absolutely shite #ENGSLO https://t.co/C4MrpCi9Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t drink half a bottle of wine when drinking  #CuttingEdge https://t.co/TNUiFhx0yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminism is pretty much like communism great on paper but if it gets into the hands of a few lunatics it’s ruined.  #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Barton getting in touch with her inner Joker with that uniform  #emmerdale https://t.co/embvsIQlQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Shatter wearing runners with a suit, he’s so down with the kids #CBLive https://t.co/D88hC5Tnl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holly is a dream while Jade is a fucking nightmare #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this bloke another date with a decent girl its least he deserves after putting up with that c**t #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Jade girl is horrendous she needs to fuck off and learn some manners #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amount of sob stories on this it’s turning into the X Factor for shagging #FirstDates https://t.co/bMUULhlT4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Count Anthony geezer driving home after his date.  #FirstDates https://t.co/r8meHo5e8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GWTW_fan He’ll probably tell her to fuck off if she asks him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard ‘I would do anything for love but I won’t do that’ what wouldn’t you do Richard? Travel more than 5 miles for love #Undateables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you like to receive more often? Parcels, letters, etc 😂😂😂😂 I couldn’t ask that with a straight face #Undateables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Richard blending in with zebras with that shirt on.  #Undateables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard is 100% correct anything past 5 miles is a waste of time and effort   #Undateables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sakho grabs Rashford’s balls it’s the closest he’s got to a ball all day against Rashford #MUNCRY #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once lost out on a job to another person who was a bit of a prick but I’m over it unlike Hillary #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary is obviously taking fashion tips off this lad  #latelate #LateLateShow https://t.co/RGqMLGIPgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet ya she says the same thing about Mongolia on the Mongolian version of the  #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This segment should be called ‘awkward middle aged man tries to flirt with good looking young lady with notions’ #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TristanACooper I always knew the Fat Controller was a bit of a cunt but that’s just confirmed my suspicion of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland Why is the horse trainer Aiden O’Brien in the squad? Good horse trainer but can he kick a ball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missposition_ It’s cool, by the way whenever I see a KitKat now, I’ll see the devil woman who wrecked my head one Monday evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missposition_ Ah you’re a monster, I only saw that other mistake when you pointed it out. My grammar and spelling is usually bang on. Devil woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missposition_ I’m delighted you weren’t worried about my very minor mistake. I’ll never put a q in where a c belongs in barbecue ever again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missposition_ Don’t worry it’s the Irish way of spelling it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How fucking dare she break Ian’s heart, the soulless hussy. You the man Ian you the man.  #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She wears a wedding dress at barbaques. #FirstDates https://t.co/3u53ytPFIl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>