<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a… https://t.co/I8jlaCHirU https://t.co/LP66uMfaId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/xZgybOqPl5 https://t.co/I8MfKgqX7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 1/31/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering Background Optics, Other- Technical Reference req5 Introduction ASML is… https://t.co/ZA2XpGi4ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Full Stack: Job Description Job ID: R44403 1750 Tysons (12023), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive… https://t.co/m3ybFCg6WR https://t.co/mzxTS5eAmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Search Technical Lead: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’… https://t.co/FlriP3guzw https://t.co/IKkguYUtrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Associate, Data Science: McLean 1 (19050), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank,… https://t.co/bgpSRvD1KX https://t.co/t52sC7GiBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Lead: Position Overview This position will be part of the Retail Lending Decision Management organization within the Credit and Collateral Standards team. The Retail Lending Decision Management team is responsible for analytics,… https://t.co/ScUmO6Efxo https://t.co/QZ0S7Mk1XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineers at Cerner Corp. in K.C., MO. Design/develop applications; Write code, test/enhance software; Participate in code review; Develop knowledge of solution, technologies, development processes &amp; ecosystem. Req. Bach. (or… https://t.co/exn9NGy5kW https://t.co/FNxFuIJoWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/fb5hv15CHh https://t.co/rAnzyArtLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 6: Security Content Development: Job Description Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer trust remains our underlying… https://t.co/sE6Y5IzG0a https://t.co/D0z140qxXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/aCuxGHrV1G https://t.co/CLRf8I9lSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Lead- Python or Java: Software Developer Lead- Python or Java ======================================= Req #: ******Location: Aurora, CO USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job… https://t.co/BrViB21HGh https://t.co/hGYIh7z9lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Python &amp; Machine Learning: San Mateo, CA Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Data Scientist with Python experience, please read on! Based in San Mateo, CA – We are a well-funded, VC-backed startup inventing predictive… https://t.co/rbd2DDWsw5 https://t.co/mOS9QhXe5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer [Django and Python Superstar]: JOB DESCRIPTION Your Responsibilities * Collect, analyse &amp; refine requirements together with our product team. * Define big picture architectures and break them down into smaller projects/ MVPs. * Build… https://t.co/OblFsQAPDP https://t.co/xY4FKUTmgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Our Company: ThreatQuotient believes that the foundation of intelligence-driven security is people. The companys open and extensible threat intelligence platform, ThreatQ, provides defenders with the context, customization and… https://t.co/GpsLKnreJe https://t.co/UfFZDBZIpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blipp Developer: Blippar is hiring a front-end software engineer for its Blipp development team, to help us build a wide range of engaging augmented reality experiences for leading brands, agencies and publishers. We are looking for enthusiastic, engaged… https://t.co/rX6uNSqPLY https://t.co/1zAL8Sk2Tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: The QA Automation Engineer will be a member of the Software Engineering team and will report to the Manager, Quality Assurance. The primary duties of the QA Automation Engineer require the exercise of discretion and independent… https://t.co/wH4DcTFnbW https://t.co/vhNWk2sJLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted 01/11/2018 Located in a beautiful office in the Mission District in San Francisco, we are an early staged funded B2C Fin-Tech start up that is combining Artificial Intelligence, Machine… https://t.co/wdYveCP6z6 https://t.co/6wh571l9cb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 6: Security Content Development: Job Description Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer trust remains our underlying… https://t.co/vsPdOBRcUu https://t.co/aB94GYRWJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 6: Security Content Development: Job Description Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer trust remains our underlying… https://t.co/AxkuR1TRrl https://t.co/pREnxUGMLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Washington, DC Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Data Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position College experience and knowledge of: – C# – Python – Scala – ETL – Beam – Flume – NoSQL –… https://t.co/8jZakhdNhf https://t.co/mZZhHJcgWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Engineer, Python: Req ID : 430773BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Are you looking for an exciting career as a Software Engineer at one of the top Aerospace and Defense Companies? A fulfilling position… https://t.co/DfFZTuxVPK https://t.co/zVTg6k4qg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/MpIh8UuM08 https://t.co/Q7efT7e4PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/6dfIKpaahj https://t.co/5IwY11cyKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python/Django): THE COMPANY Our unique online greeting card and gift system allows everyone to act quickly when prompted to reach out to othersthere has never been an easier way to send a genuine card or heartfelt gift. With just a few… https://t.co/D1bwCVJfuD https://t.co/Ka29ZtzVm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/CqRj2el09k https://t.co/uwTqVolIy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer [Django and Python Superstar]: JOB DESCRIPTION Your Responsibilities * Collect, analyse &amp; refine requirements together with our product team. * Define big picture architectures and break them down into smaller projects/ MVPs. * Build… https://t.co/xRtNkGAgVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python… https://t.co/T6Oen3krQf https://t.co/RPWj8mFUt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: In this exciting role, CW will be part of a fast-paced storage I/O R&amp;D team creating and maintaining tools for running experiments and process data in support of… https://t.co/VXpLyDdnir https://t.co/6GLviDvtdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/2Xm6RZMebU https://t.co/2iEcGPZbUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a… https://t.co/aNn8qfbD1B https://t.co/nyncF4VsHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Engineer, Python: Req ID : 430773BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Are you looking for an exciting career as a Software Engineer at one of the top Aerospace and Defense Companies? A fulfilling position… https://t.co/MGXXGVjLiF https://t.co/KbnkzJmFl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/E8t81joSYc https://t.co/6FK4HvD7Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Software Engineer – Python Jobs in Philadelphia Area | SIG Careers You are using an unsupported browser. Some features may not work correctly.Close Menu Meet Our Team Beyond Work + Benefits News + Events About Trading Quant… https://t.co/ntdUFwzZTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/40YkfSstTp https://t.co/8Oy2hjExUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/iBaM1HkPA2 https://t.co/pal58B52oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Cyber Security Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/YU6StZRTf3 https://t.co/9ROlCph6ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Location: Boston, MA Duration: Long term contract Pay Rate: $51 to 57/hr. on w2 with voluntary employee paid benefits No# of openings: 2 Required We are seeking a senior software engineer with background in… https://t.co/Tcl3qaN8QT https://t.co/xdhwuVtK34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/Y87MF2rHfC https://t.co/KDQQI9pTYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/8LcCgqWNci https://t.co/MYHMoM5zIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statistician, Predictive Analytics: Join our WINNING team as a Statistician, Predictive Analytics Are you an experienced Statistician/Data Scientist who wants to work with an endless amount of data? Want to help millions of consumers feel more confident… https://t.co/xdWcphICap https://t.co/zYCtutac2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/Cc8fvK2MXO https://t.co/T7exGDdXB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Backend Developer/Engineer Professional: Looking for a Financial Developer/Engineer Professional that has Python Backend Developement Salary: $100-120k Location: McLean, VA 1-2 years plus hard core Back End Server Side development in… https://t.co/iC2EbB19wt https://t.co/pEK2fxwYGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/rExNrsqOoM https://t.co/5klBonEaW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a… https://t.co/pCpRH08FrV https://t.co/5rrvo55XiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/KZHzSK8YYX https://t.co/nMiI7dkVRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Title:                      DevOps Engineer Category:             Exempt Department:       User &amp; Systems Support Benefits:               22 Days Annual Leave, 15 Days of Sick Leave, 3 Days Personal Leave, 15 Paid Holidays Tuition… https://t.co/NpHMlT60Vf https://t.co/LqXlU0dDRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/NKvoN1TptP https://t.co/Hw5HmeDhrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/xjhg4MprOb https://t.co/LmqDeS840L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/TOON7R6xEI https://t.co/v9IRd7HlEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/k6Vqizun4b https://t.co/PD4HbOq2ST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Cloud Email: Senior Software Engineer Cloud Email Engineering Burlington, MA, USA Role Sophos is focused on delivering the best IT security and data protection for businesses. Today Sophos products protect over 100,000 businesses… https://t.co/QBDATHiOhR https://t.co/noJ8E683d4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/r4y2zYNvXC https://t.co/AqGdc2f7lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build Release Automation Engineer: Build &amp; Release Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-14109 Location: Mountain View, California Hi, Hope you are doing great, Position: Build &amp; Release Automation Engineer Location: Mountain View, CA Full time Position –… https://t.co/UNRHRV0ETv https://t.co/Hge34eYBpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Test Engineer – Summer Intern: Open Lending is seeking a highly motivated summer intern to help expand our QA automation test suite for our flagship product Lenders Protection. This is a quality assurance development internship position… https://t.co/oSZPKBMwb4 https://t.co/aM4953Es2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: As a Software Engineer you will work as part of a top-performing team to deliver high-quality search engine marketing SaaS solutions to market. You will be able to work with minimal direction, balance multiple requirements and… https://t.co/ZjqwH6XvYI https://t.co/rKvGb7c7qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-14621 Location: san jose, California Hi, This isShipra fromEnterprise Solution Inc.I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Job Title: Python Developer Location: San Jose, CA Duration:… https://t.co/EU2PMH35iw https://t.co/YLgdiPiwzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Machine Vision: Sr. Software Engineer – Machine Vision Location Simi Valley, CA Employment type Regular – Full Time ID 87 Apply Now Who We Are Based in California, AeroVironment (AVAV) is a global leader in unmanned aircraft… https://t.co/lQEqFVYOaH https://t.co/atC7Q1k3uP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test: The Software Development Engineer in Test position is a hands-on role that contributes to the success at Esurance by designing and developing automated test processes, scripts and tools to champion the code quality… https://t.co/HS1T0EeRhz https://t.co/lNm6idDUw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Engineer ( Full Time ): Job Title: Cloud Engineer Location:Murray Hill, New Jersey MUST have networking experience. Job Profile Design, document, and implement infrastructure, processes, and automation for global complex environments oGather… https://t.co/cMsRSo7hUp https://t.co/zFnSgBuCAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Platform – SteelCentral NPM: Company Overview Riverbed accelerates business outcomes through a complete portfolio of industry-leading digital performance solutions. Performance is not just about speed, it includes different metrics that… https://t.co/wa4p0zOqRh https://t.co/8aJpvUDkNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Python Software Engineer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Sr. Financial Software Developer with Python skills. Candidate will design, develop and support systems within the financial modelling and research area.… https://t.co/GR2PtQ3E7P https://t.co/657eXf2cxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Bioinformatics Developer: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Public Trust Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: No Active Clearance Required Suitability: Public Trust Job Family: Engineering &amp; Sciences Job Description: GDIT has an opportunity… https://t.co/Rv56AUN0QY https://t.co/Ot6C3EODZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Location: Boston, MA Duration: Long term contract Pay Rate: $51 to 57/hr. on w2 with voluntary employee paid benefits No# of openings: 2 Required We are seeking a senior software engineer with background in… https://t.co/VynTNinIVJ https://t.co/Ib1fiR0N8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA – Boston, MA alexabostonjobs@amazo: Job Description Java/Python Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA – Boston, MA ************************** Job ID ****** Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 4/22/2018 Company… https://t.co/R8rpUcK2Fg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Python Developer: Jr. Python Developer Ref No.: 18-19686 Location: Sunnyvale, California – Candidate should have strong hands-on developmentexperience in python scripting – Should have hands on experience in modelling in Python – Should have… https://t.co/IeJFUVKS28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Software Engineer in Test: TVision Insights is a hyper-growth television attention measurement company pioneering the way brands, their agencies, TV networks and OTT platforms determine the true value of their video content and advertising.… https://t.co/4a3tDwMPUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/Qcb7jct29F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: The Sr. Python Software Developer shall have extensive experience in software design, development and testing, program installations, and system implementations. JOB ACTIVITIES: * Develop applications that are performant and meet the… https://t.co/URupb41gC4 https://t.co/7cKMDVg1Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Ruby Software Engineer: We are looking for our Lead Software Engineer in NYC. If building a real time predictive analytics tool interest you, look no further. We build a predictive analytics tool used by some of the largest brands in publishing… https://t.co/YTTLXbcnye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/4WkC00pRLU https://t.co/I6OJMBqKmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: ThreatQuotient understands that the foundation of intelligence-driven security is people. The companys open and extensible threat intelligence platform, ThreatQ, and cybersecurity situation room solution, ThreatQ Investigations, empower… https://t.co/iIrke5qmm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer in Test (C++, Java, Python): Tableau Software is hiring now! Check out this great Senior Software Engineer in Test (C++, Java, Python) role. Sign Up Login Back to view jobs We’re growing fast! Check out the latest jobs we have… https://t.co/mGwrG65Gkl https://t.co/5QJwcMAIq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/2mLarrMEQX https://t.co/DMl2XB4sGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build/Devops Engineer: Build Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time position Job Description: 10+ years of software development, build infrastructure engineering experience Expertise in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery Experience with build… https://t.co/Msd5KC9aNN https://t.co/tvT7LxyYIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: As Data Scientist, youll utilize advanced quantitative &amp; statistical analysis techniques to drive business model innovation for Via, and work closely with our CEO &amp; senior management to help drive decisions. Responsibilities: * Adeptly… https://t.co/Jnk9Pmjxsb https://t.co/3DLOCP3C8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/Xewn9MHjyu https://t.co/OOCBeLG9D2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Customers expect our networks to perform at a high level all the time. That’s where you come in. You will investigate, evaluate and resolve network and data performance issues to ensure… https://t.co/GxecC92wXc https://t.co/CW8RYZqTBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Engineer: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is our global vision and the common… https://t.co/V7puNRVNzi https://t.co/dQi9QautBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer Python: We are looking for a full stack Web Framework developer to work on upstream R&amp;D projects closely with a data science team, performing functional prototyping and facilitating the transfer of successful prototypes to production… https://t.co/3HleRQPgK7 https://t.co/zqzoowdLfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Pinterest is focusing on improving its support for shopping and product discovery. Youll apply state-of-art data mining and machine learning techniques to significantly increase the product search and recommendation relevance. Youll… https://t.co/qYmhCS5xJJ https://t.co/6PMXQNijSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: At Fitbit, our mission is to help people lead healthier, more active lives by empowering them with data, inspiration and guidance to reach their goals. We started our journey in 2007as a team of two with one big idea. Since then,… https://t.co/uVdwE4GzWh https://t.co/lq16kijRS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer 117257: One of the largest global financial services firms, and a recognized banking institution worldwide is seeking a Python Developer in New York. You will join a development team creating business solutions, contributing across… https://t.co/3mzWyokAxl https://t.co/gIJVlHf0Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/R8zfBaQeUI https://t.co/WEepwscOWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: Network Voice Engineer Ref No.: 18-22015 Location: Marlborough, Massachusetts Candidate will take care of IMAC for voice devices which includes but not limited to desk and conference room phones, TV Screens, and Projectors.… https://t.co/71HvuFBI8e https://t.co/KlvCzuFMHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Pinterest is focusing on improving its support for shopping and product discovery. Youll apply state-of-art data mining and machine learning techniques to significantly increase the product search and recommendation relevance. Youll… https://t.co/qh6MnPIYtq https://t.co/hopZt9QJ3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Blockchain Engineer – JavaScript, Python, A.I: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Blockchain Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in Sunnyvale, CA with recent capital investments we are a fast… https://t.co/Q07E2PMBji https://t.co/T1RCEe44PU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across… https://t.co/QurbfVZpUM https://t.co/qLPewB6IYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/uXZOLmSr0P https://t.co/DY7wulf35e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer (Python/ C++) – Hillsboro, OR: Automation Engineer (Python/ C++) Hillsboro OR Full time Job Description: Responsibilities: Work closely with the design and development team to analyze the requirements and help with defining the test… https://t.co/Imef6GpbYw https://t.co/a6tijUTwD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/XZ5JIdEtqd https://t.co/CD1NpaJAWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-Sales Engineer: Responsibilities Meet or exceed quarterly and yearly products/services sales goals. Provide extensive tactical and strategic pre-sales support for the Tufin inside sales team. Identify and develop business opportunities with potential… https://t.co/mCo3cktKbe https://t.co/9LAzcERb3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/PjMchMtBm3 https://t.co/0j9DwElvT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA Python Engineer: MySQL DBA/Software Engineer with Python Need a strong MYSQL DBA with good python knowledge to automate tasks. You will need server tuning, strong Bash or Python Scripting skills along with DBA tasks Responsibilities: Performs a… https://t.co/0syHNHGsBl https://t.co/NMMtq6PrBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer (C++/ Python) Hillsboro OR Full Time position Job Responsibilities Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework… https://t.co/bSSYfJnrrr https://t.co/0EmmaGKawi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NX Software Engineer: Division: Digital FactoryBusiness Unit: Product Lifecycle Management-PLMRequisition Number: 223719Primary Location: United States-Ohio-MilfordAssignment Category: Full-time regularExperience Level: Entry levelEducation Required… https://t.co/KSwTDq3uQb https://t.co/FRYfzFXDkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Configuration Management Analyst: Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems that make the world a safer place and help to secure… https://t.co/qOZhXhMMHA https://t.co/Da5JjLMG7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/T58koQtEHO https://t.co/MXr5NtyMoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – IT Advanced Analytics Solutions: Data Scientist Raytheon IDS – Tewksbury, MA (alternate locations – Andover or Woburn MA) Information Technology – Advanced Analytics Solutions Are you passionate about data, applied statistics,… https://t.co/kgu09RIlQF https://t.co/NPHULoxX6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Engineer: Description: Leidos has an immediate job opportunity for an Linux Systems Engineer to join our team in Bethesda, MD. Qualified/selected candidates are eligible for sign-on bonus/relocation assistance. You will also have the… https://t.co/68H50ncD8V https://t.co/eoRazzYArd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>