<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DianaJSpencer Ha! Yes, definitely agree. Although, an unintended joke that one. 10 hour flights and syntactical jokes are not my usual cocktails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the land of cold &amp; contactless payment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_bsr: G.E. Rickman Lecture tonight at the BSR- Christer Bruun (Toronto) on 'What did Rome’s emperors do for #Ostia, its economy and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Space_Syntax: #UrbanFootprint of #Bristol created using the new @Space_Syntax model of Great Britain.
 
Measures displayed are Vehicle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StuartElden: 50 Years of Environment and Planning – new website, launch of EPE: Nature and Space and 50 free-to-access articles https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit cooler today! 244km for the week, 45km in 2 hours for the day &amp; 8,500m climbing for the… https://t.co/Ou7E9uDUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After yesterdays triple IPA extravaganza, it was (70km) up to the Junction &amp; back. 199km for the… https://t.co/ZcHbak4kIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Elder. Keepin’ the dream alive! @ Bobby G's Pizzeria https://t.co/iZ37kVPNpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Younger. To celebrate turning in an 85 pg Appeal. Toughest week in a long time. Thanks to… https://t.co/izk3EzIRmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count down... HenHouse: Big Chicken &amp; Drake’s: Celebrator... @ Bobby G's Pizzeria https://t.co/ZuhBUFGHzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long (challenging) week for me. Starting the weekend w/ Heritic: Evil 3, triple IPA 11.5%. Plus,… https://t.co/eskVim3qLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheSocReview: Foucault: Neoliberalism is not laissez-faire, but permanent vigilance, activity, and intervention https://t.co/GL7d3ppJBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After an (already) long week, back in the modernist Environmental Design library today. Nice… https://t.co/30dbERLYpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo My bro-in-law has a brew kit like that. Loves it. And brews 3-4 times a month...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ripper. Keepin’ my 80s child upbringing a live. https://t.co/CZ5jfwyjg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StarWarsUK: In 100 days... #HanSolo https://t.co/NZsEJnjs3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from Team Banana! 75km this AM in 3:23.33 hours (should not have eaten… https://t.co/tOf9jkUY2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @electricarchaeo: on which note, you should really go 'splore it. https://t.co/OUsx7Nnq0L  It gives me thoughts/ideas re urban archaeolo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katrinnas I will be there. Wouldn’t miss it! Plus, I still have most of my stuff in London...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to try The Baltic Porter! https://t.co/KxIZmVZDT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough day today. So, 50km after uni crap all morning. Pipe &amp; chicken to clear my head. HenHouse:… https://t.co/UdIuuxtxLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin Good luck! You have a lot offer any Uni, but hopefully this Uni recognizes that potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread. Curling stones need to be added to more sports. https://t.co/VeJ0MIPZNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wretched hive of scum &amp; villainy. Volt BMX London. https://t.co/Cjd1BRjVH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s 310km from last Sunday to today. Starting to get ready for some centuries... https://t.co/wDYzRrwXf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast 45km to start week w/ family, SF beer week &amp; uni crap... Today was a quick cadence so, only… https://t.co/Esq4Mjzh16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mellow 72km... funny to say that, but starting to feel the miles tick over easily. https://t.co/dpCC8GzLnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GraemeEarl: Institute in Ancient Itineraries: The Digital Lives of Art History - Call for members https://t.co/Aoo2ZIgkXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @profdavidharvey: Marx’s Refusal of the Labour Theory of Value https://t.co/4Ac17BMkCt https://t.co/tZCivp5KW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @richmondcycles: Yes, there’s football and rugby on today, but come on, it’s #MilanSanRemo2018 Live on @Eurosport_UK 13.30 Forza @petosa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you ride through the rain (1st 20km), wind (last 25km), iPod dying (last 20km) &amp; do a… https://t.co/dJs0wU27Fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Emma_Cole1: A must-read for any Tier 2 visa holders contemplating further industrial action. https://t.co/nCpdZOK7Y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @classarch: It's the #IdesofMarch. What better time to discover that our bust of Julius Caesar looks a lot like #StarWars's Peter Cushin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pompei79 @_bridgetheatre ‘Paved’... #roadporn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True statement. https://t.co/YqzcU6hAoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyPAnderson @martynwendell @SectarianReview @RobLOsborn I assume most of us side with the cat in that picture... will have to listen to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo I’m getting into the politics of auditory metaphors for understanding urban space (resonance, resound, echo, etc)... lots of theoretical overlap. The metaphors carry most of the (unexamined) weight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @1ookmumnohands: Cheer on the @Milano_Sanremo LIVE on our big screen this Saturday from 1:30pm at 49 Old St. https://t.co/JRYgRKEoZi htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KathrynTempest: Happy Ides of March everyone .... https://t.co/BI3pGedGPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be working on an application, but the Apex 1 crankset, BB, cassette, derailleur &amp; chain… https://t.co/1RBix9M9Bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final tally! 88km &amp; 4 hours of closed roads (unmarked), lack of direct routes (due to closed… https://t.co/1e9M47sF1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t let the bright glow behind me fool you: I rode through lashing rain today. Got Pete’s… https://t.co/MdFF3Put4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylaurence1: Pompeii's streets interview with Matt Smith. Big thanks to @Pompeiana79 whose book I was reviewing see next AJAhttps://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: "Luke, use the Space Force." — Darth "Space" Vader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheels! Just waiting on the drivetrain... The Eddy might just come in lighter than the Logic!… https://t.co/JHTDxpQPYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: I need a space force / I'm holding out for a space force til the morning light / like the Army and Navy, except it's fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenEllis74 @mikofLohr @OUPAcademic Waiting for my ordered copy to arrive (in London). Then it has to travel to California...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As it was raging this AM, skipped a ride &amp; went back into Berkeley for more Intro writing… https://t.co/bmTEybdKPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intro is down to 17 pages &amp; 8,082 words… Now coherence &amp; chapter summaries (with the remaining 2k words). https://t.co/yks0KxbxSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pompeiana79 Writing about Ostia density today. Storey is all over the bibliography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 @Woolf_Greg There are other ways to get into a bike lock... Passed a UC Berkeley tour guide who pointed out no building on campus has two door handles on the same side to prevent protesters from locking ppl in/out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: One month today... The Brother Sean vertical tasting. Three vintages 15, 16 &amp; 17. Tickets here: https://t.co/kQurt8Ho90…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matthew46463166: Absolutely horrific news: Two married Durham academics on Tier 2 visas and their daughter given 14 days to leave the c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pint of Pliny for @tezza_mm &amp; a day in the library (pic is from this AM as it’s overcast &amp;… https://t.co/46ggsJj8GZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery revealed. https://t.co/ZHPeO1zdGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxberrytoast ‘Jansen’s? Too dry, too terribly 18th-century petty-bourgeois, &amp; as far as boredom goes, his Augustines beats even Summa Theologiae.’ (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for @foxberrytoast Lefebvre on his Catholic upbringing &amp; early studies of the history of the church to find a heresy to resurrect…(1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double days of 87 &amp; 88km. Felt pretty good the whole ride! Bit slower than yesterday, but speed… https://t.co/0S3VzCqgOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PR for the Summit of Mt Diablo. Here’s the speed to climb gradient for the whole climb. At the last bit (18.8%) I had to pass the junior Marine’s training march. Motivated a fast finish. https://t.co/6XeuPUnamF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not bad for the week so far. 1 day left... 87.5km &amp; 3:59.39 hours; feeling pretty good &amp; the… https://t.co/Rj9Oi1j0jx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StuartElden: Critical Planning issue with tributes to Jacqueline Leavitt and Ed Soja (open access) https://t.co/11uAqDZnhB https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @raylaurence1 @mcarterSKW @caatue @raylaurence1 you did that at the Kent Riverine conference! With no mention of @electricarchaeo ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My lunch break score. Add it to the list of French books I need to read (some for reviews...) https://t.co/IVhKjsRVi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On to Hillel Schwartz’s Making Noise today… This review opening gives you an idea of what this means. Trevor Pinch in Isis 104.4 (2014) https://t.co/yWyh1oH4oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back, although a bit brighter today. More cities &amp; noise... https://t.co/xVzceUq3dA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GallulaRoma Question is, how much of it did you read before getting off? Or did you just barrow it until you read it all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JshRbnsn: Asking for an 'independent valuation' is a well-laid trap by @UniversitiesUK. Even more so if the 'independent' valuation is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s tally: 1,209 words on defining &amp; approaching noise… Covered Schafer, Corbin, Thompson, Attali, &amp; Lefebvre https://t.co/UEsMvrDFzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gray on gray today. Plus, today’s stack of books, which only means one thing... back to the… https://t.co/rV17yExVEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pompei79 @Pompeiana79 @nightlightguy @raylaurence1 Ostia has a great naughty bath mosaic! Terms della Trinacria 3.16.7) https://t.co/9U2LlKzVMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ntUnderstudy: It’s on! Come and have a go on @AnspachHobday Birthday Baltic Porter https://t.co/qBNq0zgm9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ntUnderstudy: We’re launching @AnspachHobday 4th birthday brew TONIGHT! https://t.co/DduaPa98fJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[47.5 miles today! Lunch overlooking the bay; had to jump over a tree on Pinehurst; have the… https://t.co/OoiokiCI9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @1ookmumnohands: . @AnspachHobday ’s Baltic Porter is launching at 49 Old St. TOMORROW. Slurp a smooth, well rounded 7.3% porter with us…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LDNBikeKitchen: Feel that sunlight, that change in the weather? That's your cue to clean your chain! Get all that awful grit off and ge…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo I have notebooks of writing diagrams... I think I should publish all of them at the end of my career for later scholars to psychoanalyze (a Walter Benjamin arcades project type thing)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: ALL THE VENUES (2/3) for tomorrows Baltic Porter #megalaunch Where are we going to see you all then? https://t.co/SJAzHt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo Yeah, &amp; there’s plenty of time (2020/2021) so, a slow burner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo True. What a boring when to approach life (and knowledge). In other news, may have a proposal for a contribution along these lines (senses, knowledge, cities... brickstamps) need to workout some details before sending it to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensation as interpreter of the ‘limits of understanding’. 

My recent experiences lead me to believe some react w/ fear &amp; reversion, not an ‘opening up of new worlds’. https://t.co/q32N8EjzlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylaurence1: Add your name to the open letter to Universities engaging in punitive action against staff during the UCU strike and ASOS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 2 weeks off the bike, I at least have a metric century in me (although not the fastest… https://t.co/j84zZ65Hq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenEllis74 @Pompeiana79 E. has a proposal for a project w/ the Sir John Soane’s Museum in the works... physical models, environmental effects (light, rain, etc.) &amp; digital outputs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoK_UCU: 220 = number of staff from @UniKent who joined @UCU in February 2018. We are on our way to a striking 1100 members... Yipee an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Eddy made it safe. Tomorrow’s plan is to get out on the bike (the Ritchey) for a few hours… https://t.co/Y5PAoyxsOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slippers in Oakland. @ Oakland International Airport https://t.co/89CTT4zsxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slippers boarding. @ Gatwick Airport https://t.co/1gB72ZT5rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylaurence1: The chilling approach by @unikent to staff, part-time staff, hourly paid zero hours staff &amp; Grad Teaching Assistants.  ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s adventure: bus, tube, train, &amp; plane w/ this lot. https://t.co/qlzgI0WMcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just following The Cannibal’s advice... final packing is done. https://t.co/3axZQVb6Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strada Bianchi. Plus, Burning Sky: Easy Answers IPA. @ look mum no hands! https://t.co/LIr9YgiH1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brunch. Sorted. 

First attempt (not me, but other-half) at poached eggs. https://t.co/UBsvHbtMBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LSchoonderwoerd: A message to @UniKent. I am angry. I will not back down. @UoK_UCU @ucu #UCU #ucustrikes #ussstrike #ucustrike #strikef…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilHubbard1: Have just written to VC @unikent telling her I am not going to be (unpaid) external supervisor for their PGRs while they…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As my stuff is on its way to CA... Cantillon Grand Cru was in order. After a bit of Orval. The… https://t.co/Lcw5Ci01Pb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve been doing some research on the Motorola Merckx. The chrome rear triangle is odd, as most… https://t.co/JU7li60P4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The library got collected. I’ll see my books on the other side... (in 3 months)... https://t.co/rlyXEvZwX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobertEWitcher: The all-new @AntiquityJ website now hosts a full TAG archive w/ programmes &amp; abstracts of nearly every UK meeting since…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin @ihr_history @book_learning @CMH_London @UniTurku @Wickyma @lievenameel @AlastairHackney @MissSarahWise @london_rg @UrbanHistoryCUP @urbanhistgroup @CUHLeicester @LSECities Thanks! Will see what my travel possibilities (mostly budget...) will allow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StuartElden: The History of Cartography – Free Online https://t.co/RijqNyyU81]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>