<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/DAe6eYskKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/Rn30QaifvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/OCwO6dUJbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/r3geNmIjf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got rock 'n' roll in my blood. - William Shatner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/88Hbux1wSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/i0RAYFyhNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/EfwaA9pdbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/Z4AtAoa5w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/e9bBgDKtv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/fvaJB97x69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/9O0HEpdvT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/qdW5CliGYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/pt4BoW7KHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/DA2Vcz46Ig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/lDBj6XPFJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/lC4OSKW8ZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/bvkpfHi6LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/gNRO90dbcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/TD8GLDKphx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/d3pPFwdiqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/soqGHh8mWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/v4EMl7Njp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/jWjiHmRh2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/q7oCfoFr5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/9Yg2G77Aoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/0bU3gSNZXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/SV1JgNakEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/GYoEbG35mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/DuZtVcXceZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/me4WJLuRv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/s2YHJBGOII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/J335WBPPiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/hXmY3Yt5yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/aKduEklP79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/xqI8niJAkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/U5VYUc1G8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/h5mPU1ME0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is the first milestone on the road to the stars. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/IV3f9czdFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/RNieMbe1v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/5t7kp5EYee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/sCS6VzpvnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/FeBcHS6qpu]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/qpwL4nM592]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/82TW4PtP7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/AFfJpgMDTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/SZWRGZfckM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>