<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Spiritual maturity isn't about praying more.  It's about praying differently.  https://t.co/ESvmuG1vNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard. Play hard. https://t.co/ciJilhUENE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work ethic as Jesus followers isn't shaped by our advancement but by God's glory. https://t.co/zRfEJPYx7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians should work with a vigor and intensity that stands out in a sea of laziness and mediocrity.  https://t.co/mpB7TxWuio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you do your job reflects what you believe about God. https://t.co/IL9ERpqYBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get to work! Laziness profanes the name of God. https://t.co/GpwqOj2PJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing new resource for college students! Love this new project from @passion268. Check it out! https://t.co/bxin95NQVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS!!! What we're all about - death to life, enemy to daughter, sinner to saint!   Love… https://t.co/loCgy8Ev2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for all our veterans. Praying specifically for those @RCChurchDC who serve our country and sacrifice so much for our freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't accept someone because they voted differently, that's not a political problem. It's a gospel problem. https://t.co/0EbabzDE1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a non-Christian read all of your posts for the last month, would they be more or less likely to follow Jesus? Use your voice well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organize your calendar around this idea! https://t.co/t3k0gP2CKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a Christian, you are an ambassador of Christ.  Please act, speak and post like it. https://t.co/awkWXs22kH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christianity is not defined by a party, a platform or a politician.It’s defined by an empty tomb and a Risen Savior. https://t.co/ldmQcB6iDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the aftermath of this election, we have an opportunity to make hope visible. https://t.co/zCzOXrQ1DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't pray for our next President, don't blame it on disappointment.  Call it what it is - disobedience. https://t.co/SHRLnDu02b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet today like you're going to pray tomorrow, no matter who wins. #Election2016 https://t.co/GcR5tQVCZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote.  And then rejoice that our confidence is in Christ, not a candidate.https://t.co/xLuJ3KsHsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your God fits perfectly in either political party, He’s too small. And His name’s not Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you join me in making these three commitments on election day?https://t.co/wOVQ3DrhVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES! https://t.co/8f1qMOk86i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little lady.  Thanks @jessicakmann for incredible photos to help remember these days! https://t.co/Eqrizo94Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baptism Sundays = Best Sundays.  Still time for you to get baptized with us next weekend. https://t.co/vz7F9gap3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever want to get over this city.  Inspiring in so many ways! #dc https://t.co/CNVfVNMoMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headed to Restoration City.  Excited and grateful to be back in the pulpit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kids are so stoked for an extra hour of not sleeping!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect fall day in DC! https://t.co/jXKl5LEXyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planting a church is about God's mission, not your convenience. https://t.co/j4cASY2tTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is God leading you to help plant Grace Hill in Herndon, VA? Here are four questions to help you process: https://t.co/A7wanEMcSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful! https://t.co/aKnGYAfzHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of what we call drama, the Bible calls sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's going to disciple my kids. I'd like it to be me! https://t.co/xbPlqcrFJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus didn’t come to perfect your image but to transform your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: Consider serving with our Christmas Eve volunteer teams to help welcome our community in to celebrate Jesus with us! https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel isn’t a convenient accessory to our ambition. It’s a total remapping of it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time with Jesus fuels passion for Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reston/Herndon friends, here's a great opportunity to connect with a new @SummitNetwork church plant launching in 2017. https://t.co/4Rh2nd5pyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision comes from abiding.  So many of our vision problems are abiding problems in disguise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People flourish under the care of a leader and wither under the demands of a dictator. Look around you - more flourishing or withering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insecure leaders use power to hurt and control. Secure leaders to bless and release!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas should be wonderful, not stressful. New on the blog: https://t.co/lZI8btKiIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmarkcomer grateful for friends like you that point the way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So often, we keep people at a distance because we know that if we let them near, we would be forced to abandon our pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hope of Christmas is a perfect Savior, not a perfect holiday.  New on the blog: https://t.co/AoDNx901Nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, help us fear our strength more than our weakness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RickWarren: Worry all you want, that won't change ANYTHING . Pray about ANYTHING, that'll change EVERYTHING. #SEEKTOFIND #PRAY34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll never enjoy what God is doing through you if you’re obsessing about what He is or isn’t doing through someone else!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God lovingly breaks our pride so He can powerfully use our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unity doesn’t just happen. You’ve got to fight for it, sacrifice for it and forgive for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satisfaction does not come through striving, but surrender.  So proud of @jamesmarshallg and so… https://t.co/Gawkrue6f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love our friends @curatedoldtown! And this weekend they're donating 20% of your total to Gunston… https://t.co/bgyATgdVvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good! https://t.co/w6fn7S3wzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending time with God isn't an obligation, it's an opportunity.  Not a "have to" but a "get to"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's plan for you requires God's power in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generosity is trading things that won't matter a month from now for things that will last for all eternity. https://t.co/eVriOSgA9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generosity isn't measured by how much we give but by how much we give up! https://t.co/86tulfN9am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to simplify life this Christmas? Embrace generosity! https://t.co/mjFUB6BUXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our generosity at Christmas is a response to all Jesus gave up for us in a cradle and on a cross. https://t.co/Gu8PQWo7NG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church never feels like more of a family than when we're commissioning parents and dedicating… https://t.co/wGQXOsbM7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday! And, yes, my wife is an astonishingly wonderful person. Not sure how she does… https://t.co/VKM24qbi7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders sacrifice for the good of others. Dictators demand others sacrifice for their good. Don't be an accidental dictator!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growth in Christ is about dying, not trying. https://t.co/g5J2MygK1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will kill your leadership effectiveness like the belief that you always know best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace can carry us farther than our weary legs could ever hope to run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Jesus can carry the full weight of our hopes and dreams. So true and so easy to forget!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because Jesus joyfully sacrificed Himself for our salvation, we can joyfully sacrifice ourselves for His glory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss out on everything happening at Restoration City this Christmas.  Full list here: https://t.co/qg4wdO3r37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When our hearts grow cold, it's not that Christ isn't satisfying.  It's that we're not abiding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No better way to wrap up Thanksgiving weekend - communion and worship with my Restoration City community!  Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to start our new series, "Boundless: The People, Power, And Mission Of God" tomorrow… https://t.co/ll395VSB0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup, I'm in love with her! https://t.co/mxtTEiVxk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News out of Fort Lauderdale is heart breaking.  Be near, Lord Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The church is most beautiful when she's most sacrificial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our ability to rest is directly linked to our belief in God's sovereignty. He's in control, so I don't have to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobgoff: There's no school to learn how to love your neighbor, just the house next door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst thing to waste is time - no way to get it back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineCaine: If you spend too much time scrolling through everyone else's life, you forget to live your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is always telling me to "send good thoughts" to people.  It's hard to imagine a more meaningless phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting what I pray will be the most culture shaping series yet at Restoration City this… https://t.co/mnnmVm6Erm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carry the wonder of Christmas back to work with you today. https://t.co/exTbjxHAxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace doesn't leave us feeling in debt. It leaves us feeling in love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @passion268: YES! Passion 2017 will be live streamed! Tune in tonight @ 7pm EST https://t.co/pbFwfHtROR https://t.co/wplGu7Trw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The grace that forgives compels action. https://t.co/OHBkBRCT4d https://t.co/OmzA2fKaod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are loved by the God of limitless faithfulness; He’s never going to change His mind about you. https://t.co/EbZamv5rb0 https://t.co/MKJjLgfju5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back over 2016 and realizing how frequently "hardest" and "best" travel together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting gospel amnesia today at Wellspring: https://t.co/RX525rXcWb https://t.co/BtmRmvPdYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What shaped our 2016 wasn’t God’s willingness to offer grace, but rather our
responses to that grace. Read more: https://t.co/PuG5gTqJwc https://t.co/kArHH9mZXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wellspring: A New Year's Guide" starts tomorrow.  Download your copy and follow along: https://t.co/d5dQA5zdfL https://t.co/LA80364Mc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you missed this from @timkellernyc last week, it's well worth the read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God isn't just an end of life insurance policy.  He's the fountain of all our life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s impossible to get into the presence of God and leave disappointed. https://t.co/HQOmaVP3gH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't have to spend our lives looking for hope.  At Christmas, hope came to find us. https://t.co/jw0TRA1Qsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For to us a child is born, to us a son is given" (Is. 9:6) https://t.co/OZ9KQoeRTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Eve with Restoration City. 4pm. The Synetic Theater. 

Love to have you join us if… https://t.co/lor9qDu0Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbross319 would be a total game changer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I say we give a Nobel prize to the person who invents an auto-reply for text messages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus wasn't born to admire our perfection.  He was born to offer us His.  https://t.co/rsyEqXqZlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the longing for perfect prevent you from enjoying good. New blog: https://t.co/75B8BqadPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas From The McGowans. New on the blog: https://t.co/h01l3H3mBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: In town for Christmas Eve? Help us welcome our guests on Christmas Eve by serving on one of our volunteer teams! https://t.…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>