<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes God doesn’t answer our prayers with a feeling in the moment but through a friend later in the day. #LiveInCommunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we just need to be reminded of the simple things. Prayer works!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it doesn’t feel a little scary, it’s probably not vulnerability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find a friend you can be completely honest with - God will use them to pour life into your soul!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I know about the 2016 election: @realDonaldTrump &amp; @HillaryClinton aren't the problem. They're a symptom. https://t.co/ld6HkHpVCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved checking out @museumofbible construction today. Amazing vision...pretty good view as well.… https://t.co/ElopDYoW1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because the 2016 election is a circus doesn't mean it has to become an obsession: https://t.co/xNp2WgHBtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salvation is the realization that, in Christ, God has become our exceeding joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't allow the 2016 election to divide us as followers of Christ. My plea for tolerant unity: https://t.co/k3kHKa4Hj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in our worst deserts, there are still streams of hope. https://t.co/nNuGsgIiAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't read the Bible to show God how much you love Him.  Read it to be reminded of how much He loves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundays really are the best - so grateful for the people of Restoration City Church!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our longing for mercy is met through the steadfast love of Jesus.  He never waivers, even when we do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luke17_37 good for you!  Praying He blesses your steps of obedience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure isn't the worst outcome.  It's not trying that shrivels our souls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It is easier for God to hold back anger than mercy.” -Augustine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear - my weakness is greater than God's power.

Courage - God's power is greater than my weakness.

Which is driving your life right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's plans for our lives will prevail in spite of all opposition, including our own lack of faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that our church gathers where our community gathers: https://t.co/pgObictpEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can’t really lead until you find something you love more than yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can’t disagree respectfully, you’ll never be able to lead effectively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only humble hands can carry big dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus will never abandon you.  He may prune, discipline, or do the unexpected.  But He's always there. Don't run from Him - run to Him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s hard to fight with someone you regularly pray with. #marriage #ministry #friends #family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, I watched a guy I baptized years ago become an elder at our church. So proud of you, @dan_iten. https://t.co/QdbYyGaNFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team left for Nicaragua this morning. Join me in praying for them daily between now and next Wednesday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's talk from Restoration City "Live From Love: Falling In Love, For Real" is now available: https://t.co/AlraE0xSJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This! Our "Live From Love" series in one quote.  Thanks, Pedro Arupe, SJ! https://t.co/tJzoyHEC0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Week 2 of Live From Love - Jesus, help us see Your love for us! https://t.co/2X8OGtsfTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have known James and Sabrina since they were in college. Had the honor of officiating their… https://t.co/F5AiW9y5w1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Questions As We Get Ready To Vote On Elders This Sunday https://t.co/Aug6UuxoCu https://t.co/pdFzz7xapN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complacency is the precursor to decline.  Stay hungry.  Keep learning.  Never settle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like the "yelling at each other about politics on social media" thing isn't working so well.  Might be time for a new approach?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's been using these books to grow my love for Jesus: https://t.co/G9Z33KAB5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the start of "Live From Love" this past Sunday?  Catch up with the podcast: https://t.co/GRsmF650mJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength is found in surrender.  Stop trying to do what God has promised to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved kicking off our "Live From Love" series this morning at Restoration City. Really believe these are crucial talks for our church!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #DC for #Together2016 &amp; looking for a place to worship this morning?  Love to have you at Restoration City: https://t.co/w2YGmBryIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, Carter and Katie! Great day celebrating two incredible people. #whitehotwedding https://t.co/9UjW2bx4qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop seeing difficulty as a surprise and start seeing it as an opportunity: https://t.co/pO7fgkVngn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RCC College Fall Kickoff Tonight. God, raise up a generation of students who trade big roles in… https://t.co/nx27XzYyQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a leader or a task master? The answer is in your ability to delegate.  https://t.co/zomb0HZ56e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care what your title is.  If you aren't delegating, you aren't leading. https://t.co/64DKVTuluX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying God exceeds all of our expectations for this night! https://t.co/bqq1aS0lzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our team’s on campus at GW right now - please take a minute to pray for them. Asking God to use their efforts for His glory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People of God + Word of God + Worship of God = Amazing morning! @ Gunston Middle https://t.co/oz1CxBNDM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a great two weeks but so excited to be speaking at Restoration City tomorrow.  Can't wait… https://t.co/uzNkPWRrU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two weekends in a row!  Love our church! https://t.co/aN7HNSJVje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You keep him in perfect peace whose mind is stayed on You, because he trusts in You."(Is. 26:3) Knowing should lead to trusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you missed @will_mcgee's talk last Sunday at Restoration City, find time to listen.  Here's the link: https://t.co/dpg5I4Hnyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s the full list of school supplies we’re collecting this Sunday at Restoration City: https://t.co/X65g9zcJZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drmoore: College Students, Why You Need a Church (Not Just a Campus Ministry) https://t.co/W0O0qi0ypT via @TGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planting churches isn’t about writing checks. It’s about developing leaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Restoration City - if you can help us paint at Gunston this Saturday, sign up here: https://t.co/H3JpHfzx1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying yes to everybody is the fastest way to end up useful to nobody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church growth and church planting aren’t competing values. They’re complementary when motivated by the gospel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need one on one time with my kids almost as much as they need it with me.
https://t.co/MUyQm3Ciid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewardship isn’t just about money.  Same mindset for time, attitude, attention and energy - use it all wisely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not the lack of difficulty that makes a life great, it’s how we respond to the inevitable hardships!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 days of prayer for GW starts today!  Please join with our college students on this prayer journey.  https://t.co/Xne1qQLNwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So thankful for @will_mcgee and the ways God spoke through him this morning.  Amazing message!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much expectation for what God will do in this place today. https://t.co/MDjT3sGWxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So honored to celebrate with these two heroes.  Love you both, Dan &amp; Kellie! https://t.co/vT7BiIPJJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She'll always be my favorite wedding date! https://t.co/hBS04EIiGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to have @will_mcgee speaking tomorrow at Restoration City - great pastor and friend who's doing amazing things in Brooklyn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This right here is why we love meeting at Gunston.  We're for the glory of God and the good of… https://t.co/wEouxvA3wh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're free between 9.30 - 11.30 tomorrow morning, please help us come paint at Gunston.  Info &amp; sign-up: https://t.co/SnoxMLnQ7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City, we have amazing opportunities to serve Gunston these next two weeks - don't miss out!  https://t.co/Jqw1XBG0M5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura, it may not have been the best cake you've ever had but I promise it was made with a lot… https://t.co/yF38ayav6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, babe! You are joyful, loving, generous, encouraging, hard working and amazingly… https://t.co/tkx8F0dQYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commit to the daily nourishing of your soul.  It'll affect everything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't hear anything more astonishing or encouraging today than this - you matter to God! https://t.co/mnqNBvAMvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate missing Restoration City today but love what God is going to say through @dan_iten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of our souls thirst but not all of them are ever satisfied. https://t.co/ji8om98DVU https://t.co/JsYzc1sGKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about extraordinary. Focus on intentional in the ordinary. https://t.co/D8meAhMxmb https://t.co/rQm8X25lsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite place, favorite time of day. @ Henderson Harbor, Lake Ontario https://t.co/rLjICjqfCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church planting is a marathon, not a sprint.  Prepare accordingly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The strongest people I know are the ones who are most comfortable with their weakness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me &amp; @WorldRelief in asking @POTUS &amp; world leaders to take meaningful action at tomorrow's Refugee Summit: https://t.co/UORuBSt2EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preaching is a battle we fight on our knees long before we ever do on a stage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great morning with our Communuty Group Leaders - amazing servants, leaders and shepherds!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Withholding forgiveness is choosing to punish yourself for someone else’s sin. There’s freedom in forgiveness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three years ago, I came to this spot to film a video describing a church Laura and I could only… https://t.co/EMFHpIhJR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to make progress? Steward your attention according to your priorities not everyone else's demands. #Leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t let comparison cause you to doubt God’s goodness or the wisdom of His plan for you. He knows what He’s doing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how I see God shaping this fall at Restoration City:  https://t.co/F6oKu0xKJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the start of "Two Ways To Miss God" this past Sunday?  Catch the podcast here: https://t.co/y6fAHuc3CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worship is the great antidote to worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing up. https://t.co/SHI505JzYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep thinking about everything God did yesterday at Restoration City and smiling.  Absolutely love watching Jesus build His church!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonding. @ Homestead Farm https://t.co/jWN3KswisK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone else's sin is never an excuse for yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days like today are what we dreamed about in planting Restoration City! https://t.co/gnxNXHCE77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying the gospel comes “not only in word, but also in power and in the Holy Spirit and with full conviction” today at RCC. (1Thess1:5)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge day ahead tomorrow at Restoration City as we kick off this series.  Plus, we're celebrating… https://t.co/rh3nLSfGdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passive-aggressive is the least attractive form of insecure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @rocketrepublic for bringing https://t.co/jpdwNqDI54 to life.  Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership: inspiring and equipping others to achieve a common goal.  If that's not what you're doing, you're not leading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new home on the web: https://t.co/jpdwNqDI54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in Herndon/Reston/Dulles?  Check out what God is doing through the planting of Grace Hill Church. https://t.co/yZIutGUGcF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>