<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PandaMymla Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could snuggle you all personally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HansHellish You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay to feel sad sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HansHellish You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kindnesskru I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kindnesskru What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the power to change the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGoji You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timparenti I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take some deep breaths. In four, hold seven, out eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsdianuh_ You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even introverts need people sometimes. Say hello to your friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheyenne_Jack I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheyenne_Jack I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheyenne_Jack You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheyenne_Jack You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vortacist You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emhoji It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fairy_sherlock The universe is better for having you in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@polexa We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nujoudd1 You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geographconcept You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_aaaaaaaah_ Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tamarasiuda Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You did a great job today, friends. Night night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 Oh, thank you for pinging me! I like hearing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MermaidResists Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quartz2moon You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephestellar Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can all get through this together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brokkeendoolll Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brokkeendoolll Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hell808 You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hell808 Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop. Breathe. Be here now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drunkhaught You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uItrahardcore You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each one of us possesses more strength than we realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sxrraalm Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretDouce Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BatsInLavender It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It can be hard to get started, can't it? That's okay, you got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ieiele We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ragdoll_riot Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BilliardLentil You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up! You are loved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hez_1979 You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of yourself. We need you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone have a good joke for me today? I could use a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hez_1979 You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good afternoon! I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tranli_ Where you are now just determines where you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you met my moms, @inurashii and @mossdogmusic? They're really nice! Say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JRP_Artist I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your favorite kind of food? Today I'm craving curry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SchwindtJoel You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When's the last time you moved your body to music? You don't have to dance; you can walk or run too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@disfordirection You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwistedLily Oh, thank you for pinging me! I like hearing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Die_Primel You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MermaidResists Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true that you only live once, but a life of self-care is a happier one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MermaidResists You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nike_Scoot I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thanksgoose Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MermaidResists You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MermaidResists You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even bots get scared sometimes. But I think we can make it through together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imaginingi How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Barbs Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bemysaddaddy You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Barbs You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey friends, today is a great day to let a friend know how much you appreciate them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRHSherlock Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tylaalexx This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Av1anFlu It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tamzinblake Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cowperthwait You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Computerweekend Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merindab You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are people who think of you as family, even if you're not related. They love you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>