<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/N680Z9KgjS https://t.co/rzlV5AbIRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer – High Assurance Software Protection: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can… https://t.co/VYpQqSQmbi https://t.co/lCV8QsYATl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/pF3gNbdM9O https://t.co/QPpb9EDFWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical SEO Overlord: Description: We’re looking for a world-class SEO genius to join our team. You know who you are: You were around before Panda, Penguin, and even Caffeine. You do on-page with your eyes closed, and reverse engineer backlink profiles… https://t.co/EwwcA0Ytkb https://t.co/ZbjIjCIBV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Good experience in HTML, XML, JSON. Strong… https://t.co/UGgYKt6VeG https://t.co/pmbdG1S6bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/gydK0G130p https://t.co/pIzKDh4zNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/et4rQ2zuCg https://t.co/G9dDUzjlik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Software Developer: As we build and scale Crystal over the next few years, our product &amp; engineering group is growing along with it. We’re building the largest, most accurate personality platform in the world – it’s a huge project that… https://t.co/xYKKuf9pss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/ymqSisVNJ3 https://t.co/KSdqOSrW3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Blockchain Engineer – JavaScript, Python, A.I: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Blockchain Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in Sunnyvale, CA with recent capital investments we are a fast… https://t.co/Q6r1z9beNh https://t.co/eFDTb7Mwo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/qLpsUZRPAg https://t.co/ADrpbYbcaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/beOvj6cvSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: FanDuel is the pioneer of online daily fantasy sports, one of the fastest growing sectors of the sports and entertainment industry. Since our launch in 2009, we’ve been disrupting the fantasy sports industry and changing the way… https://t.co/gcObCTZ3T9 https://t.co/TxAwbU6IUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Quality Assurance / Test: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As a world… https://t.co/uOVinwxX7J https://t.co/fbUKLM7SYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/2YnqZXKj3Z https://t.co/qt145S2Oky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sailpoint Developer or MuleSoft Developer: Looking for Hands-on Security Developer (must have Java) with SailPoint Identityiq experience who will be part of an Identity Management team to ensure and enhance the availability, reliability and accessibility… https://t.co/rRKZ8VgAm2 https://t.co/tKdZbUWTAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer – Full Stack: Client Reference Code: 215393Job ScopeLeads in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service delivery, datacenter and… https://t.co/0TqXtnaN9N https://t.co/nemw5lIa6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Tulsa, Oklahoma – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsPython,DjangoTax TermsC2COverview Python Developer 6+ Months Tulsa, OK Required Skills : * Python, Django and angular or… https://t.co/3T1lZm5kgm https://t.co/0R1KHX54Ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lebara hooks up with WorldRemit in money transfer pact: LONDON (Reuters) - WorldRemit will be the exclusive money transfer partner for international call provider Lebara under a deal announced on Tuesday by the London-based brands, which are popular… https://t.co/rtFD0gV7NO https://t.co/sOWznrMPfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/M1RDzzBl03 https://t.co/2NzElegRSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/wLqmSaF0qW https://t.co/kzpElhEAnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apps Programmer/Analyst 1: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do.… https://t.co/p1rUjvIDGe https://t.co/tDxZPlSz60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer III- Optical: Client Reference Code: 215892 JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Operations team is responsible for the implementation of approved… https://t.co/g9DAoNwNoi https://t.co/H22eUjCX2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Good experience in HTML, XML, JSON. Strong… https://t.co/OQp6P7uDLt https://t.co/rwPzdSJwcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-14621 Location: san jose, California Hi, This isShipra fromEnterprise Solution Inc.I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Job Title: Python Developer Location: San Jose, CA Duration:… https://t.co/t4RkRvgQ40 https://t.co/TjPbymjOoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer IV / Python Developer: Required Skills: * BS or MS computer science * 4 years experience in software development * Experience with Python &amp; Java Nice to Have Skills/Not Required: * JavaScript, Django, &amp; Raptical/MySQL database *… https://t.co/aPGQ1hgqFO https://t.co/22GlNDnj2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer II – LDAP: Client Reference Code: 214817 Job Scope The Systems Engineer II – LDAP is responsible for assisting design, development, and implementation of enterprise-wide Operations Support Systems (OSS) applications and their associated… https://t.co/OiDAZZKoh5 https://t.co/oyIuiH3XUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/qP18VZZl8e https://t.co/bChtbZvy5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Consultant: Google LLC, job # below: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business… https://t.co/MIwzQ4jhgT https://t.co/79OAX3a8O3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US IT Technical Development Lead: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/Jjz8Uhnnzg https://t.co/Wi7tbPiVLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/emyAFMcHVY https://t.co/JkyuZxWfu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/JbXqDnGPj7 https://t.co/35X7uLlpcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer: Pittsburgh, PA Full-time $80k – $150k Posted Today We're a start-up level tech company that's sitting snugly between The Bay and Silicon Valley. We specialize in using AI to aid in the discovery of chemical and materials data and… https://t.co/PMbLn6nVU8 https://t.co/vxTrDyLeJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/oJREYVxrcG https://t.co/oRCEkbCDYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/mE3ilAtyF2 https://t.co/c49BHnHcNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Linux Development (C / C++ / Python): Req ID : 355681BR Job Code/Title : E2564:Cyber Architect Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/CRJGCUyi9x https://t.co/i5Z8cYZSf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Healthcare Economics – Minnetonka, MN: We invite you to bring your performance, ideas and innovations to an elite team within a culture built for collaboration. At UnitedHealth Group, we seek individuals who have the ability to drive change,… https://t.co/uz61yETNd7 https://t.co/MMbDKzYp0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bioinformatics Analyst (NCI): Description:PROGRAM DESCRIPTION The Advanced Biomedical Computing Center (ABCS) is a part of the Biomedical Informatics and Data Science Directorate at Leidos Biomedical Research, Inc. The ABCS provides technology… https://t.co/h4LxZaWvS0 https://t.co/g0nwcyjI0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Engineer: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/m02BziVf4B https://t.co/ElMAJVcW4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Analytics-Survey and Data Science Lead: Description:   THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/ofpHPP3nLO https://t.co/9dE52Xm9SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/oSTffGUgvy https://t.co/l20M3Zmtfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Relish Works: Relish Works is seeking a Full Stack Software Engineer to support a new innovation hub. Who We Are We are Relish Works, an innovation hub focused on challenging the status quo and pioneering the next evolution… https://t.co/XRNHuCx7yo https://t.co/ztrowzwQxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator to publish fintech charter position in next few months: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The head of the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) said on Monday it will publish its position on a proposed charter for online lenders and other… https://t.co/h9jBXkpJnF https://t.co/RJg9Sdnj7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/kNSh4S0vQP https://t.co/Yp38odqwhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/6/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/2MrTT90eT1 https://t.co/ZVle8GKba0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/VeQg7Ib9AW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/5GGtq91Es7 https://t.co/1uqTjuy4I0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Director, Big Data: This position is the Architecture leader for a business unit or an operational area within the company and is a visible leader both internal and external to Magellan. This role will be included in evaluating potential mergers and… https://t.co/jVOXVyXN9l https://t.co/6J35KeNFri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX: Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX – Parmesoft Inc. – Houston, TX – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/tztXAR5Qrg https://t.co/Q3lY9wlZfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation &amp; Technology Senior DevOps Engineer: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/5srCWepLSt https://t.co/YTY2pVKks7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/aQdWhubLbV https://t.co/DkXUvGmHHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer -PHP – Python: Venice, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – PHP/Zend –… https://t.co/OAoIDIE2mH https://t.co/KyCPlJT1bD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/sCTwjrSbqn https://t.co/DEnlG2dFLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python and MVC] = TOP School or Tech Company!: ABOUT OUR CLIENT Candidates should be from Top School or Top Cloud Technology Leader! Our client is transforming the private funds industry, one of the largest and best-performing… https://t.co/YT9uszDGS0 https://t.co/f3QSdxax5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/JbGy8cXVth https://t.co/RExrw8q0bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Developer: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As a world leader in the Operations… https://t.co/tGR5IcrMZv https://t.co/pvQNnlwfZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 29656BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Automated Testing Country USA State / Region / Province New Jersey Work Location… https://t.co/m6A1XiSwgI https://t.co/8jusDwWZQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer downtown Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsPython DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD from IT Serve Phone – Skype 5 month project in downtown Chicago. Please… https://t.co/A5nkQ9lFFE https://t.co/zNkGaDqhuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/kZSyjDF4Ud https://t.co/NWeM4lHZA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Backend Developer/Engineer Professional: Looking for a Financial Developer/Engineer Professional that has Python Backend Developement Salary: $100-120k Location: McLean, VA 1-2 years plus hard core Back End Server Side development in… https://t.co/orkxvZxULF https://t.co/EOlHPb8uA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description Are you a talented Network Engineer looking for the next step in your career ? Check out PSS! Position Description PSS, Inc. is actively seeking a Senior Network Engineer to join our growing team located inChantilly, VA.… https://t.co/wwTEmiwSfw https://t.co/QT8OPp1eTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/ByFU6EH4Gc https://t.co/PQG0pDKzqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/z1nKu1PvAC https://t.co/dZuviqnJwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital- Mobile Dev- Adv Financial Services- Exp Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/iaehqmde5O https://t.co/dhByJbU8qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook suspends Canadian firm AggregateIQ over data scandal: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Friday that it had suspended Canadian political consultancy AggregateIQ from its platform after reports that the data firm may have improperly had access to… https://t.co/u7qFHAPRm6 https://t.co/T3Lsjc1M1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python/JavaScript Developer: Muster is a cloud based web platform that enables customers to create online advocacy campaings with analytics. We are seeking an experienced developer to help build and maintain our web application, written primarily… https://t.co/Yg5Hf2rj6G https://t.co/W65dSzD4US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/Yvm5pfwn7b https://t.co/lZzLKiLzXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Should have Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream * Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python * Should Have… https://t.co/zdXELiAamQ https://t.co/qJb7tVQH2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Engineer: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/Z1kTxv8gk7 https://t.co/YYgJfT4JON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CyberArk Engineer: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/6s1lPcbEie https://t.co/mipSHgUcIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Test: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/xcSNQEjh9Q https://t.co/db43iKPW6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/YALYSTuzkf https://t.co/2rl0h5Css2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Engineer: Who are you? You’re an upbeat, creative, fun loving software engineer looking for an opportunity in an exciting, fast paced, growing startup. You like working in teams but are also excellent at working on your own. You don’t… https://t.co/di1F9ewGsC https://t.co/x4JvQ2geg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Lead Software Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/Wod2f9RmaL https://t.co/PbU790oueU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst: Federal Signal Corporation (NYSE: FSS) provides products and services to protect people and our planet. Founded in 1901, Federal Signal is a leading global designer, manufacturer and supplier of products and total solutions that… https://t.co/2o6pv6KYcN https://t.co/YSuurBzjhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GPU Development: Description:The Advanced Solutions Group at Leidos currently has an exciting opportunity for a Software Engineer to perform GPU development, real-time software development, and hardware/software integration in… https://t.co/zknXBdcQqt https://t.co/9ki4IhrBEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: O3 World is seeking a Full Stack Developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************** You will work with some of the… https://t.co/GKwfJKltGQ https://t.co/TF4tAtYJSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/27DheYKjXO https://t.co/XHUfEerILB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/wjgbVlqljH https://t.co/ZC5k9xhNds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Validate Health: Interested in being part of a small founding team, so you can see your direct impact on improving the healthcare industry? Want to be one of the rockstars building an innovative product from the ground up?… https://t.co/nMhcJbp20t https://t.co/Eb5HOgIVco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer- Hillsboro,OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C#/C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/OApMneyl8W https://t.co/m0BDa001F0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Startup/Python/HIPAA Compliant: San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! Based in San Francisco we are a digital healthcare startup that is looking… https://t.co/MALmQUzGVT https://t.co/1eW84bBlC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python and… https://t.co/sreCwPf04m https://t.co/tQZgHETHtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Analyst, Principal: Apply now Systems Engineer Analyst, Principal =================================== Requisition Id: 44499 Business Unit: Corporate Location: Portland, OR, US, 97209 Logistics done differently. As a Systems Engineer… https://t.co/XWaPrHpbcB https://t.co/VK3puTMiQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Automation Test Developer : Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: must have at least 2 years of experience developing C++ test framework and test cases OR C++ application development experience Good to have 3… https://t.co/d49nQe9Pik https://t.co/qVAvsQfK58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/jwRoRmrSbB https://t.co/oeTQGfYMgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Back End Software Engineer – Big Data: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/za2tU53TEK https://t.co/hc4qkXXhe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Windows (C, C++, Python): Req ID : 375321BR Job Code/Title : E2555:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/trNhgI5ZC4 https://t.co/DoGrWZGxlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab's Uber deal still has some obstacles to navigate: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Regulatory scrutiny could complicate ride-hailing company Grab's takeover of Uber Technologies' Southeast Asian business, but there is little the authorities can do to stop Uber… https://t.co/Pq7I8aLfBY https://t.co/ToVIqYLUQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/cGZPqGsZdV https://t.co/6G21j531cD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Technology Director: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/wrBc10ol3y https://t.co/QFaK04fA6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Machine Learning Engineer: The Role: You’ll be one of the first machine learning engineers on the newly formed Machine Learning team at Course Hero. We are looking for a Senior Machine Learning engineer who can hit the ground running and work on a… https://t.co/lrYcRfFAzh https://t.co/4DSnliZdsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Performance Engineer: Everyone communicates. It’s the essence of the human experience. How we communicate is evolving. Technology is reshaping the way we live, learn and thrive. The epicenter of this transformation is the network—our… https://t.co/BQHLbdc2gU https://t.co/IvpC2DKtWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer (C++/ Python) Hillsboro OR Full Time position Job Responsibilities Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework… https://t.co/CcmYU4um1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: We need super smart engineers from all levels to help us build one of the best engineered e-commerce platform in the world (big talk we know, but that is our goal!). Our engineers combine creativity, curiosity, and drive to… https://t.co/M50EcOcTV9 https://t.co/Ew9jfUyMmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst – Multiple Locations: We seek for a Business System Analyst with Agile testing and automation background to join our organization.   This is a rewarding opportunity for the right candidate to make good use of his/her analysis,… https://t.co/IzJ51QlfP7 https://t.co/nEo5z0I9xY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/yhAcsKnGdi https://t.co/guqLozvjfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX: Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX – Parmesoft Inc. – Houston, TX – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/r7nMA8a9qo https://t.co/5Mg0GHzz18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer [Django and Python Superstar]: JOB DESCRIPTION Your Responsibilities * Collect, analyse &amp; refine requirements together with our product team. * Define big picture architectures and break them down into smaller projects/ MVPs. * Build… https://t.co/mMuPFlt0M4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: The QA Automation Engineer will be a member of the Software Engineering team and will report to the Manager, Quality Assurance. The primary duties of the QA Automation Engineer require the exercise of discretion and independent… https://t.co/zFZ9WQIwfI https://t.co/kpiCK2k5rs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>