<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“@SportsNation: Instead of "It's all about the U," Miami's new slogan should be _____” &gt; "We used $$ to get playas and still sucked ass"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeamRickPerry: .@GovernorPerry: "Page one of any economic plan to get America working is to give a pink slip to the current resident ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeamRickPerry: .@GovernorPerry: "We don’t need a president who apologizes for America…we need a president who protects and projects  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cwall1313 Yeah Buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, if you help me get over 100 please! “@mortreport: OK, let's push @jerryrice over 100,000 followers before midnight.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You forgot: C - What's the UFL? “@darrenrovell: POLL: Will this be the UFL's last season? A-YES, B-NO”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DR-Drop-SW-SW. hahaha “@nikegolf: Nike's Anthony Kim hit his VR Pro 2-hybrid to 2ft from the pin on the par-3 265 15th...what would hit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fav Airline - Since MW is gone and thus not serving warm cookies @TheFix: An early win for Iowa trip. AirTran has wifi onboard. USA! USA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No…I think its finished.  Oh so finished.  @WestWingReport: At fundraiser, President says his administration is an “unfinished project;”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hows that treating ya? @drewhenson7 &gt; @BreakingNews: Texas sets electricity usage record for 3rd straight day; Dallas hits 109.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ascot... @TheFix:I am in the market for a new tie knot. The half Windsor has run its course. Recommendations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffBurr "So far" is key…he has a year of campaigning to blow that out of the water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriFleischer: 68% of R freshman (59/87) voted 4 deal. So did 50% of Ds (95/190). So which party has more "xtremists" who won't compr ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden thinks you're a terrorist “@GeoffBurr: I'm just gonna put this out there: I don't get the appeal of Shark Week.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewhenson7 - well well well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Krugman creeps me out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Pres_Bartlet: "Tweet your Congressman" isn't the act of a President. It's the act of a #BigBlockOfCheeseDay group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[keep em Healthy! @jschwartzlions: Sorry we had to take practice indoors, Lions fans - it was too slick outside, we didn't want guys sliding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please ignore the dancing monkey-gram that's headed your way then.... @echriqui:Guys it's not my birthday! Mine is December 10th..lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@directv Can't have a dish at my place...any updates on Sunday Ticket for iPad or Apple TV for us sad souls who cant get the service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope, firewood still less &gt; @darrenrovell: Anyone? Bueller? Bueller? RT @dcsportsbog The Redskins are selling Haynesworth jerseys for $9.95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["LUCK-Y" @GeoffBurr Albert and McNabb gone, 14 WRs on the roster and the comedic stylings of John Beck under center. 2 and 14 here we come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogRadio: Dino - FYI - 6 months is the end of January. #KaplanFail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, even DC letting peeps keep more of their own $$ - DC has $245M in unpaid tix. On 8/1 drivers can pay off tickets sans late fees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Yeah...forgot about that &gt; Government Shutdown Looms in the Fall : Roll Call News http://t.co/XqhUqju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@groupon &gt; Any chance we can get an "80% off your nat'l debt" deal. We'll buy two. No doubt we use those before they expire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously...? FAIL in ATL “@CNNLive: House Majority Leader John Boehner holds a briefing to discuss the ongoing debt ceiling issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennThrush: The leader of the free world -- cut out of direct talks with GOP -- is appealing to constituents to call their reps. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ohiogop: DONT FORGET: just 3 months ago President Obama pushed for a CLEAN debt ceiling increase. No spending cuts, no reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need u on RCN in DC! @bigtenconf  Good news! RT @BigTenNetwork: Time Warner Cable moving BTN to standard service tier for Nebraska customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brady Anderson was just tipping juiced $10 bills “@darrenrovell: RT @ek1320]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kenvogel: RT @lhfang: RT @GingeeDC: At Tiffanys trying on wedding bands, and who walks in @newtgingrich and Callista. I am not makin ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's really annoying &gt; “@SI_PeterKing: No "Hard Knocks" this year. I repeat: No "Hard Knocks."”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cat at 1600 keeps saying his offer on debt is generous...hey guy...that's our dough you are being SO generous with. #needsareminder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama playing serious politics of fear saying House GOP responsible if Gov't checks don't go out to seniors and veterans in August.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got that 4 sum1 else I hope “@TheFix: Bad: Me ordering a hot cinnamon dolce latte today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a migraine from reading about migraines....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey DC interns. Quit walking behind @mortreport. If u can't resist...get him and George a beer. They've been out there for hours. #damnhot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NavGlobal: 3...2...1...“@PoliticalTicker: Perry blasts off on end of shuttle program - http://t.co/d3zneFJ”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching these college kids at PSU on TV makes me want to call my parents and ask how big an ass I was when I was that age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@drewhenson7: Worst CFB scandal ever...” Easily. Goes so much deeper than just football. Lives ruined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@LuISmyname213: And how does @espn not have a camera there?” &gt; no kidding. Isn't this what they do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell...headlines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that was brutal...“@murphymike: Hunts should have just done the whole 30 seconds in Chinese.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was praying to Tebow for $30M over 10 years &gt; “@HotlineReid: Pujols totally Tebowed after the last out.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogUnleashed &gt; VanPelt took a shot at the doggie to close his show!  Flipped over during commercial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMikeRogers ...welcome to the twitterverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@ErinAndrews: Well hello chilly East Lansing...#mercy” Its the college town of college towns, EA!  a burger at the Peanut Barrel will help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hurtful, but funny. “@RobStutzman: Breaking News! Miguel Cabrera has been spotted approaching home plate! #postseason”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[co-sign “@HotlineReid: Why is my Facebook overrun with other people posting photos of stupid things? How do I make it stop?”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Some! “@DetroitLionsNFL: The @MNF_on_ESPN bus has arrived. #Lions http://t.co/mKRD6Ox3” #Lions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JayTurk33: @Buster_ESPN your an idiot”...clearly aced grammar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought u said in all seriousness “@chucktodd: In all seriousness, Palin is speaking at the "World Knowledge Forum" next Tuesday in Seoul.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Conner pls call ur office “@joshjonsmith: Is this when they take over? RT @dangerroom: Exclusive: Computer Virus Hits U.S. Drone Fleet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Snap &gt; Romney: "If you do not want America to be the strongest nation on Earth, I am not your president. You have that president today."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@BobbyHonold: I mean: "Trade Rod"” ...you spell like he bats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogUnleashed &gt; any Papa Grande Valverde love now from you and Torre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha!  A-Rod!  #Tigers #ALCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathing again. Sorta. #Tigers #ALDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sensing a little pucker pucker pucker...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Green! “@mikeallen: help @mark_miner (Michigan State) come back strong in folllower derby w/ @tweetrobjohnson (SMU)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Highlights of TBS ALDS coverage...Big Bang Theory Commercials and the @ConanOBrien blimp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verlander = Dealing. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogUnleashed - Ultimate salt in wound last night...Crawford made Rays lower the fence that Longoria "double" went over last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good “@nickschaper: Granted, I've only seen a small portion of the universe, but Jimmy John's is one of the best sandwich chains in it.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConanOBrien: A new book claims Sarah Palin had sex with NBA star Glen Rice.  That’s where she got the phrase, “Drill, Baby, Drill.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell on earth. The DC DMV....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@NDmom: Dam u Tom Rinaldi”…EA got me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFix: Zero jobs created in August. President Obama, call your office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dickie V is Butt Tweeting BAAAABY!!!!! “@DickieV: 0Yp090”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Spain if your local affiliate switches to Hurricane coverage, they will let you know which channel the race will be on...via @NASCAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MGolicJR57: That is the funniest thing ive ever seen. RT @DPFoxy: Everyone needs to follow @oldmansearch Just read the bio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just went all super dork when I read this. “@TFLAMB: Michael Bay Directing Transformers 4; Release Date: 6/29/2014 http://t.co/qnBy6HWK”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@dawsonry23: @KyleKizzier_DC Baller! Where u going?” &gt; at Hill Country for some bluegrass. Get some!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out for a cruise with my man Zahid from @Uber_DC. #über]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santorum lands the very difficult simultaneous double junk kick. #CNNdebate #fldebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio!!! Drink x2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt to control border simply by laying down. That tummy is way taller than the fence. 

I can say that. I have a big tummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santorum in sh*t kickers. I'm down with that. And he brought his mom. Mom's rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamVerdugo: GOP Strategist Mike Murphy's (@murphymike) highlight reel from Sunday's @meetthepress -- Top "Murphyisms" http://t.co/e ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My only beef with Mitch's response was the volume of his shirt. SNAP - that joint is loud!

#GOPresponse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh. God. Please don't have me up here next year staring at Newt's hind end for 3 hours. #boehnerthoughtbubble #sotu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame Bush!!!  DRINK FOOLS!  #SOTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dude is talking about red tape like he isn't the one who keeps a big ass roll of it in his desk.... #KEYSTONE #sotu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is pretty cool to watch the faces of the folks POTUS talks about. Their expressions are priceless. #sotu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheFix: John Kerry thought bubble: "That could, wait, should, have been me up there." #sotu” &gt; same thought bubble as 80 other Sens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest Gen. OBL Dead. Military Great. China Bad. Ohio. Wisconsin. Michigan. Me. I. My.

Anyone else feel like its a campaign stop? #SOTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ménage-a-Newt/Paul/Santo...Icky. #fldebate #nbcdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[softball....“@grantbosse: CBS News now tweeting that Fidel Castro has died. #FLdebate”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya know. My mom is watching this. If we could keep being a lobbyist just this side of being  a Manson it will make holidays a lot easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I guess if I call you an a-hole I am calling you a friend? @RobStutzman: “@dtoddharris: "Friend" is Washington Speak for "Asshole"”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrewStoren: Over/Under 14 minutes for Ed Hercules to explain OT rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt is scary. Scary good. Scary bad. #CNNdebate #Gingrich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HotlineReid: I cannot handle the speed of my Twitter feed right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucktodd make sure to kill apps running in background. Turn off searching for wifi. Also disable game center in settings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobStutzman so you were "feeling pretty good" about that win I'm sure. Too bad there's no Fayo in Elk Grove to celebrate at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe...what I just saw. #49ers #Saints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markschlereth: Tell me Oline isn't a skill position did you see how fast Staley was running, 20 yards down field cutting down a DB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Drew Tebow time... #Saints  #49ers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a call.... #49ers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>