<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/rBqJT4iIAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/T4z0lUqMkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/lAPQou2yja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/qegzRFUZux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/5XtzhzNgk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/H4leU8ACwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/U6dwd9IrFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/fte8HopdPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/YHsi6SRRwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/SR7WASTBbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/tmAWKvoaKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/A3XdHaDoDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/a7nlwmnZeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/xqwLUk9Yt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/rdfccgWY74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/pq2V8Zf8wH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/cMrR7reI4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/aaM0apLe6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/Lss3uBDqio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/i6YX8fvNX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/BDufunfaH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/nceArSEtVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/YvwvkBQLIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/aCw3igwv2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6IUJZkcQWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/xlYDoWbdDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/KYvavhcrxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/QlrKnthB4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/l6vlLaJvjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/ecAzN04xUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/TrKm9tFGen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/mueDZMPvzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/msF2yvmSuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/e27jcF8GqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/gy7W35u4qM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/2UMGC7zAMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/LZtP0sdh4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/anriMtQfOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/qaMH9kvd5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/oDGn7xemDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/NUrYunWSWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/nsfjIOubk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/h8RFB4UBRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/aX8WeXxaA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/3JG0uKH2XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/h8e1cov7Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/8wks2ONhcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/nBEhdSsQwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/6qGbuptgRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/QlrKnthB4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/ubkQHdKMJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/15ufwDyh8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>