<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I don t want to be Romeo and iet, prince charming and Cinderella, or even Ken and Barbie. I want us to make our own story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love me or leave me, but I m not going to stay here and let you disrespect me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2If a girl ever steals your man, there is no better revenge than to let her keep him. REAL MEN can t be stolen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To change the future, change your choices. Keep giving the same, keep getting the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when someone says, "You two should go out!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he says those 3 words to you in front of his friends... it s true love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me you love me because you mean it, not because you want to hear it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst feeling in the world is when you know you re losing someone and there s nothing that you can do to prevent being replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m dying to talk to you, but I refuse to text you first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I m invisible to you now? That s cool. I ve always wanted a superpower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never leave something good to find something better, because once you realize you had the best, the best has found better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I laid there on his chest, listening to his heart beat, I knew at that moment that I loved him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes never lie, even when the lips do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to get knocked down lower than you have ever been before to stand back up taller than you ever were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dunno why they call it heartbreak.. It feels like every part of your body is BROKEN too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You re the reason I check my phone every five minutes. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is BOTH pain and beauty. But if the relationship mostly consists of pain, then it s not called Love. It s just a burden to the heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We fight like a married couple, talk like best friends, flirt like 1st loves, &amp; protect each other like siblings. Face it, we re meant to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fool me once, shame on you. Fool me twice, shame on me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1Look clearly at your life and commit to letting go of whatever is holding you back including toxic habits, emotions, and relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest thing about knowing you don t love me, is that you spent so much time pretending that you did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ignore a person who loves and cares for you, cause one day you may realize that you ve lost the moon while counting the stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the worst feelings is when you show a person how much you love them by your actions.. And they don t show the love back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when i look into your eyes, i know that everything is okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play your games and have your fun, just don t expect me to be here when you re done...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sad thing in life is when you meet someone who means a lot to you, only to find out in the end that it was never meant to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sucks that you cheated on her before understanding that she was the one for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you meet someone special...you ll know. Your heart will beat more rapidly and you ll smile for no reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2Don t you love when someone can make you smile over a text message? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sucks because you didn t even give me at least HALF the love I gave to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know how I know I m not over you? I still wonder what it would be like if you came back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ll gladly let my guard down when people stop giving me reasons to keep it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He isn t my boyfriend, but I love his hugs, smile, advice, kindness, &amp; the times we laugh together. I just fell in love with our friendship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m not saying gentlemen are extinct, I m just saying they are an endangered species...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No relationship is all sunshine...but two people can share one umbrella if they huddle real close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn t make things easier... just worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you have to wait for something, the more you will appreciate it when it finally arrives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he really meant it when he said "I love you", you wouldn t be single right now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, treat your girls right when you have them because you may never be able to get them back once they leave no matter how hard you try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have so much love to give, but no one to give it to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 reasons to read 50 Shades of Grey ==&gt; http://t.co/p3Nk7K1NTM - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile is the best way to keep your lips in shape for the kiss that might follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all the things in life I've lost, I miss my mind the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are almost 7 billion people in the world. So why do I only want you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our conversations never last long, after awhile we run out of things to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am someone who is looking for love...real love...ridiculous, inconvient, consuming, can't-live-without-each-other love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though you broke my heart... deep down I really still love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the facts and truth can be right in front of your face, but no matter what, you refuse to accept any of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were a dream. Then a reality. Then a nightmare. Now a memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smart female would rather be single than to be lied to, cheated on, and disrespected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no love without forgiveness, and there is no forgiveness without love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you lie there at night do you ever still think of me Questions like this are what keep me holding on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was told, "If you don t have anything nice to say, don t say anything at all..."And some people wonder why I m so quiet around them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All things come to an eventual end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ThingsThatDontMakeSense love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to get over someone after they've gotten under your skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a great thing, especially when it's in your heart and not on your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I wish that someday love will lead you back to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's always that one special person that no matter they do to you, you just can't let them go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowhere on your birth certificate did it say life would be fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sucks because you didn t even give me at least HALF the love I gave to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't regret meeting you, I don't regret loving you. I only regret not fighting enough for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes guts to fall in love. But it takes nerve to go back to the one who broke you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like clouds. When they disappear, it's a brighter day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is, you had my heart from the first time you made me smile...It just took me awhile to realzie it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday we will meet again. When we have our second chance at love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing your eyes while something is loading and hoping that it will finish when you open. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ability to live is the rarest gift. No matter how life disappoints you, overcome it. Because you are given an option to survive. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we fail to appreciate the things that we already have because we are trying to look hard on the things that we don t have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to think I was special until I noticed you talk to everyone like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I was finally going to get my happily ever after...then reality hit and reminded me that they don't exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It hurts when you have someone in your heart, but you can't have them in your arms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of all this non-existent bullshit my mind makes up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have had my heart broken so many times it's % glue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish there's a way to photoshop my face... Literally. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're fighting for love, doesn't it mean you've already lost it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are settling down, some are settling and some people refuse to settle for anything less. Than butterflies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move on. Its just another chapter in the past. Don't close the book. Just turn the page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what makes letting go of a crush so hard The fear that the minute you let go... they'll catch on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That super sexy face you make when you try to hold back a sneeze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think about your past or future if they just distract your present. The most important thing is to enjoy your present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never stop believing in who I am. I will never change myself for another person. I will always respect and adore who I am. I AM ME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather beat my remote to make it work, rather than change the batteries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes life throws at us the unexpected. You either learn to roll with the punches or get knocked down by them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have an attitude problem, you have a problem with my attitude. That's your problem, not mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If something is not happening for you it does not mean it s never going to; it just means that you re not ready for it yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are hard to find, difficult to leave and impossible to forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every day, I miss you. For every hour, I need you. For every minute, I feel you. For every second, I want you. Forever, I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how perfectly I place my earpieces, they always end up getting entangled together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to think that if I loved you enough you would realize it and love me back, but I can only love so much for so long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not compare what you are best at, compare what you are worst at, and win it. Then only you are a true winner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing how one little conversation can change things forever. #ThatsLove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like an open book. You have to keep turning new pages and growing into new chapters and just hope for a happy ending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let your past dictate who you are, but let it be a part of who you will become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you like penguins! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many times do I have to fall and get hurt until that one guy catches me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something about you is so addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind every player is a girl that broke his heart, behind every bitch is a guy that tore her apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT moment when you hear something that completely breaks your heart to pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you really love a person you just don't give up... in your mind you wanna give up, but in your heart you just cant..]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>