<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's get coutinho to score then win 2-0 I will be happy. Come on #Reddders #lfcfamily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody MNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've fallen in love with Olive Bread.... It's bloody gorge.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @escapeartistes: Best Daily Mail comment ever. Feel free to upvote. http://t.co/o4TgBRaUia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the game tonight! Let's get at them and win this #LFC #lfcfamily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wallaceme: Via @mikeysmith, even ISIS nutjobs leave passive aggressive notes in the kitchen at work. http://t.co/aWdrqUukDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easiest way to share large files? Free of course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way to upload music and not soundcloud?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Traktors a piece of kit then init!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FREE_bets: Football stars at the Cheltenham races 2015... Brilliant once again from the talented @DFImpressionist

https://t.co/RWbFtXj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually like a #Blur song well I never..... Think it's because ol Coxon is driving this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zodman100: Falcao playing in the #MUFC U21s tonight was subbed for showing the kids his worldclass skills.... https://t.co/JTuwGdvxbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dwauctioneer: Lot of talk about 3 Muslim girls. No one mentions the 4 radicalised white Christian kids who went abroad to fight with th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartMaconie just had to play the full length version of Sylvester Do you wanna Funk after the show today. Finally dug out the vinyl...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub ok thanks for your help, I will return the one I have back to Leeds store. Rgds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmclark: @JTFShoppingClub hi did your buyer get any news from Sunrain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gumtree'd this if anyone interested?? http://t.co/rRxhBrgaqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good O'l Twitter http://t.co/3zoeS2YTiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat in the cold shed listening to this on scratchy vinyl My Friend Sam Feat Viola Wills - Its My Pleasure (Extended M http://t.co/3xzVHr2nuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub hi did your buyer get any news from Sunrain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheBigPaintingChallenge is almost exactly the same as.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASA @MarsCuriosity concrete dust, Mars could be just a lump of concrete! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReeceShearsmith @BBCRadio4 @RealBobMortimer it wall brilliant too really enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliecullen @Guy_Garvey @garydbales is it me or is Guy slowly turning into Stephen Fry???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndyVoices: If teenage girls want to join Isis then they should leave and never return, says @gracedent http://t.co/iRCz8PZ1FY http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Grimsdale is on #TopGear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jacqueline_Gold: No hiding as police release 3 photos of Chelsea fans they are looking to identify for racist chanting #kickoutracism h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am sure The penalty incident will be taken care of in the dressing room ;) good luck with that !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first units in the O'l Shed ready for??? http://t.co/INnymobYga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub great. Just emailed you, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub thank you so much..... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub by the way if it can go on a 12mm hearth its a great selling point for JTF too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub it depends if the fire heats the base above 100 degree or not most don't but I need to know before I can install. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTFShoppingClub a 12mm hearth is non combustible but i need to know specifically from Sunrain if it's suitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeachyBooks didn't see it, will have another look ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick___Collins must be something in the air, same here! That view from the office helps though.... http://t.co/hwualMnGcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whitby... http://t.co/jRoR7FozHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ySMZI8TFo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive spider in bath the other day now one on wall in bedroom.... #spiderinvasion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy upload stems??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick___Collins know that feeling Nick ..... Still tomorrow brings a new dawn!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's my ear worm expunged on @BBC6Music with cam obs but the chorus about French summat has given me French disco now!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Heaton the Veals nice.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#firstrecord6music here it is haha http://t.co/XyBfkKw2Ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FirstRecord6Music and just as I'm typing here it is..... Spooky!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#firstrecord6music don't remember 1st single but remember going to Woolworths in York and buying... FFS Adam and the ants!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#android #TV #stream #football help please what's a good steam to watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian stream and delayed 5 live on radio..... It works haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BkkGreg: 11-year old tells class that med marijuana might not be all bad, gets detained, mom is arrested, might lose custody. http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SundayShoutsFC @rinit31 what a knob!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#JFT96 #YNWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Burgess oh my.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBcommentator @kartpfi have fun JB and enjoy the car drive home... Feels like your driving a sofa haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kowalski yeah..... Only took £6 haha http://t.co/2kXkudm4I3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win win today 1st a Kowalski on grab machine for youngest now @CCfunkandsoul on radio.  LV these weekends off with family,I don't get many]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won a Kowalski on the grab machine for my daughter and £3 on the national for me.. It's been A Good Day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#101 followers..... Will be back to 90 tomorrow though I bet 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Forster: I NEED empty/not needed tubes of paint for a 3D project. Happy to pay postage :) please RT for #artists http://t.co/0ji0Q…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roscoe Peeeeee Coltraine! http://t.co/TkYXTtWAsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryannehobbs morning Maryanne from a not so misty Leeds today. http://t.co/UXsxh6QBxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckin Awful #TheVoiceUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrjakehumphrey: PLEASE retweet this. It will take you a moment &amp; may save the life of my friends beautiful son
http://t.co/vEXumYZouR h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikewhills: MT @ASE: The photo of the little Syrian girl with her hands raised was actually genuine http://t.co/Elu3qEnVGJ http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Iranianatheist1: http://t.co/OcqZRCQlwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mostly enjoying this...
Andrew Weatherall – 19th March 2015 « NTS RADIO | DON'T ASSUME http://t.co/IgSkd0TD61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@History_Pics didn't know John Pertwee was in the Beatles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stackee @dannywallace @featuresjourno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zodman100: Morning reds. Sturridge, Lallana &amp; Sterling all out of the stupid Internationals. Excellent! #LFC https://t.co/Ex4CA5Jm94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tacwise thanks for your help Tony!
I spoke to Michael and he's sorted out my problem straight away! Very happy....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tacwise hi Ken, still not heard anything it's starting to look like the CS dept is not too good to me..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the FUCK is on itv now!! FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@97MDE that surprises me thought it would be the Chelski!! Although I can see why WH don't like Tots...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@97MDE good win but who's your scum as I see Man Utd were already mentioned ;) please say Chelsea.....!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamHarrisOrg: Crystal clarity from Ayaan Hirsi Ali: http://t.co/DR9De6Qq2F
@AHAFoundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eclipse 2 http://t.co/dQIqCkpjZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eclipse no1 http://t.co/FC9jWtTDAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tacwise great will do thanks....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeasaMelon: 26 years on trying to find out who the man on the right is in pic.He rescued my brother Toby Beasley @HJC_Official http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tacwise hi Im trying to get a spare part but no-one seems to want to talk to me? Ive called and emailed but no reply? Any ideas?? Thnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Okeating: @KitchenNo7 You shouldn't! https://t.co/zh9sy2ZkPd Watch this @jakeyapp sketch. You'll love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arthur_Strong brilliant news!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Arthur_Strong: It's my very great delight to announce that BBBC1 in their finite wisden have commissioned a 3rd series of Count Arthur …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AstroSamantha: So many patterns and shapes drawn on our planet. #ColorsOfTheEarth http://t.co/RkHnnjUs4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tompeck: Luis Figo's withdrawal statement from the Presidential race is quite something. http://t.co/I3stIEqGvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Heaton how many times have we said the club miss managed something! Bye bye Sterling go warm a bench somewhere....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alanferrier: Millionaire Banker, Tory Advisor and member of Countryside Alliance Sir David Scholey. https://t.co/cPNassLJkq http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Distinctboxes certainly is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stop looking at it https://t.co/fl9709G0WV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Distinctboxes wow that is extraordinary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Talk_Yorkshire he'll only last a few months then they'll be into the next one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thereaIbanksy real live zelma from scooby doo haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyKanaan @rinit31 why did we though? Great defender but pod suppose injuries?? Didn't get it myself....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music’s Not For Everyone w/ Andrew Weatherall – 16th April 2015 « NTS RADIO | DON'T ASSUME best show on the web yeah! http://t.co/2KGo6co6dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BSPOfficial hey any news on Sea of Brass shipping yet?? Can't wait to get my copy!!! Thanks G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac has any one suggested Nick cave for pied piper??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recording the game should be home for  half 6 to watch it all. Not looking forward to it tbh..... #LFC #LFCFamily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music only gone and got 2 tickets for Nils and it's my birthday too.... Good stuff!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac ahh I remember hearing Thom Yorke do this live on the Mark and Lard show on the defunct Radio1 great version too.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Charliecondou: I can't stop playing this. Kanye broke character for a quick second but then spotted the camera https://t.co/H6W30emXFj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>