<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["I think fame is nothing in itself, but it can be put to good use – by generating money for charity." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning and dining, drinking and driving, excessive buying, overdosin' dying. On our drugs and our love, and our dreams and our rage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Singles: 'Cola' (Worldwide) and 'Dark Paradise' (in Germany) + the videos! Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me kiss you hard in the pouring rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know what I'm saying, but I'm praying for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to take you out, I don't feel like it's wrong. Me and my momma, we don't get along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo:  http://t.co/oXw3zWM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got that summertime, summertime sadness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be with the man I love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmen, Carmen, staying up till morning. Only seventeen, but she walks the streets so mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use that voice, sing that song and tell me to come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I SING THE BODY ELECTRIC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_LanaDelRey You're welcome! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do you love Lana Del Rey?" — Team Lana: ... http://t.co/6g78Srcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I belong to everybody that I walk by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once I had you, I had everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diamonds on my wrist, whiskey on my tongue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in high school, in the yard, we used to fight. But you would sneak into my window every night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else is gonna put up with me this way? I need you, I breathe you, I'll never leave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my bad baby by my heavenly side I know if I go, I'll die happy tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have you created a life for yourself where you’re free to experience them? I Have." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote Lana at Virgin Media Awards — Best Solo Artist http://t.co/FrcBGAXL | Best Album http://t.co/L0IcPiC5 | Best Video http://t.co/6kCbXxAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Dreamland: An ambitious amusement park at Coney Island — 1905-1911' by Chuck Grant. http://t.co/eY0mCP0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whitman is my daddy, Monaco's my mother, diamonds are my bestest friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cry, honey, crazy girl. Don't you know you are the world? Every time you feel unsure, try to remember what you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel so alone on a friday night. Can you make it feel like home, if I tell you you're mine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey You laugh like god, your mind's like a diamond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should never come between a woman and her dream &amp; a man who never knew his place, there's no easy way to come back from where you came.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The things around me have changed. There are now people who listen to and like my music." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelReyWorld Thank you! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's one of the times when you're feeling electrified by someone else &amp; they make you happy to be alive." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When someone finally has a success &amp; people feel touched by your music, the sensation of satisfaction appears." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the money, and two for the show. I love you honey, I'm ready to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are, by far, the brightest star I've ever seen. And I never dreamed I'd be so happy that I could die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I thought I've had found someone who could take care of me and that I could take care too, I saw everything fall apart." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget safety. Live where you fear to live. Destroy your reputation. Be notorious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Lana Del Rey. http://t.co/tEOJpzQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like things from the past because they take me back to that time." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not as sad as I sound in my songs." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey by Naomi Shon. — COMING SOON! (http://t.co/N8yyt3r4) http://t.co/0HA0hPsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow us on Tumblr: http://t.co/Iy6DrARY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep making me laugh, let's go get high. The road is long, we carry on try to have fun in the meantime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey's secret. http://t.co/IRhQF6SV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you keep secrets, your secrets keep you. It's really dangerous unless you find the right person to confide in." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What happens if you want to be a great singer but your own home country says: 'No, you're not?'" —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that I’m fun, you know that I’m young. So tell me your mind, let’s get it on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know what the boys want, I'm not gonna play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're so fresh to death &amp; sick as cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody told me love was blind, then I saw your face and you blew my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been tryin’ hard not to get in trouble, but I, I’ve got a war in my mind. I just ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo:  http://t.co/xMseiPDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's all! Thanks for playing #TeamLana, I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#6 The right answer is American. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @rebecazbsmith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LAST ROUND: I don't even know what I'm saying, but I'm praying for you. #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#5 The right answer is Yayo. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @SeksyPaulo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND 5: Hello heaven, you are a tunnel lined with yellow lights on a dark night. #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#4 The right answer is My Best Days. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @SamiClara_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND 4:  In my wildest dreams I never knew I found somebody like you. #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#3 The right answer is Jump. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @baukebos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND 3: Palm trees in black and white. Last thing I saw before I died. #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2 The right answer is Last Girl On Earth. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @efisotiropoulou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND 2: No one lives forever, but that's no reason to give up. Dont you wanna fall in love? #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#1 The right answer is Paris. FOLLOW THE WINNER: @ranmenhem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND 1: I wanna be that fantasy that you got on your mind. Flying across the sea to somewhere that they'll never find. #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoutout for the first person to answer correctly the title song of the lyrics that I give. Ready? #GuessDelReySongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to play #GuessDelReySongs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elvis is my daddy, Marilyn's my mother, 
Jesus is my bestest friend. http://t.co/wIVV11aT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then she starts to cry, mascara running down her little Bambi eyes. "Lana how I hate those guys."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnAtheistPriest: @taylorswift13 You should help us trend #CantWaitForColaVideo since you're such a huge fan and all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CantWaitForColaVideo Come on baby let's ride, we can escape to the great sunshine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CantWaitForColaVideo http://t.co/VPAkcwP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Top10GreatestVoices Queen Lana Del Rey http://t.co/AOSrMTZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick me up and take me like a vitamin
'Cause my body's sweet like sugar venom oh yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey — Video Games http://t.co/c13f6vud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it wrong? If it's wrong, I don't wanna be right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pussy tastes like Pepsi Cola. My eyes are wide like cherry pies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not a real Team Lana just knowing every single thing about Lana Del Rey. You're a real Team Lana if you stay and support her forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing in the old bars. Swinging with the old stars. Living for the fame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer's in the air, and baby, heaven's in your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm off to the races, laces, leather on my waist is tight and I am fallin' down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We get crazy every Friday night. Drop it like it's hot in the pale moonlight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He loves me with every beat of his cocaine heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There has always been the melancholy in me called desire." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve got a burning desire for you baby. http://t.co/7PZ40xi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drive fast, wind in my hair. I push you to the limits 'cause I just don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day Team Lana! http://t.co/jAOl5Zto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: Lana Del Rey's New Music Video "Burning Desire" featuring @JaguarUSA! Watch here: http://t.co/9YFabedd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honoring love even when it's lost." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think life is more interesting and makes me happy when I have the opportunity to be creative and spontaneous." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy, its late, walk me home, put your hand in mine. Let the game stop and say be my valentine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to make it fun, don't trust anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love me hardcore, then don't walk away. It's a game, boy, I don't wanna play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your soul is haunting me and telling me that everything is fine. But I wish I was dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood's dead, Elvis is crying, Marilyn's sad, Hendrix is lying there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Grammys. http://t.co/ORp6oG3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it for the thrill of the rush. Love you just a little too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I like this roller coaster, maybe it keeps me high. Maybe the speed it brings me closer, I could sparkle up your eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in the kindness of strangers. And when I'm at war with myself- I Ride. I just Ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a war in my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um, do you think you'll buy me lots of diamonds?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>