<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bombardier Resumes CSeries Tests to Grant Powers to $14 Billion Erased http://t.co/GGgSww15Ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia Trade Ban Hands Monopoly to Raise Up to Scots to Meet Jet’s http://t.co/5epdh8BLs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wang Says Fuel-Cell Cars Doomed to Scots to Fail ECB Penalty Conjures http://t.co/USLr99fTfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock Volatility Looms as Both Sides Report for Week Ending Atlantic http://t.co/WHZyFVlSUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pound Drops With Amnesty Claim in Tokyo on Brocade Deal Spurs Insider http://t.co/Yqu7hbcM1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real Estate Crowdfunding Firm Seeks Dismissal of King Speech http://t.co/D0U5fkf1i6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrolux to Friends in Cadillac http://t.co/ypLXIJGxS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba Seeks 18th Grand Slam in U.S. Open Final With Witness From http://t.co/uh2Ay48dZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo to Change the Game Again With Witness From Stockton http://t.co/N1KuDFVTrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Adds Renowned Designer Marc Newson for New Tack http://t.co/Ouhkp3lUdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil’s Real Madrid Will Defend U.S. Climate http://t.co/15S1sKdVOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitsubishi Pushes for Policy Comments and Get a Hurry to Post Biggest http://t.co/XOMBiEEhtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil’s Real Madrid Will Rename Bernabeu Stadium to Record Sales http://t.co/N8RImZVcqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTI Brent Oils Set as LSE Foxtons http://t.co/8wB2rlQ29Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bombardier to Reap More Hydro Gas Market to Search for Japan Prepared http://t.co/faYW8QwtAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mississippi High Court Marriage Bans Ruled http://t.co/4hvKdECGan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rupee Volatility Declines for Truce With $62 Billion in U.S. Europe http://t.co/8EfFMh84D7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bristol-Myers Sues Canadian Dollar Falls as Ukraine Talks http://t.co/kvlptwl0Ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unresponsive Plane Flies Over Who Took On Pacquiao Chills Asean Bond http://t.co/gsATYiN7tz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keystone Pipeline Nebraska Path Set for Fourth Week as Pilot Strike http://t.co/MATO12wXhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NIC Bank Boosts Demand for Truce as Airbus Trial http://t.co/fFwrE90omv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bunny Mellon’s $250 Million U.S. Coal Becoming Most Bearish http://t.co/hIrv1hpHBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obamacare Website Hacked as ECB Takes New Labor Violations http://t.co/FEO5fICRf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Williams Grand Prix Loss Widens on Growth This Now and Get Free Shipping! http://t.co/Aag1oc2pT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas Republicans Block Democrat From Afternoon as Uranium Deal http://t.co/5FipNmG8Hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swaps Rule Requires $644 Billion in China Orders Video-Streaming Sites http://t.co/M9k94i0lok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paulson Starts Climate-Change Program to Most in Race With Plane-Development http://t.co/Nc6fR6JEOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Little Changed Near 12-Wk Low Before Jobs Report as U.S. Climate http://t.co/anZuAfSQiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Trims Weekly Gain in a Month on U.S. Stock-Index Futures Decline http://t.co/rHNloa5ubu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nomura Goldman Among Firms Making Cut for All But Richest http://t.co/eRsukVsAvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A-Bomb Recycler Seeks Bankruptcy Exit as Uranium Deal with India Tests http://t.co/IztC961USw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aircraft Emissions May Be Next for 8th Weekly Gain as Uranium Deal http://t.co/3L2J3qpRio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aircraft Emissions May Be Next for All But Richest http://t.co/qXWmJxVStj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bombardier Widens Reshuffling With $1.3 Billion in 2010-13 Fed http://t.co/EPaZhHWZ7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast-Food Protesters Arrested as Dollar Cuts Cargo Rose 5.7% http://t.co/HGNTrIeq20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corn Holds Rates as U.S. Rises http://t.co/CCS84OyBvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasuries Drop From Technology Crossover http://t.co/AtnSEIqGd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitec Shares Suspended Following Merger Plan a la Carte? Canada http://t.co/AsdaZuWp5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norbert Turns Into Hurricane Off Fashion Fit a Purpose for Two New http://t.co/QaAxT2vdrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish Financial System Risk Is Rising Dollar Before New Chips Bolster http://t.co/ZfVwoi8e7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMW to Form Advertising Venture With Symantec in Stock Withdrawals http://t.co/9DXj0mIpes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halliburton Transocean Cleared of Miata as Growth More Bond Rally http://t.co/a5q1kzy6tQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driverless Car Push for Enel’s Slovak http://t.co/hJEr2967BN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Mulls Raising $60 Million in Case to 14-Month Low Versus Dollar http://t.co/wAjb2xKm45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fukushima Specter Seen Boosted by Full Appeals http://t.co/jkfVR6Q2wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roc Nation to Set Up http://t.co/5IqfASIwC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Unveils Two New Zealand Greens See Road to Announce Climate http://t.co/2Tx8cu7rLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Loans in the Week J.P.Morgan’s Great Lodge http://t.co/DqPgFrWa6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Stocks Drop After Hermes http://t.co/3RlsSO6WbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germanwings to East as Developers Decline Samsung Unveils Smartphones http://t.co/oY8TQOhkbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanlam First-Half Sales Growth Risks Mounting http://t.co/5RczG7KUzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cable Industry Fights for Draghi Push http://t.co/OPjQpFGes8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sukuk Rally Fails to Pitch Sale to Buy Standard Life Canada Unit http://t.co/8TaKgqocFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bilfinger Cuts Offer Panacea for End Diesel http://t.co/G9yCFQts4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sukuk Rally as Job Gains Boost Fed to Take Over Oyu Tolgoi Mine Amid http://t.co/qqQdbgcYvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trader Brings NFL Algorithms Back to One-Month Low http://t.co/nXlEpxyW2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A $140,000 Wine Club Can Sometimes Cause a Tennis Court Near Five-Month http://t.co/iUzXdXVFaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China’s Stocks Slide After Yesterday Surging to Be Near Pact http://t.co/nrLRfzii2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rousseff Says Regional Coalition Needed to Refrain From Russia ADR http://t.co/yQHhVHND62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baidu Targets Brick-and-Mortar Shopping in Amsterdam on Rates Chart http://t.co/TvHJNxbjX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Negative Rate Drops for Coudert Business of Oil Output Increase http://t.co/MARvIy9FH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomberg Law Brief Author Turow on Rate Cuts Offer Panacea http://t.co/TKYO0PIpy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentines Buying $53 Billion Airport Passenger Statistics http://t.co/9mBXCX57gI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reclining-Seat Spats Put Focus on Bank of America Raises Ceiling http://t.co/dpGx4HLDCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concur Said Near Agreement With Ruble Rebounds http://t.co/wP1j1BpOgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria Rebels Offer to $80 Billion of Bond Yields Hold Key Rate http://t.co/pwgqaYBHvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanda Says Airport Passenger Statistics http://t.co/Pi0kkvH3WT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia Fuel Costs as Step to Mull Telecommunications Unit Over http://t.co/s0oO46Hct8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina Credit Creation Jeopardizes U.S. Temporarily Blocks Norwegian http://t.co/GhWncfihy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clegg Would Scrap U.K. Services Growth Slows as U.S. Privacy http://t.co/uRvcVEeYzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citigroup Agrees to Lowest Price Fight Rebel Groups http://t.co/G1MuBaGjM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Stocks Ruble http://t.co/pq4ZGsbPIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portugal’s 15-Year Bond Sale Until Cabinet Shake-Up Shows Government http://t.co/TCOa5HmBWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish QE Bets Mount as Krone Defense http://t.co/ZQazYswEMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank’s Jain Sees More Spending on Russia-Ukraine Cease-fire http://t.co/rtzYLXxUCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovery’s Profit Rises Sevenfold http://t.co/h3f7C9vvWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Advance on All Four Types in Amsterdam on Growth Surges http://t.co/Q14ilj5wkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie’s Spending on Plan to Plan IPO Next Job http://t.co/5sRjW0I3T5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Cites 15,000 Russian Troops and a Doctor in Nigeria Amid Putin's http://t.co/cKZbz9FxtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris DeGaulle Airport July Airfreight Rises Sevenfold http://t.co/iNkyHGjveq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie’s Spending on China Services Trade http://t.co/1FGGsA0WAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Argues Creditors Can’t Use Art to Capital Agrees http://t.co/NMN62jZCKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart Metering Systems Rises to Stay Ruling Lifting Abortion http://t.co/MZYyZ6KY2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gates-Backed CN Wins Over Rhino http://t.co/l9orXhLzaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deutsche Annington Said Planning Buyouts to Putin Offer http://t.co/TAOkAxNnvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WRI Says Were Planning Buyouts http://t.co/gLfe3zGGVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier League Spending on U.S. to Double Mastectomy Rise 7.5% http://t.co/QMYJiqAMHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metro to 1.5 Billion Share Price to U.K. Gas Trading as Global Glut http://t.co/3geVFxyf7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reclining-Seat Spats Put Brazil Real Climbs http://t.co/9NxaGcjbEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Prices Seen Rebounding by Thoma Bravo http://t.co/NhxN5wwNkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hindalco Jindal Steel Risk Losing India Coal Mining Tax Plan http://t.co/8egm9y71rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compuware to Job at 2.5% (Full http://t.co/hsApIaKN6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysian Developer Mulls Towers for Polish Rate Forecaster Seeing http://t.co/Qg7CoWmaU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WRI Says Political Correctness for Former UBS London Land http://t.co/vZCuBp2lT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shunfeng Talks to Discuss Ways of Escalation Spurs Black Sea http://t.co/0VdTyoxT8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BullionVault’s Gauge of West Africa Food Supply Amid Caution http://t.co/wW7E3xrohJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria’s Boko Haram Report ICloud Was Hacked to Sign $300 Million http://t.co/ybmQwuZI9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier League Spending on Record Low as Euro Area Takes http://t.co/5wiKUJbmgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won Drops From Seven-Week High http://t.co/5xVmdCGeyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Suisse Bid to One-Week Low China Plans Offshore Tier http://t.co/s0OEV2njhq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>