<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. There are people who are never satisfied with anything their spouses do. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12. God expressed His love for us by allowing His son to die for us because He thought we were worth it. #PastErrors #iCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 11. ...you forgive even when you think the person does not 'deserve' it. #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10. You do not forgive because the wrong has been made right,... #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9.Everyone errs, of course,to different degrees,but "forgiveness is not a reward,it is a gift" -@familyaffairs05 #PastErr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8. Would you rather hold on to the hurt than consider the good of the marriage/relationship? #PastErrors #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 7. Some people say it is difficult to let go of certain things, how important is that relationship to you? #PastErrors #i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/m8vTp0m6He]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some yrs ago, I got emotionally involved..

Hang out with Chidi Akunna on Twitter @chidi_akunna TODAY, 30 March 2017, at 6PM GMT #PastErrors https://t.co/dnLkmLkqgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the 'worst' spouse still has some good qualities. Look for the best in each other! - Victor Akunna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Escape 2 by Victor Akunna: When I got there, I saw some boys dancing and chatting… https://t.co/ddlwjlMLkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Escape 2 by Victor Akunna: When I got there, I saw some boys dancing and chatting… https://t.co/ZMFtL6Jals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Friend,

Have you downloaded your copy?

Free download link: 
https://t.co/S117cw7edW https://t.co/Tz5TuBeQNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26. Now, when you say you have forgiven, why do you keep bringing it up and linking it to every move? #PastErrors #iConne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Romantic #Family #Romance #love #Intimacy https://t.co/QDUyszTnwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/DTilSSiFyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, marriage in 3 Ds - You, your spouse and God. https://t.co/bb7EbGQ8Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said you forgave me, yet you recall every little detail by Chidi and Victor Akunna: You… https://t.co/1mUNv14Hxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said you forgave me, yet you recall every little detail by Chidi and Victor Akunna: You… https://t.co/5S4xRtVRBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 62. Make up your mind to raise world-class children while pursuing your own dreams as well. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 61. If you are a single mum, don't let the circumstances of your past rule your future. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 60. Addressing stereotypes like this starts with you and I.That said, single mums should not be castigated, but supported…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 59. The notion that daughters of single mums are often wild is a stereotype. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 58. As the daughter of a single mum, you can decide to be virtuous. Virtue is attractive. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHear…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 57. Yes, training them to be independent is good, but let them also know the importance of virtue. #SingleMumPalaver #iCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 56. Single mums can play their part by instilling the right values into their children. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 55. Our environment affects us, but we create the future we want. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 51. "When the love wanes, the next thing is fight. She wouldn't even know why she is fighting you." #SingleMumPalaver #iC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 50. "No one wants to marry trouble in a packaged as a spouse. " #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 49. They unconsciously see the man as an opponent, as someone whose authority is to be defied to prove a point. #SingleMu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 48. Thus,some of these ladies go into relationship with people they love with their guards up and their 'boxing gloves on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 47. "Sadly some raised their daughters not to allow any man 'take advantage of them'. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 46. "It depends on the family culture,there are women who are single mums because their husbands died or left the marriag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 45. "Environment has a role, but a lot of folks I know have been able to beat positively, the past, environment&amp;culture."…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 42."...at a certain age, a child is able to make a right or bad decision, regardless of his/her training." #SingleMumPala…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 40. "I have seen great examples, good girls raised by single mums and some raised by both parents."  #SingleMumPalaver
#i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 39. "The competition of stereotyping is there, they fight that by instilling positivity into their girls." #SingleMumPala…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 38. "God fearing and believing mums will still bring up their girls positively." #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 37. "What matters most is to find out if the single mom fears God." #SingleMumPalaver  #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 36."One of the best Neurosurgeons of our time, who wrote Gifted Hands, Think Big and The Big Picture was Dr. Ben Carson..…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 35. "A single mum isn't the issue.Most single mums are tracking (on the right with discipline and morals)."#SingleMumPala…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 34. Some responses got me excited. I will share them. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 33.I asked the honest opinion of some men, "would you advise a single guy to get married to a girl raised by a single mum…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 28. Check; be sure of the person you want to embark on the journey of marriage with and do not allow stereotype limit you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26. The buyer has to do a lot of checks to be aware of the property to be invested in. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 25. In Property Law, there is a famous caveat - "Let the Buyer beware". #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 24. Who would blame anyone who was trying to apply due diligence to a lifetime investment as marriage?  #SingleMumPalaver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 21. "Girls raised by single mums are often stereotyped as materialistic&amp;failures, I don't agree as I am living with one."…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20."My wife is humble and material things are not a problem to her. She is content." #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 19b. ...compared to the girls I dated in the past who had both parents as pastors/positions in the church and government.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 19. He went on, "My wife isn't the best girl in life, but she has given 100 percent..." #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18. A man said, "My wife and her sister were raised by their mum alone until she travelled out to go pave way for them. #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17. Sometimes, it is down to the individual and the choices made by him/her.#SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 16.Just like the famous story of the dad with 2 sons who turned out differently - one was impactful&amp;the other was wastefu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 15. I understand the concerns of some young men, but not every child turns out like his/her parents. #SingleMumPalaver #i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14. Hmmm.... that's something to think about. #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. She went on, "they tend to portray single mums of boys as prayerful women who teach their boys culinary skills." #Sin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12. A lady who has had a similar experience said to me, "what would ladies do about guys who were raised by single mums?"…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 10.In fact,love to me,is him getting involved in activities that would help us develop healthy lifestyles. #SingleMumPala…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9.Another lady let out,"the fact that my mum is fat does not mean I'd end up like that,I don't intend to". #SingleMumPala…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 7b. ...he believed she would end up like her mum and could not imagine himself with someone like that. #SingleMumPalaver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 5. "I am a divorcee due to no fault of mine, her dad left because I couldn't conceive after having her, he wanted a boy."…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 3. She has had her fair share of stigma, but did not think it would ever affect her daughter this way. #SingleMumPalaver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 2. As I listened to her speak about her daughter being turned down by a man she was in love with, I could feel her pain.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 1. "He won't marry my daughter because she was raised by a single mum!" #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He won't marry my daughter because she was raised by a single mum!"

As I listened to this mum speak about her... https://t.co/em2bC1ews8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be deliberate about doing little things that capture your spouse's heart, attention and happiness. They don't have to be expensive ... https://t.co/gWsMjcwDN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 41. Someone also said, "don't throw away the act of choice..." #SingleMumPalaver #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FREE BOOK  To download your copy, click here: https://t.co/sCf6SsmGiC https://t.co/p1w15IxcK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FREE BOOK  To download your copy, click here: https://t.co/sCf6SsmGiC https://t.co/BlwZnXwP3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Couples Avoid Counselling - Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna

Sometimes, people have their reservations about going for... https://t.co/iHzoQsESkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Couples Avoid Counselling - Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna

Sometimes, people have their reservations about going for... https://t.co/bHPbkk7Wnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Couples Avoid Counselling – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Sometimes, people have their… https://t.co/sc9RFv9Fsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Couples Avoid #Counselling – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Sometimes, people have their… https://t.co/NRDXxKSnQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dirty Window! By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: My Dirty Window! Sometime ago, I read a story… https://t.co/MOkOQOc9eR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dirty Window! By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: My Dirty Window! Sometime ago, I read a story… https://t.co/6rQAdiI05h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Right by Chidi and Victor Akunna
There is an African proverb that states that we must learn to change... https://t.co/vV110tmX8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join our closed Facebook group for more intimate discussions on love, relationship and marital romance.... https://t.co/6rcEwpKAsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Right By Chidi and Victor Akunna: There is an African proverb that states that we… https://t.co/tOwLwwbwek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Right By Chidi and Victor Akunna: There is an African proverb that states that we… https://t.co/jEdPyu9mOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Right By Chidi and Victor Akunna: There is an African proverb that states that we… https://t.co/3OQID5D1vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Right By Chidi and Victor Akunna: There is an African proverb that states that we… https://t.co/8PbkCt1KB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Map

Everything God made was made for a purpose, including your family.

Sometimes, we believe this... https://t.co/WUriaKqnKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be proactive!

#romantic 
#husbandandwife 
#family 
#husband 
#wife 
#we @ London, United Kingdom https://t.co/eFa7hRfoO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Family Map by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Everything God made was made for a #purpose… https://t.co/rOfDdmX4py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Map by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Everything God made was made for a purpose, including… https://t.co/8WPUMWKDNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage Booster

We must give our spouses a special place of honour in our hearts, at home, and at gatherings,... https://t.co/qNchzh9dWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gentleman called to let me know that he was seriously interested in one of the ladies around me. I was so... https://t.co/a9UjxG2KSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. We hope you will take action immediately to move your marriage from good to GREAT marriage. We celebrate your greatness! God bless you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. Come up with creative ideas on how to date your spouse. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20. After being married for a while, you should know what works best for your spouse. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Let it be so memorable that you both look forward to the next one. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. Draw up an agenda &amp; do your best to make it fun &amp; positively memorable by considering what you both enjoy. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. Just start, it doesn't have to be perfect, break out of the inertia and choose a location. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. Don't postpone, start it today. Pick up your calendar, choose a convenient day with your spouse and start. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15. The opposite of spicy romance is a draining and crisis-ridden marriage. #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. Are you leveraging on 'dating' to spice up your marital romance? #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13. Are you taking advantage of the benefits of dating to bridge the gap between you and your spouse? #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Are you proactive about your marriage? Are you deliberate? #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. Are you one of those who wait only for special occasions like Valentine's Day?😉 #DatingMySpouse #SpicyRomance]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>