<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/gqEeG63i0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/81vMakolj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/cta2tlJdIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/iUzxBN6v7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/nayfxNtNJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/10040DoKx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A business has to be involving, it has to be fun, and it has to exercise your creative instincts. - Richard Branson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/zdAWXQi4zP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/PxyyAWCCv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/7lWlM9Tfvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/0hzzVtoc68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/JsvKCpPSYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/94m8FBvUre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/X6GF3hY3bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/TscQRDMFwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/qArHvng6dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/LkVVxxs7jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/76j9HlqmJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/hQkNueTFrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/b2ezpQsy0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/W69e0xxKbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/NGIdGmvwRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/saSsvzGtQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/ImV9vh44Xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/M56YFoa3tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/iooVixRhaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/82kNDO5EYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/8VP9AQEfQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/6HSZfCtZLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/ZjLTQIVwt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/5Xe22WcnwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/BAOKvUzlzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/8dpFBLYC9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/hGi3k0bC7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SE5BqK1Ywm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/d4PZzydFiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/xAxpbKB1Kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/szWjMcIc08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/qW36bb6XQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/KuWOUar4RX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/Y5VAJLo6Zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/mhVdntB7yh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/ErocwNbKq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/A46kk8uyDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/1UTJ5Qs0gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>