<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/heOm09FIoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/wGOx5RvxC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/hB50UOfMfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/aLeaXQNyv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/dQSxo1TR6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/AKommrRjQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/kPzqPIEhrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/OkKm3yjtkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/OVqGTo9zcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/tvrzzej9Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/Xqtt4oUBRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/0E6Lhcd9PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/axT3OA9n9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/zkq8ENJopm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/YdTW1tXuTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/gv1sZ4Yy9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/6QbL2c13n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/NPCPCTo2lZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/tVcDf4mfjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/6257XFvFUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/BGsv5lVGtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/ID2daeSZzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/gNHKgdGw9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/O47RMsUBqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/lmixnKPHwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/kbcSaeh9Fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/AHyfeDv9HI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/ElDC61oOO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/ceYYfEBnDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love sports?  Read about the great sports teams of the Northern California Bay Area!  http://t.co/9XuFLz311P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/qzJMr9T2VA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/CYKOto75kY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/BOSzJCOluR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/sEmvXp8jRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/nfledx6VU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/Eeh0MMHkY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/Olic0DtdsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/cMbRaxvtT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/Xqtt4oUBRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/mYUZ398ZGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/AbCwGuraae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/FZQjx0uPBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/afqbTTYND5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/cK3dseAtC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/797OvMbzuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/PuEbsgLUiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/i761SS1dHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/K4acMKK7xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/sgB5txc91G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/fIYCVTIibt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/FUpDpKIpOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/MkbyNqotcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/vSv8LqvLNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/iVAexyUFXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>