<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/eHShvjMEMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/QbBfc077hB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/y9yPhYXWDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/HpWQoHPVeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/4pXirVGOm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/wS3bCv78hT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/5pqOkjOT4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/8o1CCa2Fa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/g9tJZGhdG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/fLbomPNECJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/cCbtav8pqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/GVq0BQ4TN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/8o1CCa2Fa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/81cyTivDpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/cEQ3IID8Rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/S439V8lV4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/Nw1x7Wzi5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/7Fr6YATnrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/iBTmLL33g6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/yvorLAhnLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/lbCrf4MeSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/otdKUuRpIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/DXdrwIhUpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/0VMRbwQmn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/0uZVbfKHoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/ownfdpo8Dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/kGWjn1Rnfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/8Ew358l75z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/4Gk2oFR3IB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/AF9E1HK3It]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/oOz4KR1kZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/Fa51amZJp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/OFUc1W0QfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/RF4eKRQ7Pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last word of the Emperor Montezuma, "Someone tell those Marines to stop singing in the halls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/q7OKattODU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/6H8kefR8zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/pDcn6iZEFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/UfU4sDHxIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/HA4eBWU3uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/C3ECEN1UqD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>