<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We either make ourselves miserable or we make ourselves strong. The amount of work is the same. -Carlos Castaneda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To have what we want is riches; but to be able to do without is power. -George MacDonald #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you take no risks, you'll never be hurt, but you won't really live, either. -Dr. James… https://t.co/ZIL2B17B99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is always room for those who can be relied upon to delivery the goods when they say they will. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To find what you seek in the road of life, the best proverb of all is that which says: "Leave no stone unturned." -E. Lytton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the world you may be one person, but to one person you may be the world. -Paulette Mitchell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's Purpose You Will Win https://t.co/eUfW7lScmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing nothing is the most tiresome job in the world because you cannot quit and rest. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we obtain too cheap, we esteem too lightly; it is dearness only that gives every thing its value. -Thomas Paine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working hard, you get to play hard, guilt-free. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little minds are too much wounded by little things; great minds see all these little things and are not hurt. -Rochefoucauld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problems Quotes https://t.co/yoFgue1OW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All problems become smaller if you don't dodge them, but confront them. -William F. Halsey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is better to remain silent and be thought a fool than to open one's mouth and remove all doubt. -Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you take no risks, you'll never be hurt, but you won't really live, either. -Dr. James Shiovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is just another way to learn how to do something right. -Marian Wright Edelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I Want My Children To Remember About Home https://t.co/Cpf5HycWvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All life is a chance. So take it! The person who goes furthest is the one who is willing to do and dare. -Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ambition is the path to success, persistence is the vehicle you arrive in. -William IV Eardley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only he who keeps his eye fixed on the far horizon will find his right road. -Dag Hammarskjold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every achiever that I have ever met says, "My life turned around when I began to believe in me." -Robert H. Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Good Motivational Quotes Software Programs https://t.co/CEiO9RFZpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistency requires you to be as ignorant today as you were a year ago. -Bernard Berenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not pray for a lighter load, but for a stronger back. -Phillips Brooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest not. Life is sweeping by; go and dare before you die. -Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make no mistakes is not in the power of man; but from their errors &amp; mistakes, the wise &amp; good learn wisdom for the future. -Plutarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stability or Flashyness? https://t.co/vLeFwlDeMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lives of great men all remind us we can make our lives sublime!" -Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most certain sign of wisdom is cheerfulness.  -Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the ordinary business of life, industry can do anything which genius can do, and very many things which it cannot. -HW Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a mirror and will reflect back to the thinker what he thinks into it. -Ernest Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought Quotes https://t.co/CwUYx1tru6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As is our confidence, so is our capacity." -William Hazlitt #quotes #inspirational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up.  The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. -Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragedy of life doesn't lie in not reaching your goal. The tragedy lies in having no goals to reach. -Benjamin Mays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is far better to know our own weaknesses and failings than to point out those of another. -Jawaharlal Nehru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Busy...Or Else https://t.co/uRX47S9v2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people do the icky stuff! -Kyle Eastham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength and growth come only through continuous effort and struggle. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Silence is one of the great arts of conversation." -Hannah More #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The highest reward for a person's toil is not what they get for it, but what they become by it. -John Ruskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories Quotes - Memory Quotes https://t.co/gCTXuRHXOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You always pass failure on the way to success. -Mickey Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debate is the death of conversation. -Emil Ludwig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be tested is good. The challenged life may be the best therapist. -Gail Sheehy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is more frequently from want of energy than want of capital. -Daniel Webster (1782-1852)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing In Yourself Quotes https://t.co/PnB4nG9IZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't just read the easy stuff. You may be entertained by it, but you will never grow from it. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a rarity to find someone who can weigh other people's faults without putting his own thumbs on the scale. -Paraguayan Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The surest cure for loneliness, the quickest way to happiness, is found in this, a simple creed: Go serve someone in greater need. -W Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the negativity given to you by the world disempower you. Instead give to yourself that which empowers you. -Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice Quotes https://t.co/kOABQ35NB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest pleasure in life is doing what people say you cannot do. -Walter Bagehot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest of faults, I should say, is to be conscious of none. -Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How far that little candle throws its beams! So shines a good deed in a naughty world. -William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If A equals success, then the formula is A equals X plus Y and Z, with X being work, Y play, and Z keeping your mouth shut. -Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy Quotes https://t.co/eXtykjnd9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making mistakes simply means you are learning faster. -Weston Agor

#quotes #sayings #proverbs… https://t.co/iyKrg15b1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Possible's slow fuse is lit by the imagination. -Emily Dickinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is through cooperation, rather than conflict, that your greatest successes will be derived. -Ralph Charell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can imagine no more comfortable frame of mind for the conduct of life than a humorous resignation. -W. Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we argue for our limitations, we get to keep them. -Peter McWilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vacillating People https://t.co/OJH9sg2wBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Set too many goals and keep adding more goals. Goals have a tendency to be realized all at once. -Mark Victor Hansen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should not let our fears hold us back from pursuing our hopes. -John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No man is lonely while eating spaghetti; it requires so much attention. -Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some books are to be tasted; others to be swallowed; and some few to be chewed and digested.  -Francis Bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Mistakes Quotes https://t.co/7OYU9Qrdmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In these times you have to be an optimist to open your eyes when you wake in the morning. -Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a great big canvas, and you should throw all the paint you can on it. -Danny Kaye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be. -Kurt Vonnegut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confidence is the result of hours and days and weeks and years of constant work and dedication.… https://t.co/wcepzoqGnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have confidence that if you have done a little thing well, you can do a bigger thing well too. -David Storey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength Quotes https://t.co/5dWpPyiuQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One must be a wise reader to quote wisely and well. -Amos Bronson Alcott #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each day can be one of triumph if you keep up your interests. -George Adams #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take a chance! All life is a chance. The man who goes farthest is generally the one who is willing to do and dare." -Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I discovered a long time ago that if I helped people get what they wanted, I would always get what I wanted... -Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gossip Quotes https://t.co/sPIcRyPjRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not think about your future, you cannot have one. -John Galsworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere, something incredible is waiting to be known. -Carl Edward Sagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatness is not found in possessions, power, position, or prestige. It is discovered in goodness, humility, service &amp; character. -W Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is consistency of purpose. -Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upward Reaching https://t.co/TYrHnuxXeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not to be occupied and not to exist amount to the same thing." -Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charity and personal force are the only investments worth anything. -Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be kind; everyone you meet is fighting a hard battle." -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities are usually disguised by hard work, so most people don't recognize them. -Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance: The Slender Force of Human Beings https://t.co/SBkEsdaqA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rust consumes iron and envy consumes itself. -Danish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Flying off the handle sometimes causes hammers and humans to lose their heads, as well as their effectiveness." -William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are lifting the world upward and onward are those who encourage more than criticize.… https://t.co/PUokl7EIWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness Poem https://t.co/QANvEkNG97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introspection Quotes https://t.co/ZvbZ5odErD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cure for boredom is curiosity. There is no cure for curiosity. -Ellen Parr #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is something that comes into our lives through doors we don't even remember leaving open. -Rose Lane #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge if stored away and not put into use may corrode in time. -Eva Arrington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overcoming Trials Quotes https://t.co/qeC0No9bO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A soul without a high aim is like a ship without a rudder. -Eileen Caddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cherish forever what makes you unique, 'cuz you're really a yawn if it goes! -Bette Midler]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>