<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/4p8eIXV7K7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/Nh32CTpFVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/JWePFGNuG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/NcOlOFdaSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/KpNfPeEqFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/2phJlTegXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/c3bB96ADuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/Ym6yhloYFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/A1U9DodcHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/LUarsL6yBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/kGq0e8RMb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/k2rYljQjYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/4LLAs69Qxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the confidence that makeup gives me. --&gt; Tyra Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/QM3cj7byai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/GZyehneWRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/YAsoIi17zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/R8EwnI6eLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/YYnRMZrnu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/jf1cJSQBBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/Z7JSZ27aBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/b1dthnKEPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/HO9Epskb58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Gm5Hly5FC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/XjOY19quWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/vZ0HQLrSL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/zpTYfwlGmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/p7BVMUhcv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/uJcvBayndp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/Avn1nAflqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/ZvR01kk60b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/NrplkiLILc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/uCMZFbDMyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/TvbcTDesDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/hccAJxJgCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/2CqmEP40As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/K0Sri3mCKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/NCimQHhs2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/dEthf3fXMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/qX8vLKGpUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/fgAbYK3lEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/zr3NHoBlff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/IcOOQNgqLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/MTS24WNIvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/tL2Qp8VQTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/JTudZTy7Wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/Les7lhwN3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/qtUBgPkw6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>