<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/O4HrpPQJ6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/HzlxcResHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9R50ORoyC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home"Â - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/f58Emmm38T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/7ngkDO43cC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/fT1QxyzIsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/P5AfKRRg64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/zLo3ZNcL8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/quFunfxT7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/3N5PrQQHLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/gi2yy1QNlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/j39eTyGXpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/zEOtgotbG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/8BiXbKjLdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/Wph0o8SZYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/3lNxxdKPx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/ef6pj6Zvpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/wUxoUXXT9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/Swvx9gqml8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/uJRWt7dV3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/LwNpFrkFBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/XzUJFInstD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/BMJCKE91nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the confidence that makeup gives me. --&gt; Tyra Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/gKtQEkadKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/2Z8NQ1r3mQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/YC7Y9ulupl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/aPwQlb9TaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/6H8kefR8zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/OFUc1W0QfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/n6KFnZA2NQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/bLw7mqoVk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/b8fJKQC93n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/YCIAeaoIFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/gwCbciwfoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/LlUbqTuGtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/Cup93VZ2KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/zXkqtMX4nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KML0JkbUqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/n8ac3UIWN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/pFt1Ulm4ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/e8BUwCmMRk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>