<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: @EPAScottPruitt @lisamurkowski @SenatorTomUdall @SenatorLeahy @backtobasics @SenatorTester @ChrisVanHollen @ChrisVanHollen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: @JohnFCross @NRDCFedGov He's long said that cross-state-border pollution is EPA's *only* proper constitutional role. @EPA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt says he "prioritizes" superfund. @SenatorTester points out he wants to cut it by nearly a third. #DirtyBudget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorTomUdall: I'm questioning #EPA admin Pruitt abt his dangerous budget to gut EPA's core missions of clean air &amp; water. Watch: htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt talks about cross-state pollution like it's the only reason EPA exists. (Also, he sued against the Cross-State Air Pollution Rule.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: @EPAScottPruitt @lisamurkowski @SenatorTomUdall @SenatorLeahy @backtobasics @EPAScottPruitt resorts to claim that EPA serve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt predictably opens saying EPA needing to respect "rule of law," never having won any of ~20 court cases against the EPA. #dirtybudget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_Climate: "This administration is tearing down the legacies of the Clean Air Act &amp; Clean Water Act" - @SenatorLeahy #DirtyBudget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In litany of #dirtybudget's problems, @tomudall points out this proposal "virtually eliminates every EPA dollar related to climate change"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: @EPAScottPruitt @lisamurkowski @SenatorTomUdall @SenatorTomUdall to @EPAScottPruitt: the proposed Trump EPA budget is a "ba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenTomUdall starts off hearing on Trump and Pruitt's #dirtybudget saying it's "downright offensive."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt's Senate testimony  on the #DirtyBudget is starting momentarily - https://t.co/aao6eETRhL https://t.co/Sb5TuSBdEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch I want to start a campaign to get Star Fox 2 released for the actually-classic system. Ol' snessie deserves one last blaze of glory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseload shmaseload. https://t.co/CSU97DH4Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Congressional Budget Office sees 22 million more uninsured by 2026 under Senate health bill in latest hurdle for GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glasscannonpod [He'll] be back. [They] always come back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: @drvox @NRDC, @LungAssociation &amp; other health &amp; environmental groups strongly oppose this irresponsible bill. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solo: No mystical energy field controls my destiny! It's all a lot of simple tricks and nonsense. 

Narrator: There was, and it wasn't. https://t.co/pKdw1sfmTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most devastating thing for democrats about the #GA06 election has been the overwrought reaction to the #GA06 election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: 1. Trump’s EPA illegally blocks mercury rule. 

2. @NRDC sues. 

3. EPA gives in and is now touting benefits of the new rule. 

😎…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emilyhholden: "The only time the administrator really perked up was when he heard the word 'coal,'" a source tells me of Pruitt https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @benwikler: These Medicaid cuts are insidious.  Designed to get bigger every year—so, outside window that CBO scores, they asphyxiate th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Here’s why President Trump’s 2018 budget proposal would be disastrous for energy efficiency. https://t.co/zFchb06xn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Trump’s FY18 federal budget proposal took a sledgehammer to our nation’s energy efficiency &amp; clean energy programs. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stapf: JOB KILLER:  Killing Clean Power Plan means throwing away 560,000 potential #jobs and $52 billion in #GDP growth. https://t.co/O…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_Wild: Zinke @Interior budget hearing: Folks in Montana have read this budget and say it ain't gonna cut it. —@SenatorTester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch We definitely need an entire movie for Mysterio, the most relatable of all comic book characters. The people have been clamoring for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems maybe #PollutingPruitt didn't want to face the public as he left his talk in NYC today. I wonder why. #ActonClimate https://t.co/N4AmaqRU9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Tell Congress to oppose the RAA—a dangerous bill that would make it harder to enact new health &amp; safety protections: https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christina_mcmac Really though? You can't send that out with every email. We all know at least a couple of times a day it's not *all* your *best.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece on Batman &amp; Robin = ultimate refinement of @AaronCouch's 2005 dorm room chats about awesomely bad movies https://t.co/0uQJ7O9niu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The intertribal council speaks for the tribes more than you do and they say this is a slap in the face." @SenFranken to Zinke on Bears Ears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: It didn’t take long for @SecretaryZinke to focus @Interior's goals on catering to the oil and gas industry. https://t.co/8gPbJzUo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell points out Trump and Zinke's #dirtybudget would 'pump the brakes' on a booming outdoor recreation industry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: LIVE NOW: @SecretaryZinke is testifying to Senate Committee re: Trump’s proposed 2018 @Interior budget. Watch here: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plugging your ears to scientists does not make you an "intellectually engaged person," @SecretaryPerry https://t.co/LZCcgWJVsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahkliff: We asked 8 Senate Republicans what their health care bill is trying to do.

The answers are pretty stunning.
https://t.co/Q…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianklaas: A neurosurgeon and a wedding planner walk into a bar...no just kidding they control US Federal Housing. https://t.co/MJHCwL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts en route to NYC: Sky Mall should have sister magazine named Rail Mall full of reasonable and affordable things you might want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well there's oil, coal, gas, nuclear, hydro... hmmm what am I missing...

#ActOnClimate https://t.co/iHW5R1FvJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glasscannonpod I know a guy who'd be happy to tell you exactly where you'll be for the low low price of 2... 300 dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCFedGov: "It's time to stop scapegoating NEPA" says @LovNRDC in must-read @NRDC blog post https://t.co/v99CVYgtbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adbeitman: Congress to Pruitt: How will you protect X while cutting funding for it?
@EPAScottPruitt: It's so important to protect X, th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt claimed to have "won" lawsuits he never did. Tally it up with forgetting he wants to cut Great Lakes restoration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Great Lakes restoration funding is altogether eliminated in Trump's proposed #DirtyBudget. https://t.co/aOOGstGxMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EPAScottPruitt, you should remember when and whether you expose Americans to major threats to their health and environment. https://t.co/t8bHCMFNKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt grilled by @RepKaptur_Marcy on zeroing out Great Lakes restoration fund. His answer was that he doesn't recall doing so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The narrative will be 'Republicans want to weaken clean air standards'" complains @RepChrisStewart. Cause and effect. Like climate change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepChrisStewart (R-UT) says anyone who believes threat of climate change can't support #ParisAgreement because it doesn't do enough. #What]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: @BettyMcCollum04 @EPAScottPruitt @RepHalRogers @RepDerekKilmer @chelliepingree 27. @EPAScottPruitt: says, falsely, that Con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt says "I started bilateral discussions" w/ G7 on reducing carbon. Only in terms of leaving #ParisAgreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Complain about legality of @EPA actions
2. Fail to win suits against @EPA
3. If you can't beat 'em, take credit for 'em

#PollutingPruitt https://t.co/KByzNQwk2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping states lead by taking away their protections *and* their funding. Not sure that will work out, #PollutingPruitt. https://t.co/dMg4OF4bLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt chastises @EPA legal overreach. But what's his record against EPA in over ~20 cases again? #scoreboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Funding could be an issue" for #pollutingPruitt's so-called priorities with Superfund clean ups. That'll happen with a 31% gutting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCWater: .@EPAScottPruitt statement at #DirtyBudget hearing is astonishingly deceptive: as @EPA leader, he's attacked rules to reduce…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we do our job well, we get great environmental outcomes." But you're proposing not to do your job, #PollutingPruitt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @taykuy: Congressional hearing on EPA budget on now. Budget would slash far more EPA jobs than coal has added since Trump https://t.co/Q…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt's hearing on Trump's budget starts w/ @NitaLowey calling out his "willful ignorance" of threats to health and environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Preventing the media from interviewing senators in the hallway should never have been proposed. Thanks to everyone that spoke out…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StevenTDennis: Trump dips in Gallup to 36 (-2).
59% disapprove.
Worst since 35/59 on March 28.
Highest disapproval for new POTUS in his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dominicholden: At this point in the Obama presidency, a big scandal for Fox News was when he ordered the wrong mustard. https://t.co/fB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brendanguy: Mayors of Pittsburgh and Paris: We Have Our Own #ActOnClimate Deal https://t.co/sJv9K25TKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: Kinda looks like the President stole hundreds of thousands of dollars from a charity for kids with cancer?  https://t.co/B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next, Trump will propose a moat around the wall, composed entirely of safe drinking water. https://t.co/5S85IWaftq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: Trump: "We're out." Everyone else: "No, actually, we're in." #IAmStillIn #ParisAgreement https://t.co/YVZJzfnuxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lissajoylynch: hey look what we did this morning: https://t.co/Myz2VoLBA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Save_EPA: .@EPAScottPruitt on @MeetThePress: US has "added almost 50,000 jobs in the coal sector" under Trump. Wrong. @USDOL: 51k TOTAL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billmckibben: Biggest news of the day: Pittsburgh is going 100% renewable. Pittsburgh, not Paris. https://t.co/J6lkyd7k7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played, France. #ParisAgreement https://t.co/gA35ibp5kU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Governors of New York, California, and Washington announce the formation of the "United States Climate Alliance". https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jschmidtnrdc talking about how we need to fight from cities to the world to #actonclimate! #ParisAgreeement https://t.co/A07wtvBNx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hey there @Oceana! #coalitionbuddies #parisagreement https://t.co/INh8nxz67j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous leaders: we are the canaries in the coal mine. #actonclimate #ParisAgreeement https://t.co/Lr3esBRtuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Nigeria didn't join because it wasn't strong enough.) https://t.co/G90ZN0F1Qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responsible journalism from @weatherchannel. #ParisAgreeement https://t.co/ZsRUZ3tTV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: U.S. Senate Hall of Shame: these 22 Senators urged Trump to pull the U.S. from the Paris climate accord, joining outliers S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: At what point do they start laughing at us as a country?

Now. https://t.co/SlPYWRkuOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: Trump's decision to withdraw the US from the Paris climate agreement is an abdication of American leadership and an interna…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hanchennrdc: Trump continues making false claims about China and India and the Paris Agreement https://t.co/wfVoeJwZ2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: BREAKING: President Trump announced his decision to withdraw the U.S. from the #ParisAgreement. This is a foolish &amp; reckless mist…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. is not "the world leader in environmental protection," least of all since the beginning of this speech. #parisagreement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBWall: "Here's how Earth could suffer." —@weatherchannel on Trump's despicable actions today #ActOnClimate https://t.co/lmF1eKvlm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: Pulling out of the Paris Agreement would be a massive step back for racial justice, and an assault on communities of color across…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Benioff: Dear President Trump, as some of the largest companies in the US, we strongly urge you to keep the US in the Paris Agreement.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: He’s abandoning U.S. climate and clean energy leadership. He’s breaking our promise to the rest of the world. https://t.co/RnE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's announcement on the #ParisAgreement coming in 30 minutes. It's the deep breath before the plunge. https://t.co/5zQbIDPaDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenKamalaHarris: We can either be part of a climate change solution or force generations to come to deal with this problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMConstible: This is a dark week for our climate &amp; health, but at least it's a pretty day for 5 pm #ParisAgreement rally at the White H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WRIClimate: U.S. states play an important leadership role for advancing the #ParisAgreement | #ActonClimate https://t.co/3CmGtPaYXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could only possibly be true if you're talking about a literal, physical fight. https://t.co/u2NVjUJU2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowy_types Seeing @andrewbird on Sunday! With Spoon. And Belle &amp; Sebastian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTW, the first words of the Boy Scout Law are "a scout is trustworthy." Not that it would be the first law he broke. https://t.co/dS3daPd7XQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaanastasia @AaronCouch Thunder god hangs out with superheroes sometimes. Hijinks ensue. Sometimes because his brother is sneaky evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: Trump's NYT comments revealed he has zero sense of obligation to public.

In the last 24 hours, it's gotten worse.

http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean what could a health plan cost?

"$12 dollars"?

 https://t.co/QCGandlg2D https://t.co/P0ruRASVKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EnergyDems: David Bernhardt didn’t respect science during his first stint @Interior &amp; he won’t this time either #foxinthehenhouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clocking in at 4.6 misleading statements per day from our president: https://t.co/Cd0jnD2VRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin is boasting about 
1) forgoing their responsibilities and 
2) following through on illegal 1-for-2 order
https://t.co/aMPOJD0kIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientist at @Interior blows whistle on Trump admin sabotaging agencies and silencing truth of #climate impacts:
  
https://t.co/ayBrKF5BUW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>