<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/udeTYDExgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/n8PwyQ4KWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/svQtcI9wkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/Q2X07rCPhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/U6frNkUaMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/JzO2iktceC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/SdMcWhRvz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/GDvJVgb7Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/ideVLmSrys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/gNATUKxSsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/Cw59RqKcQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/p2eXIqH5og]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/zUfX3GiUqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/m0WtJBEGyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/fxvkhZ7aMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/oFDylEh0wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/uu7UtONT8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/YLcEzQL6zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/K8wn2D0RUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/iqU6XbmHoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/hiPPpTHA63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/P1GMebdVWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/gsorSLvtFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/3El52AnqZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/IopXnZEcfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/DlWRhC0Pg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/MInk11T3Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/wA2SyGpFeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/INGH7HaAW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/CmmSwwnA8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/MtN4PrmEVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/NVmf4e5gpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/fmhlvArwoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/fONK8F6ga4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/4vGyLcxtUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/0cEza05RJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/JazFMU5bGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/GDvJVgb7Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/sfOc023PT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/n8PwyQ4KWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/i6WuOJdirF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/HSTUcdpXf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/YLcEzQL6zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/bpD2MiTsc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/sEc0VedoYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/vXtmy4PhpE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>