<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Rural Council Celebrates Its One Year Anniversary: 

    President Barack Obama holds a town ha... http://t.co/kJszz8ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Guide Highlights Best Practices and Innovations in Helping Veterans Thrive in the Private Sector: 
	Last Nov... http://t.co/JXUNauAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Must Act to Keep Our Teachers on the Job: 
	President Obama urges Congress to take acti... http://t.co/MEKs7hYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: The Road to Recovery: 

  Click here to see the video. 

		Here's a quick glimpse at this... http://t.co/uYwp2Azh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes NY Giants to the White House: 

    President Barack Obama welcomes the four-time ... http://t.co/1VNoBKZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses the State of the Economy: 

    President Barack Obama delivers a statement on th... http://t.co/qTIrGDlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Good News for Women and Families: 
	Today we got more good news showing the difference the health care law ... http://t.co/ygUMEbcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join Us for an Online Seniors’ Health Town Hall: 
	This past Thursday, officials from the White House and the De... http://t.co/K7KGgXD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 06/08/2012 or "Roll Up Our Sleeves and Never Quit": 
	This week, the President traveled to Honey... http://t.co/9294MHgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Talks Income Based Repayment at UNLV: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks on coll... http://t.co/e4I16KWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Refi?  You tell us.: 
	Yesterday, we told you about President Obama’s proposal to cut through the red tape t... http://t.co/6jpbLDHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Southern Stanza: 
	Ed. note: This is a cross-post from the blog of the Library of Congress. It originally appe... http://t.co/QqThUbU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping Americans Manage Student Loan Debt: 
	Ed note: this post originally appeared on Treasury Notes, the offi... http://t.co/NUnhOrsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: College Affordability: 
	This afternoon, President Obama is traveling to UNLV where he... http://t.co/C0OqHVr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting Jobs in the American Wind Industry: 

    Heather Zichal speaks at the WINDPOWER 2012 Conference... http://t.co/o479ItHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Income Based Repayment: Everything You Need to Know: 
	Over the past several years, the Obama Administration has... http://t.co/SoeLbnx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the Facts on Tax Cuts: 
	Recently there’s been renewed debate about whether Republicans will stick by th... http://t.co/psqPLjBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Want Your Feedback: 
	Millions of families who bought homes before the financial crisis are locked in at the ... http://t.co/mNq59RXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Discusses College Affordability with College and University Officials: 

    Vice President ... http://t.co/br1MLThn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress Says No to Equal Pay: 
	Equal pay for women is about more than just fairness. Women are breadwinners in... http://t.co/kkPXoLZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $26,000: 

	Today’s college students graduate with an average of $26,000 in student loan debt.... http://t.co/N2dNLek7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reaching Out to Fight Veteran Homelessness: 
	The White House would like to congratulate the finalists dedicated... http://t.co/cqHHJ9qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama’s Message for Queen Elizabeth II: 
	President Obama took a moment to record a message for Queen ... http://t.co/p8BDlkjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equipping Small Business with More Tools: Procurement Day at National Small Business Week: 
	Ed Note: This is a ... http://t.co/aQ5UnCiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join Us for an Online Women’s Health Town Hall: 
	As part of our focus on women’s health, the White House and th... http://t.co/vaLCT3p0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance Rebates on the Way: 
	Consumers across the country are starting to hear the good news about their heal... http://t.co/VieSAkIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $431,000: 

	The gender wage gap puts women at a... http://t.co/bSMm3Hcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Rosye Cloud: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to wor... http://t.co/gOEO3iZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Lookback” Progress: 
	President Obama is committed to a regulatory approach that protects public safety and wel... http://t.co/pWwNFhYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're Invited: Learn More About the Paycheck Fairness Act: 
	President Obama has long supported equal pay for e... http://t.co/IcrErrBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: It’s Time for Congress to Get to Work: 
	President Obama speaks to the American people from a Ho... http://t.co/17SJktFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Sacrifices and Accomplishments: 

  Click here to see the video. 

	Here's a quick glimpse ... http://t.co/jTuXFjc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama: We Have to Deliver for Our Veterans: 
	In Minnesota today, President Obama was introduced by Ry... http://t.co/GZwfTzrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Entrepreneurs Are Creating Jobs: An Interactive Timeline: 
	The worst economic crisis since the Great Depr... http://t.co/LclIkar8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equal Pay for Equal Work?: 
	It's 2012, but did you know that women are still paid less than men?

	On average, ... http://t.co/V1yof4lD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for this Year’s Hurricane Season: 
	Today marks the start of the 2012 Atlantic Hurricane Season. Under... http://t.co/0HZlM5b2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in May: 
	Problems in the job market were long in the making and will not be solved ove... http://t.co/TKhKWB8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 05/31/12 or "Each of Them Loved This Country . . . More Than Life Itself.": 
	This week, the Pre... http://t.co/LEuuyTrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Unveils the Official Portrait of President George W. Bush: 

    President Barack Obama and... http://t.co/8pyFYmEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May Morning Harvest in the White House Garden: 
	Back in March, a group of students from across the country join... http://t.co/lbas1LWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prioritizing Low-Income Families and Creating Pathways to Opportunity for All Americans: 
	Ed. Note: This op-ed ... http://t.co/bJ4X7hTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: John Holdren: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to wo... http://t.co/VV1SJrMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden at West Point: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	Last weekend, Vice President Bi... http://t.co/bAf18nNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs Renewal of the Export-Import Bank: 

    President Barack Obama signs the Export-Impo... http://t.co/0cx3ZMXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Medal of Freedom Means to Me: John Glenn: 
	When President Obama presented John Glenn with the Presiden... http://t.co/8QoOqifk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Medal of Freedom Means to Me: Madeleine Albright: 
	When President Obama presented Madeleine Albright w... http://t.co/1S0dyPST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State and District Education Leaders Collaborate to Transform the Teaching Profession: 
	Last week, state and di... http://t.co/YU57xo38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Awards the Medal of Freedom: 
	Today, President Obama honored 13 Americans with the Presidential... http://t.co/tnD3EsGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Care and the House of Representatives: By the Numbers: 
	The health care law President Obama signed in 20... http://t.co/ZENNIJBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask an Expert: Why Am I Locked Out Of Refinancing Just Because My Mortgage Isn't Backed By A GSE?: 
	Tomorrow, S... http://t.co/uzYOAyrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 97 Percent: 

	President Obama is calling on Congress to extend the middle class tax cuts for ... http://t.co/KGTbDmZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Hmvs3cbO Launches New Resources for Spanish-Speaking Homeowners at Risk of Foreclosure: 
	Studie... http://t.co/CYMrA7ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 98 Percent: 

	Yesterday, President Obama called on Congress to extend the middle-class tax cu... http://t.co/DTYTbikM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask an Expert: How Are We Helping Underwater Borrowers?: 
	On Thursday, Secretary of Housing and Urban Developme... http://t.co/xJjXSC7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House responds to a We the People Petition on the Bush Tax Cuts: 
	Today, the White House responded to... http://t.co/udTBmp77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask an Expert About Refinancing: 
	This afternoon, we sent the message below to the White House email list to he... http://t.co/SwWuGthp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extending Middle Class Tax Cuts for 98% of Americans and 97% of Small Businesses: 
	Today the President called o... http://t.co/6XL2r09l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs Bill to Create Jobs, Restore America's Transportation System: 
	Ed. Note: This is a cross-... http://t.co/xNrjmrSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us for a White House Google+ Hangout with Secretary Donovan Moderated by Zillow, Inc.: 
	Today, home intere... http://t.co/GCG9ti9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Pushing Congress to Create Jobs, Keep College in Reach for Middle Class: 
	President Obama discu... http://t.co/OwuWbKQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: President Obama Hosts a Twitter Town Hall: 
	One year ago today, July 6, 2011, President Obam... http://t.co/UZsB5vQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs the Transportation and Student Loan Bill: 
	This afternoon, President Obama signed legisla... http://t.co/wDZzrpoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Summer Jobs+ Helped Me: 
	Ed. Note: Aviation High School in New York City is a uniquely specialized, co-educ... http://t.co/JqP7eTOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Your Voice Matters on Student Loans: 
	Just a few weeks ago, there was a real possibility that Congress woul... http://t.co/tXjPTzrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in June: 
	While the economy is continuing to heal from the worst economic downturn sin... http://t.co/QeMCH1t2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 7/6/2012 or "The Freedom Everybody is Looking For": 
	This week, the President traveled to Color... http://t.co/diCu6Tjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: President Obama Travels to Russia, Italy, and Ghana: 
	On July 5, 2009, President Obama embar... http://t.co/1dTU2DOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourth of July at the White House: 

    Brad Paisley performs on the South Lawn of the White House, July... http://t.co/Sp3aq2Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Salutes New American Citizens: 

    President Barack Obama listens as Secretary of Homelan... http://t.co/8fWJTy83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Remembers Andy Griffith: 
	Andy Griffith, who charmed audiences for half a century as an actor, ... http://t.co/C2rgSRn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America the Beautiful: 
	Musician Keb Mo recently visited the White House and performed his bluesy rendition of ... http://t.co/WQYvX5bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Independence Day at the White House: 
	In each of the past three years, President Obama has marked I... http://t.co/wmOVGK3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: A Fourth of July with the Presidents: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	See the fu... http://t.co/CdaYJEeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Affordable Care Act by the Numbers: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	Upheld last week by the Sup... http://t.co/QV4J7jLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community Colleges: Bridges to the Future: 
	Last week, I continued my Community College to Career tour at Valen... http://t.co/YTpDTn90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama at the African Methodist Episcopal Church's General Conference: 

    First Lady ... http://t.co/QH5GzI6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: An All-Hands-On-Deck Approach to Fighting the Colorado Wildfires: 
	President Obama speaks to th... http://t.co/TZnd0JvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major Step Forward for Gulf Coast Restoration: 
	Today Congress took a major step in our efforts to restore the ... http://t.co/s6t7xE84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Reflection of Our Values: 
	Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on http://t.co/4TLOL8vz:

  Cl... http://t.co/1CSsxq1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partnership for Sustainable Communities Marks Three Years Helping Communities Build a Foundation for Prosperity:... http://t.co/lsZIYz9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.3 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/KtjYJG0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Tours Wildfire Damage in Colorado: 

    President Barack Obama tours fire damage with elec... http://t.co/pd6GGAZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landmark Court Decision Upholds EPA's Actions to Protect Families: 
	Earlier this week, the United States Court ... http://t.co/DfDLeO29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upholding the Affordable Care Act is a Win for Small Businesses: 
	The Supreme Court’s decision this week to uph... http://t.co/En7IhHeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 6/29/121 or "The Right Thing to Do": 
	This week, the President spoke at the annual NALEO confer... http://t.co/ZE5osNon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natoma Canfield's Letter to President Obama: 
		This letter in my office is a reminder of how health reform bene... http://t.co/KsdejskQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: The Affordable Care Act: 
	Today, the Supreme Court announced its decision to uphold t... http://t.co/49M4QDIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Upholds President Obama's Health Care Reform: 

	Today, the Supreme Court's decision to uphold t... http://t.co/felqvmjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretary of Education Arne Duncan Answers Your Questions on College Affordability: 
	Since the State of the Uni... http://t.co/p75oYgKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Momentum: 
	As of this week, more than 100 public and private sector partners have come together throug... http://t.co/dQah49zh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you share this?: 
	We've been talking to you about President Obama's plan to cut through the red tape keepi... http://t.co/vOCiRJDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See How the Health Care Law Is Helping People in Your State: 
	President Obama signed the health care law – the ... http://t.co/3mVm9FbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Is National HIV Testing Day: 
	To locate an HIV testing site near you, text your Zip Code to “KNOWIT” (566... http://t.co/XTLtVVQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 States Have Now Passed Pro-Military Spouse License Portability Measures: 
	Earlier today in Chicago, I had th... http://t.co/1Mis79dB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religious Leaders Support President Obama’s Stance on Immigration Reform: 
	From Pope Benedict to prominent Prot... http://t.co/iUjb40Yq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responding to Tropical Storm Debby: 
	Tropical Storm Debby tracked eastward today, dropping as much as 20 inches... http://t.co/6MR74jjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours with Secretary of Education Arne Duncan: 
	Secretary of Education Arne Duncan is joinin... http://t.co/RXBWLQAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Us Shape Our Strategy for Intellectual Property Enforcement: 
	Today my office is starting the process of g... http://t.co/oC8mMznx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would You Qualify for Refi? Find Out: 
	Did yout know that the average homeowner could save $3,000 a year by ref... http://t.co/Y8bKazx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tropical Storm Debby forms in the Gulf of Mexico: 
	Ed. Note: This is cross-posted from the FEMA blog.

	Today’s... http://t.co/4qlNX8dS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>