<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/5gQl3zPgtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/UGf9VlQYdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/1PzIFztnIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/FRX0lmrNo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/YmvlRmaqTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/jJJsF5TdZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/QEFxFgrQhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/tvcfwNoqmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/HjQMvs3xeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/0zkBj9r8vG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/j8OG666mmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/l5PSLnvJX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trouble with a kitten is that eventually it becomes a Cat - Ogden Nash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/wtbUU1NlHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/6qtfsM7wRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/Q3SxTaD63H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/CTB71yMgVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/M3KJe7NnQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/5f6HmjWzuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/rZoLhX8zLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/3gV7zCBj44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/JqgCROp4jX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/ogyIHzEU8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Z7G79WdgZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/jUwAiYkuF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/GUVaNLRJyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/tj1ospzAdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/YEGJlHIi3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/m0ECmDE6M7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/MSNDkj2h7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/PLEiv8dDbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/JKJdl5OppX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/OqRJZ30Gf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/p5hJgy9kAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/CF0DSNx0yh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/u91q9WeKqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/m0ECmDE6M7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/AufxRBjAAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/ybI9z59KQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/E9HsIQxe6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of The Hollywood Sign  http://t.co/S576iDwpXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/IN1x8JT7Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/KrXv3wQ7JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/BtNngdt1zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/bZ6E1B7LHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/jp1C64CVCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/fubVwMVmDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>