<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/li3GfcTCL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/pprRvePc4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/XReXIMhjD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/h3tWqjbZDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/caTpx5JPTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/ab6JYrNiNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ZUO1CbGopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/WFu7LSJQ1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/KRELeL6M4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/zs7TvOvc6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/TJ5kWZ3P2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/MK6dTVnHe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/bP68ELRj5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/LDkjb7QJvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/m9aKdyIagW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/AOBCytu5GI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/BuFxW35rxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/OVaJyZ7OpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/UFSZShtY8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/m22XP4IODI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/beiebCR8yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/NSuw31upg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/Wl352qgZqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/roNPJTbvbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/k7e2VDii4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoes are special shoes for discerning feet. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/mBOlZxYjCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/ipEMVws8Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/czQV0f7vv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/gJ8k4UcXdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/fSUbuvcWQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/nsjO0PUWOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/2SNfFUEvQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/ivTszceztS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/3rkqGXcQOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/gQu5rXSQS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/LCjvTzr22e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/3FlHYmP27X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/CFayE4bXeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/cVXJXqsGTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/GwL7FIbeCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/hVhQbcb3x0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/pLNEgyYEMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/yn8jDZSbz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/3YO2dSTEZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/8E0wyvav2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/7pohNj6IOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/NjnEWMy0j6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/7dA5iVnlqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>