<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicSchulenberg1 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brexitproblems Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GA_London: Learn how to use analytical tools to make data driven design decisions @ishmatt &gt;&gt; https://t.co/KAwXdcWgTo https://t.co/HMWC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballRamble: Our first book, about the joys (and despair) of football, is available in all formats to buy now! Christmas is around t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YellowLabs_NZ Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HRWright: This has got to be the best party political broadcast of all time. https://t.co/iZDsRGeTQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to use mouse heatmaps for UX research https://t.co/mFjkMmapcP https://t.co/4PW1Lvm8om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting ideas about how to alter our relationship with technology (mobile): The Binge Breaker https://t.co/TcR2T3b4vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarinaHyde: Only time I saw Coburn was on UKIP flotilla. He was waving a glass of sauvignon blanc &amp; bellowing "this is what real fisher…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: use vertical filters https://t.co/GS8IRtN8LC https://t.co/7UEyZXG6FS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThoughtDoctorTV Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Promoter Score: What a Customer-Relations Metric Can Tell You About Your User Experience https://t.co/WUH96IgKxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a free guide to 10 tools for Evidence-Based UX Design https://t.co/FHr0khHPyt #ux https://t.co/4fbi3eEsES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jburnmurdoch: The tweetstorm was great, the article is even better. @mixedknuts nails the case for smarter football commentary https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: keep checkout a single column https://t.co/eeat9CWBWm https://t.co/Z9G9dEEcb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @susborne: Great bit of Brexit map geekery. This one shows areas where &gt;50% of eligible voters voted one way or the other. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahcpr: Donald Trump reminds me of this Fred Armisen character who can't finish a single sentence https://t.co/hlV3cL2RmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the next few years look like for VR https://t.co/44QqPIksny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDataJunki Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating and basically the last word on Trump https://t.co/t0Mmt1O6Gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: start with great images https://t.co/3k2Sq6GXnc https://t.co/ZsjXxplguu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Information Architecture Warning Signs in Your Analytics Reports https://t.co/xlwwAqUEo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VertoAnalytics Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: have a clear button to start shopping https://t.co/qCDrOkTBv2 https://t.co/FzmHpbYssA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ecommerce UX Design Hints &amp; Tips, a guide https://t.co/2ZLbVYKbks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rafaelbehr: We're gonna get a huge deal. You've never seen a deal this huge. Really. It's such a beautiful deal. And we're gonna make G…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The unprofitable SaaS business model trap (and the myth of growth to profit) https://t.co/vGGUv3hVwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wejumpstart Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhonescoreNet Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting on the Apple Music balancing act https://t.co/AfvYcqVZJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wearehanno Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising's Century of Flat-Line Growth https://t.co/A5byMsYTWt &lt; they don't increase, they just move platform https://t.co/ap1GDeKMfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good tips for simplifying search filtering https://t.co/7q02o2iPdl https://t.co/FSAXFMpfh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why VR won't take over everything, especially not our workspaces https://t.co/MTULIeNeYx https://t.co/fh81pCJhzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyGirling Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/hx3yULUQy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithdevon Not sure what the options are there, I just record my voice and the audio coming from speakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithdevon For anything I want to record off my screen I just use Quicktime's screen recording function, which tends to do the job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Immorality of Corbynism https://t.co/qJ6SkdGPGp https://t.co/qLzeZrLund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uxcam: The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Customer Interviews
https://t.co/hPEN8mhZjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aygyun_gyul: The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide https://t.co/Bk2pRJWrPl via @ishmatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Anatomy of The Perfect Mobile E-Commerce Checkout Page https://t.co/M8tPK1ZtUS &lt; Good advice here https://t.co/u432Rhhz8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brownorama: Post-truth = lying
Fake news = propaganda
Alt-right = white supremacy

Prevent double-speak.
Use the correct words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to encrypt your entire life in less than an hour https://t.co/MDLFUzLU3H &lt; Handy advice now the gov will be keeping records on you https://t.co/xTHWrU5upL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamParkhomenko: Hillary has received more votes for president than any white male in the history of the United States. Including Donal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a thing I wrote about doing good Customer Interviews https://t.co/M1WqFEZeqo #ux https://t.co/yviK193RkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Negativity Bias in User Experience https://t.co/0SKHIRz81S &lt; Why getting the basics right matters so much more in UX https://t.co/sUcS17nRnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Election from The Post-Truth Future https://t.co/OwC5FQDgt8 &lt; The West is turning into China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProductPlan: The Evidence-Based #UX Guide: 28 methods with ranked by how often they should be used in your #design process. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JOE_co_uk: When Nigel met Donald... https://t.co/zLRbrZT3gW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending out my latest email newsletter tomorrow (and every Wednesday) https://t.co/wmwJrX1bfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewjrivera Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Best practices' should just be a starting point... https://t.co/Pib4IbC6us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Law_and_policy: "Don't you understand that the government can't show its cards?"

But there are no cards, never have been. They don't h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConversionSci Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wowprotein Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: The World Is Getting Better https://t.co/1oWx2isrj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson What you need is an app...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Instagram Is Destroying Our Natural Wonders (and inspiring people to get outside too) https://t.co/sXwVbIXngW https://t.co/N7NEKWHMQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ustwo Rethinks the Agency Business Model https://t.co/FoGITJinMn &lt;&lt;&lt; All about diversifying revenue streams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UXColumbo Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robdelaney: Beautiful! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 https://t.co/jD6PKNHirC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charlesarthur: This is great by @jamesallworth explaining both Brexit and Trump: humans demand fair division of spoils https://t.co/GKO…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Marine Le Pen is a guest on @MarrShow tomorrow.
Right wing extremism should never be given a platform - especially on Re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emilybell: NB Mark Zuckerberg's tone on fake news on Facebook is reminiscent of Twitter on trolls and abuse, which didn't end well. Per…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rschooley: Trump is already bored to death.  https://t.co/rh5CUHjhbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Has Quietly Dropped Ban on Personally Identifiable Web Tracking https://t.co/vNcZcSRrg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iCandySF Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last liberals https://t.co/t0XMvkPCw6 "80% of Canadians think immigrants are good for the economy" https://t.co/e9quX2ATKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson Lets just keep an eye on him, check he doesn't show any aspirations to be in politics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prediction: Donald Trump will be the Sam Allardyce of the American Presidency. I give him two months. https://t.co/3ElGwzt7Y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read on their history &gt;&gt;&gt; Alastair Campbell vs The Mail https://t.co/foMQzRi8m4 https://t.co/WKxtrOajPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Sacking Off the City and Moving to the Countryside Actually Make You Happier? https://t.co/lDs3yp7bo5 (A: Yep) https://t.co/a8HkewTHBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidanparr Tempted to redraw them all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidanparr Has potential! I struggled with them being arranged in four semi-circles – would be good if lined up in rows for comparison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magical history tour: the Beatles in infographics &lt; disappointing, other than clothing one, none need to be graphics https://t.co/AdLCqQhnQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide https://t.co/VyGIZG32Iy https://t.co/4GMAJjle52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's I thing I've signed that you can sign to try and change the messages people get fed: https://t.co/dQlnVzWu7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jk_rowling: ... said the free man freely on free media. Nobody's silencing you. What you mean is, you don't like disagreement. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Harkaway: Because I don't know if you've noticed, but 1) it effectively provides for warrantless surveillance and intrusion for three d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acjimbo: It'll be interesting to see the reaction to this. A simple point, gracefully made https://t.co/TO1XOhrupj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's Middle-of-Nowhere Strategy in Rural Japan https://t.co/Do1aglXWWP https://t.co/u9bTogZpjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoidaLawGroup Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: start with great images https://t.co/yP7UlutCyx https://t.co/f4xMvzDFXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joelgolby: Sam Kriss can really fucking write https://t.co/qnyXxKOnjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great takedown of some particularly sketchy startups: The "Women Are Broken" Industry https://t.co/QWt02nNkgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MediocreDave: The poor, disenfranchised, working class Americans sending a message to the liberal elite. https://t.co/oDdAZyJOzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thugclive: Trump is just the final logical step for a nation that can't deal with losing it's footing, it's excesses and it's vanities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff on the challenge facing so many new ecommerce businesses... Free Shipping Is A Lie https://t.co/4Z3lzSbSY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeOttenX: Look on the bright side. Trump could easily have been lying about everything he intends to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not good news for the stereotype of the ignorant American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure I can handle seeing his face any more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up after votes in 2016... not this again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! https://t.co/WYjNro7Ga7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of book selling is small book shops... https://t.co/Mxuhrg7948]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoanasimsWarren Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy impressive... Your brilliant Kickstarter idea could be on sale in China before you’ve even finished funding it https://t.co/YMAowwqLW7 https://t.co/u12AX9nrer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markhurrell Very much enjoyed. Loved the the filmmaker at the end asking why he was allowed to film *shrug*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeHolden42: @IanDunt After Article 50 is triggered... https://t.co/zMqdHVyuHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mapfelba: This seems to sum up both campaigns nicely. Data &amp; discipline v. Misogyny &amp; excuses @bpolitics https://t.co/RMyVTOkEo0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>