<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft BI Developer: MICROSOFT BI DEVELOPER QUALIFICATIONS * 1+ year contract for a Microsoft BI Developer with multiple possibilities for renewal. * Mid to Sr. level BI Developer. * Strong SSIS and TSQL knowledge. * Knowledge of SSAS and… https://t.co/SMNP30X2HT https://t.co/IrZhhJjhTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager – Companion Diagnostics: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables,… https://t.co/4pAhvU6w2A https://t.co/7dUd15nSDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Configuration/Release Engineer: Tesla, Inc. has the following positions available at its Palo Alto corporate headquarters and the Tesla campuses in Fremont and San Mateo. PALO ALTO POSITIONS Engineering Firmware Engineer. GG-031191. Approx.… https://t.co/vTjgVohzWU https://t.co/SEaoXrg1AH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk Network Administrator: Do you have the right stuff? Gullview Technologies is an exciting new and rapidly growing technology company focused on taking on the most vital and challenging business and technical challenges our clients face in… https://t.co/KPwK8QuBGN https://t.co/fRumAYFbj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to install &amp; maintain critical sys’s running red Hat Enterprise Linux &amp; Suse Linux employing enterprise cluster apps in 24×7 datacenter environ. Bachelor’s in Comp Sci, Eng’g, Math, or… https://t.co/N1gAd70dgF https://t.co/90dDfxER6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Location San Diego – CA, US Level Master Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 4/13/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Electrical Engineering, Design Engineering Background Software Engineering, Information Technology,… https://t.co/T861w9PF01 https://t.co/OfVIvWXogp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Retail Minor Renovation): Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY Thank you for your interest in CBRE. This position is being published in an effort to build our candidate pipeline for our upcoming opportunities. If an opportunity opens… https://t.co/vB6RV4Y8D0 https://t.co/4G91vLpqHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst II or III #80237P: Information Technology Services (ITS) at Iowa State University is seeking qualified candidates for a Systems Analyst position. Depending on the level of experience, the individual may be hired as a Systems Analyst II or… https://t.co/NsLJ2LgZnQ https://t.co/R2PqsdKmK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/IuzjxV4fF9 https://t.co/VReUzCMUqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer OR: Test Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime position Job Description: Responsible for writing test cases, executing tests and automating tests for the OPAE, which is the software infrastructure for Intel Xeon +FPGA… https://t.co/DHoHk4fCAI https://t.co/yAUDa9alfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Supply Chain Management Director: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/4paAZ3vtGh https://t.co/cGNRQe3UoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title Senior Mission-Critical Software Developer for GNC Systems: Job Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 2 months ago(2/26/2018 4:59 PM) Requisition ID 2017-2999 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development… https://t.co/IS84jbSDg3 https://t.co/a7IjRcrlZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Terminal Developer: Scientific Games is a global leader in providing customized, end-to-end gaming solutions to lottery and gaming organizations worldwide. Scientific Games’ integrated array of products and services include instant lottery games,… https://t.co/DpZtS4NhS3 https://t.co/OkvbZx5U6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Writer: UX Writer Job ID #: 7808 Location: VA – Richmond Shockoe Position Category: Marketing Department: Marketing and Advertising Division: CarMax Home Office Education Required: Not Indicated Position Type: Full-Time Regular Relocation Provided:… https://t.co/54cOZanfoD https://t.co/zgpzHlrsZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Engineer: ENGINEERING: Software Development Engineer (LogMeIn USA, Inc. Mountain View, CA) Develop, test, troubleshoot, maintain &amp; debug components for existing &amp; new applications software products throughout software engineering lifecycle.… https://t.co/qUS6l3GYK5 https://t.co/bkRgQ6WvJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: Technology: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: Business Intelligence Analyst (Requisition#A44URZ) Manage Data &amp; Logistics system that drive &amp; support the operations for Apple in the Americas… https://t.co/WYJHxUkSlx https://t.co/3jgtZvB97Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer: Bendix Commercial Vehicle Systems LLC, Engineer 2, Test, Irvine, CA. Design, develop and test automation, intelligent systems, industrial systems control, and coordinate and provide engineering support to conduct standard and… https://t.co/hbVr0MvVul https://t.co/6KRIIxKcRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Engineer Software 3 (18008765) Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18008765 Location : United States-California-El Segundo US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/x9CuCgeJOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Mgr Sr-EPMO: Duties and Responsibilities This position provides management for all phases of Strategic Enterprise Projects as identified by UMB Executive Management. Responsible for managing one or more projects within the constraints of scope,… https://t.co/7XvYWT7DEI https://t.co/lhwhwXWe8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructor Developer: Komatsu is an indispensable partner to the construction, mining, industrial and forestry industries that maximizes value for customers through innovative solutions. With a full line of products supported by our advanced IoT… https://t.co/Fz7LPMxCPq https://t.co/jCWc9bdxFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Systems Development Specialist Principal: Location: Springfield, Virginia Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Office Job Summary The role of the System Development Specialist Principal is to design, code, test,… https://t.co/XexGGS7z6d https://t.co/j7G5HoJqsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Developer II – Ref #COLSTA: Computer Molina Healthcare of Ohio, Inc. has an opportunity in Columbus, OH for a Report Developer II. Experience with SSIS or DTS required. Must be legally authorize to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. An Equal… https://t.co/OtXc9ef8Lw https://t.co/62CGzp3Rlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Test Engineer – Job No. 1800006I: Senior Quality Assurance (QA) Test Engineer (First Data Technologies, Inc. – Hagerstown, MD): Job No. 1800006I Duties: Establish best practices and provide technical solutions to validating… https://t.co/2iR9kcT9Tg https://t.co/HpKj7w7oVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/08qFna5sZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2 – Real Time Software Engineer: Active Secret Clearance, NOT REQUIRED to start. Assists with the development, documentation and maintenance of architectures, requirements, algorithms, interfaces and designs for software systems.… https://t.co/OBUYSdq6e3 https://t.co/qBcyxItDn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Software Development: OVERVIEW Teradek manufactures wireless video devices for remote video capture, live ENG backhaul, real-time monitoring, proxy recording and webcasting. For complex IP video systems, Teradek’s cloud-based management… https://t.co/XYFojO1d6n https://t.co/dJF445lj0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/J2EE Web Applications Developer: Req ID: 21427    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market… https://t.co/TCZpCK3aUd https://t.co/7HOstk7RVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer – Autonomous Haulage System Innovation. Quality. Results. We are Modular Made. Modular Mining Systems is the global leader in mine management technology and a wholly owned subsidiary of Komatsu Ltd. Our… https://t.co/7V0HAoh6K4 https://t.co/BqULC9osQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: At Maxwell, we are inspired by the opportunity to make a difference in society by helping people make better health, wellness and financial decisions. We build applications that support a rich set of interactions among… https://t.co/UB7DKuQFFi https://t.co/XJhiLcslG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Entry: Web Developer – Entry Ref No.:18-00187 Category: ************* Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD, Maryland Position Type:Full-time Experience Level: 2 Years Start Date: 05/14/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work… https://t.co/RALr9Z0BT3 https://t.co/GztUILuVQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Developer: .Net Software Developer ======================= Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description As an emerging authority,… https://t.co/xOvG1MJqJm https://t.co/fHVp1rJuV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Product Engineer – Data Science: Location San Diego – CA, US Level Master Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2/23/2018 Functional area Manufacturing, Electrical Engineering, Research &amp; Development Background Physics / Mathematics, Information… https://t.co/xcjvwMSWSq https://t.co/ukZMqyIXN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Engineer: About Us: Mercury Protocol is the future of communications, powered by blockchain. We are a well funded, early-stage startup with a world-class team that is backed by Mark Cuban. Based in Los Angeles, we are a passionate team… https://t.co/vyu3i163s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Drive Software Engineer: There are 7 billion people on this planet. And by 2050, there will be 2 billion more… many moving into urban centers at an unprecedented rate. Making sure there is enough food, fiber and infrastructure for our rapidly… https://t.co/96oDGjKrst https://t.co/oow5Izqol0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Engineer: Granite Background &amp; History Granite is one of the premier communications services provider to businesses across the United States and Canada. We provide exceptional customized service with an emphasis on reliability and outstanding… https://t.co/3QIf6U0UMV https://t.co/o8K2XR4LNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Contract Renewals: About the Team: Our Maintenance Renewals Team is currently looking for an intern or temp to possible hire for their busy group in Waltham, MA. As a member of the Account Maintenance team you will be responsible for following… https://t.co/dMquJPNYJf https://t.co/pMhTayz8oQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (North Reading): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and… https://t.co/htp06qvcNz https://t.co/OI0d974Nyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/Yl7xx0L5GY https://t.co/1MWIfK5gL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Developer: Were looking for a Full Stack developer who will take a key role on our team. Our Full Stack developer must have knowledge in all stages of software development. Youll be working alongside other engineers and developers,… https://t.co/vBh5l8n9e2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Specialist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fayetteville, NC Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/8/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to… https://t.co/Gzi1FwMIYR https://t.co/ROkjPXP1zC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Java Architect Ref No.: 18-21409 Location: jersey city, New Jersey Hi, This isAnuradhafromEnterprise Solution Inc.I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Please send your updated resume if interested for this role… https://t.co/5HAevEjsEX https://t.co/nCSjeNHCez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer: The Kennedy Center is the nation’s busiest performing arts center, offering over 2000 performances and welcoming over two million visitors a year.  The IT Department provides, supports and maintains all the technology systems used by… https://t.co/QojFltGJZg https://t.co/w5H6ZBwnFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Ashland): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/rcFQLS8iaK https://t.co/5doqMNCbb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/SMd1zru04g https://t.co/1CGLW1Twiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Education Researcher–Digital Learning in Young Children, Literacy: Sr Education Researcher–Digital Learning in Young Children, Literacy Arlington, VA, Menlo Park, CA The SRI Education Early Learning Program is helping to further understanding and… https://t.co/Y4Y4ah7NX3 https://t.co/JwWWZqrHz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java: Req ID : 429706BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : The CSI Program is looking for world class SW engineers to build an Agile Development Team to support a system's development evolution to today's… https://t.co/5NiqdL3diO https://t.co/iOMI3V18So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer Graphics: Sr Software Engineer – 3D Graphics | HERE – Products &amp; Services – Industries – Partners – Vision – Company – Careers – Blog – ************* – Map Updates – Developer Portal – Map Community – HERE Automotive Suite – HERE… https://t.co/XTp19gBspe https://t.co/CafPUIFXej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer in Chantilly, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us –… https://t.co/m28X2tsohc https://t.co/SVfDZtMmEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Operations Project Manager: Company Description: Operating across the southeast, into the northeast &amp; mid-west, we provide industry leaders a workforce to perform residential installations, service and repairs for digital TV &amp; Internet… https://t.co/NLznPfZMjP https://t.co/ipMxLypu3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator:   Job Description – Systems Administrator (17008527) Systems Administrator Requisition ID : 17008527 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance available Clearance Type: Secret… https://t.co/zrjC6Gz2SN https://t.co/VxHSbpvxd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer Bellevue, Washington Job Duties: Design, develop and implement new tools for interactive game development. Analyze requirements and user needs for media pipeline tools, core engine editor tools, and backend infrastructure. Design and… https://t.co/FZunTr0Af5 https://t.co/f4BYmdafdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategy, Commercial &amp; Marketing Manager #R10001214: Strategy, Commercial &amp; Marketing Manager, Creative Solutions job open at Fox Networks Group, Inc. dba Fox Networks Digital Consumer Group in Los Angeles, CA.  recblid xmrjtzo30m31yi5f43wemmiw8aljij https://t.co/JU3XpSIywX https://t.co/Zb52kl2gQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager IT Client Support: Logistics done differently. You know how to bring out the best in your team. You’re ready to grow as a professional—to go bigger and better. At XPO Logistics, we know that strong leadership is at the heart of our… https://t.co/UiJb8wtMVo https://t.co/jsJZsY2WrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST: “Does your career fit your dreams?” ARE YOU IN AN INDUSTRY WITH A LOW INCOME CEILING OR HAS A LONG RAMP UP PERIOD? If so, our On Demand Loan Officer Training Academy may be an excellent opportunity for you! NO MORTGAGE… https://t.co/pk7oA3H5SW https://t.co/9oSvO4i6SQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metadata Analyst: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’ lives. We’ll help… https://t.co/avcjmrjyCP https://t.co/Ac0IHZZ3Yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sustaining Software Engineer: Sustaining Software Engineer – The Drobo Difference – myDrobo Platform – How It Works – BeyondRAID – Hybrid Storage Solutions – Products Direct Attached – 5C – 5D &amp; 5Dt – 5D3 – – Special EditionsNetwork Attached – 5N – 5N2 –… https://t.co/4f7IV6IoDK https://t.co/qbpo2ktU2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Software Tester (Cary, NC): Smart people. Great clients. A culture that fosters innovation, teamwork and professional enrichment. These are just a few reasons why so many individuals have built long and lucrative careers with IDeaS. That next… https://t.co/97sG5cBl9W https://t.co/sN4Q3o64Kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Automation Engineer: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a composite of… https://t.co/sM4crxcOSD https://t.co/Z8RJZdl97w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: – Associate Software Engineer – BLOG – COMMUNITY – LOGIN – Solutions – Customers – Platform – Apps – Resources – About – Get demo Associate Software Engineer Development San Francisco, United States Apply now Description… https://t.co/Yzwl3Wwpjp https://t.co/MLwvASVh9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer / Software Development Engineer: Workday Inc. is accepting resumes for the following positions at various levels in San Mateo, CA: Software Engineer / Software Development Engineer (P3/4-SESDESM 4/29) – Analyzes, designs, programs,… https://t.co/DOzylny4CH https://t.co/6oRBWveIwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – Data Acquisition, Integration and Analytics: Pharmacyclics is committed to the development and commercialization of novel therapies intended to improve the quality and duration of life and to resolve serious unmet medical needs for cancer… https://t.co/gd09SeovcR https://t.co/No42DaWlyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Analyst: Description: In this role you will work closely with the government Information Assurance Manager (IAM) in implementing DoD and Air Force Policy on the DC3 networks. Member of a team of IA professional’s responsible… https://t.co/epQUgCjSov https://t.co/QIjgZSIeTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Date Posted: 17/Apr/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: System Administrator Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories… https://t.co/StXeCwwlMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Web Developer: PRIMARY PURPOSE: Under minimum supervision, this position is responsible for assisting in the discovery, development, implementation, and support of software applications across BSI, its affiliates and business units. Responsible for… https://t.co/O93H20mMb1 https://t.co/PvxvjHy88P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developers – Mid to Sr. level: DESCRIPTION: Employer has an immediate opening for a mid to senior JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER with Web User Interface (UI) experience supporting the C2 Systems Division in San Diego, CA. Position will support the… https://t.co/zFohQsCkr3 https://t.co/aIResgjFL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASIC Design Engineer: Technology: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: ASIC Design Engineer (Req#A7T2PZ) Create software to verify architecture and functionality of pre-silicon hardware designs. ASIC Design Engineer… https://t.co/M1q143q6T1 https://t.co/VRLT9lTyfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Candia): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/QqYmHEsiQh https://t.co/qs2xNXTQ88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II- DOCSIS: Client Reference Code: 217414JOB SCOPE:Under limited supervision, assists in the planning, forecasting, implementation, and identification of resource requirements for network systems within the 11 different DOCSIS regions… https://t.co/jfV0xzTpxf https://t.co/4gcfvnsdHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Harrisburg, PA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today If you are an Architect with extensive application architecture experience, please read on! We are located in the beautiful Harrisburg, PA area and we are a leading IT/Electronics… https://t.co/7iKSzDuamk https://t.co/EnnIw2YuLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Solution Architect / Rockville, MD: Req ID : 431901BR Job Code/Title : E1804:Comp Systems Architect Stf Job Description : Lockheed Martin Corporation is currently seeking a Solutions Architect with a strong system architecture and technical leadership… https://t.co/pzrA4thQV5 https://t.co/W9s4wdzYvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Advisory Senior Consultant – IT Audit: Overview As a Top 20 CPA firm nationally, we combine deep industry experience, comprehensive accounting and advisory services and a strong commitment to personal service. Responsibilties * May provide the… https://t.co/INrBIQl3MO https://t.co/YTVNCJKlwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Specialist: Desktop Support Specialist REQ# *******M Position Overview The Desktop Support Specialist will identify and correct a wide variety of hardware and software problems through discussions with PC end users, application… https://t.co/SOB2DLOCVs https://t.co/9xYeghqQlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect, Postgres: Data Architect, Postgres – About – Our Story – Management – Board of Directors – Innovate with Us – Products – Health &amp; Nutrition – Personal Care – Industrial – News – Press Releases – Blog – Investors – Overview – Press… https://t.co/XVSNFrJyJq https://t.co/DsJvyrLidr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer- Sales Force: What you’ll be doing… Verizon Business Markets (VBM) is a newly created strategic business unit within Operations, to serve the wireline communications and networking technology needs of U.S.-based small and medium… https://t.co/Yru8Kptye3 https://t.co/EkT0AHtsxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIRTUALIZATION ENGINEER: Virtualization Engineer (Fort Worth, TX): Liaise with business owners to utilize the Application Lifecycle Framework. Collaborate with the Desktop Engineering Packaging team to ensure high standards. Maximize the number of… https://t.co/GhsmMx5KE4 https://t.co/bc7zrprwj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Product Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer (Req #8EH1919) Develop &amp; execute product qualification plans. Work on the product release of the tools. Technical Project/ Program… https://t.co/U4m3t4AEam https://t.co/L0639UyLhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Applications Engineer / Applications Engineer: ENGINEER Sr. Applications Engineer/ Applications Engineer Job site: San Jose, CA. Send resume to: Monolithic Power Systems, Inc. 79 Great Oaks Blvd., San Jose, CA 95119recblid… https://t.co/NXnUE3CE6D https://t.co/WXsmxjbzea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate River Engineer – Peterborough, UK: CH2M is now Jacobs. CH2M are looking for keen and enthusiastic Engineers to work on a broad range of projects covering all aspects of flood risk management including assessments, solution development and… https://t.co/y2ltCfFww8 https://t.co/YVpi4NfbUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Associate: GET TO KNOW ALORICA At Alorica, we only do one thing – make lives better, one interaction at a time. We’re a global leader in customer service and experience, serving the world’s biggest brands with tens of thousands of… https://t.co/ggYBHsmk1d https://t.co/Si0MQsTlYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Systems Software): Description: Position Requires a Top Secret (TS/SCI) Clearance with a Polygraph. ****** OPEN TO ALL SKILL LEVELS ******* The Sponsor is looking for a Software Developer to join our organization to perform full… https://t.co/F6myJsu5RE https://t.co/EOWzlOMbmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer I: Tompkins International &gt; Careers &gt; Current Openings Submit SearchTompkins International Tompkins – Your Supply Chain. The Right Way. Tompkins Home Menu User Login Open Search Form Search this Site – Company – Services – Industries… https://t.co/1j3q8GX53Q https://t.co/ZXsZa0fvfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developers: DESCRIPTION: We have immediate opportunities for SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPERSto join aworld class, center of excellence. Employer was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes’ "America’s Top 500" list. At… https://t.co/HvDorM0ORs https://t.co/9oebn7pZzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: In 2011 SkySlope started out in the third bedroom of our CEOs house with just him and two others. Every year since then weve experienced insane growth and after growing out of our previous 3 offices we have now settled into our… https://t.co/5iQjCVJNFI https://t.co/CsaMhfmuMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Systems Engineer- EO/IR Video Enhancement Algorithms: Overview The position is for a Staff System Engineer Subject Matter Expert (SME) to design, implement, and test EO/IR Video Correction and Enhancement algorithms. Algorithms will support Missile… https://t.co/xfdqyfFelj https://t.co/RoiMUDqFD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SDE – Backend: We’re seeking smart people who are excited about solving tough problems and building software used by millions of people. We value product-oriented engineers who are able to own, architect and implement features from start to… https://t.co/1YblBLpFRr https://t.co/gBfo6o6uL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – JavaScript: Overview Use your JavaScript expertise to develop visualization software to understand data when proximity and location matter. Your work will help developer communities reimagine the capabilities of location-aware… https://t.co/eo6bblYdl9 https://t.co/gUJh6ibFLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer: PIEtech, Inc. is currently looking for a Software Developer in Richmond, VA PIEtechSM located in Powhatan, VA, is the developer of MoneyGuidePro financial planning software which is designed for financial advisors. As an industry… https://t.co/zmVIVsprsN https://t.co/XZxWny3Afj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Software Engineer (Android): Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users… https://t.co/1CIvdG5Adb https://t.co/KOSkhEAgEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development-General Application: Welcome! Are you interested in joining an amazing team of growing Engineer professionals? At Certent, we use fresh and advanced technology so that you are free to create solutions that work and feel good to use.… https://t.co/MSX481Z4Fe https://t.co/BreIqBU8B7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director: Accounting Beauty Consumer Product Firm $130K-$140K Melville, New York, United States 9/25/16 Job ID: 33266 Qualifications Advanced degree with emphasis in Business Administration/Finance 10+ years of risk-related business experience Strong… https://t.co/jeDV86C9wX https://t.co/aWqizfLcfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr of Programs 3:   Job Description – Mgr of Programs 3 (18003788) Mgr of Programs 3 Requisition ID : 18003788 Location : United States-Maryland-Woodlawn US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance… https://t.co/sk8AHDKWZJ https://t.co/q4sEgfLVIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Threat Intel Lead: Cyber Threat Intel Lead Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10327 Minimum Clearance Required TS/SCI Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is seeking a Cyber Threat Intel Lead (CBP). The Threat Intel… https://t.co/vPJQ4b0rFT https://t.co/h8zoylWLq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: TS/SCI Cleared Network Admin -Washington D.C -IAT II (Sec+CE) Tier 1 &amp; 2 Roles open. Preferred Experience: -Basic Network troubleshooting experience -Knowledge of BGP &amp; OSPF Protocols -Experience troubleshooting LAN &amp; WAN… https://t.co/yMIVhyzGGt https://t.co/e1CzF7KQIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer – System Architect: We are hiring an experienced Systems Architect to work on cutting edge technology in a super fast paced industry in which Bohemia is forging the way and introducing new paradigms! Join a group of expert developers with… https://t.co/A4RWVclz9y https://t.co/h25KRWOd6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front-End Developer: Lead Front-End Developer – Clinicient – Login / Support – ************ – Toggle Menu Skip to content – Products &amp; Services – INSIGHT Platform – EMR – Billing &amp; Collection Services – About – About Us – Contact Us – Careers –… https://t.co/wAZev1d4pp https://t.co/YZBYPyLvFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Senior DevOps Engineer Looking for Senior DevOps Engineer with VSTS/TFS. You will need to be a developer (VSTS/TFS DEVOPS DEVELOPER, .NET, JAVA, POWERSHELL, JS) to contribute to the development and support of DevSecOps. You must… https://t.co/xBYeImaBcp https://t.co/G5UOxcUOEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Network Engineer: Join our Winning Team as a Cloud Network Engineer Are you a Network Engineer who specializes in highly secure, complex IT environments? Does the idea of joining a team responsible for innovation and maintaining and supporting a… https://t.co/xkCPkFBzPF https://t.co/1dVA2i7bq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FrontEnd Developer — Javascript/React/Node: Front End Developer with JavaScript/React/Node Join our Consumer Experience team, which has full responsibility for the CARFAX online presence, as a Front End developer!  At CARFAX, we create websites for our… https://t.co/JfHZNksahF https://t.co/wRrRHhoCQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Dev Ops Security Analyst: Join our Winning Team as a Senior Dev Ops Security Analyst At CARFAX we are constantly EXPANDING our product and technology offerings!  This means we are continually bringing new, innovative products to market through… https://t.co/J31eAP0Os8 https://t.co/R0yRxPOP3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Marketer-Canvassing- No experience needed: Field Marketer – FT &amp; PT PositionsAvailable   Field Marketer – FT &amp; PT PositionsAvailable! If you are looking fora fun and exciting top paying career that has plenty of room for advancement,you’ve found… https://t.co/yioEETAc1K https://t.co/A8ixTmk62C]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>