<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you choose to be your reality is your reality." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I knew Elvis's songs would be the soundtrack to my life as soon as I laid my eyes on his photograph." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The thing that makes me happy now isn’t really singing, it’s just trying to live with grace and dignity in my community." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm your National Anthem. Boy, put your hands up, give me a standing ovation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelReyWorld You're welcome! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2013WillBeGreat http://t.co/kGYyIj2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year #TeamLana! Get ready for "Lana Del Rey World Tour 2013"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDReyOnline Love you too guys,  thank you for keeping us up to date in 2012! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Sources for Lana Del Rey on Twitter (2012) http://t.co/II4zCr1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dear_Lana_Rey Yes, that's very sweet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyWishIn2013 to meet Lana Del Rey &amp; touch that hair! http://t.co/2U2wmgn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamLana http://t.co/gnA82kHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take me to Paris, let's go there and never look back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glamorous, famous, notorious, dangerous, but I'm crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was trying to tell my life's story through songs." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I freak the fuck out.” —Lana Del Rey http://t.co/AKeAamTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LyricsYouLikeToScream I'm tired of feeling like I'm fucking crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you talk, it's like a movie and you're makin' me crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just do what you love, just do what you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And even then I knew that we were something serious, that you would dominate my thoughts like radio deserious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust no one † Paradise — http://t.co/jrliOo9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born bad. But then I met you, you made me nice for a while, but my dark side's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was addicted to you, but I didn't know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every once in a lifetime, dreams can come true. Now and then when the stars shine, you meet somebody like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm your little scarlet, starlet, singin' in the garden. Kiss me on my open mouth, ready for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh haters, fakers, mass-manipulators. Don’t know what you’re tryin’ to prove. I’m the New York City queen, you should hear me sing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLUE JEANS. http://t.co/bPqTwng0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me life is beautiful, they all think I have it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't know what you've done to me. You're heavier than heavenly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Bond 007: Lucky Ones. http://t.co/Y8E9Ntex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fucking crazy, but I'm free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every now and then the stars align, boy and girl meet by the great design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing more gorgeous than a Hundred Dollar Bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was always an unusual girl." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind in my hair, hand on the back of my neck. I said, 'Can we party later on?' – He said, 'Yes, yes.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your hands are on my hips, your name is on my lips. Over, over again like my only prayer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I make you feel like Chrismas time? Put me in a party dress one time. Love me till I see the sunshine, say you'll never leave me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Define Lana. http://t.co/pdC3zM1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think we'll be in love forever? Do you think we'll be in love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanasCigarette Merry Xmas :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to my Queen @LanaDelRey &amp; all our followers! Love you #TeamLana :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanasApostle Merry Xmas to you too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey on Santa Claus. http://t.co/nTUEaHAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! — http://t.co/CrSQWN15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is a special time between Christmas &amp; New Year, everyone creates a balance in their life and how it is supposed to continue."  —Lana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I’m a very happy person, but life is hard sometimes and relationships are shit sometimes." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Her voice is the charm, so rich in emotions and just magnetic." —VOGUE China on Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We had nothing to lose, nothing to gain, nothing we desired anymore. Except to make our lives into a work of art." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's important to have agency within your own life, very important because otherwise you'll get into trouble." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I get nervous, I put Cayenne pepper on my lips. It calms me down." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've always written. It's the only thing I've ever been good at. It's not difficult, like math." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Holidays Team Lana! http://t.co/7Xq6cjAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMERICAN. http://t.co/zYIncTxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say that the world was built for two. Only worth living if somebody is loving you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A freshman generation of degenerate beauty queens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You taught me that it was good to be crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diet Mountain Dew baby, New York City. Never was there ever a girl so pretty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the choice to hear the noise or hear the sweet sound of your sweet voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ask me where I've been, I've been everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is she a Ride or Die bitch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day is over. Another day is done. And now I'm getting closer, to the rising sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Death and paradise for me are linked." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three words. Ten letters. One name. My life: LANA DEL REY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I close my eyes, it's like a dark paradise. No one compares to you, but there's no you, except in my dreams tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I get a little prettier, can I be your baby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elvis is my daddy, Marilyn's my mother, Jesus is my bestest friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I lost my reputation, I forgot my truth. But I have my beauty and I have my youth." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey’s Grandmother: Beatrice Dautresme for Vogue Paris, April 1969. http://t.co/7bXQh75B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think ’Born To Die’ and ’BTD: The Paradise Edition’ are #PerfectAlbums http://t.co/QsWJRYnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the anthem of success. So, before we go out, what's your address?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is my saviour, I can be whatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A funny little thing about love is that you're blind of the time, and even when you think you had enough, you're wanting more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I remember when I met him, it was so clear that he was the only one for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey on her dance. http://t.co/Lj8P8ylv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey has been awarded as Favorite Pop Artist of 2012 by Amazon. Congrats Queen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUST NO ONE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you walked out that door, a piece of me died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother Lizzy. http://t.co/GBiqEfSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana: "I use Twitter only as a promotional tool." – Me: ... http://t.co/5Vlxe4Y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hollywood is just the most famous symbol that I could have chosen for a girl's idea of her life's dream." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody wants to go fast, but they can't compare. I don't really want the rest, only you can take me there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen of Vogue. http://t.co/Hw34g3Sy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thingsilikeaboutmyself I'm a Team Lana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello, hello. Can you hear me? I can be your china doll, if you want to see me fall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whenever I look at it, I remember that life can be great." —Lana on her 'Nabokov Whitman' tattoo. http://t.co/wg05xDm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've learned to get used to my sadness." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/YOqlGvhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Internet is something abstract that I probably didn't understand until now." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can do a lot of bad things in one second that you can't take back." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play me your National Anthem, cause we were Born To Die. This is a Summertime Sadness, so lets rock it in our Blue Jeans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow is coming down like rain. I'm at it myself again. A little tired, even more confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for fun, getting high for free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take me to the Hamptons, Bugatti Veyron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lana Del Rey isn't sexy." — http://t.co/n5luTYWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear the birds on the summer breeze, I drive fast. I am alone in the night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby, I can’t go it alone, ‘cause you’re the one that I want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitch, please RT @MTV: Tell me I'm your national anthem, @Beyonce: http://t.co/fPSF2Ma7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my dreams and all the lights mean nothing without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana &amp; Woodkid. http://t.co/dbRurNnW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>