<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/K87bMLx66S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/ggnvMEZjG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/gEUPXoGHfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/I3Xj8Q1T75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge : " Your wife charges that you haven't spoken to her in  5 years. Why is that?" Defendant: "I didn't dare interrupt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/Jmi4C27lOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/ijuMWd9f20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/K8qd9PhaFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/BsyjCEP1yD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/mueDZMPvzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/LwJ76vMLT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/wmAwXj9Loq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/8t8k2Pr1Na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/YzByaiia3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/MxqrWJbnTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/ZtVeeybrON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/epa3oUDUpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/JwLHiTYz9O]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/ARG5WZdhGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/zNFyDFnX6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/Rw4Fsx3RL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/tjTT9FE8oK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/YubEhgVr1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/wBZQTqZkCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't tell how much spirit a team has until it starts losing. - Rocky Colavito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/fn1A4vrATb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/Q1kNFOJXR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/jDmM9wt03Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/PrJpU8lj9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/7ngBSIrSO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/FZ969GCMmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/9HhP7x6M3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/jtQR0j1P0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/E0Yu0Vx2v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/iKdwqsr8bA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/6p1RxJomYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/wultfzx1S2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/ZtVeeybrON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/a0QdIkg45S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/yhiKVcyUEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/7kvyqCYZCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/ZwuLctIHBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/6gGm3GlRvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/oZA5eqrHGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/T3LB0mS7ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/QJfCGYHX6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/CotzMAXKCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/w4EAcpuNHH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>