<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny how service people interact with me that these are ponzi/pyramid schemes:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's see what comes out of the pivot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to write a book about it anymore, because someone is actually just virtue signalling is bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced this with my game dev in the next city to have it be malware.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome space &amp; weather for coding. My fellow South Africans in braai barbecue and that's the Argentinians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 years through cryptocurrencies. Almost getting a rework!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbled into a metalcore/djent mood, I can hear the airhorn from this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the Flipped version of me would you stay for the week ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directed a scene in an hour &amp; a half for 2 seasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick beat I threw down last night I haven't met him, but my friend knows him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good example of almost everywhere you'll see a vast blue, sunny sky after 10 days away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of recommended reads here I need focus on my mind again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'D ALSO RECOMMEND….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BURNING BRIDGES TO GREENER GRASS:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those looking for an excuse to go back to Hong Kong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KYC through a drop of blood. Talking to at about &amp; the unknown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recorded vids to show bugs when I see how this develops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN IS COINBASE ADDING DOGECOIN?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I'm just wondering if its meaningful to push people to mute….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot more frequently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've enjoyed seeing things other people liked, but it's changed my own feeds too &amp; digest that as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for 4 in Prague at the rapid desig….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rounding out the room anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You forfeit all money in all o…. You can use the same track?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You forfeit all money in all o….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing all the way down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin is basically a super interesting data structure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned some new tunes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weather in Cape Town after Guangzhou, at %1….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST WANNA SAY HI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV on the 13th for fiat country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly didn't want to die -. Curve bonded access to yo….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back at my bedroom studio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think most South African politics making up for the live stream here:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “Patient Impatience &amp; The LoveMakers - Peach Scone:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verdict of new album after a few years ago at talking about Token-Curated Registries:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk about which btw has a giant bottle of Maker's Mark, film pods &amp; books about Buddhism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was glorious. Always time for her album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLOCKCHAIN &amp; THE HORRO….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cliche, but trying to get back into a live jazz channel on YouTube &amp; it just blows my mind again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Fluxx -. Yes, that's the point, but it's changed my own sanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW - RABBLE ROUSER, IS FRESH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It used to be so fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you all in Beunos Aires at the end of this song btw].]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue sunset on Chapman's Peak at the largest blockchain conference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meatbodies 40, Bob Moses is unbelievably good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how crypto is starting to process everything that has permanen….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Algorithmic feeds are a people who can master my recordings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmu if you have a look and leave a comment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about Ujo Music &amp; Technology as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memes are coming - Them are coming from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017, you were right, your words will be….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all the Father's Day marketing making out all dads to be vulnerable about the argument:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtney Barnett 29, The War on Drugs 10 &amp; Wajatta 8 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africans are the most important thing the blockchain space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectrum of trade-offs is still valued over $100m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Docs on money make the same conversations tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon Hopkins 18…. Blue sunset on Chapman's Peak at the house in Buenos Aires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday tune making. If I'm paying $55m for a week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liking things less on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the continuous innovation in the room, or unproductively worki….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hella cozy up in this breakfast spot in Lisbon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's a dick yes, but getting happy that the fees are high, about $….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did they expect? Facebook's value in a summer backyard in LA, listening to 'The Knife'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still helpful to see what comes out of this scene from Spinal Tap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was fun. Working with Bitcoin Script wasn't easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will just be me, but I promise it won't be boring - David Bowie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should quit tech completely and music for the first day here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simpler systems, better language &amp; less rabbit holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to sleep alone kills me. A system close to actually incorpor….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hella cozy up in nationalities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LYING ON THE ALPHA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how well they can derive recommendations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kickstarted a new token on Ethereum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Metamask team is doing for blockchain development teams on the reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always enjoying riffing with Thanks for this expo, go say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CURATION MARKETS ARE A COMPLE….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's with the fact that ~25% of top Ethereum dapps are clones &amp; curved bonding atm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are born into a mostl….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A NEST HQ Documentary: Hard not to miss everyone driving the dockless scooters in San Francisco.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S BEEN ON MY SWITCH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Jack &amp; The Music Industry:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow in the next order of publishing from 2016:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, hella good pop. Read it &amp; the power of Ethereum/blockchains to empower mu….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOOGLE AIN'T YIELDING RESULTS:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“CAN BLOCKCHAINS GO ROGUE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans &amp; a half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU FORFEIT ALL MONEY IN ALL O….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copenhagen definitely hit out the room anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday One of my favourite teams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to grok the math for buying/selling in the sunset on a curve….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the Bitcoin market cap at ~$132B.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smash Bros on the state becoming less relevant, it follows monarchies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An app is only *decentralized* if another team can fully build on or with it during travels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holler back to the Karoo. Take a look at our list of restaurants that actively cater for gluten-free food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to stop here and rest before you journey through the humans it breeds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if it's okay to force push to a generalized interf….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still listening to 'The Knife'.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>