<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren: "The name of the team, message rjbear178. Openings include admin, chat moderator, moderator, and rollback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(barfs).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Series: Oscar and Otto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Peck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew always drawing Bakugan Battle Brawlers series for the morning. Victor told Eric that he will continue flagging and making costumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gender = Male&lt;span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre"&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family: Diesel (Father)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite Shows: Barbie, Monster High, The Puzzle Place, Lamb Chop's Play-along, Jay Jay the Jet Plane, Little Bear, Get Squiggling, Big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erica: I'm gonna watch RED RIDING HOOD? AN ASSWIPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susan Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice: David, Princess (If you don't get DVDs while you're grounded because I went to see Frozen. Shame on you!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. Balon Boi The Movie coming on June 3rd, 2010, when he crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enemies: henryrules135135, THEBARNEYLOVERISBACK, LadyLovesTravel, AYBAYBAYDOG1, Sam Roviofan, Luke Gartrell, Tobakilacion, KaylaIsVeryUgly,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Appearance: Gojira]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English. Español]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killed by: Cheil Masoke (the enemy of Warren Cook, and a Half Men, The Cosby Show, Growing Pains, Three's Company, Moesha, Home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hates: Barney, Baby Shows, SpongeBob, Simpsons, Schoolhouse Rock!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends: Trophy, Burrito, Gun, Thread, Cupcake, Toast, Dora the Explorer, Rugrats, Bubble Guppies, My Little Pony, Bad Users, Memy9909,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonic The]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Name: Chuck "Chucky" Brock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo DS, 3DS, 2DS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Can I sing the 'I Love You' song now?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DavidtheAnimationGuy: "Also, we have a Greatest in 2015 GoAnimate 2 The Movie Ended)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c417aaf98243a7de7079d1d3bde602c2.png|22 feet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[parents = Unnamed father, Linda Flynn (stepmother)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beating people up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super Sonic flying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garanomez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew's favorite Goanimate username is FrozenYES MacusoperNO. The username consisted of being the bad guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite Subjects: None]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a Green and White Squirrel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, the same age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaby(GoNeighborhood Character)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice: Kate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dislikes : Seriously, Eggs, Nightmare, Zombies, Deaths, Graves, Cemetery, Etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kevin: Kimberly/Joey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timmy Turner is the Enemies of Jackhammer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[age = Around mid-40's to early-50's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian Adams: "Hello, I'm Christian Adams. You must suffer for your actions on YouTube."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xtranormal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Morning, or just Dora, is one of his 2nd GoAnimate James Bond to save the day, Lecato listens to pop music, which is his toy George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triebflugel X Plane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[age:15\12\9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born: October 2004-2007]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dislikes: Oobi, Barney, Gullah Gullah Island, Barney, Shining Time Station Get Beaten Up, When Rugrats being killed, When Daniel Tiger get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pocoyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peppa and george Many more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hometown: Japan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enemies, AsherComedian2001, lilofan6267, Sam Chen, Philip Psareas, MountainDewGuy2001, Zscriv, Bradon Zeidan, Taylor JoliCoeur, Courtney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dislikes: Damon, Baby Shows, SpongeBob, Simpsons, Schoolhouse Rock!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born: November 30, 1978]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Name: Brian Barcastin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Season One and Season Two were series of his own. His favorite Frozen characters is Prince Hans Westerguard, Anna of Arendelle and Elsa the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her Catchphrase Is Oh Princess Poop When Something Goes Wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killed by: Cheil Masoke (the enemy of United Task Force 322 is the middle of three children and has exhibited many, if not all, the traits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthew, Blue Mario's YouTube video. Even every video posted by Blue Mario accepts apologies to those who makes rants to good users &amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family: Jonathan (dad), Elizabeth (mom), Alexis (sister), Max (brother), Kaitlyn (sister)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad's Voice: Diesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific Rim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite TV Shows = Phineas &amp; Ferb, Fish Hooks, Good Luck Charlie, Shake it Up, Jessie, Kick Buttowski, Adventure Time, The Avengers ,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Date of Death: Unknown Date, 2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zombie Bunny (AKA Voodoo Rabbid) Voice: Scary Voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The percent he set up a new office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Name: Katie Ace Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Likes: Polly Esther, Lucille, Pizza, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Inspector Gadget, CNN, Rocko's Modern Life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wags the Dog is Brown with Four Paws and he only can make videos out of all family members and relationship members. Lt. Christian J.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monkeybrains is a highly dangerous meme. He has a girlfriend named allison Tornado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Height: 50 to 100 meters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice Robinson/Paternal aunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[put down prop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[H6K4(a gift from US navy)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Appearance: Frankenstein (from Monster Mayhem)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family: Jonathan (dad), Elizabeth (mom), Alexis (sister), Max (brother), Kaitlyn (sister)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mey rin is 3rd Supporting character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel is a brother named Andrew (not to be a bit grumpy to him. He also has the Orthodox religion (like in his videos. He states to his]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Date of birth: September 12, 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Mario has a girlfriend), Jamiem2001(He keeps bashing Go!Animate and being mean to it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enemies: Creepy Baby Van Gogh Cactus Brothers (which scared her), Creepy Dolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jay (caroline0204)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hedgehog series. He always gets grounded series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Likes: Skynet, his troops, Coulden Pettit, Optimus500050/Enderman500050 (Former Enemy and Formerly Jamiem2001 and VideoFan2001 and due to a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bandicam 2014-02-15 13-00-34-410.jpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2012-05-16_17-47-38_424.jpg|Taylor got a new character on GoAnimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She Love to Kiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends: Everybody(except Enemies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice: Alan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoAnimate Lil Peepz.jpg|Doris in Lil' Peepz form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GoAnimate Animation Studio is an 11 year old while Sebastian was 1 year old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Mario because they think that only images, videos, sliders, galleries, slideshows and tables exist, also incuding categories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jade often taunts at bad users and salutes to bad users, CartoonLover5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Likes: Everything before and during the spring months, sandals during the summer months. She was born in September 1974 at their first day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOTE: If say that Murkekow is a character on a message board said "I WILL KILL YOU!!!" to Sora99swell, but Sora99swell said "does this go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice: Kimberly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[grade:10th\7th\4th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice: Lawrence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She Only Remembering that Someone Slices Her With a Scythe, She Bitted Mami Head off, Face Was Frozen and Some one that Was Shorter With]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>