<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dive Under the Ice With the Brave Robots of Antarctica: Sending a robot into the icy depths and getting it back alive can be more challenging than communicating with a Mars rover millions of miles away. https://t.co/ElFIexyaPp https://t.co/GYSvVTlDW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplier Quality Technician/Data Analyst: Job Description BAE Systems is looking for an experienced Supplier Quality Technician/Data Analyst who: Would be excited to join a leading top tier global aerospace &amp; defense enterprise Has a long standing… https://t.co/hEpaGNRM75 https://t.co/44FWUIYtKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/XbdfQZ8MGD https://t.co/H4ZaFHalUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Software Engineer: Automation Software Engineer – Aquantia Corp – Customer Portal – Products – Back – Automotive – Corporate Data Center – Enterprise Infrastructure – Client Connectivity – FPGA-Programmable PHYs – SFP+ Modules – Technology –… https://t.co/r8LcRCfFv8 https://t.co/w8g1koupar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer .NET/C#: Job Description Sr. Software Developer .NET/C# Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you’re helping to create a better world. Our customers operate the largest electrical transmission and… https://t.co/vAoahX834K https://t.co/ep07qIO35M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Revenue Accounting Operations and Reporting: Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown… https://t.co/CqYjnNEgLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services Tests Out Two Tools to Help Keep the Cloud Secure: Amid frequent customer data exposures, Amazon Web Services is pushing to spot errors and promote access control. https://t.co/66dt1OSKlb https://t.co/atWjN2xNcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .net Software Engineer: JOB TITLE: SENIOR .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER LOCATION: WINSTON SALEM, NC SALARY: $100-$115K Rapidly growing Winston Salem based company has an immediate need for two Senior .net Software Engineers for permanent positions.… https://t.co/boZJbAUDjR https://t.co/UVlRGaIUYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator/Project Manager-Nampa, ID: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by… https://t.co/OJrtGV0fxW https://t.co/jHvscT6Uba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Application Developer: Infoshare Systems, Inc. (Mission Viejo, CA) needs: Project Manager: supervise multiple employees, provide project mgt. throughout the life of project: Sr. Application Developer: design, develop &amp; test software solutions using… https://t.co/tqN7pqTSwB https://t.co/jUiUgWO4xA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Systems Specialist (IT Security Analyst 3): Stanford University seeks an Info Security Systems Specialist (IT Security Analyst 3) to protect confidentiality, integrity, &amp; availability of Stanford’s info assets. Position reqs Bach. in comp sci,… https://t.co/AQcfMkSMfL https://t.co/9Vy10xd1TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Statistician: H &amp; R Block seeks a Senior Statistician – Pricing in Kansas City, MO. Build and maintain predictive models.MasterStats, Math, Econ, MIS+ 2 years stat. exp. recblid sabgtlb4c4hgxu3ri99kvjb42bs6wk https://t.co/O0lQoE9y57 https://t.co/UQ3zXWg3EK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Manager #XGGS19FC0718RIC1: Technology: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Manager in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Provide technology-enabled consulting… https://t.co/pZen5rL9zx https://t.co/xaOX37k8k2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description The Software Engineer position will be supporting the Logistics Data Warehouse (LDW). This position will be part of the Logistics team supporting the U.S. and U.K. Trident II Strategic Weapons System, the U.K. Successor… https://t.co/ISl7GhteyC https://t.co/U9JeGZlUvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Writer – Developer: For Siemens Technical Writer – Developer job – Engineering – Charlotte, North Carolina Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens… https://t.co/t5pApCWFOv https://t.co/8wmPXWgdPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Scientist Staff / CATIA V4-V5 / Aerodynamics / Thermodynamics: Req ID : 421271BR Job Code/Title : E1484:Research Scientist Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe… https://t.co/dYuPSW5gnM https://t.co/7kHdnWQvWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Embedded Software Engineer Job – Why Work For Us – Get to Know PACCAR – A Great Place to Work – Equal Opportunity Employer – Job Opportunities – Engineering Jobs – Finance &amp; Accounting Jobs – Human Resources &amp; Admin Jobs –… https://t.co/tS6sKOjTBa https://t.co/MzHBI3vLH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO: SAP FICO Ref No.: 18-30013 Location: Toledo, Ohio Required 8-10 years of SAP FICO experience Good Communication skills Strong Knowledge on FICO GL, AP, AR, AA, BA, CCA, PCA, IOCO-PAPS Good experience on Bank Accounting and IDOCs Knowledge on… https://t.co/th8S3WoXQW https://t.co/PvR29FPgZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Google's Safe Browsing Helped Build a More Secure Web: You may not have heard of Safe Browsing, but it's made the web more secure for over a decade. Here's its story, from the people who built it. https://t.co/0Q2E1QQAwg https://t.co/nVHFjOJFFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Delivery Manager: Western Union is changing. Yes, we’re the company that moves money around the world quickly and reliably in 200 countries and territories. We are also present in over 510,000 locations bringing immense distribution convenience to our… https://t.co/JF1trHP5f2 https://t.co/IoVf229Po7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5156-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/A9WggdzL7Z https://t.co/gw72i2tyzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio, Warner Stress Election Security After Trump-Putin Summit: Senators Mark Warner and Marco Rubio both cast President Trump's appearance in Helsinki as a major setback in the fight against Russian interference in elections around the world. https://t.co/aK82S8S5nv https://t.co/sjTNrKLPDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CS FF NXE Installations System Integration Engineer: Job Description LocationHillsboro – OR, US LevelUp to Bachelor Experience0-2 Starter Available since6/4/2018 Functional areaMechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, System Engineering… https://t.co/kR3cZN3ezp https://t.co/ifrpeWFpks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position Title Digital Project Manager – Marketing, Insights and Communications: Number of Openings 1 Closing Date 07/01/2018 Type of Search Staff Who May This position is open to all qualified applicants. Position Number 2018-3510 Campus St. Paul… https://t.co/mn4vOuGzO4 https://t.co/JE9zSff4TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Project Manager II: Job Description – Transportation Project Manager II Job LocationUS-CA-Santa AnaJob ID0618-18698 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager II – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time CategoryEngineering-Civil/Structural Why… https://t.co/bf21jQ8SDi https://t.co/NMSF56kQ1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Engineer 3/4:   Job Description – Info Assurance Engineer 3/4 (18010117) Info Assurance Engineer 3/4 Requisition ID : 18010117 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/uw4uwWiwDu https://t.co/CqeANyFYMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Software Engineer: Job Description Job Title: Research Software Engineer Job ID: 4880 Location: Multiple locations Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Title Research Software Engineer Overview of RAND The RAND Corporation is a… https://t.co/MecsoKUu7C https://t.co/EXgVukofCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent Optimization Specialist: Job Title: Talent Optimization Specialist Location: Omaha, NE Job Number: JO-1807-27901 Description ProKarma is currently searching for an ambitious Talent Optimization Specialist to join our team in Omaha, NE. We are… https://t.co/Rww9mrpZKU https://t.co/QHly1mzhnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr QA Engr: Ooma Inc (Sunnyvale, CA) is seeking: Sr QA Engr, Req’s BS CS/ Engg &amp; 5 yrs exp. Other req’s apply. (Job # 3660). Sr SW Engr, BS in CS &amp; 5 yrs exp. Other req’s apply. (Job# 3650). recblid muuyb192bq5pozuwrc5tql35mw7y0c https://t.co/YBmQ5n676V https://t.co/ay0UAhGDbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast and AT&amp;T Are Fighting to Become Media Companies: Transmitting data makes steady, low returns. But the telecom giants want a grander life: in high-risk, high-reward, high-margins media. https://t.co/k4yMeKgl0f https://t.co/BUDAcA3c4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master – Are you ready to make a difference? School Specialty is dedicated to changing education for the better. That means working closely with educators, sharing experience, and traveling into unchartered territories together. – Are… https://t.co/lF2PA8uIW9 https://t.co/VBkOpLs1lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philanthropy Database Specialist: Job Description Adventist Healthcare Care. Compassion. Community. Responsibilities The Database Specialist will join a strategically focused and highly motivated team of Philanthropy professionals who are committed to… https://t.co/nJZvIILIK4 https://t.co/bGXgQuUkJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Solutions Architect- Fraud and Risk (government and/or private healthcare): Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/nB2jpTO6aV https://t.co/zlgpuMq7so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russians Found One Use for Bitcoin: Hacking the 2016 US Election: The 12 Russian intelligence officers accused of hacking the DNC allegedly used $95,000 worth of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies to fund their operation. https://t.co/rV49qbVDU4 https://t.co/NzRT8nPvb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Implementation Project Manager (Financial/Banking): Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/CXeZDsGzrV https://t.co/hxcuTGW0Mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Careers Center | Technical Support Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/dCy1nZ3a4b https://t.co/tz5SrSBsUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Network Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-39008 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the design and development of voice, video,… https://t.co/WgiLUbtdAi https://t.co/WVz00sVwE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pininfarina's Back With a $2 Million Electric Hypercar: The famed Italian design house hopes to win over customers with the PF0, a battery-powered ride that hits 60 mph in under two seconds and offers 310 miles of range. https://t.co/R4XaAgxVrl https://t.co/p9j53Pv7Tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineer: For American Express Senior QA Engineer job – Digital Commerce, Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation American Express – Life at American Express – Our Company – Career Areas – Student Opportunities –… https://t.co/s4R2jswMPB https://t.co/8ZZyvIjrIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include… https://t.co/n0B7dgmY08 https://t.co/AWffAQNkuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Carbon-Saving Tip? Travel by Cargo Ship: Container ships sometimes have a handful of passenger cabins—the peak of carbon emissions frugality. https://t.co/1xif9RYiwT https://t.co/vq3hqV9kla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Hereditary’ Proves Satanists Just Aren’t Scary Anymore: The new horror movie is very frightening—but not entirely because of its occult twist. https://t.co/xb5PfBdAUT https://t.co/F2ewH6DTQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Selenium and Java: QA Engineer – Selenium and Java in Teaneck, US-NJ, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home… https://t.co/Rc7QigaU7t https://t.co/aW8x0kLYT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer, Sr. – Ft. Belvoir – TS/SCI is required: Requisition ID 2018-40345 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Senior Network Engineer Ft. Belvoir, VA Active… https://t.co/1Yzpo2ufbi https://t.co/CsYWfbaX9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer: Senior Java Engineer – GlobalLogic, Inc. Senior Java Engineer – Engineering – Austin TX – At least 5+ yrs of relevant experience – Strong in java backend coding. – Experience in Web Servers, Web client, http, css/html is a must –… https://t.co/cCg15rxOlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Company Wants Your Fertility Data: Celmatix sells a genetic test for reproductive health, and it's looking to expand. https://t.co/5acdbfjfBT https://t.co/O1YFarKH54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Medicare / Healthcare Experience: Project Manager – Healthcare / Medicare Long Beach, Ca 90806 6 months contract This position will join an existing team that supports the oversight and deployment of Star Quality programs and… https://t.co/MzG1iDbt0U https://t.co/DklHHLjGLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Director, IT Account Management: Job Title: Associate Director, IT Account Management – ACC****** Description Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and Canada, is a global health care leader with a… https://t.co/lUDXPOP1FW https://t.co/TpYaPuTMTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ServiceNow CMDB Architect: TitleSenior ServiceNow CMDB Architect Location Department NameEnterprise Services Description Windward Consulting is at the forefront of Service-Centric IT. With strategic consulting, unparalleled technical expertise and… https://t.co/vZXA6Xh2Tr https://t.co/80m8MWs29Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Android Software Engineer: Job Description Senior Android Software Engineer (17269) Introduction: Are you passionate about providing real impact to the country’s toughest national security problems? Are you searching for engaging work with an… https://t.co/QR20UlGXFj https://t.co/SFobWUcJ92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slime Molds Remember—But Do They Learn?: Evidence mounts that organisms without nervous systems can in some sense learn and solve problems, but researchers disagree about whether this is “primitive cognition.” https://t.co/MMsVaoqTzg https://t.co/setKa3gvrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Careers Center | Software Engineer II Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/QNFbdfz95a https://t.co/3K7rsDoYOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst Lead: OVERVIEW Provides professional expertise in national defense functional disciplines or areas with a focus on military Command, Control, and Intelligence (C3I) and combat support; interoperability of military tactical and fixed… https://t.co/JTQMVR1XEw https://t.co/Wi8OPVmYR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer Spanish Speaking: Who We Are Malwarebytes is the next-gen cybersecurity company that millions worldwide trust. Malwarebytes proactively protects people and businesses against dangerous threats such as malware, ransomware, and… https://t.co/MuDvdK7PqI https://t.co/igmuNTyJy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Job TitleSolution Architect – ID:31506 Duration24 Months Start DateASAP Job Skills Java, NoSQL technology (CouchBase or MongoDB) and integrations (Jboss/IBM Data Power) LocationMarysville, OH Date Posted04/17/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE… https://t.co/zY03hxepjw https://t.co/0HRraNei8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Signal Processing Systems Engineer: Senior Principal Signal Processing Systems Engineer Posted Date 3 months ago(3/7/2018 9:42 PM) ID 2018-30387 Job Location USA-CA-San Jose Required Clearance TS/SCI Category Engineering-Systems… https://t.co/XamBWnWgBX https://t.co/cAb79EZH7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator TS/SCI with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-42262 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description * Manages the functionality… https://t.co/4E8NcxQUoR https://t.co/3273eGfImk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) – GI Lab: Job Description Registered Nurse (RN) – GI Lab DepartmentGI Lab Contact LocationLa Crosse Schedule/ShiftDay FTE0.8 FTE Benefit EligibleYes Temporary PositionNo Job Details GI Lab 64 hours every two weeks 8 and 9 hours… https://t.co/QOAvm22hBT https://t.co/OFdk7ycyxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Designer: Cerner Skip to main content Skip to main navigation Skip to footer – Your Career Path – Client Services – Clinical – Corporate – Engineering &amp; Technology – Sales, Marketing &amp; Strategy – Students &amp; Graduates – How We Hire – Our Teams –… https://t.co/89875PD5QK https://t.co/NIIJMED9l9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Emmy-Nominated Shows You Can Binge to Escape Reality: The best Emmy nominated shows to binge watch to relax, from 'Killing Eve' to 'The Good Place.' https://t.co/1FMJPFwqyv https://t.co/b8B4if3xHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Fortnite' Season 5 Is Here, and the Rest of the Week in Games: It's been a busy week in gaming. Let's catch up. https://t.co/slKinGGIHR https://t.co/olTbveij9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Reporting Analyst Online Reporting System: Job Location US-DC Job ID 9395 Job Location United States Category Project Management Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing Reporting… https://t.co/NhwjSRPOhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager: Sr. Project Manager Description at FRESENIUS – Fresenius Fraud Notice As a company with over 60,000 dedicated employees, Fresenius Medical Care North America is quite aware of the many scams that job seekers may face. If you receive… https://t.co/XH3ImrVqTX https://t.co/M1e8XvCZEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP HANA: SAP HANA Ref No.: 18-27244 Location: Plainfield, Indiana Job Title : SAP HANA Location : Plainfield, IN Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Have in depth knowledge in SAP Hana Technically sound candidate . https://t.co/ja2KAAGr8d https://t.co/vsE2oyCvYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the US Government Planted 'Spy Phones' on Suspects: In at least one instance, DEA agents sold an encrypted BlackBerry to a suspected drug smuggler—and kept the encryption key. https://t.co/SyrBS9Ke7r https://t.co/hjFdcqD3BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modification / Retrofit Project Manager: Job Description This position is an F-35 Time Compliance Technical Directive (TCTD) Project Manager. The role will be located at the customer’s site in Ft Worth, Texas. This position will provide support to the… https://t.co/Aw7vdwkUoU https://t.co/XdwKRaaUEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transit/Rail Senior Program Director / Traction Power Department Manager: Job Description – Transit/Rail – Senior Program Director / Traction Power Department Manager Job LocationUS-CA-Santa AnaJob ID0318-18089 HNTB Job TitleProject Director Position… https://t.co/kIWq3x38gn https://t.co/6xiCNY63RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With 112 Emmy Nominations, Netflix Officially Rules Television: For the first time in 18 years, HBO isn't at the top of the Television Academy heap. https://t.co/ZaWD8Geh8i https://t.co/ZrxggffVay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Programmer Analyst: Location: North Charleston Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Analyst Jobs We have an exciting opportunity for a Mid-Level Programmer Analyst to join our team in North Charleston, South Carolina! This position… https://t.co/AM52brepwk https://t.co/DKZTwR0LJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Global Partner Solutions Architect – IBM Alliance: Location US-NC-Raleigh Posting date 2 hours ago(7/10/2018 9:37 AM) Job ID 64144 Category Solution Architecture Remote base US-NC-Raleigh Company description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative… https://t.co/cD3XqwZL6f https://t.co/vE3WwDT5sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Einride's T-log Is a Self-Driving Truck Made for the Forest: The Swedish robo-truck ditches the engine for batteries, the human for software, and the container for a big pile of logs. https://t.co/rQZjHfaQK3 https://t.co/j4kskiAXpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineer Full Stack: Principal Engineer Full Stack in Boston, US-MA, USA | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/KoV9BLLS2e https://t.co/N2JhNRZaBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators Fear Meltdown and Spectre Disclosure Gave China an Edge: By not informing the US government of two industry-wide hardware flaws, Intel may have inadvertently given ammo to China's hackers. https://t.co/BYelsBYpJk https://t.co/JbVunVtObs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Analyst Manhattan: Job Description Job Title: Sr. Systems Analyst – Manhattan Requisition Number: 23509 Position Type: Full Time City: Plainfield Campus: Indy State/Province: Indiana Job Description: The Sr. Systems Analyst – Manhattan is… https://t.co/Bdh9VOtuLk https://t.co/z2ZvT7WrnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Developer: Mobile Developer in Austin, Texas, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers –… https://t.co/Dp89EEIUrC https://t.co/1UyvIoeJGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Engineering Behind Elon Musk's Bid to Save Thailand's Cave Boys: The SpaceX and Tesla CEO's work to help the rescue operation captivated the internet and reinforced the most flattering image of Musk, as a brilliant engineer with a nose for unexpected… https://t.co/VBZTChAoXc https://t.co/gdgURCqTEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCL Programmer: When you join Employer in Pasadena, CA, you are aligning yourself with an organization whose values drive our philosophy of care. Our focus on delivering quality, service, and cutting edge care, enables Employer to be an organization… https://t.co/ohDZXUyico https://t.co/CVt4dAckje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Angular developer: Java Angular developer Ref No.: 18-29332 Location: Buffalo Grove, Illinois Java Angular developer Buffalo Grove, IL Contract Required skills:- AngularJS, Digital : Spring Boot, Foundation : Hibernate ORM, Core Java, GUI &amp; Rich… https://t.co/hEW2MbMceU https://t.co/ir2aeE8RQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst (SAP ABAP Developer): Job Summary =========== Programmer Analyst – SAP ABAP Developer is responsible for working alongside Information systems and Business Resources to gather project requirements, convert the requirements into a… https://t.co/rG93o9zgkX https://t.co/Zbv9fADlHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Department Mobile – ReachMobi Employment Type Full-Time Minimum Experience Experienced About ReachMobi ReachMobi is more than just one of the world’s largest mobile content providers. Our audience of over 20 million plus subscribers… https://t.co/YDyNabex3E https://t.co/cx1GQjak86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Neumeric Technologies Corporation, an information technologies firm in Westerville, Ohio, is looking for Software Engineers, Application Analysts, Database Administrators and QA Analysts to fill multiple positions ranging from entry… https://t.co/hH5pJfuqoe https://t.co/ihL3Evbi2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Administrator: Social Media Administrator Eden Foods (Lenawee County, MI) seeks a full-time Social Media Administrator for an internal marketing team – experienced, organized and motivated. Teamwork and communication skills are critical.… https://t.co/Ms4xzmuaD8 https://t.co/5Ywrh2W8R3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/5j1RvILwhJ https://t.co/QM5adqeKzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Foxborough, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Position: Windows Software Engineer Apex Job ID: ****** Location: Foxborough, MA Rate:… https://t.co/t3IXFdwXOT https://t.co/BR4Rdesqtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: General Dynamics Health Solutions/ARMA would like to meet candidates interested in human performance and behavioral health careers. Schedule a time to talk to us at one of our Virtual Job Fairs, Oct. 24-26. Please schedule a time that… https://t.co/X3qXkn59ZC https://t.co/1e7awOq3SY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Company Description About Visa Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind – making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is our global vision and… https://t.co/y4lGZLksPX https://t.co/xBSbGIPsV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDP Developers (Python Development): EDP Developers (Python Development) Ref No.: 18-26274 Location: Sunnyvale, California EDP Developer(s) Strong SDLC experience with the ability to excel in a RAD DevOps model with biweekly releases Hands on expertise… https://t.co/kPuZlHs9Eb https://t.co/2MfipEdkgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Dev, Senior: SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER RESPONSIBILITIES: – Participate in Requirements Analysis; design Applications based on System Requirements and Architecture, prototype if necessary, develop, unit test and deploy applications – Champion efforts… https://t.co/nD45QBYVig https://t.co/tVdrvt65mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructional Designer, User-Experience Designer, Website De: Instructional Designer, User-Experience Designer, Website De in Denver, CO or Colorado Springs, CO or Fort Collins, CO | Information Technology at UCHealth Toggle menu – About us – Careers –… https://t.co/6TvSv2sHEq https://t.co/eLHWoyFXC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/22/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/vXZNW0XKdT https://t.co/MSi7BKdJx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Springfield, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/dniEmAR4JA https://t.co/gJtiF428El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineering Manager 1 (Spectrum Sustaining Support):   Job Description – Test Engineering Manager 1 (Spectrum Sustaining Support) (18012670) Test Engineering Manager 1 (Spectrum Sustaining Support) Requisition ID : 18012670 Location : United… https://t.co/qpfo7TQ0Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT Systems Developer: * 2018-17836 Posted Date 4 months ago(2/27/2018 6:09 PM) Title IoT Systems Developer Job Location US-TX-Fort Worth Shift Schedule Day Manages Others No Company Profiles Weir has been in business since 1871 and our sustainability… https://t.co/D5vrXONqQa https://t.co/Qn30d0Qy8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Just Lecture Robots—Make Them *Learn*: By drawing on prior experience, a humanoid-ish robot can watch a human pick up an apple and drop it in a bowl, then do the same itself, even if it’s never seen an apple before. https://t.co/wFHO84sYNI https://t.co/65FjgNlkUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Lead IT Software Developer: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?Log… https://t.co/kkr2End1c0 https://t.co/ATh3cxwNHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET (Trading Platform): SDET (Trading Platform) boston, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 07/05/18, Posted Date – 07/05/18 Primary SkillsNATax TermsC2COverview Job Description : Proven background in software development, software quality… https://t.co/MS8RyEaAI4 https://t.co/nnIxKJdm1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulgaria's First New Plane in Decades Is a Freakishly Strong Drone: Brothers Svilen and Konstantin Rangelov are working on a drone they say will someday haul 800 pounds up to 1,550 miles. https://t.co/zD9igaOFxn https://t.co/JUJ8tu3X4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: TECHNOLOGY Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Engineer Applications (REQ#9P349X) Dsgn &amp; arch lrge-scle, high thrghput entrprse apps. Firmware Engineer (REQ#AFKQU5) Dsgn and dev frmwre and sw for embedded… https://t.co/KaxyBviIvs https://t.co/C9OFFRVZTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst Evaluate business, function &amp; technical requirements. Component design documents. Design, develop &amp; code modules based on TIBCO, Java standards. Enhance technical document &amp; implement changes. Module &amp; integration… https://t.co/LyeHAVz769 https://t.co/9lljfMOusq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Ditko Was More Than Just the Guy Behind Spider-Man: The comics artist co-created many iconic characters—but that's not the only reason he should be remembered. https://t.co/6K0tHiR0g3 https://t.co/3piAvW81KO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>