<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/Brq70Vwfb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/CIN1DMnJbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/zJZ39QTzUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/MDwDMzosko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/suVd1ibNfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/qo3PM62The]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/wEPHfCmuO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/VyV7Pi7RCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/1rqV9LUkcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/5hA292UH4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/eGLR0c2KAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/HAaM9e6Cww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/0aobM9PQnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/oN1vU03Qql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/OQvgNPKDox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/fLsai0Dazt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/hVwJlb9hVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/mZcBhw5mhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/jczBibnqrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/7G8xpGtHU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/8siIY7GNAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/35RBCrLBJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/o4WQblZ3Kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else. - James M. Barrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/ODOHScEO57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/YRCmxglPw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/flRCI8H2tj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/ez3Se2SKxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/lQErAgVvyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/91QSV9GjIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/BgNAbbjria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/OM8APwiq3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/BSdOAJlAbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire character. Train skill. - Peter Schutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/qXRMjvae4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/JWJ0Ztj9Ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/qnHqhRQZlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/SngBPB6sas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/JWJ0Ztj9Ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/zqPIx8ip6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/MDwDMzosko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/5d7DTQnChg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/jV45TKPhMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/J7cbTzgYYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/ei9wKF73SN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/diM2zRzujR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/hPoo7IAtN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/EHafdUIctD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/ZL1tfDRCMK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>