<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In the season finale, Elaine Chao admits to Jeff Sessions that tech executives are crushed by excessive regulations. The White House chef tells a "your mama" joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Wilbur Ross calmly tells Omarosa Manigault that Lutherans are enlightened leaders. George Will wears pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Jason Chaffetz confesses to Omarosa Manigault that Russian agents are disciples of Cthulhu. Cthulhu seeks justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Twitter, Lamar Alexander confesses to Katrina Pierson that drug dealers are not very affluent. Alex Jones shrieks in terror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Rand Paul convinces Katrina Pierson that White House employees are not reading Breitbart. Don King gets a swastika tattoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Pete Sessions reluctantly explains to Katrina Pierson that liberal activists are part of the deep state. Arnold Schwarzenegger passes the Voight-Kampff test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Darrell Issa accidentally convinces Jeff Sessions that Russian officials are alcoholics. Corey Lewandowski discreetly applies for other jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Roger Stone tries to persuade Kellyanne Conway that civil rights activists are conservative Christians. Corey Lewandowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Paul LePage divulges to Omarosa Manigault that Trump's sons are carrying concealed weapons. A mysterious man runs over a homeless person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jealous Rick Scott informs Rick Perry that NBC reporters are cannibals. Kayleigh McEnany finds a wallet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Steven Mnuchin mistakenly tells President Trump that Syrian refugees are infiltrators. Pat Buchanan watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Lindsey Graham convinces President Trump that tech executives are watching Fox News. Richard Spencer snorts a few lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During yoga, Elaine Chao accidentally convinces Betsy DeVos that Chinese officials are actually gay. Jon Voight pulls a muscle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Peter King reveals to Ben Carson that Alaskans are ripe for the plucking. Eric Trump gets a second job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of H.R. McMaster fails to convince President Trump that reporters are deserving of a tax cut. Ivanka's bodyguard paints Trump's official portrait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Lamar Smith boldly informs President Trump that poets are untrustworthy. Karl Rove has plastic surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, H.R. McMaster decides not to tell Melania that Asian immigrants are lurking everywhere. Corey Lewandowski gets amnesia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a scheme, Jared Kushner carefully explains to Ben Carson that NRA members are indebted to Satan. The sommelier knits a lovely hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Steve Bannon reveals to Jeff Sessions that the minions of Soros are just like the rest of us. An obnoxious neighbor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Jared Kushner politely tells Rick Perry that European immigrants are about as dangerous as kittens. Bobby Jindal normalizes fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Rick Santorum patiently explains to Kellyanne Conway that prison guards are dangerous. Dana Perino tries MDMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, Jared Kushner announces to Melania that WSJ reporters are dangerous. A White House tourist learns to cook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a long hike, Rex Tillerson informs Rick Perry that kinksters are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Newt Gingrich goes to the grocery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Rand Paul calmly tells Katrina Pierson that agnostics are on Air Force One. Hulk Hogan plays a prank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Jeb Bush mistakenly tells Ben Carson that CIA agents are trying to make ends meet. Richard Spencer sacrifices a black cat to Satan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Scott Pruitt rudely informs President Trump that Black Lives Matter activists are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. Pat Buchanan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedraggled Louie Gohmert admits to President Trump that drug dealers are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. Bobby Jindal quotes Sartre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Liz Cheney accidentally convinces President Trump that the in-laws are total losers. Cthulhu sends out many resumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Kevin McCarthy reveals to President Trump that Nordstroms employees are big fans. Sarah Palin gets the band back together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Pentagon, Jared Kushner convinces Kellyanne Conway that Biggie and Tupac are planning something ominous. Tucker Carlson bogarts the joint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Scott Pruitt boldly informs President Trump that Democrats are withering under excessive regulations. Dennis Miller admits to pranking Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, H.R. McMaster rudely informs Katrina Pierson that convicts are calling for impeachment. A man in a yellow cloak opens all the windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Pete Sessions decides not to tell President Trump that LA Times reporters are selling body parts. Cthulhu interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On live TV, Reince Preibus reluctantly admits to President Trump that government employees are watching Fox News. Scottie Nell Hughes jumps in the pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a conference call, Steve Bannon admits to President Trump that Kremlin officials are hoarding Trump steaks. A local TV anchor balances the budget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Stephen Miller calmly tells President Trump that Chicago teens are heavily armed. Barry Goldwater's ghost rides off into the sunset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Christmas special, Mark Sanford persuades Kellyanne Conway that the Koch brothers are phishing .gov email accounts. Vladimir Putin tries tai chi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Kevin McCarthy rudely informs Rick Perry that Iranian immigrants are comfortable with nudity. Don King brown-noses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On live TV, General Mattis informs Melania that the Clintons are hunting dolphins. Cthulhu learns to cook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covered in rashes, VP Pence convinces Katrina Pierson that civil rights activists are filing a lawsuit. Glenn Beck tries to slip in through a window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Wilbur Ross announces to President Trump that Hollywood liberals are part of the prank. Scott Baio has to fly coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Reince Preibus politely tells President Trump that Presbyterians are particularly smelly. Larry the Cable Guy shakes the wrong hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, Scott Pruitt calmly tells Melania that Russian oil executives are fake news. Erick Erickson pukes in Trump's lap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, VP Pence convinces Betsy DeVos that Russian spies are drilling for oil. Ted Nugent joins the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Matt Bevin reluctantly explains to President Trump that the New York Mets are big league. Willie Robertson commits seppuku.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Sam Brownback tries to persuade Jeff Sessions that oil executives are not very smart. A "fixer" balances the budget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the balcony, Ryan Zinke proclaims to Rick Perry that Lyft and Uber are becoming too powerful. Arnold Schwarzenegger erases hard drives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While on vacation, Justin Amash politely tells Rick Perry that government employees are very affordable. Cthulhu is hired, then fired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Saturday, Jared Kushner politely tells Jeff Sessions that MSNBC pundits are withering under excessive regulations. Trump's bodyguard hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Roger Stone politely tells President Trump that oil executives are faithful conservatives. Trump's bodyguard leaks to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Rick Scott reluctantly explains to Kellyanne Conway that Chicago teens are coming over for Christmas. The maid pops a zit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Lindsey Graham tries to convince Jeff Sessions that abortion doctors are in covert ops. Tila Tequila donates three dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Ryan Zinke politely tells Omarosa Manigault that CIA agents are total winners. Michelle Malkin tries mixed martial arts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Steve Scalise politely tells Ben Carson that tech executives are pro-Trump. The butler vanishes without a trace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Mark Sanford overhears someone tell Omarosa Manigault that unicorns are big supporters. Peggy Noonan gets ready for the Big Night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Lamar Smith reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that Nation of Islam members are watching Fox News. Carl Higbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Wilbur Ross tells President Trump that the servants are in the Oval Office. Melania's bodyguard rides off into the sunset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Wilbur Ross fails to persuade President Trump that conspiracy theorists are vandalizing statues. Carl Higbie uses the wrong door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the balcony, Jason Chaffetz convinces Katrina Pierson that Israeli politicians are ripe for a prank. James Woods learns to knit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Mitch McConnell politely tells Betsy DeVos that those guys are not that powerful. Scottie Nell Hughes compulsively shoplifts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Steve Scalise reluctantly admits to President Trump that Amway executives are not really important. An obnoxious neighbor gets the band back together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Twitter, Carly Fiorina decides not to tell Ben Carson that Chinese officials are immortal. James Caan picks a scab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Jared Kushner politely tells Kellyanne Conway that Mar-a-Lago members are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Trump Junior is trapped in a phone booth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over coffee, Elaine Chao reluctantly explains to President Trump that KGB spies are part of the shadow government. Trump's body double collects a welfare check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Jared Kushner persuades President Trump that Canadians are useful idiots. Trump's body double learns how to gamble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Rick Snyder politely tells Ben Carson that angry parents are struggling to raise money. Erick Erickson learns to knit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Mitch McConnell accidentally convinces Rick Perry that FBI agents are moving in next door. Adam Sandler writes a poem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prankster dressed as Roger Stone fails to convince President Trump that Communists are jealous of Trump. Jeffrey Lord celebrates an anniversary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Ryan Zinke accidentally convinces Katrina Pierson that retirees are at Mar-a-Lago. Peggy Noonan gets amnesia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via email, Rick Scott overhears someone tell President Trump that Chinese officials are big supporters. Corey Lewandowski eats the entire cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, General Mattis persuades Betsy DeVos that NSA agents are calling for impeachment. Barry Goldwater's ghost celebrates an anniversary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covered in rashes, Mike Huckabee admits to President Trump that corporate executives are fake news. Milo Yiannopoulos picks flowers and sighs deeply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Mike Huckabee calmly tells President Trump that Nazis are on point. Stacey Dash erases hard drives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Mike Huckabee tells President Trump that evangelicals are making America great again. Milo Yiannopoulos gets way too drunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Lindsey Graham overhears someone tell President Trump that several dictators are boycotting Ivanka's products. The sommelier learns how to rap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While on vacation, Stephen Miller accidentally convinces Betsy DeVos that journalists are dropping big hints. Jon Voight records all conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Jared Kushner boldly informs Betsy DeVos that the hired help are privy to many secrets. Arnold Schwarzenegger drunkenly accosts strangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to Rick Perry that Tea Party Patriots are not watching Fox News. Barry Goldwater's ghost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Reince Preibus rudely informs President Trump that MSNBC pundits are too turnt. An ambassador slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Sam Brownback overhears someone tell Kellyanne Conway that Mar-a-Lago members are moving in next door. Trump's body double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the War Room, Wilbur Ross tells President Trump that those guys are heavily armed. A man in a yellow cloak wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Liz Cheney tells Omarosa Manigault that Asian immigrants are not very smart. Ivanka's bodyguard sneaks out after midnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Rick Snyder accidentally convinces President Trump that the Bushes are headed to prison. The butler learns to knit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intense Kevin McCarthy admits to Rick Perry that coal miners are potential threats. Scottie Nell Hughes quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Pete Sessions patiently explains to President Trump that squirrels are crushed by excessive regulations. Erick Erickson downloads an app.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Mitch McConnell persuades Omarosa Manigault that abortion doctors are calling for impeachment. Kayleigh McEnany pulls a muscle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visibly sick Rick Santorum informs President Trump that Russian oil executives are double agents. The butler slowly gets undressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Steve Bannon fails to persuade President Trump that Republicans are fake news. Don King cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While skinny-dipping, Butch Otter reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that CNN reporters are capable of great things. Chris Christie shows off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday, VP Pence persuades Kellyanne Conway that Catholics are Rosie O'Donnell fans. A "fixer" goes shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday, VP Pence persuades Kellyanne Conway that Catholics are Rosie O'Donnell fans. A "fixer" goes shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Sam Brownback accidentally convinces President Trump that Republicans are astonishingly successful. Sarah Palin sends out many resumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Lindsey Graham patiently explains to Betsy DeVos that leftist college students are tying up the phone lines. Tila Tequila quotes Aristotle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Rex Tillerson tries to persuade President Trump that kinksters are not real. An obsequious reporter tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, John Kasich tries to convince Ben Carson that Somalian immigrants are fake news. Clint Eastwood uses the wrong door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Lamar Smith calmly tells Omarosa Manigault that kinksters are struggling to raise money. Richard Spencer wears a tutu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Christmas special, Mark Sanford rudely informs Melania that Fox reporters are filing another lawsuit. Kayleigh McEnany brown-noses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Mitch McConnell insists to Betsy DeVos that socialists are vandalizing statues. Carl Higbie wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Mike Huckabee confesses to Rick Perry that Native Americans are astonishingly successful. A "fixer" runs over a homeless person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the War Room, Roger Stone tells President Trump that rappers are crushed by excessive regulations. A White House tourist runs for office.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>