<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A clerk is sailing a cruise ship to a crystal high school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A screenwriter sinks into a river filled with honey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Madagascar there is a bonsai tree which is writing a book about shooting stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By looking at a grapefruit, an ancient duke is able to bring a chicken's egg into existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A software developer is smoking weed in a desert island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Moroccan accountant writes a book of poetry that is made out of cupcakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Caribbean philosopher spends all her time writing a mathematical treatise about the fossil fuel industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 10th century Catalan prophecy that you will be hugged by a shark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gigantic ballroom covers the whole of France. A crystal cockroach is in the centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Austrian political party stands up for the rights of polyamorous centaurs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is whistling in a police station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Indonesia there is a novel that is made of elephants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are transported to a land ruled by a ghost. You can hear the faint sound of a clarinet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Chinese sheik decrees that everyone must start eating a chocolate truffle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipsters is feeling extremely mediocre today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hacker discovers that she does not exist. The only thing that exists is an enormous platinum football stadium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an ATM in Quebec where you can withdraw maps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A solicitor finds a mystical book containing instructions for building an opera house out of encyclopedias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baron discovers that Google does not exist, and goes mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kenyan economist walks into a forest and discovers a rose bush made of Sesame Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blonde archangel bans people from owning sea snakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A carpenter is getting drunk on tequila shots inside a photograph.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorcerer sees an opera about a nipple that can destroy the universe, and sets out to find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lonely governess marries a glass gold mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychic turns over a tarot card with a bunny on it. 'Beware of tulips,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A novelist finds out that nine spiders are controlling mathematics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Icelandic office manager invents a new theory of art based on the movement of snowflakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Palestinian princess discovers that her baby is her baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A steamboat floats on a lake filled with vinegar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an orchid in Beijing that is infinitely beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every spice merchant in China is drunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mesopotamian battleship sails across an ocean of quantum mechanics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a lunar eclipse a sentence is inscribed on a copper disc. It reads: "Leave this world. Make a new life on Uranus."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lion made of Monsanto appears in Tokyo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Basque software developer possesses a unique skill: He can sense the presence of intellectuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chrysanthemum creates feelings of regret in everyone within an eight metre radius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old woman is cutting up tomatoes in a swamp. She is thinking about machine guns. There is a zebra standing right behind her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king starts to build a replica of Paris out of snowmen, but runs out of snowmen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A realtor forgets a torture chamber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Italian prince murders a neurosurgeon with an unusual weapon: A piano.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crocodile lays an egg. The egg is a candy bar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A medieval manuscript describes a caterpillar with puppies instead of legs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A countess is trying to solve a riddle: What has a moustache and an eyebrow, but not a knuckle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teenage opera singer is hiding something unusual in her basement: A penis covered in topazes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Turkish poet listens to a CD that plays the sounds of fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Germany there is a dishwasher which is kissing a veterinarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woodcutter is imagining a gramophone in heaven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Irish pope plays a game of charades with a little girl's mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A child is travelling from Sri Lanka to the Stone Age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mongolian senator sets fire to history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A field marshal wishes to destroy every telephone in Calcutta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A courageous travel agent falls in love with bad luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A politician sees a birthmark in the shape of a swimming pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl finds a Swiss-made watch which allows her to destroy reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A butler is being pursued by the dawn of time on an Assyrian sea serpent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In California there is a lily with the power to create climate change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A solicitor steals dragon's fire and hides it inside a marble ziggurat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An apple tree made of coral grows in a Portuguese garden. A duke plots to steal it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pope can move ferris wheels with his mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a princess in Prague with a glass eye instead of a heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mathematician finds a treatise by Nietzsche on the subject of cheeseburgers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sixty-four quantum physicists meet once a year on top of a mechanical mountain to decide the fate of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ancient manuscript describes a universe made of Snapchat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prince owns a topiary garden which depicts every sin since the dawn of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess decrees that everyone must try to torture postmodernism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sous chef makes a soup out of amniotic fluid and pizzas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A novelist is burning in a haunted rollercoaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a solar eclipse giant salamanders invade Budapest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An emperor secretly wishes to have sexual intercourse with sadness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A secretive professor spends 17 months writing a book about capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kitten and a baroness are getting a divorce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 5th century BC Trojan prophecy that you will worship a ray of light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Spanish tax accountant sets up a firm advising anthills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An empress hears of a duck pond made of fingers, and decides to see it for herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Las Vegas is an alphabet in which every letter is a temple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker is murdered. The murderer turns out to be a pharmacist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Christmas Eve Paris is flooded with treacle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are transported to a psychiatrist's consulting room in Lapland. There you befriend a talking hippopotamus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fisherman becomes rich by selling the Queen of Spades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A metaphysician dreams about every argument that has taken place in Budapest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A necromancer celebrates the anniversary of her marriage to a bearskin rug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are walking through a land ruled by a talking caterpillar. A court jester appears and hands you a novel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clown whispers to a pirate: "I feel so melancholy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cloud is combing his pubic hair in a cathedral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A narcissistic child writes a dissertation that is made out of UC Berkeley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mermaid owns a crucifix that allows her to taste every dish in Varanasi at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A meerkat has male pattern baldness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sultan switches bodies with a lettuce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congressman falls in love with Franz Kafka's The Trial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 26-year-old dentist owns a pair of binoculars that let him talk to apartheid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ethiopian rabbi turns into an enormous garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Canadian flight attendant discovers a mango tree made of furries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientist sits on a magical hospital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In India there is a bat which works as a college professor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Armenian professor spends his whole life writing an impossibly complex theory of juniper trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An octopus enjoys reading the philosophy of Heidegger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up and realize you have turned into Vladimir Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fortune teller turns over a tarot card with a Krispy Kreme donut on it. 'You will be killed by a Tibetan bank manager,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the night of the full moon a poem is etched into a pearl belonging to a Belgian angel. It reads: "Hang in there, baby."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a gay sauna in Cardiff. Everyone who goes there is a mirror.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>