<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/bymdzIOtnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/4VzyBinZRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/omiJpMGszL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/a3pA7UPzsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/wMUkpPfl2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/TNLCkTeSGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/yNBxZMED92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last words to the 'Star Spangled Banner?' 'Play ball!' - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/gijgH0cMRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/A2iwBeBGYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/BSQv6guBnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/szp7pPZC4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/8qab81d10E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/k3EKuep76U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/lO6kJpdt1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/HisxAcoqTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/E5zsxNbJem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/oBZm3sC63i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/0ICo5d8f1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/Re773QWy8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/hfBVhVVY64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/DL6MZy5B5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/hfBVhVVY64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/SksQGjoaU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/g6hKhAYeNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/Y8Vo23XBD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/DfldFllK7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/G9rn1fXhOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have heard of Bitcoin?  Read these 10 important things you should know... http://t.co/gdyHFK3qUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/aiTYGd7YqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/zJFyNvN5TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/bLJiV4uZef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/tNSEEktDJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/YEsZi7Buot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/Rp2DrRup7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Introduction to Ray Bradbury  http://t.co/bO5bG6032x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/SdWK96ozVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9OewQagblt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/mKExVPHYam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/qUOVdh2YXq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>