<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if it will be a White Xmas? Typical #Vancouver, it snows it warms turns to rain and washes away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlyRoseMusic you've already won. America get out and vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AllAboutTaurus: Most #Taurus have great fundamentals never betray, keep a secret, tell the truth and speak from the heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: “Let us put our minds together and see what life we can make for our children” – Sitting Bull #Dallas #FeedTexas #Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: Pls RT Give the gift that keeps on giving. 1yr of savings across America plus 30 meals to those in need. Visit http://t.c ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement” – Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow could it be lucky 13 for me? #PickMeEllen #12DaysofGiveaways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessJoules same as Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daily affirmation and motto for success: #Persistence, #Patience and #Passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FunnyOrTruth: Before you “assume” try this crazy method called “asking”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: Only 7 days til xmas. Do you have all your shopping done? Give the gift of savings plus help #feedtexas http://t.co/ibSKH0vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir @RichardBranson &amp; son Sam are exposing the failure &amp; "Breaking The Taboo" - Film: http://t.co/tFxihM7b via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While enjoying an amazing meal by chef Ricci #spoiltrotten thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #Beatles documentary yelling at voice over to shut up and let's hear the music! #greatest music ever!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at the gym after 2 weeks of procrastinating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Courage is not living without fear. Courage is being scared to death and doing the right thing anyway." - Chae Richardson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @levie: The only question is, who are the 2.9%? http://t.co/Zl3MzVjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DepressedDarth: This would be terrible http://t.co/xGZMyGnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erichrich oh hello!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart and prayers go out to all those affected by today's Connecticut school shooting. Such a senseless tragedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are defined more by how you rise then by how you fall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Dubstep Christmas Lights House - First Of The Year http://t.co/9m0CNjBR via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Dubstep Christmas Lights House 2012 - Bangarang and Cinema Mix by...: http://t.co/yJ7BlTVx via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homemade meatballs and tomato sauce with spaghetti. Love my live in chef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@ayymiPAPITO: COOLEST GIF EVER http://t.co/PgeG9sF1” sweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a $700 package from @FairmontPacific via @cwistal http://t.co/YLJkOFkf RT to enter! #VcB12DaysofGiveaways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessJoules awww such a great pic! I miss Jaclyn and Jasmine is getting so big. Cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing as usual. Pulled pork eggs Benny at El Camino on main street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GanzHydraulus: "little by little, a little becomes a lot" http://t.co/m8nV19sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying Toshi sushi. Best in #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing any road work gets done with so many workers standing around watching one guy work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to shave the goatee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Diamondkwhite great attitude! Now you are free, go soar and become a big star! You are on your way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see @Diamondkwhite going home. #WeLoveDiamond I look forward to your future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LA_Reid disappointed man. No harmony over @Diamondkwhite? Seriously? So much for the love #xfactorusa #epicfail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just entered @VanChristmas Sweepstakes for chance to win German Christmas Market river cruise: http://t.co/OEBrOcHV. Check it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow #PickMeEllen!!!! Big fan love your work and what you have done for so many!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow #PickMeEllen love u and ur show! Help @feedtexas &amp; http://t.co/A6nmYQ82 provide #1millionmeals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help RETHINK HUNGER and provide #1millionmeals to #feedtexas Visit: http://t.co/A6nmYQ82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rihanna simply amazing! #VSFashionShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn I love that song @BrunoMars #VictoriaSecret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alan_Stiff: 20 Quotes That Reveal How Mark Cuban Became Everyone's Favorite Billionaire  http://t.co/ihwDtuhz by @sai via @CEOdotcom ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Will and Kate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My baby made me the most amazing meatloaf tonight. Yes, meatloaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mind is always planning, wanting to be unleashed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedingAmerica: We are so close to 100,000 followers! Can you help push us over the edge? Pls RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: “Don’t sit down and wait for the opportunities to come. Get up and make them.” – Madam C.J. Walker #BeEpic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chillynking Wow! Cool pic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't procrastinate. Be strong, kick yourself in the ass and take charge of you health. Life will be easier better and longer for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening ceremonies #2010 #Vancouver #Olympics 70,000+ people w lights #Inspiration http://t.co/ft0PTtDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Caution: parading is not recommended..." "In this garment"- Comedians in cars getting coffee @JerrySeinfeld #brilliant #lol #funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a balance of holding on and letting go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You seem to have lost sight of the forest for all the trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Hawks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to be right as rain. It's better when something is wrong. You get excitement in your bones And everything you do's a game - Adele]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @high_on_glitter: That door is opening once again. And this time, it’s opening for #You.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ogwodavies: There are some people who walk into your life and shed a new light in your entire being. Be grateful to such people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not til we are lost do we begin to find ourselves http://t.co/6yzWlQxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: Learn from the past, set goals for the future, and live in the only moment of time you have and control: now. Help #feedt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GanzHydraulus: Don't look back, you are not going that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it" – Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Scientists are discovering that while anger and hatred eat into our immune system, warm-heartedness and compassion are go ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream as if you'll live forever. Live as if you'll die today" - #JamesDean Amen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Good luck Tina &amp; Amy at the @goldenglobes! Be funny &amp; fearless &amp; have a blast. Love from Ricky, the pig, a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is I'm inspired to work on next steps, come up with strategy and excited to be on the path I'm on. #Onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I don't feel like doing anything. I just wanna lay in my bed. Don't feel like picking up my phone, so leave a message at the tone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancin around living room w @BrunoMars cranked #RunawayBaby Beautiful #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never forget you or our time together but in the short term, I must do both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be who you want to be. People are going to judge you no matter what you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pipejaramillo20 "Sometimes love is not enough and the road gets tough i dont know why…." - so true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you reach the end or your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on." - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@a_skenny: @2ChrisSimpson better than not ever try to get things done !!” haha I'm working on it! Onwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get back up, dust self off, repair heart, deep breaths and focus. Opportunities are knocking. Easier said than done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast of champions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiest http://t.co/0JZCLUWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's official it is a Downton Abbey marathon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already #addicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Settling in to watch season 3 of Downton Abbey. Hope I remember season 2, it's been awhile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GanzHydraulus: If you can dream it, you can do it - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The key is to keep company only with people who uplift you, whose presence calls forth your best." - Epictetus #BeEpic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tiger doesn't lose sleep over the opinions of sheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23:00hrs at home working on a competitive analysis, no shirt, pjs and about to watch the news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words to live by http://t.co/bqUSOTaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: Focus and commitment work close together; Don't let distractions divide the two! #BeEpic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a new day, a new year. Time to focus and set 2013 on a course for great success! Onwards!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losing love is like a window in your heart. Everybody sees you're blown apart. Everybody see the wind blow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinolearytv: The future is uncertain and the end is always near. From a poem by @JimMorrison of the Doors. Words I live by. 
http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers to 2013! May it bring health, happiness and good fortune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When "the one" turns out not to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was too good to be true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to putting 2012 behind me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are so worried about what they eat over the holidays. They should really worry about what they eat the rest of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GanzHydraulus: We will open the book.  Its pages are blank.  The book is called Opportunity and its first chapter is New Year's Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: Sometimes a small thing you do can mean everything in another person's life! #BeEpic #MerryChristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DepressedDarth: It's better to give than to receive, especially if you're receiving a lightsaber to the midsection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ogwodavies: Like sun, from the East, may you rise!!! The world needs your light. Shine!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is over. The future may never be. The present is all that exists. Live each moment to the fullest. Zen]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>