<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Customer Care and Performance Tuning: Senior Software Engineer, Customer Care and Performance Tuning As a key member of the Equinix Enterprise application development team, the candidate will be leading the development of… https://t.co/5Ta43vFaE5 https://t.co/KMsOcw01pD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Technology Systems – Learning and Development: Job Description Job Description This position is responsible for configuring/maintaining enterprise MetroPCS HR Learning Management systems including but not limited to updating/creating business… https://t.co/RI4mZqZsjg https://t.co/SxhJnIw47L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economist Glen Weyl on Three Radical Paths to Equality: Pay users for their data. Eliminate one-person-one-vote. And let individuals sponsor migrants. https://t.co/nPZhbvrx5B https://t.co/E6SlQmUGJt https://t.co/CWxLh3OvBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIM Coordinator/Hardware Engineer: **BIM Coordinator/Hardware Engineer** Locations:Irving, Texas Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Postal, Parcel, and Airport Logistics **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/cSPyM70hc7 https://t.co/J3xHXMBM9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Scrum Master: Information Security Scrum Master : 18-02293 Ref No.: 18-02293 Location: Farmers Branch, Texas Akraya is looking for a Information Security Scrum Master for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit,… https://t.co/v6qeaeSBqa https://t.co/81ma5nbjrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Worth, TX Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/21/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position is responsible for analysis, codes, tests and documents moderately complex applications… https://t.co/fqZGj99nNk https://t.co/pJKJFyPi8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .NET Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contract to Hire Location: Dallas, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/21/2018 Job Description Sr .Net Developer DISYS is currently looking for a Sr .NET Developer… https://t.co/EChKugjhj8 https://t.co/OmB1wz6spS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox… https://t.co/O1iqUqUAIK https://t.co/FiLo1On81N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer with Infrastructure Experience – Mid Level Job: Java Engineer with Infrastructure Experience – Mid Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA –… https://t.co/Cj29hrfhaZ https://t.co/jOXBPAVRhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-37612 Location: Irving, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing well !! Please go through the below requirement details and let me know if you are interested. Please send me your updated resume along with contact details.… https://t.co/CFbyaeiehD https://t.co/YWNodx6FqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Operations Manager: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’ lives. We’ll… https://t.co/Q3bp1NX3Iu https://t.co/KHYKZoVBN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BB- Infrastructure Developer – Java/REST/NoSQL/Big Data/Hadoop – Hydra: AIC Talent Solutions is interviewing candidates to fill a large project for an enterprise wide solution across the United States. This project is to evaluate a large national… https://t.co/da2YReodch https://t.co/qo25tADSUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/sql developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/sql developer – ID:31484 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL/SQL, Billing LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/13/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for GIS… https://t.co/mkgdSSnxoZ https://t.co/DZgtAp0ywb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Early Career: Location: Plano Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers Jobs The Boeing Company is seeking Software Engineers in support of a Flight Electronics Utilities Development Team. This position will part… https://t.co/IZb0y1YVXO https://t.co/h7iAWhGYIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager – IT Strategy and Analytics: What you’ll be doing… As a Senior Manager, you’ll serve in this crucial role for driving emerging technology implementation across Supply Chain IT, which includes Verizon Spend Visibility (Big Data) and… https://t.co/iIdNbdh1WN https://t.co/IwD1DfichA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Developer: Job TitleAndroid Application Developer – ID:32289 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsDesktop LocationDallas, TX Date Posted08/07/2018 Qualifications Qualified candidates will have a Bachelor’s degree or 5+ years… https://t.co/2iZNsGQFWp https://t.co/3bU1RpdBXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer-: Job ID : ****** Location : Irving, TX US Level : Experienced Professional Job Category : Information TechnologyDescription : Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting,… https://t.co/2TCPishbx3 https://t.co/syixs8BDaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Controls/Automation Engineer, P.E. (Design Group): Design Group is a leading Engineering, Systems Integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial… https://t.co/jp1vR2V097 https://t.co/lFV4jR8Ead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Web Developer – Front End Design: Job ID 2018-9480 Overview Aegion Corporation is looking for a Sr. Web Developer – Asset Integrity Management Aegion combines innovative technologies with market-leading expertise to maintain, rehabilitate and… https://t.co/CvTYkGAeq8 https://t.co/gdsEPhOqux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer at EXPERIAN Skip Navigation – Consumer – Small Business – Business – More…X Experian Site Sections – About Experian – Consumer Support – Credit Advice – Global Sites – Company Profile – Corporate Fact… https://t.co/iVDV6SFIb7 https://t.co/IaLAM3xXOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Developer: Senior C++ Developer Job no: CGM-****** Work type: Full time Location: Houston Group: Corporate Operations Group Division: Technology Recruiter: Andrew Baker Key Responsibilities: * Implement software and environment solution to… https://t.co/dD08Exl1Hs https://t.co/BiLvmcVie3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 22/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 22667 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/pnbKnz85sZ https://t.co/rdoTiKIc3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Job Description This individual will be responsible for installing and administrating systems, applications, and processes and ensuring that all issues are identified and resolved in a timely manner. He/she will be responsible for… https://t.co/KeykYOdQZw https://t.co/RjoV1IXVxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls/Automation Engineer: Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, Systems Integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial sectors.… https://t.co/RyYWh9Je9T https://t.co/10ZxkdzkJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meditech Clinical Help Desk Support Analyst: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 22/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 28858 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything… https://t.co/TyMk4HmBE3 https://t.co/3FUdxfKG1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: QA Engineer at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact Sheet Principal Businesses Areas of Expertise… https://t.co/iLfOuBIRnG https://t.co/fHsjT7IebD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer (GIS): A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a global consulting, engineering and construction management firm that provides technology-enabled solutions to the power, oil and gas,… https://t.co/Z1B4k5Gye8 https://t.co/8WlMU5JNsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Utility Billing – Lubbock, Texas: Job Description Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Utility Billing Tyler’s Incode Utility Billing suite of applications are a perfect fit for both municipal and… https://t.co/yOGxtka2lp https://t.co/1EulXNSZbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Linux Storage/NVME Storage: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing,… https://t.co/vSMAYR5qAV https://t.co/v53rosyEzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Early Career: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 08/20/2018 Location Plano Texas United States Job Description The Boeing Company is seeking Software Engineers in support of a Flight Electronics Utilities… https://t.co/gjJN2hTkHm https://t.co/RcMt7bSfbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Service Desk: Job Description Job Description Manager, Service Desk Description The Service Desk Manager is to develop, lead and motivate a high performance team of Service Desk professionals to deliver excellent technical support with a high… https://t.co/XP9lFbgsxJ https://t.co/XnDCP2dyDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Senior Project Manager, IT: Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 21468 Overview Join us for a career with endless possibilities. Looking for a job where a passion for innovation, a culture of… https://t.co/GhlJ4ByYEJ https://t.co/2lafqKQzaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco ISE Network Engineer – Pomona, CA: Date: Aug 22, 2018 Location: Pomona, CA, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 28657 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment… https://t.co/ZCqmbFxujh https://t.co/vzPaVGI2FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Technology Systems – Learning and Development: Job Description Job Description This position is responsible for configuring/maintaining enterprise MetroPCS HR Learning Management systems including but not limited to updating/creating business… https://t.co/sqNHyktYWj https://t.co/PH9uW2DYuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Programmer: * CNC Programmer Location US-TX-Waller ID 16913 Business Unit Superior Completion Services SES, LLC – Completion Services, a Superior Energy Services Company, has the technology, resources and experience to deliver effective sand control… https://t.co/M8mS52KrS3 https://t.co/kgf4iMu7XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Threat Hunting Analyst/ Security Data Scientist (Houston: Company description:Shell is a global group of energy and petrochemicals companies with over 90,000 employees in more than 70 countries and territories. In the US, we have operated for over… https://t.co/ffHWVsVx0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Integrator: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Software Developer &amp; Integrator Senior Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software development… https://t.co/gjYCrBpEkV https://t.co/X3BJmfCNfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Java: Job ID : ****** Location : Irving, TX US Level : Experienced Professional Job Category : Information TechnologyDescription : Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting,… https://t.co/niOA5l5QUt https://t.co/CjCZAsTvNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer – Web Services – Senior Level: PURPOSE OF JOB We are currently seeking talented Java Software Engineers Senior Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. Employer Java Software Engineers create and maintain APIs for our business… https://t.co/BsmjMS0XcH https://t.co/cw1ed3Ye1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tibco Java Developer: Tibco Java Developer Irving, TX $90-120K Company’s Unified Customer View – Technology Solutions (UCV-TS) team is responsible for delivering new functionality to support the UCV data platform and providing the business with a 360… https://t.co/HJ71jwA6pL https://t.co/gZvJXVbFxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer with Infrastructure Experience – Mid Level Job: Java Engineer with Infrastructure Experience – Mid Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA –… https://t.co/8TMdRNQ0g3 https://t.co/5BxkkpZlCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP/PI consultant RDF: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:37 Req ID: 2621 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/y5GknqpQv0 https://t.co/LylmZ3RQHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: Costa Rica Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 21234 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and… https://t.co/Ci4LkayZew https://t.co/xCrOFaa5oD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Developer: Deltek Talent Management – Mobile Developer – (C.18.1) This site attempts to protect users against Cross-Site Request Forgeries attacks. In order to do so, you must have JavaScript enabled in your web browser otherwise this site will… https://t.co/xSpGCnxCWM https://t.co/GTyYntdbgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .NET Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contract to Hire Location: Dallas, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/21/2018 Job Description Sr .Net Developer DISYS is currently looking for a Sr .NET Developer… https://t.co/U19oaMiYFW https://t.co/XmoKNZnz0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: SR Number APPS/APPS/2018/****** Designation Technical Lead Location Texas Job Family Development (Development) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for managing technology in projects and providing technical guidance / solutions… https://t.co/FuG1QOuSho https://t.co/SsSuLZOMtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Summary:The primary responsibility of the Automation Engineer is to design, develop and further automate the infrastructure which supports our business platforms and continuously improve to meet the evolving technology used at Global… https://t.co/bYDIu4oZbZ https://t.co/k1to8ZohYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Job Locations US-TX-Plano Job ID 2018-4965 # of Openings 1 Overview Beyondsoft is a leading IT consulting and managed services provider specializing in consulting, product engineering, IT services and business process… https://t.co/RjOxt7TJ1O https://t.co/zx1GY6qCWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach Enterprise Applications ORACLE, SAP or SALESFORCE: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:33 Req ID: 14163 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on… https://t.co/UNvx9bHMLw https://t.co/EEFzEco526]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Spring, Hibernate, Webservices Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:31 Req ID: 23639 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/eLP5MDekN8 https://t.co/4qlovpUNRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 21/08/2018 00:29 Req ID: 20990 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/mJqDvHqwiy https://t.co/rEBO1ZaZOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the… https://t.co/D1ChMd6bFr https://t.co/lpdhjkTVAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Production Support Analyst: Date: Aug 1, 2018 Location: Charlotte, NC, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27238 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of… https://t.co/zt4ssNy4nE https://t.co/aL9kJHER7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Infrastructure Tiger Team Solutions Architect: Location US-TX-Plano Posting date 7 hours ago(8/20/2018 3:30 AM) Job ID 64504 Category PreSales, Solution Architecture Company description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers,… https://t.co/Ir5MC9W9Xq https://t.co/tD1Do4luP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Arizona Address: Post Date: 25/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 29029 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/gvmGMqs2ns https://t.co/wjEjn1NIVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-37612 Location: Irving, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing well !! Please go through the below requirement details and let me know if you are interested. Please send me your updated resume along with contact details.… https://t.co/oVzn1CTLDj https://t.co/KJPXubffug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: – Interface with clients to understand their issues – Help our business analysts find and provide workarounds for critical issues – Debug complex systems and make appropriate changes to resolve client issues, includes C# applications,… https://t.co/XQusN1QPuX https://t.co/6a2z78MrXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C/C++ Embedded Infotainment Software Developer (HMI and Applicatio…: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 06/09/2018 00:09 Req ID: 30293 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right… https://t.co/wxpS9qDiJt https://t.co/DAc9D9Hfty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media Group Search… https://t.co/GYwFkRWyhs https://t.co/KCPdDQC1d7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Lewisville: Expert in Core Java and designtechnique as well as experience working across largeenvironments with multiple operatingsystems/infrastructure for large-scale programs (e.g.,Expert Engineers) starting to be firm-wide resourcesworking… https://t.co/3tv3W0ZGtN https://t.co/u95YeAi2Oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Solution Architect: Company Summary =============== Join our team! As a global leader in providing title insurance, settlement services and risk solutions for real estate transactions, First American Title Insurance Company (NYSE: FAF) is an… https://t.co/QQXfHvuUn3 https://t.co/zvGWNqjqaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect: Job Description Adobe believes in hiring the very best. We are known for our vibrant, dynamic and rewarding workplace where personal and professional fulfillment and company success go hand in hand. We take pride in creating… https://t.co/4vm0GKn3VJ https://t.co/ZNP5Gnr9wI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Incident Response Analyst: Cyber Incident Response Analyst Job no: COG-****** Work type: Full time Location: Houston Group: Corporate Operations Group Division: Technology Recruiter: Andrew Baker As a Cyber Incident Response Analyst, you’ll be… https://t.co/wOdFgynjhX https://t.co/cZXL7KpG27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator III: The IT d Services Department at the University of North Texas System is seeking to hire a Systems Administrator III to join our team. This position performs complex (journey-level) computer systems analysis work. Work involves… https://t.co/d30XBLQ7kr https://t.co/3fISB5ptob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Engineer Advanced Arlington, TX or Milford, OH: For Siemens User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/QFY5WawHzq https://t.co/j6DNIljUdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of our bleeding-edge networks and platforms. Utilizing your… https://t.co/8PwPZy2P7F https://t.co/KJYebFpS67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMS Developer Java based CMS: Job Ref: ******* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:32 Req ID: 23577 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/vtB95jRf6o https://t.co/TTPUfazzOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Finance Functional Consultant: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:21 Req ID: 2782 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/hMhRA7ObEN https://t.co/8hoAeHamI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitefinity Developer Support Advisor Relocation Available: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:30 Req ID: 21802 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on… https://t.co/FMmudet9le https://t.co/KvJOgphDN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Job TitleNetwork Engineer – ID:32234 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsRouter, Switches LocationGrapevine, TX Date Posted07/27/2018 Position Title: Network Engineer Location: Grapevine, TX Duration: Direct Hire/ Full Time BASIC… https://t.co/llYlZcbTE4 https://t.co/M38m8ElOko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of our bleeding-edge networks and platforms. Utilizing your… https://t.co/UKyN1JnUPS https://t.co/4tDbMksUTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scala Software Engineer – BB: The Finance Reporting Infrastructure (FRI) Technology team will execute a ramp up strategy to add resources to our Software Engineering teams to meet the high demand for FRI platform, onboard more data sources and model more… https://t.co/COlmHHEJPv https://t.co/bsD0kBBuTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description Senior Software Engineer ABB is seeking a Senior Software Engineer for its Sugar Land, Texas location. This role is responsible for leading the development efforts for software applications for electrical… https://t.co/8AqY2S08EJ https://t.co/CZ6PSPDMPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Employer Texas A &amp; M University-Corpus Christi Location 78412 Posted Aug 20, 2018 Institution Type Four-Year Institution You need to sign in or create an account to save IT Business Analyst Job Title IT Business Analyst Agency Texas… https://t.co/2S6bKb2VsF https://t.co/sp8nfdCT77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Techno Functional Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing… At Verizon, we innovate constantly to help the biggest names in business do business – quicker and smarter. It takes vision. It takes focus. And we apply both every bit as much to the… https://t.co/dfBMFCDoRp https://t.co/lSirq2ZIdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System-Administrator: GuideIT is a is a US based technology services company focused on providing value to its’ customers through technology alignment and optimization. We are currently looking for a Systems Administrator to join our team in Plano, TX.… https://t.co/bOZvOSZRZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Senior Analyst-: Date: Sep 3, 2018 Location: San Jose, SJ, CR Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 29561 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of… https://t.co/UrttTJ4V6C https://t.co/ipxyEcpr8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence/ETL Engineer Mid Level: PURPOSE OF JOB We are currently seeking talented Business Intelligence/ETL Engineers Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. Employer Business Intelligence/ETL Engineers are not only experts in data… https://t.co/HHMXvjXGxV https://t.co/2lIsFPoOpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job Description Scrum Master Essential Duties: – Strongly serving and supporting the Product Owner and Development Team in their quest to do everything possible to delight customers. – Providing all support to the team using a servant… https://t.co/ciHuGSNVWM https://t.co/ZwOW046LcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOAMS Online Support (30945): Requisition ID 30945 – Posted 06/19/2018 – Quality and Risk Management – United States – Texas – Permanent A WORLD LEADER IN TESTING, INSPECTION &amp; CERTIFICATION SERVICES Bureau Veritas offers dynamic, exciting employment… https://t.co/9rhLzJDEsb https://t.co/zvfI5n4cGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microservices Developer: Microservices Developer job | Cognizant job in Irving, Texas, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/A8pSiEa9fb https://t.co/bIf76sd3UY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Software Engineer: Job Description Senior Applications Software Engineer Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you’re helping to create a better world. Our customers operate the largest electrical transmission… https://t.co/yooEbyXQo1 https://t.co/O6VFJwOmHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Consultant Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing. A Contact Center Services (CCS) Principal Consultant is a Professional Services Executive Consultant and is viewed by the customer as a subject matter expert responsible for… https://t.co/2zuTCiiJsX https://t.co/8iZX2CZAmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. BPCS Developer Technical and Functional: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 23397 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything… https://t.co/y2kfhwPLlS https://t.co/0ReRxLjyVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Automation Engineer: For Siemens Software Quality Assurance Automation Engineer job – Information Technology – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard –… https://t.co/Uv3MqJxglR https://t.co/Fwi7srKVT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist, GSPE – Round Rock, TX: Senior Data Scientist, GSPE – Round Rock, TX at Dell Careers Skip to main content – Life at Dell – How We Work and Lead – Who We Are – How We Hire – FAQs – Working at Dell – Why Work Here – Diversity &amp;… https://t.co/4I6JfJyzx1 https://t.co/EMasZhHL14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Control Group (PCG) Control Systems Support Specialist: Company Name: Marathon Petroleum Company LP Location Name: Texas City, TX Location Address: 2401 5th Avenue South, Texas City, TX, United States (US), 77590 Education Level: High School… https://t.co/Jeruerl4wh https://t.co/EYk6REjGvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP/PI consultant PROJ: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 02/08/2018 00:29 Req ID: 2543 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/2HJHFDfwAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logistics Network Engineer: Logistics Network Engineer in Coppell, TX at Brink’s – Careers Home – About Brink’s – Veterans – – Featured Careers – Driver-Messenger – Cash Logistics Processors – Corporate – All Jobs – Join Our Talent Network SEARCH OUR… https://t.co/pkDZXj167Z https://t.co/aoxkKtYT4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst, AA Credit Union Application Support: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Analyst Jobs Location: AAFCU Headquarters (DFW-AACU) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 21312 Overview Join us for a career… https://t.co/y8BKQCDW0K https://t.co/sHfgYmGqQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic Application Support Level 2 Manager Plano, TX or US Remote: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:19 Req ID: 20461 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people… https://t.co/qhE4nAJMq7 https://t.co/kdbi4a6xPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer – ITMS: EnPro Industries – Job – Embedded Software Engineer – ITMS – Search Embedded Software Engineer – ITMS Sign up to receive career updates before completing the application Note: You will complete the application on the… https://t.co/artRAU3e63 https://t.co/McfUSepl0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer – IT: Principal Software Engineer – IT at Dell Careers Skip to main content – Life at Dell – How We Work and Lead – Who We Are – How We Hire – FAQs – Working at Dell – Why Work Here – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Growing Your… https://t.co/4gTH2pdCfx https://t.co/DJkD2rXRKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of our bleeding-edge networks and platforms. Utilizing your… https://t.co/2F6zk6hSeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Georgia Address: Post Date: 23/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 29005 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/OgjuXu5qlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Representative, eSolutions (Temporary): Software Support Representative, eSolutions (Temporary) ======================================================= The Software Support Representative on the Application Support Team is responsible… https://t.co/avXsDeBQCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 33899BR Domain Healthcare Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Automation Tools Programming Languages , Java Country USA State / Region /… https://t.co/dmv3VwMdkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Public Safety Solution: Project Manager, Public Safety Solution ======================================= The Project Manager successfully manages the implementation of Tyler software for new and existing accounts, from the contract… https://t.co/54oA7d3yZJ https://t.co/SzSU7vXUCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integrator/ System Administrator 3- TS/SCI Required: System Integrator/ System Administrator 3- TS/SCI Required ========================================================== Req #: ******Location: Austin, TX USJob Category: Information… https://t.co/gdGWW4GKiC https://t.co/v2H04OmBVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Brazos: Project Manager, Brazos ======================= The Project Manager position is an external client-facing position. The Project Manager understands the clients business needs and translates those needs into a plan to deliver… https://t.co/RsKB1TItto https://t.co/5oycivz4og]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>