<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/O31LELxevz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoes are special shoes for discerning feet. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/dNPRUYkrj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/dRrBcG11eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/tuiaVQRb8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/sbC9rJnu60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/UmzxWe2eiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/41RuopjTpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/qiVwdyzuNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/9Tz6rRn7sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/edtFKwfb6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/nBUHLiP4SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/l8634Lnrp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/R5wKrxkN6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/H6Ed1uZXiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/AzHAXCNla4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/agjx8fKjMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/HpXq1r82jM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/J1Ja7ZIVAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/P9J3WFuqVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/BadT4erFXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/jV45TKPhMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/eVkzOC8ZG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/efo9sKGBNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/0DkH2hh9af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/VckfBQxSbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/AMycsAkV6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/r2akFjUVc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/ksBoH0nqeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/XhgHVgQfUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/9lEkiB6YIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/t3R2h44Vz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/AkVBgdl4Nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/W8l7lHzeih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/zqPIx8ip6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/PFSxtdltGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/0bYtBhFUrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/2Bv5S8CLYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/ChSzOZf9Bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/ZdccJOPbnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/ywrNgjFy6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/1F17CqcIo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/6DeumgTazU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/v8eDUPQSnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/b0DQrRwt6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/OudeppqQa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>