<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Be sure to taste your words before you spit them out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is always right to do what is right. - Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep smiling :) https://t.co/zlROWlkYJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence. -Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let someone dim your light simply because it's shining in their eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mother_know: Stay strong! https://t.co/V4UxkY0nh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to forget what's gone, appreciate what remains, and look forward to what's coming next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is to short to spend it with the wrong people. https://t.co/s8jIzf87gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be who you were created to be and you will set the world on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you woke up today with only the things you thanked God for yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/u3rOlpQQbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Any poodle lovers here? ;)

Get this poodle t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/Z5M2H3pO4x https://t.co/4iZjqjbZhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are afraid of failure you don't deserve to be successful! -Charles Barkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this thought. https://t.co/ZDKM3wUUpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positivity is a choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain is nothing compared to what it feels like to quit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Stay strong. Even when it feels like everything is falling apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most powerful weapon on earth is the human soul on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All dreams come true if we have the courage to pursue them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted. -Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great point :) https://t.co/5JS1eQEPGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: Accept your past without regret, handle your present with confidence and face your future without fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The strongest people aren't always the people who win, but the people who don't give up when they lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be slapped by the truth than kissed with a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomanDoItAll: https://t.co/jrCFfdROj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all need love. https://t.co/GNvKOloul5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace is not the absense of trouble, but the presence of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the silly little dramas of each day get you down. For you are here to do great things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are you trying so hard to fit in when you were born to stand out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A life spent making mistakes is more honorable than a life spent doing nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live your life and forget your age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, be the reason someone feels loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are beautiful. https://t.co/UcwRt5fbNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DCoffeeDG: Have faith and have another cup. https://t.co/gjDO6PwF0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust in the LORD with all your heart &amp; lean not on your own understanding. -Proverbs 3:5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful with your words. Once they are said, they can only be forgiven, nor forgotten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/bGSAt4oM8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_HQ: ...and you are NOT a quitter ;)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/b2w8A69kih https://t.co/11e66QVuQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask yourself what is really important and then have the courage to build your life around your answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen without defending; speak without offending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A daughter is one of the most BEAUTIFUL gifts this world has to give. -Laurel Atherton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Don't be afraid to give up the good and go for the great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to give up the good and go for the great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lion doesn't concern himself with the opinions of a sheep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to smile. https://t.co/cy6Vjg8rvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wherever you go, no matter what the weather, always bring your own sunshine. -Anthony J. D'Angelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making mistakes is something everyone does. Learning from them is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have not gone where you intended to go, but you will end up where you need to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have faith when you pray, you will be given whatever you ask for. -Matthew 21:22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can, doesn't mean you should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losing is a learning experience. It teaches you humility. It teaches you to work harder. It's also a powerful motivator. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl deserves a guy that can make her heart forget that it was ever broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasure the love you receive above all. It will survive long after your gold and good health have vanished. - Og Mandino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for something positive in each day, even if some days you have to look a little harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything will be okay in the end. If it's not okay, it's not the end. https://t.co/0Dn7On8ESh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe that God put us on this earth to be ordinary. - Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: It's that time of the year! :)

Get your bonfire tee here --&gt; https://t.co/nOadWSc9iM https://t.co/JTUZv5o2F6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is not something you postpone for the future; it is something you design for the present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest mistake we make is living in constant fear that we will make one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovemypug: Cuteness explosion https://t.co/UHzG3SN13I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You truly are :) https://t.co/LVKTj8CbU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a man's determination. -Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/pwU9i1mASO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things are right around the corner. https://t.co/2zPQukkCwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at life through the windshield, not the rear view mirror. -Byrd Baggett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovemypug: I call this look - too cool for everyone https://t.co/y6GZI4OdnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing what you can accomplish if you do not care who gets the credit. - Harry S. Truman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith and start a new tomorrow. https://t.co/Sr17CjzYMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your dreams be bigger than your fears and your actions be louder than your words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/IztsvWxIyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with those who bring out the best in you, not the stress in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent thought. https://t.co/vwOI4BYb8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live every day as if it's your last, embracing each experience as if it's your first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you do speaks so loud that I cannot hear what you say. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is hard to fail, but it is worse never have tried to succeed. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The richest man is not he who has the most, but he who needs the least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So important https://t.co/nBNBO8YNM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people know the difference between patience &amp; procrastination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are what we think. All that we are arises with our thoughts. With our thoughts, we make the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust takes years to build, seconds to break and forever to repair. https://t.co/Nh9p18S8ED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: That's all that matters! :)

Get your positive tee here --&gt; https://t.co/qSsu78arH1 https://t.co/BoQQMLgtnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleHeadBigH: Without Dreams
We reach nothing.
Without Love
We feel nothing.
Without God
We are nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be a great champion you must believe you are the best. If you're not, pretend you are. -Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith and carry on. https://t.co/RXzCftlPro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/Af4fXOz2Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Coffee&amp;Cats = perfect combination ^^

Get this t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/sfAAiYa27h https://t.co/ialsDHQWYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are valuable and irreplaceable. If you are ever told otherwise, do not believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream as if you'll live forever, live as if you'll die today. -James Dean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Comparison is the thief of joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait for it to happen, go make it happen.
Never lose hope. Never lose faith.
Silence says a lot more than you think.
Do the best you can with what you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minds are like parachutes - they only function when open. -Thomas Dewar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith and push on. https://t.co/AZ3FubqHrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day do something that will inch you closer to a better tomorrow - Doug Firebaugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things define you: Your patience when you have nothing, and your attitude when you have everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Learn to appreciate what you have, before time makes you appreciate what you had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anger is an acid that can do more harm to the vessel in which it is stored than to anything on which it is poured. -Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREAT ADVICE https://t.co/P9Fqs595mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is like a tea bag: you cannot tell how strong she is until you put her in hot water. -Nancy Reagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first step before anyone else in the world believes it is that you have to believe it. -Will smith]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>