<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Engineer: We are currently looking for a full-time Senior Quality Assurance Engineer for our Engineering team. Do you find yourself reporting bugs in applications that you regularly use? Do you enjoy telling developers that… https://t.co/WiMRQuHv39 https://t.co/w5URTq3wkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Lead: Job Summary Apria Healthcare is one of nation’s leading providers of home healthcare products and services including respiratory therapy, sleep apnea therapy, non-invasive ventilation therapy, enteral nutrition therapy, negative… https://t.co/GdW3UnEFQk https://t.co/XnFrD60H5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: StackWave’s mission is to accelerate life-saving scientific discoveries by equipping scientists and engineers in the life sciences with powerful and intuitive tools. We are a small engineering-driven company with a track record… https://t.co/lTVhcoF7bj https://t.co/IYYvfTwh3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geoscience Application Support Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 30 minutes ago Expires 14 May 2018 Qualifications None Geoscience Application Support Analyst in Houston, TX, US,… https://t.co/kg9glUqQ6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Desktop and Network Technician: Provides hardware, software, and network administration and support to internal users’ computer information systems and resources. Responsible for daily operations involving networks, cloud based systems, servers,… https://t.co/p3XQ5n2nEw https://t.co/MBKczbgt6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Project Manager (CPM): Location: Houston, Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Airport Category: Senior Manager Position Description The Customer Project Manager reports to the Director of Airframe Operations and will be responsible for the overall… https://t.co/kf3231vAxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home Hemo Registered Nurse- Dialysis Experience Required: Job Description In Center- RN DaVita is seeking a Registered Nurse who is looking to give life in an outpatient dialysis center.  You can make an exceptional difference in the lives of our… https://t.co/cd3vhojT0i https://t.co/el7ryJudd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber loses its license in southern UK coastal city of Brighton: LONDON (Reuters) - Uber's license in the southern English coastal city of Brighton will not be renewed, the local council said on Tuesday, adding the taxi app is not "fit and proper" and… https://t.co/toaul0JARv https://t.co/fYehHWnRaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Partner Account Manager: Location: Houston, Texas, US Additional Location(s) Austin, TX, Dallas, TX Area of Interest Sales – Product Job Type Professional Technology Interest Security Job Id 1221799 New What You'll DoGlobal Security Sales… https://t.co/i5HDCYgWmb https://t.co/Wbx01rqWaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Hotel Construction – REMOTE: Houston, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a commercial construction company located in… https://t.co/7c45WTkatn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Manager – Store 2510 (Meyerland): As the Geek Squad Manager, youll be responsible for day-to-day operations inclusive of the Precinct and Autotech Bay. Oversees the execution of company sales strategies and fulfillment of Geek Squad services… https://t.co/OAHd92T6jt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Posting Title Technical Support Consultant: – Technical Support Consultant Job Locations US-TX-Houston Req # 9796 # of Openings 3 Job Posting Category Technical Support &amp; Training Overview Aspen Technology, Inc. seeks multiple Technical Support… https://t.co/Vi1RXKyvT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator, Senior – Yeshiva Univ: Network Administrator, Senior – Yeshiva Univ Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 1 Role Description Performs hands on LAN, WAN, Security, Phone system, Server, Storage, Computer Equipment and… https://t.co/BNrHjx4tFX https://t.co/U6Ydmu1EQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Vehicle Embedded Software Engineer: Space Vehicle Embedded Software Engineer in Houston, TX | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | –… https://t.co/x184djcfXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xamarin developers: ******/Xamarin developers Ref No.: 18-18573 Location: Houston, Texas Lead Developer: Masters/bachelor’s degree in computer science/Computer Engineering or other related fields with a minimum of 8 years of experience in Mobile… https://t.co/J6bnOZvxdT https://t.co/BmG5SpWtnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Partner Account Manager: Location: Houston, Texas, US Additional Location(s) Austin, TX, Dallas, TX Area of Interest Sales – Product Job Type Professional Technology Interest Security Job Id 1221799 New What You'll DoGlobal Security Sales… https://t.co/1yD7ppWdzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: StackWave’s mission is to accelerate life-saving scientific discoveries by equipping scientists and engineers in the life sciences with powerful and intuitive tools. We are a small engineering-driven company with a track record… https://t.co/RNApjQMMJw https://t.co/qFyaILK9kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Account Executive – IT Operations Management Software: SALES ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE, IT OPERATIONS SOFTWARE Micro Focus Houston, Texas Discover the new Micro Focus now the worlds 7th largest pure-play software company. By combining HPE Software and… https://t.co/gAeymaqsdg https://t.co/WhmRAZPOfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Windows Developer: We are looking for an exceptionally strong Windows developer for one of our clients in North Houston. Be part of a team developing cutting-edge technology for subsurface imaging solutions. JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful… https://t.co/45j9z2Gp7P https://t.co/ticdD9O3a7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Engineering Graduate Space Vehicle Dynamics Simulation and Software Engineer: New Engineering Graduate Space Vehicle Dynamics Simulation and Software Engineer ================================================================ Req #: ******Location:… https://t.co/6KDlAHNLoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL SERVER: SQL SERVER Ref No.: 18-18387 Location: houston, Texas experience using secure code storage TFS. Strong communication skills (written and verbal). Strong customer service skills. Strong commitment to fostering and promoting teamwork. Ability… https://t.co/MckWgWQgMe https://t.co/PQdHKq0wcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk Content Developer/Consultant: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and… https://t.co/jV0ch8JhKR https://t.co/3kLc3UD3ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 429605BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : We are on a journey to Mars and we're closer than ever. Lockheed Martin built NASA's first Mars lander 40 years ago and has been a part of every NASA… https://t.co/Aimpy0bhtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Developer: Job Description: Avanade Inc. seeks a Senior Cloud Developer in Houston, TX to lead collaborative team efforts in the design, development, testing, and implementation of mission-critical enterprise solutions for clients, including… https://t.co/BSdoeezopF https://t.co/7gkrdptu2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITC – IT Function Communication Manager: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 25 minutes ago Expires 11 May 2018 Qualifications None ITC – IT Function Communication Manager in Houston, TX… https://t.co/n8fpUfmUS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Engineering – Specialty Chemicals, Full-time: Business unit: AMPE About AkzoNobel Industries worldwide rely on our essential chemistry in the manufacture of everyday products such as paper, plastics, building materials, and personal care… https://t.co/7KXgz77N32 https://t.co/00jl6CsQcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin frenzy settles down as big players muscle into market: LONDON/NEW YORK/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - After bouncing up, falling down and keeping investors on the edges of their seats, bitcoin may be maturing into a period of relatively boring stability,… https://t.co/u1LkCelk8A https://t.co/MqbZ6Mpg1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Double Agent, Appliance – NW, N, NE Houston: Our Appliance Install and Repair Tech is responsible for a variety of fulfillment duties which may include delivery, installation, integration, networking, and repair of consumer electronics… https://t.co/kbVEVt4R5V https://t.co/CUX85RPuIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upstream SAP Production Revenue Accounting (PRA) Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 30 minutes ago Expires 14 May 2018 Qualifications None Upstream SAP Production Revenue Accounting… https://t.co/RkhbCu00xc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical): What’s the opportunity? Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical; located off of highway 249) is responsible for the overall management and coordination of project operations in… https://t.co/HGclv0HoWu https://t.co/l8Gu9U2hht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Engineer: We currently have over 40 openings for Entry Level Software Engineers, in multiple locations throughout the United States. No prior coding experience is required. You will receive the necessary training on after you are… https://t.co/xIi3B7gVxE https://t.co/sE0mXynelX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Support Analyst: WHO WE ARE Founded in 2012, Gympass is a disruptive health and wellness platform that connects gyms, studios, and health clubs to companies and their employees. We believe in healthy and active lifestyle, and it is our goal to… https://t.co/axIJ2ZsSYe https://t.co/Yn20ge8gUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Consultant, Professional Services: TriNet is a leading provider of comprehensive human resources solutions for small to midsize businesses (SMBs). We enhance business productivity by enabling our clients to outsource their HR function to one… https://t.co/2iz9Pttxxc https://t.co/2ABzzcFfyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Application Developer: Cherry Companies Junior Application Developer Houston, TX 77048 Cherry Companies is looking for a Microsoft c# .net software developer to Join our small Development Team. The right candidate Works well with a small team and… https://t.co/3I2F0WvRA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Chip wars - China closing in on second $19 billion semiconductor fund: sources: HONG KONG/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - China's state-backed semiconductor fund is near to closing a 120 billion yuan ($18.98 billion)investment round for a second fund to… https://t.co/3Qxv4rbzoJ https://t.co/A19kJo7VgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Software Developer: We are seeking Senior C++ Software Developers to help design, build, and operate our state of the art trading systems. Ideally, you’d work out of our Houston, Denver, or Jersey City offices. What you’ll do: As the member of… https://t.co/x9JEhwVECg https://t.co/7RcneLe2ER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer I: Position Description Developing the platform presents complex challenges. You’ll apply your knowledge of software design principles, systems programming, algorithms, data structures, and multiple programming languages. The ideal… https://t.co/gjsmjALZMO https://t.co/mdHVtU6tsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotel key cards, even invalid ones, help hackers break into rooms: HELSINKI (Reuters) - By getting hold of a widely used hotel key card, an attacker could create a master key to unlock any room in the building without leaving a trace, Finnish security… https://t.co/NjIj22fpXV https://t.co/cKzAaJuITK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, Apple CEO Cook to talk trade at White House: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Donald Trump was set to meet with Apple Inc Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook to discuss trade issues on Wednesday as the technology industry grapples with a U.S. spat… https://t.co/swHqV1wxRV https://t.co/OwhPPIkmIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Microservices: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop, support and integrate software systems in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Systems capabilities… https://t.co/rpSO3pgh9P https://t.co/slPQILiIDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFDC Marketing Cloud – Sr. Consultant – FT role – (Top Management Consulting): Sr. Consultant Level * 5+ years of consulting experience and/or Marketing project implementation experience. No Contractors or Job Hoppers! * 2+ full life cycle projects with… https://t.co/I5uWaOcP7y https://t.co/OAvscEmFZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin climbs to six-week high as market sentiment improves: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Bitcoin rose to a six-week high on Tuesday on positive headlines that included the possible entry of major financial institutions into the space, lifting sentiment on the… https://t.co/bKDC2v5v9n https://t.co/2A06PChbHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researcher in Facebook scandal says: my work was no good for targeted advertising: LONDON (Reuters) - A researcher at the center of a scandal over the alleged misuse of the data of nearly 100 million Facebook users said on Tuesday the work he did was not… https://t.co/OpeMktJ3Qm https://t.co/MA4CdKpxtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Lead: Job Summary Apria Healthcare is one of nation’s leading providers of home healthcare products and services including respiratory therapy, sleep apnea therapy, non-invasive ventilation therapy, enteral nutrition therapy, negative… https://t.co/L9YPJCm7iZ https://t.co/UAzqTCkGpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk Developer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Houston, TX Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/jy6lzyiGPJ https://t.co/gqtlhfIxOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Space Station Program Developer – Summer Intern: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Houston, TX Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/qm67PwoBqU https://t.co/aP1srfC9CT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Security Software Program/Project Manager: Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLearning &amp;… https://t.co/JHJOIUnM7c https://t.co/4YEjw6Vx6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Hotel Construction – REMOTE: Houston, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a commercial construction company located in… https://t.co/wp6nlXjCQ2 https://t.co/F7FSPMOFZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux System Administrator: Company Overview Nabors Industries owns and operates the world’s largest land-based drilling rig fleet and is a leading provider of offshore drilling rigs in the United States and multiple international markets. Nabors… https://t.co/XPZhIdJceT https://t.co/OYFgGlaJqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/xcJCbr05M1 https://t.co/thvH2eniRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pivotal Cloud Foundry Architect: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Pivotal Cloud Foundry Architect with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position At Least 3 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Java… https://t.co/xSDr6Rw4gH https://t.co/U4np9Jkurq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Care Specialist: Role Summary: At ITJobPro, we’re committed to helping our customers achieve success in their recruitment efforts! Our Customer Care Specialists provide premier support to our high-valued customers ensuring high customer… https://t.co/4JRweu8bDC https://t.co/IAVkWbjRYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Audit / Auditor: Job Description Hi Jose, We have been engaged by a client of ours in the Central Houston area. They are seeking an Internal Auditor for a Temporary to Hire role.The company is a top flight organization that boasts a great work… https://t.co/SvG6EAe1bJ https://t.co/xvkKrX87Zj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Controller: Houston, TX Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Corporate Controller with experience, please read on! Based in the Houston, we are one of the biggest realty management companies in Texas. With multiple locations across… https://t.co/NdzaXBSDnJ https://t.co/ikHTMaKVve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Open Source Architect: Houston, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Principle Architect, specializing in open source technologies, please read on! What You Will Be Doing – Design, develop, and test new features for… https://t.co/THuwNMmYR1 https://t.co/JCGFWE6iQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home Hemo Registered Nurse- Dialysis Experience Required: Job Description In Center- RN DaVita is seeking a Registered Nurse who is looking to give life in an outpatient dialysis center.  You can make an exceptional difference in the lives of our… https://t.co/kvHlkQ0jlO https://t.co/afbYqOncTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Heavy Industrial: Houston, TX Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today We are one of the nation's leaders in heavy industrial construction and fabrication. We are looking for more project managers with either heavy industrial or heavy civil… https://t.co/GWmnHFZSNc https://t.co/enQrbPvWhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Technical Consultant II:   Job Description – Lead Technical Consultant II (SUP05041) Job Description*  Lead Technical Consultant II-SUP05041 Description   JOB DESCRIPTION TEMPLATE Job Title Salary Range Lead Technician II Location Reports To Virtual… https://t.co/pdhnL3FkXR https://t.co/IY4ZUQlMr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 429605BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : We are on a journey to Mars and we're closer than ever. Lockheed Martin built NASA's first Mars lander 40 years ago and has been a part of every NASA… https://t.co/yNI1lPYkXv https://t.co/VqPoCPvBVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: In search of a Desktop Support Technician for a direct hire role in Houston, TX. The Desktop/Network Technician role supports the overall Help Desk function and ensures that end users are receiving the appropriate level of… https://t.co/7CSubFkZxH https://t.co/3vSitXHIo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need AEM Manager, Tech Lead and Developers: Need AEM Manager, Tech Lead and Developers – Katalyst Technologies Inc. – Houston, TX – 03-28-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career… https://t.co/88K6qExOy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Controller: Houston, TX Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Corporate Controller with experience, please read on! Based in the Houston, we are one of the biggest realty management companies in Texas. With multiple locations across… https://t.co/dkaenVk4lr https://t.co/a3On3fV27k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Open Source Architect: Houston, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Principle Architect, specializing in open source technologies, please read on! What You Will Be Doing – Design, develop, and test new features for… https://t.co/fZp5CXfEaV https://t.co/nFlN0po5As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Vehicle Embedded Software Engineer: Space Vehicle Embedded Software Engineer in Houston, TX | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | –… https://t.co/FJo8U16h2D https://t.co/z64pUv9fsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Specialist: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global technology… https://t.co/gLMT7J3h03 https://t.co/qrWhxdMc8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geoscience Application Support Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 30 minutes ago Expires 14 May 2018 Qualifications None Geoscience Application Support Analyst in Houston, TX, US,… https://t.co/zlpfokdonp https://t.co/19PyfWphlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Marine Project Manager: _SR. MARINE PROJECT MANAGER_ JOB DESCRIPTION: The Sr. Project Manager is responsible for the overall direction, coordination, implementation, execution, control and completion of specific projects ensuring consistency with… https://t.co/UtLEPfki8J https://t.co/26TUHBQN75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/KFY2nRXQff https://t.co/u4pXZEsFYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We’re Softway. We are an independent agency with offices in Houston, TX and Bengaluru, India. We do work we’re proud of. Work that makes an impact on our clients’ business and, hopefully, the world. We do it by bringing bright people… https://t.co/9ayVmfKH82 https://t.co/823rkycx5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FracCommand Applications Specialist: PRIMARY FUNCTION: This position contributes to the companys success by acting as the technical specialist supporting * the rollout of new products(involved in all aspects of the whole process from feature requests and… https://t.co/VZ6DRBrrOz https://t.co/h9byoITwNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Hotel Construction – REMOTE: Houston, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a commercial construction company located in… https://t.co/tFq3HhNeiK https://t.co/u2AQnl6xng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance engineer: Performance engineer Ref No.: 18-13185 Location: houston, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great! Please have a look at the job description below and let me know if you are interested:. JOB Title: Performance engineer Location: Houston,… https://t.co/jY8zicZ8MX https://t.co/qSty0y7JDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold Fusion/.NET Developer Job: Date: Apr 13, 2018 Location:Houston, TX, US Company: SAIC Cold Fusion/.NET Developer (Job Number:433986) Description: SAIC has an opening for a .Net Developer to work with our team in Houston, Texas. The individual will… https://t.co/7CrP9P7g3M https://t.co/5FAOCdsWDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialty Elastomers Market Developer: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 25 minutes ago Expires 11 May 2018 Qualifications None Specialty Elastomers Market Developer in Houston, TX, US,… https://t.co/7buk54bpdM https://t.co/x4odQFwO12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Manager of UX- Interconnected Retail: POSITION PURPOSE Global Custom Commerce is looking for a Sr. Manager UX who will lead our design team and work collaboratively with engineers, product managers, and other managers throughout the product… https://t.co/09bS2WL1au https://t.co/SMxB6tvckT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upstream SAP Production Revenue Accounting (PRA) Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 30 minutes ago Expires 14 May 2018 Qualifications None Upstream SAP Production Revenue Accounting… https://t.co/Q8LiOspenC https://t.co/u25SrEk3Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter bans ads from Russia's Kaspersky Lab: (Reuters) - Twitter Inc said on Friday that it has banned ads from Moscow-based Kaspersky Lab, saying the cyber-security company's business model conflicts with advertising rules and citing U.S. government… https://t.co/viAObuUOJh https://t.co/FeHn41qjG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orion Software Integration Deputy Lead: Req ID : 429698BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Orion Software Integration Deputy Lead responsible for helping to develop and track the overall software integration plan and… https://t.co/qajlURryPp https://t.co/Gz9IgZKu6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Systems Administrator: A manufacturing and distribution client located in Houston, TX is actively searching for a Financial Systems Administrator to be responsible for all aspects of their consolidation tool, OneStream. The job encompasses… https://t.co/coDpXpCSu5 https://t.co/Mba7zzhI3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GC Manager of Analytics and Data Science: POSITION PURPOSE Want to be a key member of the centralized analytics team within The Home Depot’s hub of innovation and one of the fastest growing segments of .com? Global Custom Commerce is looking for its next… https://t.co/oGxKLKZcaV https://t.co/omKBMvdWz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RD Lead Software Developer: R &amp; D Lead Software Developer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate… https://t.co/9ko0mHr8eP https://t.co/m4floDYyjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager – Houston, TX (15870): Requisition ID 15870 – Posted 05/24/2017 – Management – United States – Texas – Permanent A WORLD LEADER IN TESTING, INSPECTION &amp; CERTIFICATION SERVICES Bureau Veritas offers dynamic, exciting… https://t.co/67LTR2IQUC https://t.co/YnlwvoetUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITC – IT Function Communication Manager: Chevron is one of the world’s leading energy companies, with approximately 60,000 employees working in countries around the world. We explore, produce and transport crude oil and natural gas; refine, market and… https://t.co/VuRqp6KQiW https://t.co/VPSTIZc2ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Audit / Auditor: Job Description Hi Jose, We have been engaged by a client of ours in the Central Houston area. They are seeking an Internal Auditor for a Temporary to Hire role.The company is a top flight organization that boasts a great work… https://t.co/hLLohejpjN https://t.co/ErX0WyF96r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Resource Analyst: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global technology… https://t.co/gT0bQ38IDz https://t.co/s3VqOkdB5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global technology and… https://t.co/LMMpW8NMjF https://t.co/sR26cRi6kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Consultant: Developer Consultant What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At the heart… https://t.co/y7DqsQYDFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk Content Developer/Consultant: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Houston, TX Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/12/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/RlJ1z71dzb https://t.co/5hMVBcyy80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan's cryptocurrency exchanges need tighter rules: Monex CEO: TOKYO (Reuters) - Japan's cryptocurrency exchanges should be regulated more like banks as they hold investors' assets while offering trading platforms, the chief executive of online… https://t.co/73UAjhbOgT https://t.co/wy8HH9DSce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Fence Sales Project Manager/Estimator: Are you looking an exciting career in the construction industry with high income potential? Are you a quick-study, adaptive, and self-motivated? If so, Backwater Fence is the place for you. We have become… https://t.co/fR7SVkSinC https://t.co/IPmQdJIFPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Specialist: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global technology… https://t.co/nAP50Vhl8L https://t.co/p5UO7wW9nM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 75636BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position Summary Rockwell Automation is… https://t.co/T8atNnlAgw https://t.co/dg1d1v5qT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, HP Tax Operations, Projects u0026amp; Communications: Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLearning &amp;… https://t.co/7v8gSqvBQL https://t.co/Pbi3BgszbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cognos Report Developer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride… https://t.co/yaqKbjGKdE https://t.co/6Gy0pVHnoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Req ID : 410768BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Orion Test &amp; Verification Engineer. This person will be responsible for writing test success criteria, developing test procedures, scripts and… https://t.co/2ilhHxN5N1 https://t.co/PM6dkugKlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer – V3Main ************** – Home – About – Mission, Vision, &amp; Values – Leadership – Government – Cybersecurity – News – Services – IT Managed Services – Agile Software Development – Custom Software Development &gt;… https://t.co/xEtILoCrKc https://t.co/j20NWi6Oov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Real Estate Development: What Real Estate Development contributes to Cardinal Health Corporate Real Estate (CRE): CRE services are provided through a core group of technical professionals in concert with select industry… https://t.co/gVFbKCKBcR https://t.co/UPoJQRayxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Manager – Houston, TX (23843): Requisition ID 23843 – Posted 03/01/2018 – Management – United States – Texas – Permanent A WORLD LEADER IN TESTING, INSPECTION &amp; CERTIFICATION SERVICES Bureau Veritas offers dynamic, exciting employment… https://t.co/FDRJ1Fa3he https://t.co/eVb5FLZ5t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Job Summary Lone Star Legal Aid is looking for an experienced Data Analyst who is able to turn project data into custom formatted data reports. The successful candidate will also oversee dozens of automated report sets and work directly… https://t.co/f101cFAf5p https://t.co/RrPdKe2CiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Consultant: Developer Consultant What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At the heart… https://t.co/fDR8zYifX5 https://t.co/8u9SyHhkYU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>