<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/GC9q5s3sXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/jUX3kXZPdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/rtQfD7XVY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/jeEKDAT3PG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/jG2A9bHjBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/NxTmIf4Xuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/cKPKYPQfU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/4aDw6DWBkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/q3KDs2g0qT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/g1hBSOqx7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/xuZQs021xY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/1qbfjba49R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/MdWthWLNPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/xDsxNqYbwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/x64pVqX9xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/MzPCcpreyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/i1Hc6pxRfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/eE00SET4TQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/X7E74rGp1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/d9NExTavck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/zddArD4J4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/n4zRjZ1HlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/MWM6sSPyf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/VC5Za6jtAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/CpnSHyajKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/HcZhL8fj10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/1gtG9zHxVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/vcWmuSAhQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/37aKskIWpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/BQKnvPEkq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/9AgOzOaVWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/Nb9LUeDaD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/2OcQqRuXyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/vrq8JBQCPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/Zyo9sE2uYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/wfHdle1qhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/Bwa1IpvoLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/k6KcvKWt10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/zlvXBnCXuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/E2USAv6E90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/D8kNDDmc7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/XapbsWPkWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/uWUV5luUVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/yojAWXef5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/jyOhyN77xI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/NFKrpwM9Tz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/d5P5bE4Pgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/YksHs7VoTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/j2PXr3xx82]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>