<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/W7CAi4dXBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/7OZWvYAeA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/8U2Y06Yncp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/uco579LIf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/9dCLMhd7ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/fX9gNRTxQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/ablHs8mGyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/uxP434WdRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/tX6rR949U2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/oOuoadBOVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/aWIrCz9T9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/HvIeIVHgtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/t4GLh0m4RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/A4L6lUag7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/EvjNXPMynl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 12 - And so it begins...  http://t.co/IT31stqYR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/40qo2v6TpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/iclPfmrc6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/QZce8Cc6Dc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/F6qQsXFMs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/sBCgzu6QTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/jgS5mnPlzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/n0c34AReST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell that you're in trouble when you feel the air on the back of your neck instead of in your face. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/sRvcRoVV96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/tl25xik8gD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/yGbK8zF7bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/8SOisK9mQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/bUyfWAA0F5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/AucbEnqrfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/k7o7g8xYcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/aWIrCz9T9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/MWbJyYl4Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/AEgusYXTk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/lwyOWVbUlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/I2EZ3h927J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/50j9uWjJFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/E906wnVS7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/JbxxGmaXeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/hiB1TNJE1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/nMyk9sVmXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/8K4Eq5urOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/jsB0OCMX27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dqDWjUjokE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/qtTYmdeOFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>