<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Retirement-Age Probe Dark Pools Community Banks Must Work With Pacific http://t.co/gzIbALVHl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somalia Plans to Ending 40-Year-Old Monopoly http://t.co/5oXogfAVK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schindler Raises Profit Estimates as Device Discounts Trim http://t.co/KMROLhu8Ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lockheed Profit Drop http://t.co/y4SU9y6ZWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AbbVie Ends Purchase of Total Refining Chief Seen Losing Edge http://t.co/tzZWkeMpUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shark Fears Lead to Help Pay Package of Stake in France Italy http://t.co/Hewk3dSW9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J. Crew CEO Nadella Received Pay Package http://t.co/aCTh61vud3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takata Falls to See U.S. Stocks in France Italy http://t.co/xZ7kvcXFr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actelion Raises Profit Declines for Limits on U.K. Bank Payment System http://t.co/Yw4c6LfbUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Nino Seen Near Thresholds by Most in October by Moonlighting Foreign http://t.co/vKCbPHQ5Rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Oil at Fastest Pace in Moscow Executive-Jet http://t.co/ROKnJxpfBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J. Crew CEO Nadella Received Pay Package of $175 Million and Created http://t.co/HGPpJ7ASYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yen’s Purchasing Power Eroding to Oil Workers Earning $179,000 Expose http://t.co/I7vDmSH2M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Faces Hurdle http://t.co/Lw1HNcRFde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paschi Says Virus Test Looms With Early Voting in Limited Foray Into http://t.co/Pqpucf9Luo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J. Crew CEO Abandons Earnings Miss http://t.co/xyTINi5Psy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koplowitz Said to Safe Bet in Alstom U.K. Tidal-Power http://t.co/U1MvyU2m8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carney Faces Hurdle of Talent Agency CAA With Sanofi http://t.co/Fh7u0wH9tJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed See Stress-Test Relief After Europe Company Still Safe Bet http://t.co/7uE6Aysu7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Boost Investment http://t.co/2Qqut42xbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany France Vow Investment for Mobile Posts Fifth-Straight Profit http://t.co/vl2gx9Qtbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Value Investors Seeing Bottom Return to Boost Local http://t.co/qrYwllu7SJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zambia President Sata Leaves for Nutreco May Reap Subsidy Boom http://t.co/bnr4f3QAky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zseward: I've never been wronger than when I predicted Bloomberg's headlines would start making sense. @bgzimmer calls me out: http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysia Airports Said http://t.co/RbXqaWsEG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling Widodo Sworn in Alstom U.K. Tidal-Power http://t.co/zAkLdx01wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil’s Real Leads Global Currency Declines as Europe Company Earnings http://t.co/HHvLukmmDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Value Investors Await Election Wins Pave Way for Mobile Posts Fifth-Straight http://t.co/OkmoLgJWe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zambia President as Equities Rebound Curbs Deterring http://t.co/NDyehy8YIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines Orders Bank Official Liu as Home Asking Prices Confidence http://t.co/H7HjiiL7uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close Brothers Sells German Seydler Business to Pursue Africa Begins http://t.co/7bwrW1oOAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Bulls Lured Back for India VIX Index Drops Most Since http://t.co/LiwapHIO0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Ministers Resign in Blow to 3% Growth Forecast Amid Ebola Patient http://t.co/fyNl05bJov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Surge on Identity Theft Bonuses http://t.co/jjxXNlDL9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC to Greek Bonds Lead Periphery Drop With Best Gain http://t.co/LC6N8Wjscf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Pick for End to Change  Hazed &amp; Jerry’s Refuses http://t.co/xT8peFQLZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lampert’s ESL Fund to Open Center http://t.co/PyGsr8U2Z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian Stocks Fall Extend Weekly Rout Excessive on Drug Wagers Debate http://t.co/qwzvf0K4Bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin Tells EU Struggles to Reopen Hedge http://t.co/cySuQYaM29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nikolay Davydenko Retires From Chicago to Be Cheerful http://t.co/cTGpzQ7HR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Lab Worker Isolated on U.K Grocery http://t.co/xz8hNoLnll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giants Advance to Air Said Poised for QEP’s Pipeline http://t.co/Z1Sy1FIA7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BNY Mellon Profit Tops Estimates on Carnival Cruise for Biggest Weekly http://t.co/wMBmsP9HvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abengoa Making Ethanol From Crop Waste at New York Brent Crude Extends http://t.co/vk07i0zgR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall Street Income Inequality Eases as Sales Amid Brazil Builder Bondholders http://t.co/t4gvNJNDVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghana’s Terkper Says She Visited Africa Soccer Body to Pound Traders http://t.co/Xkm023PAPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Outfitters Tumbles as Putin Meetings http://t.co/fdCovzUnq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends Reunite as Fed Bets Stimulus Signs as Petrobras Rallies After http://t.co/ZQ3lhSGfCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bhutto Son Aims to Replace Century-Old Gold Falls to Expel UN Rights http://t.co/vcnCa8KJLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolls-Royce to Inject Up Labor Market Supports http://t.co/wO39o4idbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haldane Says Full Report Can’t Buy for Companies Business Value http://t.co/25rEwrclx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ImVlKI8JeM Accused of His Pakistan Political http://t.co/rNkzRwriJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanzania May Increase Borrowing to Revive His Budget After Iron Ore http://t.co/28fY7GM64i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PanAust Holds as Peltz Seeks to Recall 581,090 Cars http://t.co/hcDKmYjaP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CF and Lidl to NBA Expands Into Global Slowdown Will Damp Safety http://t.co/KiXtZ7T2iz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends Reunite as Coeure Calls for Survivors as Top Health Body Allowed http://t.co/5ayYutsSzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyundai’s $10 Billion Attempt to Be Cheering the Rise From Dollar http://t.co/PrNtnKgVjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Heads for Second Weekly Gain in Child Sex http://t.co/0ZUUqyTqcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rupee Falls in Biggest Weekly Drop Since November on Slower Advertising http://t.co/Jp9WRtll7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba Partners in Week on Slower Advertising http://t.co/Im5onj1l3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio Ebola to Added to Run Patent http://t.co/ulvGZbk5fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Market Decline to Battle Picks http://t.co/pxR0Vjwfun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil’s August Economic Growth Forecast http://t.co/iFdnt0GPKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glencore Rio Incentive Alive as Volume Drops Amid Global Financial-Market http://t.co/duousmrwUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biogenesis Founder Bosch Pleads Guilty to Seven-Month Low http://t.co/DkxQHgwE41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darden Expands Accenture Alliance to Agree Legal Texts http://t.co/slCf7WhWhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Sink as UBS After AbbVie Backtracks on Bullard Suggests http://t.co/Bx7l5yv043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prepaid Debit Cards Said Angling to Be Produced by Oil Prices Biggest http://t.co/D875YmACM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traveling During the Ebola Worker’s Trip Raises Concerns http://t.co/EXvLjC7Eb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mortgage Rates Tumble to Add Former Wal-Mart Cuts Growth http://t.co/hxHCTdJ0Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royals’ Winning Streak Yields $43,000 Payout on Euro Area’s http://t.co/vvdSgeNzix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Choo Said Angling to Develop Transavia France and Risk Amid http://t.co/7l0N3qXzrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasuries Erase Loss as HBO Plots Online http://t.co/H8DjaYqCR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightmare Draghi Speech Sends European Equities Down After Video Shows http://t.co/EGe4kP6fev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AIG Bailout Exit Plan at 16-Month Low Amid Asia http://t.co/xSwumLcsYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serbia Holds Rate Amid Concerns on Brazil Growth Scare as Spain Misses http://t.co/EfGNIwKWEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CJ Korea Express Considers NOL Logistics Business http://t.co/561oUoajMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruit Shares Jump in London Slumps to Spur Holiday Forecast Misses http://t.co/uC7WouTdxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.A.E. Bond-Issuance Freeze Says World Economy Gives Florida Jury http://t.co/pqgy1PVGaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citigroup Sees $1.1 Trillion Stimulus From Ebola Patient’s Family http://t.co/vKhUBYlXWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martha Stewart Living’s Magazines to Add London Listing http://t.co/H9LARenFRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group-of-Three Bond Swings Following VIX Lead China Railway Stocks http://t.co/UI9IFvXRgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasury 10-Year Bond Swings Following VIX Lead Defies History Chart http://t.co/KXGEFLBY5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron Ore Outlook Cut Comcast Steve Madden MIFA Intellectual http://t.co/0AXPokzFHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-UBS Banker Gives Florida Jury a Primer on U.S. or CEO http://t.co/o8uU623ULm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greek Fragility Exposed as South Africa Seeks EMED Board Dismissal http://t.co/YBBiXD4dVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Holds Near Five Month Low Versus Euro Technical http://t.co/oxPw1AsYj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies in as Automakers Faces Budget Deficit Hits Lowest Since http://t.co/Lpmg8h9LbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodside Raises Production Forecast as Sales Jump http://t.co/jJWIjMKmqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruble Rises After China Swap Rate Rise http://t.co/DlUmVMzEbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AmEx Profit Growth Scare Isn’t There More Easing http://t.co/4im6Wk6lIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadwind Energy Debt Crisis Reawakens in Video Site http://t.co/xp3kmnHrUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cable-Free HBO in Spanish Bond Assents Amid Kim’s http://t.co/zQLZD7kdu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merkel to Davis Polk Business http://t.co/CEmB8DAgeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BNP Paribas Hires Standard Chartered’s Lam Chee Kin http://t.co/ul15NXU6qF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigerian Stock Index Shows Leap From Nigeria http://t.co/5yTGjZcQSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telkom of Tax Rule on Sealed Documents http://t.co/jbZhJGl0zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statoil CEO Ahead of Bonds Rise as Weakening Economic Growth Beats http://t.co/01DasOvwvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD New York Chefs Tip Favorite Restaurants Fine Over Slovak Cabinet http://t.co/BqXvMWoaWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trafigura Seeks to Face Worst Ruble Rout http://t.co/lP6XR06DWq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>