<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/e8tIvmGFvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/Nt9Ddrybt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/qCU0amEJm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/AWxr97303T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/F4LZKEHAKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/byUNWaQpUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/laH0ndEV4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/QPa8SYpKKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/wiiToRWvuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/qgp1CCoIQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/4dsyczI2j0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/JNeaDEJYYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/hRzoz4NFkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/J5vuiCQ2EH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/tR9iTHZs0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/VBI7rxFrje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jammin Pet Hoodies for Your Little Furry Loved Ones :&gt;) http://t.co/1bUcTLco5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/U0UQmOGEpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/4Agr9AxXRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/5eXh1X2S8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/hdX7Teuj6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/lwQ1JYH8VU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/WvwaaSRcNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/ps76Sa3Eaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/Ccw4qOBryM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/y8c83Gkiku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/OESSnScLjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/PhvoJLMrTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/GSOsVaqKza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/YUir0lExvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/dEQ5DGw4M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/LqoMac46HB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/G6K70IYlv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/DJ1zLldJiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/m0G3qloxB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/iXI57LuEa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/iMKjZvsNaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/3GmBr0trui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/Ug17CvarPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/NLfKk3sUb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/W7TD5GIio3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/n5QVmO3MyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/KrLjGQySfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/fvHEndnMvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/H5JxjKb1Ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/UAg7N8YQ8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/GIiVvEuC9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affiliate marketing has made businesses millions and ordinary people millionaires. - Bo Bennett]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>