<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[l'm signing copies of SILENCE OF DOGS IN CARS @TLBGallery tomorrow at 11:30, Chelsea, London http://t.co/rDqA3DWe2s http://t.co/1XLoMtftRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Workshopxnews: A series about the universal fear of being alone and unheard - Dogs in Cars by @MartinUsborne : http://t.co/KM6Qbd9Ps ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: @MartinUsborne will be signing copies of #TheSilenceofDogsinCars tomorrow at 11.30 @TLBGallery! See you there! http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @b2sl2s: 'The Silence of Dogs in Cars' by @MartinUsborne is one of the greatest photographic series I've seen in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@b2sl2s too kind! thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's so bad about eating horse...or dog for that matter? Inflammatory blog post: http://t.co/hY16T2dZSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidvaaknin: The Silence of Dogs in Cars by  @MartinUsborne now open @TLBGallery in west London, check out the online gallery at 
h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loupepper what is?? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new website is up! Simpler, cleaner, come look: http://t.co/CHGktu9x0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to all that came to the opening  @TLBGallery Am signing books this saturday 11:30 - 12:30. See you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Great review of our @MartinUsborne – The Silence Of Dogs In Cars @TLBGallery @The_Upcoming http://t.co/LypozbZIIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lu_Flux @independent @tlbgallery sorry you couldn't come!! Great opening last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: See new 'In Conversation with Max Houghton' section on @TLBGallery website! Staring with @MartinUsborne @MaxFoto8  http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new solo show The Silence of Dogs in Cars, now open @TLBGallery in west London. Looks gorgeous, come on down http://t.co/LbFOmR6IWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ilovelondontown: Love dogs? And photography? @MartinUsborne's The Silence of Dogs in Cars at @TLBGallery is a forlorn yet beautiful  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @photofoundation: @MartinUsborne exhibition The Silence of Dogs in Cars opens today @TLBGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Our @MartinUsborne exhibition is on the wall! Opening tomorrow at 11am! #TheSIlenceofDogsinCars #photograph  #dogs http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: @whosjacklondon / we love them!  The Silence Of Dogs In Cars - http://t.co/GOaEiBEYNU @tlbgallery @martinusborne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: If only he could speak ... Burt by @MartinUsborne .. in the frame .. todays @Independent @TLBGallery opens next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upcoming show in the independent today http://t.co/u41H3jWngT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francescaaliceb thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @portmagazine: Photographer @MartinUsborne talks us thru his expo on silent dogs in silent cars @TLBGallery http://t.co/rE4kFhUKT9 ht ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaDaines thanks maria!! kind tweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MariaDaines: How many animals can 1 man save in 365 days http://t.co/sdD8skLDgw best blog on the planet! follow @MartinUsborne #dog  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: @CompletelyLDN on our @MartinUsborne exhibition opening next week! Why isn't it in your diaries already?! http://t.co/K6 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[building up to the Dogs in Cars show launch in London next week @TLBGallery  http://t.co/Kcs1fsNiP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pupaid: Look at these disgusting puppy farm conditions - please help @pupaid raise awareness RT http://t.co/clWAgXy4qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @visualcultclub: @MartinUsborne @Kehrer_Verlag great task. Hope U will condense it into a #project. Keep up the good work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francescaaliceb thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline thank you, don't dare watch yet but will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Art Preview: The Silence Of Dogs In Cars @martinusborne @TLBGallery @Londonist http://t.co/sC1VJ2Du9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photographing rescued hunting dogs in Spain #galgos http://t.co/aIU6xxTAcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@animal_drawings feeling that I might spend my life not having helped at all ...that wasn't nice. Thanks for following]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaDaines thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: @MartinUsborne in todays @TelegraphSeven The Silence of Dogs In Cars @TLBGallery from 19 March #dogs http://t.co/bEucmONpPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My photo in opening page of todays Sunday telegraph mag for upcoming show @TLBGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the article I got in daily mail online about the spanish dog rescue centre I worked with http://t.co/SpO1b5M7a4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I think I would get ANY sleep surrounded by 500 nervous rescue dogs #earplugsdontwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 212: I’M OFF TO RESCUE A BEAR WHILST WEARING MASCARA http://t.co/ErIntX3WS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How – I wonder – can I help a bear that is strong enough to rip my face off? http://t.co/GB0zohUFI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 210: I’VE OPENED UP A CAN OF BEARS: http://t.co/sv6W48TNPf http://t.co/Q8XNwm10Gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tamara_Beckwith: Dalmatian mania @martinusborne @thelittleblackgallery #dogs #cars #caughtmoments #mansbestfriend @ The… http://t.co/da…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[learn things i didn't know about illegal wildlife trade here: http://t.co/vfFt4VFXK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: After a great closing party last night we have only two days left of our @MartinUsborne #TheSilenceofDogsinCars! http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Attenborough on Pangolins. Video here: http://t.co/Eo4C7TjObp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos from my series on Joseph can now be seen at the hackney museum. more here: http://t.co/i13X0p6kAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 207: A SHOCKING READ ON FLIGHT TO JUNGLE GIVES ME MOTIVATION http://t.co/9yAgKT7rBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper please do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper yay!! Glad you like!! Thanks for supporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Last wk of doggies in cars @MartinUsborne. Plus we are donating 20% of all sales to great charity @DogsTrust. Must see! Mus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there are murmurings of a wildlife trade rescue I may be able help but information is scant. more here tomorrow: http://t.co/sXOBE2Ln1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegal trade in wildlife has now reached a scale that poses an immediate risk to wildlife and to people: http://t.co/rOYWedoI6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 205: HOW DANGEROUS IS IT TO RESCUE WILDLIFE IN INDIA? http://t.co/4gbPvlPqcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife SOS work extends to all wild creatures that suffer at the hands of man in India. http://t.co/QDZUNlhetj http://t.co/gABfQKhOXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kartick : A bear of a man.......http://t.co/QDZUNlhetj http://t.co/0RFnMomAaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahmbrogan that's great. Thanks so much!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 203: THOSE WHO RESCUE BEARS ARE VERY TIRED INDEED http://t.co/QDZUNlhetj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahmbrogan great to hear you enjoy the book!! woof woof from moose!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to help animals you got to stop the humans screwing up. But how can I? http://t.co/1uIIXjtIv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife only needs helping when it comes into contact with man. So what do we do? http://t.co/1uIIXjtIv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/YW30MQrxOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 200: BACK IN INDIA- BUT THIS TIME TO HELP WILDLIFE : http://t.co/1uIIXjtIv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...which is at @TLBGallery with 20% going to @DogsTrust from sales of my dog photos. Till 26th april]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dogstrust come down to my show and support a wonderful dog charity!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francescaaliceb @smbil thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Our v cute @DogsTrust box just arrived @TLBGallery as we are donating 20% of all sales from @MartinUsborne pix nxt wk ht ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does San Miguel's support of a restaurant illegally selling dog meat put you off? http://t.co/6QpVbYkNup @SMBIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Buongiorno! For the Italian speakers amongst you - http://t.co/Md1x3T9Yk4 @MartinUsborne #TheSilenceofDogsinCars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear San Miguel -do you know you seem to be sponsoring a dog meat restaurant? see here: http://t.co/6QpVbYkNup @SMBIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zoologist_Jess THANK YOU JESS, you are a wonderful thing too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zoologist_Jess: @MartinUsborne I just took a look at http://t.co/9RatxRL8hY ...and i think it's wonderful.  EVERYBODY LOOK AT THIS W ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated photo of mango- looking very happy!! She must know she is coming to the UK! http://t.co/r4fZcpPgPq http://t.co/Fwo8yTlwEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We did it!! Mango the puppy is coming to the UK !!! http://t.co/r4fZcpPgPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angelicasuzart thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper no way!! Too funny.. Say hi from me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDillingPhoto thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog post where I admit to still eating the occassional steak ..... http://t.co/WPZB9BkBOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Daily News on Dogs in Cars: http://t.co/EamVloYcmU @nydailynews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog Post : DAY 197: HALF YEAR REVIEW – part 2 http://t.co/WPZB9BkBOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper ah you ordered one!! Hope all is well with you??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rooms_Magazine: Animal lovers: The Silence of Dogs in Cars by @MartinUsborne
@therhiannon @TLBGallery
http://t.co/Cv71WylsQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 196: A (slightly late) HALF YEAR REVIEW (part 1) http://t.co/5gw23v2V0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper thanks for the support vicki!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NotesOnTheRoad: http://t.co/lUkAsRNcmZ the Silence of #dogs in #cars: #photographs by @MartinUsborne #pets #waiting http://t.co/J3Iv ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received a copy of the lovely @fourandsons journal in the post today. Thank you! Very happy to be included http://t.co/sbnqYplv35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My show is still on at The Little Black Gallery until 27 April. Don't forget to visit!! @TLBGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Great review of our @MartinUsborne exhibition by the @nydailynews! A fresh look - taking each photograph one by one! htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Last few weeks of The Silence of Dogs in Cars http://t.co/65kGbrkSPi @martinusborne @tlbgallery Woof woof!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trying to find the best way to fly mango to the uk. who knows best airlines to use? ps you can donate here: http://t.co/V0HNI2Mn3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog post where I save a fly. Again. Sort of... http://t.co/gQmn35rZL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great mention of Dogs in Cars show here: http://t.co/pnFygYAWrc @thecoolist @TLBGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: A Poignant Photo Series Captures The Silence Of Dogs In Cars @martinusborne @tlbgallery http://t.co/G0KsWkPGQ3 via @Fast ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who is cuter - me or mango? order prints here: http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ or donate here: http://t.co/19P0qI9u2o http://t.co/wAeetNCY8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MariaDaines: A song for Cordelia http://t.co/plAlPVknNQ now you sail the seas... @MartinUsborne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog post -DAY 194: BACK TO THE UK ONLY TO FLY OUT TO INDIA (again): http://t.co/gQmn35rZL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibertyLndnGirl puppy saved from being sold for meat - trying to get her to UK. RT please http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ http://t.co/W6Njpi4yyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thecoolist: Dogs in Cars by Martin Usborne: 
The relationship between humanity and companion species is a profound interes... http:/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets bring Mango back to the UK and give her a new home. Mangoes really are the sweetest! http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 249: I’M GETTING POLITICAL – WAS IT SOMETHING I ATE? http://t.co/E6stpINZec]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>