<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/dVKw8RW4cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/d8TBszqmLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/hrPFbp0Woj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Cicerone Beer?  http://t.co/xQxg9TiUJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/CtReTlwR3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/bC8Uqvhu0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/HDAHVfAzlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/HfMsaA7BM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/wHUuJC2kP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/rG8bPu2WSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/7rVH8If0hT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/Wf0mhJxczL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/yy76MAkTsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/QpQTYk4GM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/yRYntocHAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/DdJxFJIRMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/Vge4uMfCts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/WFhBRn7Vil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/SuZZ8OX1G1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/LMbu1nOj7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/YTtrHBsmsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/SotrRugWIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/Rr8F2Bk9Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/CgqON5LEYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/qn4nyIKuPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/ICRSRD2LPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/ZDNOPFMMTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Bz4z2jIwy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/NtKoGXpjhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/VcmTpi1gGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/NWwYJBLrLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/FelRYNLChM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/nb7f6Pd6eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/PNRhG6OyJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/Mr2lzimvK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/Q09ZfBdCPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/w8wMEpU0X2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/6PDMscuVwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/yCVwyhMoip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/qn4nyIKuPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/TTj4a1AOey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/pgNXzPelF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/Q09ZfBdCPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/z5IgFPQ3We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/zoJTQo2M9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>