<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nrusse  Thanks, Nate. Yes, very similar 2 my Dead Frog media strategy re Sleemans lit.  Good comments from … (cont) http://deck.ly/~i8m9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miss604 There's nothing like walking thru YVR from an intl flight. Even at 1 a.m. it's splendid and makes me proud. @news1130radio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice! FB vs Twitter stats RT @bibliotheeka: @lawyerPR thanks! now here's a cool one for you http://is.gd/dsjMLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites  Phew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Yeah, and there's certainly enough of THAT going on in the world. Whoops, was that my outside voice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Great idea, that'll be quick, easy & painless. Better to wait for TweetDeck to install coin slot… (cont) http://deck.ly/~ryBYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyMyrland Hey Nancy! See you in a few weeks, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Ohhhh sure there is! Shall we pass the hat around? U know, collect some coins for Kev's BC Ferry trip and maybe a little lunch $?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites  No way!  MOST of my Canuck pals I get to see often ... only those .... or 1 in particular , based in Victoria, is elusive ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@betsiroach :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing my American LMA pals ... it's times like this the world feels too large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you'll go."… (cont) http://deck.ly/~MFvbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraCain Customization is  sweet! ... provided there's training, of course :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bibliotheeka  Sure do!  Here is the video "Is social media a fad?": http://youtu.be/lFZ0z5Fm-Ng  Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasmineDecarie: Foot in mouth..swallow RT @newsaboutwomen: David Cameron: appoint more women directors to reduce executive pay  http ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Looks like that dog is ready to take flight!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea: Get a few top non-partisan headhunters from diff geog mkt to assess candidate  qualifctns + provide recmdtion. #Pittmeadows #ElectPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute! Why don't we see resumes + interview candidates for Mayor, just as we would 4 any other exec position?  #electpm #Pittmeadows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to YOU! RT @terrybecker: Happy #FF  @Matt_Brennancom @thriveorg @lawyerpr @thesocialchicks (all 3 of you!… (cont) http://t.co/ud1038mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites This is Friday. Get back to work. #fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wooo Hoooo! TEXAS, baby! RT @Bettina_R: Welcome Texas! RT @JeremyHoders: Big News --&gt; LMA announces Texas chapter.  #lmamkt #lmamini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UpThePitt: Happy about equal access to British throne for women, but man - it's not exactly the equality rights story of the year, i ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gordmac980: VGH says 1 patient died from yesterday's plane crash in Richmond.   2 critical cond.  4 stable conditon.  2 dischrgd.  #CKNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey PR & Mktg folks: need a good photog in the Fraser Valley (will wk in Van also)? Go to @Matt_Brennancom.  http://t.co/PlClBOD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #FF goes out to these engaging professionals:  @douglasbing  @MyMapleRidge @Matt_Brennancom  @thriveorg @time2simplify @rocketmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx Vicki! RT @vicki_mcleod: The Vicki McLeod Daily is out! http://t.co/mq9NxBpO ▸ Top stories today via @lawye… (cont) http://t.co/QwLysoje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you people ever SLEEP? RT @terrybecker: Full table of candidates at #mapleridge meeting for #electmr. Just getting underway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hitting a fly w/a sledgehammer: RT @HoboLittlest: Hobo wander onto Mayor  Ford's lawn; he say Hobo scare cat. Then he call Governor General.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Today story: @ejohnbecker "to accelerate waste mngt 4 families" if elected. http://t.co/Rk94lpXM #electpm #Pittmeadows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Hr has 22 Minutes has last laugh as Rob Ford claims he was "attacked" by show host/Princess Warrior Mar… (cont) http://t.co/3QqZwSRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another reason for e-books! RT @cbcnewsbc: Bedbugs found in Vancouver library book:  af... http://t.co/hXcravRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@douglasbing "electioneering"? I love it! #pittmeadows #electpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick! What are the 3 most imp attributes that qualify a person to effectively serve as #Pittmeadows Mayor? #electpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MapleRidgeNews: #pittmeadows MacLean back Becker for mayor: ‘I think the city should be run like a business’ http://t.co/hgiXsa5A #m ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Becker for Pitt Meadows Mayor launch event -- join us this Thurs. @ 7 p.m. South Bonson Comm. Ctr! http://t.co/pee5RTyZ  #pittmeadows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@time2simplify Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rocketmatter Belated thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinmcconnell Beautiful pics. So happy for you! Is Willis Best Dog at the wedding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sade concert last night in Vanc was amazing -- beautiful voice and visuals. Wished it would never end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: Sesame Street says Bert and Ernie aren't gay, tho I find it suspicious that the last episode was brought to you by th ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pierblue95 Yeah, yellow.. . that'll blend into the natural landscape beautifully :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing 3-D printing -- a concept right out of a Star Trek movie, but real: http://www.wimp.com/functionaltools/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O.M.G. RT @matwilcox: This must be a typo. RT @jsteffenhagen: RT @seanlesliebc: Review finds BC Hydro has 14… (cont) http://deck.ly/~wWCXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dialoguedivaray: CFO Mag: Beyond Mentoring. Women are 56% of graduates & 36% of all MBAs, but fill just 9% of CFO roles http://lnkd. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understand yur clients' knowledge first RT @sallyschmidt: RT @ronfriedmann: Above the Law-Bringing A Client Up To Speed http://bit.ly/nrVcSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chengsophia: Anyone interested? "looking for freelance camera operators with their own equipment to shoot Tuesday of next week... an ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 tips for media interviews: http://www.slaw.ca/2011/06/29/lawyers-and-the-media/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My most lofty thought while recently camping: why are tarps BLUE, not green?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most generous! RT @rebeccawcheung: movers and shakers! #FF @crystalreinitz @lawyerPR @sarahcandice @oveyyeun… (cont) http://deck.ly/~FRqqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdoch's "We are sorry" ad published way too late and now today, WSJ publisher resigns. Read the eerie ad:  http://bit.ly/qmo5W7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great info + photos! Tx!  RT @Miss604: New Post: Langley Circle Farm Tour http://ow.ly/5FBkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a pasta strainer was accepted as headgear for an Austrian drivers licence photo - love the expression! http://bbc.in/qvduLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shinng @netflix needs to reign in this story NOW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant, Hugh! RT @SusanEJacobsen: Love this &gt; Hugh Grant hacks the hackers & skewers News of the World Editor | @TIME http://ti.me/po47qA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clebc sent the best follow-up letter today acknowledging my contribution +  some feedback on speaking at Lawyers and the Media conf. Bravo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try to push through on a sunny Friday afternoon. Don't look out the window, don't look out the window ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... he had a magazine article in his file that quoted me  ... it was dated 2001. OK, now that's loooooong term residual benefits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya know, there's a stat somewhere stating .0001% of ppl w/computers don't google professionals BF hiring them? He called me....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ElevenPR: Cool & scary. Check out pic of pre-riot crowd in Van. zoom to see every face in hi-res. 9,500… (cont) http://deck.ly/~b1S8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ejohnbecker in running for Pitt Meadows Mayor! http://bit.ly/nBCW7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day, but looking forward to meeting a client on a sunny patio for lunch today. Ahhh... sunny Vancouver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colincameron: Join the discussion on trends in partner compensation systems http://linkd.in/jlHTvW ll Law Firm Profitability group o ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[72 is elderly? RT @cbcnewsbc: Elderly Okanagan man charged 4 fatal crash: A 72-year-old B.C. man is facing charges ... http://bit.ly/m06Wlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unmarketing Right after she mailed you a letter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That explains a couple of odd DMs from U RT @John_L_Daly: Clean up the debris caused by hacker . . Trying to get help from Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites BABIES, I tell ya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too weird... I used to babysit one of the outgoing Van Board of Trade members AND an incoming one. Either they are young, or I am ...#in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too weird... I used to babysit one of the outgoing Van Board of Trade members AND an incoming one. Either they are young, or I am ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WendyHartley: Grouse Mountain new web site with cool Grouse Grind stats page http://t.co/nqlaKVI via @jince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: B.C. teachers threaten job action in Sept.: The president of the B.C. Teachers Federation says if contract negot... http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice piece, Nicole! RT @NGartonJones: Story about Heritage Law in the Vancouver Sun today http://tinyurl.com/65fj9lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The internet does not have a delete button"- Carmi Levy via Van Sun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like chasing a train + waving our arms in the air. Yup, done that. RT @CherylBame: A Day Late and A Dollar Short http://lnkd.in/akuXJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you see this Family Lawyer posting? *Existing practice*, nice firm, lifestyle.Act fast! http://www.beckerlawyers.ca/wp/about-us/join-us/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool your pup w/puppy popsicle: make layer of ice , add dog treats w/inch of water, freeze + repeat. Serve frozen on grass on hot day  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diana at @CampaignMonitor so responsive! Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Becker lawyer GFraser - RT @WeedPlaces_NM: Man awarded $30K 4 medical marijuana costs: Van Sun Michael Joinson says... http://bit.ly/ihzLtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Becker lawyer GFraser case RT @molinelobo: RT @MedicinalTHC: Med420 News  Man awarded $30K 4 medical pot - Vancouver Sun http://t.co/QGk5zGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to G.Fraser + @EJohnBecker for signif. win in BC Supreme Crt re medicinal pot award. See Van Sun story: http://bit.ly/jaVPO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh- oh, someone has some 'splaning to do RT @John_L_Daly:Chief to vpd: I confirmed yesterday that Mr. Whitelaw did not write the 1994 report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to Mark, you + team! RT @MeganHamilton_: CBA - Work Life Balance Forum Awards today: http://bit.ly/kB… (cont) http://deck.ly/~0JBsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx Ian! RT @ianmulgrew: BC Supreme Court awards $30,000 for medical marijuana to victim in a personal injur… (cont) http://deck.ly/~yPYjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SgtJennPound: IHIT called in 4 what appears 2 be homicide in Maple Ridge I'm enroute + will have more info after briefing. #PittMeadows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinaschenbren: Really great tip on #contentmarketing by #JPR's @laltman #LawFirm #Marketing  http://t.co/H6bmCfm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for all litigators: how do you select a mediator? What are the top 2 things you look for? How imp is name-recognition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLE sale! Cool! RT @CLEBC: We're having a Seat Sale! Up to 50% off selected courses. http://t.co/SMwpFXzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancityCrimLaw: @simisara980 I was Duty Counsel in Rmd yesterday. I heard TWO judges express their disgust with the chronic underfun ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember Washington Gaylord conf? GRT @heather_morse: Attending #lma12 ? Better wear your flats. Place is huge. #LMAMKT http://t.co/RGhdhxtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sweet, so lovely RT @matwilcox: What a wonderful world.  A little calm in your day....http://youtu.be/auSo1MyWf8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["House of horrors?" + hate 2 think what the gift shop sells RT @News1130radio: VPD opens new state of the art facility http://t.co/VVW6mDUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law firm merger in works? Bring your senior mktg people in early (pre-merger) to ensure u max PR opps + have seamless transition .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bettina_R: Check out the library of practical, informative articles written for Mass Lawyers Weekly by our very own LMA NE...: http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have relevant credentials, experience or knowledge to your area of law? Shout it out in website bio, twitter + LinkedIn profile etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.RT @erindermer: Has anyone succeeded in getting an app pulled based on copyright infringement? Advice appreciated. #BCLegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @erindermer: Has anyone succeeded in getting an app pulled based on copyright infringement? Advice appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock up on coffee RT @nortonrose_ca: Norton Rose Canada acting for Semtech in its plan to acquire Gennum for $500M http://t.co/MQeQ86P5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reference RT @Hannasus: Useful note on terminology (Inuit, Métis, 1st Nations, & Aboriginal) given current events: http://t.co/VdQrEoV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasmineDecarie: Hey, Marketing people, if you are doing a presentation & have a Twitter account, post your handle on your materials!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just blew dust off followers list. Reaction was delight ("OH look who's following NOW!") + shock ("EWWwww.. where's that block option?")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a writer /reporter contacts u 4 a comment, take a moment + consider how u can help.  U have a lot u can say w/o going offside.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>