<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Pt2 "...You're less anxious about loosing other's love when you've found your own." - John Amodeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pt1 "You can take more risks to be yourself as you feel stronger within yourself...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for different, sometimes longer, more indepth quotes, follow me on FB http://www.facebook.com/LoveQuotations this week's theme: self-love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...self-love is the basis of all love." - Thomas Traherne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you please others in hopes of being accepted, you lose your self-worth in the process." - Dave Pelzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone is a mirror image of yourself—your own thinking coming back to you." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The willingness to accept responsibility for one's own life is the source from which self-respect springs." - Joan Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I prefer the word “homemaker” because “housewife” always implies that there may be a wife someplace else." - Bella Abzug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kindness in giving creates love." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember there's no such thing as a small act of kindness. Every act creates a ripple with no logical end." - Scott Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be generous with kindly words, especially about those who are absent." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Write injuries in sand, kindnesses in marble" - French Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forget injuries, never forget kindnesses" - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "It is only possible to live happily-ever-after on a day-to-day basis." ~Margaret Bonnano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Compassion and love are qualities that are of tremendous importance for the individual, society, and the community at large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love & kindness R never wasted. They always make a difference. They bless the 1 who receives them, & they bless U the giver." B de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The three ingredients of a successful union between two . . . humor, commitment & undying love." - Bill Cosby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Resentment is 1 burden that is incompatible w ur success. Always b the 1st to forgive; & forgive yourself 1st always" - Dan Zadra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Living from your heart means living less defensively." - John Amodeo, Ph.D. - The Authentic Heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love thee, with the breath, Smiles, tears, of all my life!" - Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Come live with & be my love & we will some new pleasures prove, of golden sands & crystal brooks w silken lines & silver hook" - John Donne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HisHoliness: Learning to forgive is much more useful than merely picking up a stone and throwing it at the object of one's anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How much u love yourself & how u feel about urself r directly proportionate to the quality & integrity of ur word" Don Miguel Ruiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: This is how I would die into the love I have for you. As pieces of cloud dissolve into the sunlight. Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What cannot be achieved in one lifetime will happen when one lifetime is joined to another." - Harold Kushner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gentleness is the antidote for cruelty." - Phaedrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Women marry men hoping they will change. Men marry women hoping they will not. So each is inevitably disappointed." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that is the stuff life is made of." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Come out of the circle of time and into the circle of love." - Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Loving is never a waste of time." - Astrid Alauda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't measure love with time, only with timeless moments." - Jeremiah Feinburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the emblem of eternity; it confounds all notion of time: effaces all memory of a beginning, all fear of an end" Madame de Stael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gravitation can not be held responsible for people falling in love." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When u r sorrowful look again in ur heart & u shall see that in truth u r weeping for that which has been ur delight" Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whoever is careless with the truth in small matters cannot be trusted with important matters." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love takes off masks that we fear we cannot live without and know we cannot live within." - James Arthur Baldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whenever you have truth it must be given with love, or the message & the messenger will be rejected" - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Truth never damages a cause that is just." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the answer, but while you're waiting for the answer, sex raises some pretty good questions." - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pt2:  "...and help strengthen the universal bond all people have." - Sara Paddison, Hidden Power of the Heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pt1: "Appreciating each other is a true family value, one that will bail out much of the stress on the planet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF RT @DalaiLama: A mind committed to compassion is like an overflowing reservoir - a constant source of energy, determination and kindness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF RT @ByronKatie: The teacher you need is the person you're living with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF RT @mikedooley: We are timeless and so are our connections with one another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Flattery is from the teeth out. Sincere appreciation is from the heart out." - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As we express our gratitude, we must never forget that the highest appreciation is not to utter words, but to live by them." - JFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be verbal in acknowledging your appreciation." - Catherine Pulsifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Appreciation is a wonderful thing: It makes what is excellent in others belong to us as well." - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Don't cry for a man who's left you, the next one may fall for your smile.” ~ Mae West]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to find your perfect match is to meet love halfway." ~ Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But to see her was to love her, Love but her, and love her for ever." ~ Robert Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why It Is Wise to Worship a Woman: http://huff.to/c1QJsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["make a practice, a discipline, of telling ur woman, or any woman, 10 times a day something which u adore about her" ~ Arjuna Ardagh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody has ever measured, even poets, how much a heart can hold." ~ Zelda Fitzgerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sing like no 1's listening, love like u've never been hurt, dance like nobody's watching, & live like its heaven on earth" ~Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In every possible way we conspire to know freedom and love." ~ Hafiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is devoid of the power to forgive, is devoid of the power to love." - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True forgiveness is not an action after the fact, it is an attitude with which you enter each moment." - David Ridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: If you have strong compassion, strong respect for others, then forgiveness is much easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HisHoliness: What irritates us in the first place is that our wishes are not fulfilled. But remaining upset does nothing to help ful ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikedooley: Beyond what’s “necessary,” shed all behavioral expectations you may have for your partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EckhartTolle: ...denial, reactions, judgements, labels are the many forms of mental and emotional resistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To forgive is to set a prisoner free and discover that the prisoner was you." - Lewis B. Smedes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To forgive is the highest, most beautiful form of love. In return, you will receive untold peace and happiness." - Robert Muller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no love without forgiveness, and there is no forgiveness without love." - Bryant H. McGill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Like a blooming night flower, Bestow your vital fragrance of happiness, And giving, Upon our intimate assembly." - Hafiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life without love is like a tree without blossoms or fruit." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can complain because rose bushes have thorns, or rejoice because thorn bushes have roses." - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I had a single flower for every time I think about you, I could walk forever in my garden." - Claudia Ghandi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video of "all your failed relationships compressed into a 3-minute conversation" made me laugh out loud: http://bit.ly/dvUuNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not whether ur words or actions r tough or gentle; it is the spirit behind ur actions & words that announces ur inner state -Rene Char]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LoveQ turns 2 years old today! I am so grateful to each of you for following, re-tweeting, & sharing the love. I♥YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Clothe yourselves with compassion, kindness, humility, gentleness and patience." – The Apostle Paul (Col 3:12)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "Be gentle first with yourself if you wish to be gentle with others." ~Lama Yeshe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: I believe that, fundamentally, human nature is positive, gentle; therefore, the non-violent way is the human way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Men and women should stay apart, till their hearts grow gentle towards one another again." - David Herbert Lawrence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gratitude is not only the greatest of virtues, but the parent of all others." ~ Cicero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forgiveness is not about forgetting. It is about letting go of another person's throat." ~ William P. Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not easy to find love in ourselves, and impossible to find it elsewhere." ~ Agnes Repplier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Please don't go and build a fence around your heart, like you've done before, when you're losing grace." ~ Man Man, Banana Ghost lyrics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The test of a vocation is the love of the drudgery it involves." ~ Logan P. Smith [have a happy labor day!]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust is the fruit of a relationship in which you know you are loved." ~ William P. Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OSHOtimes All that is beautiful grows in the heart; all that is valuable comes out of the heart-your love, compassion, meditation #ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaryJaneRyan "took the risk yesterday to reach out to an old love and apologize for my behavior 25 years ago. Feels great!" #ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikedooley "It’s never too late to find euphoric happiness or to become wildly fulfilled." #ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha "Appreciation is an excellent thing. It makes what is excellent in others belong to us, as well." ~Voltaire #ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is triumph of imagination over intelligence." ~ H.L. Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Open up to the Roof. Make a new water-mark on your excitement, And love." ~ Hafiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friends need not agree in everything or go always together, or have no comparable other friendships of the same intimacy" ~George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was nauseous and tingly all over. I was either in love or I had smallpox." ~ Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go to the truth beyond the mind. Love is the bridge." ~ Stephen Levine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The love of life is not something rational, or founded on experience of life. It's something antecedent & spontaneous." ~ George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ultimate test of a relationship is to disagree, but still hold hands." - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the only game that is not called on account of darkness." ~ Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is not impatient is not in love." ~ Italian Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is but the discovery of ourselves in others, and the delight in the recognition." ~ Alexander Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Upon waking each day, My first words to my heart always are, 'Tell me all your news of Love.'" ~ Hafiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those whose suffering is due to love are, as we say of certain invalids, their own physicians" ~ Marcel Proust]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>