<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer – Imaging – £50k: C++ Software Developer / C++ Developer / C++ Programmer / Software Engineer / Windows / Linux / Applications Developer / Software Design Engineer / Newcastle / Gateshead / Tyne and Wear / Durham / Sunderland /… https://t.co/ZDBxd5a5dP https://t.co/ZDgGWzK37z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mnuchin speaks with US bank executives to reassure investors after Wall Street whiplash: In a precautionary move, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin spent Sunday on the phone speaking with the chief executives of some of the country's largest banks to… https://t.co/YOPJVijsOa https://t.co/GNYvxjPSxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Cloud Engineering: FINTEC recruit is seeking a Head of Cloud Engineering (Saas Software) for an international business. This position is based in Glasgow, with salary £90,000 to £100,000. You will require to have experience of managing SaaS… https://t.co/PopnnmS8IZ https://t.co/E4s1xxgYWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Chance of Extension – Glasgow: NET Developer – Chance of Extension – Glasgow .NET Developer required for our client in Glasgow. I am currently helping my client source an experienced .NET developer for a contract position in Glasgow. You… https://t.co/ylMYBwOkzv https://t.co/pt0c6uKmuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Nissan chief to spend Christmas in jail: Former Nissan chief Carlos Ghosn, detained for the past five weeks on charges he underreported his income, will spend Christmas and New Year's Eve in a Tokyo jail cell https://t.co/iHtfcA5GXE https://t.co/79aPPdE66P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Spring Boot Developer: Java Developer Software Consultancy London £35,000 – £100,000 (Dependent on experience) Java, Spring, Hibernate, Spring Boot, Microservices, JavaScript, AWS, Cloud, DevOps One of Europe’s largest tech firms is searching for an… https://t.co/lorIqF12sw https://t.co/g1scNCDZGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Infrastructure Analyst: As our IT Technical Infrastructure Analyst you'll troubleshooting and resolving issues with Unix servers, Oracle/SQL Server databases and performing software installation and upgrades – no two weeks will ever be the… https://t.co/KfF421RiS7 https://t.co/9INRYn1l91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corker on shutdown: Trump trying to 'look like he's fighting': Tennessee GOP Sen. Bob Corker said on Sunday that President Donald Trump pushed the government into partial shutdown as an act of political posturing. https://t.co/ykEXTB6TOy https://t.co/0leTfpi0Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: A Data Architect is required to join a UK financial services organisation in Bristol to take on some business analysis duties on a long term contract. The will create a more sophisticated approach to how it manages it data and how it… https://t.co/EuaVRAgnBf https://t.co/c1PneXOEsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst Front Office Banking: **Position Description** **Join Us!** Fiserv has been named to FORTUNE magazine’s 2017 list of World’s Most Admired Companies. This is the second consecutive year the company has been named to the list,… https://t.co/fRABPglVSs https://t.co/KY76sZyWtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Juul made vaping viral to become worth a dirty $38 billion: A Juul is not a cigarette. It’s much easier than that. Through devilishly slick product design I’ll discuss here, the startup has massively lowered the barrier to getting hooked on nicotine.… https://t.co/mWJEMvBJ4C https://t.co/lHZG12grGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA Engineer: – Sr. QA Engineer Job Locations US-CA-Sunnyvale Req No. 2018-4789 Category Engineering Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience, Cloud Networking, and Cloud Edge solutions, Riverbed – The Digital Performance… https://t.co/gwkO6y6lFx https://t.co/OedJW3u6zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 arrested over Gatwick airport drone chaos released: Two people arrested over the widespread disruption of flights at London's Gatwick Airport through the illegal use of drones have been released without charge on Sunday. https://t.co/LuLjc8cfHW https://t.co/timnzvD6Dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst Front Office Banking: Position Description Join Us! Fiserv has been named to FORTUNE magazine’s 2017 list of World’s Most Admired Companies. This is the second consecutive year the company has been named to the list, which is a… https://t.co/Bv1Y2fR7yB https://t.co/rIzzo9IkZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Development/Engineering: Head of Development/Engineering** Location: Manchester Salary: Up to £95,000 This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced Head of Development/Software Manager to join a rapidly expanding and ambitious organisation,… https://t.co/JID2UzIJbp https://t.co/TCYy6u1SBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Analyst – Night Shift: As part of the Security and Network Operations Command Center staff you will be instrumental in supporting customers as part of our managed services and support offerings. All staff will be placed in our on the job… https://t.co/jBLoDTCtrF https://t.co/zqBLb42CHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Magento / PHP / Symfony: Senior Web Developer (Magento &amp; JavaScript) Up to £40K Diss, Suffolk Our partners are highly accredited and one of the largest veterinary service providers in the UK looking for a Senior Web Developer to join… https://t.co/yDJcDfqJ7W https://t.co/rJuiqphK5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In pictures: Latest tsunami hits Indonesia beaches: A tsunami that hit Pandeglang, Serang and South Lampung, Indonesia, Saturday night, killed at least 168 people and injured at least 745, Sutopo Purwo Nugroho, head of public relations at Indonesia's… https://t.co/rpUuPUWthj https://t.co/pD9lrTIDPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Manager – Software Development: A leading provider of Software solutions who are development applications that affect thousands of patient lives every year are urgently looking for an experienced Test Manager to join the team on a Permanent basis.… https://t.co/jGKbe7d7M6 https://t.co/CXafPSEpTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Our growing national client based in Bourne is seeking an experience Web Developer to join them on a permanent basis. You will be responsible for producing high quality, clean code and it is essential that you are experienced in… https://t.co/Zdgq3H8MFY https://t.co/2zto4cIO4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smerconish: Trump's biggest threat isn't Mueller: CNN's Michael Smerconish discusses what he says are the biggest threats to President Trump: the market, Robert Mueller, the military, and the media. https://t.co/n6u51fbE0M https://t.co/AjtxVm35b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (24919): Req Id 24919 – Posted 10/18/2018 – Herndon, VA – TS/SCI Are you passionate about solving challenging problems? Do you thrive being a critical part of an elite team of like-minded people? How would you like for your next career… https://t.co/og2NvfxxOM https://t.co/Hol3hK5LI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Tutor / Trainer – Intrastructure: Intrastructure Technician Level 3 Assessor Trainer – Manchester (Regional Role) – £40,000 – £45,000 depending upon experience / Pension, all travel expenses. The Role: Intrastructure Technician Level 3 Assessor… https://t.co/OzbiF4bACv https://t.co/8igLLIBsaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: San Diego, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted 12/20/2018 If you are a Full Stack Developer with 3+ years of experience have demonstrable UI skills, please apply today! Based out of San Diego, the textbook example of beautiful… https://t.co/tscwmHajFy https://t.co/boARWh4aFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsunami kills 43 in Indonesia. More than 500 others are injured: A tsunami hit Pandeglang, Serang and South Lampung, Indonesia, early Sunday, killing 20 people and injuring 165, according to a tweet from Sutopo Purwo Nugroho, head of public relations at… https://t.co/SUjBonNTWk https://t.co/6eYyPZb2pN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Role: Infrastructure Engineer Location: Cambridge Type: Immediate start 12 month FTC Salary: Up to £55,000 Are you an experienced Infrastructure Engineer, VMware Ninja or Virtual2Virual Server Migration specialist? Want an… https://t.co/YAPtYRhXJs https://t.co/BiuYYo3EkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/OBXoD9FXy1’s billionaire founder Richard Liu won’t be charged in sexual misconduct case: Roughly four months after https://t.co/OBXoD9FXy1’s billionaire CEO Richard Liu was arrested and later released by Minneapolis police on suspicion of… https://t.co/6h2ykSWXJu https://t.co/8SrzBDtXe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENG-LON-AP-27: Junior Software Engineer – 14 weeks free training – London – Immediate – £23k – £26k + employee perks Sparta Global is looking for graduates who want to launch their careers in tech as full stack engineers with the ability to write and… https://t.co/pI1hoTXcYW https://t.co/DpkrNempHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend developer: Urgent Requirement- React.js Developer // 3 Month + Contract // London My market leading client, based in London is currently looking for a React.js Developer for an initial 3 month contract. The successful candidate will be working… https://t.co/hMFR09EEiF https://t.co/NbQY3PkoAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ron Paul: Withdrawing US troops from Syria is 'fantastic': Former presidential candidate and congressman Ron Paul supports President Donald Trump's widely criticized decision to pull more than 2,000 US troops from Syria, calling his announcement… https://t.co/qVY9GfNuBl https://t.co/1EIaow4Ojq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP System Developer – Leeds – £35,000 + 10% Bonus: PHP System Developer – Leeds – £35,000 + 10% Bonus Based in the centre of Leeds, this is an in-house role for an industry leading company looking to implement a complete rebuild and upgrade of their… https://t.co/KxA8kUtQ5e https://t.co/pe1yI4CaiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Analyst: DESCRIPTION In our team, user experience insight analysts work collaboratively with project owners to understand &amp; record their goals and analysis requirements, then with developers to turn these requirements into technical measurement… https://t.co/zPspAfUuDh https://t.co/BqtNI4BZ0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineering Specialist: Overview Every day at Employer, we enable hundreds of thousands of people to take on our nations most important work. Were a company founded on a diverse set of capabilities and skills, bound together by a single… https://t.co/VQbVNOgGAU https://t.co/wgs1hmyiGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi crown prince 'ordered' killing of Khashoggi, Corker says: Lawmakers briefed Tuesday by CIA Director Gina Haspel accused Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman of being responsible for the killing of Washington Post journalist Jamal Khashoggi. https://t.co/DzdrcoAhdU https://t.co/PFThl7WRPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Manager: We are looking for a new Software Development Manager to join a SaaS company based is Uxbridge and bring their off shore team of C# .NET Developers to the UK. This has been a strategic decision to help innovate the product… https://t.co/lyoalV7OE6 https://t.co/QmERGIhQUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics Finance – Product Manager – London, Greater Londo: Role You be a senior member of a large team, with responsibility for developing the Dynamics Product, at a leading Partner firm. As well as developing the Product Solution you will… https://t.co/7H6CwkzUZo https://t.co/etYAWNtBCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Linux Systems Administrator, Manchester, £26,000, Urgent: Junior Linux Systems Administrator, Manchester, £26,000, Urgent I am currently looking for a Junior Linux Systems administrator for a Manchester based company. My client is experiencing… https://t.co/IgTAQjC02i https://t.co/PAXzG4pC39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet 2018's highest-paid YouTuber: Seven-year-old Ryan, the host of the Ryan ToysReview YouTube channel, has earned more than $22 million this year and was named Forbes' highest-paid YouTube star. https://t.co/Jn1XdRsHvp https://t.co/0GO4XvdTFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA – 12 months, outside IR35: Department of Business Energy and Industrial Strategy SQL Database Admin Specialist Deadline for asking questions Tuesday 4 December 2018 at 11:59pm GMT Closing date for applications Friday 7 December 2018 at 11:59pm… https://t.co/XxqgnucAfB https://t.co/2w8exUTgBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Cyber – iOS Applications: 12-Apr-2018 Software Engineer, Cyber – iOS Applications Space Virginia 429772BR • Software development, writing in Python, C, C++ • Demonstrated in-depth experience with iOS cyber development, writing… https://t.co/SkMlKkjSrH https://t.co/f1bbhErjVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer – C#, .Net Core, Agile: Senior .Net Developer – C#, .Net Core, Agile Location: Liverpool Salary: to £50k plus benefits Keywords: Senior .Net Developer, Lead Developer, Software Developer, C# Developer, .Net, Web API, Senior .Net… https://t.co/YUyzGfHjxz https://t.co/29A5VYfkVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VOIP Support Engineer – SIP, TCP, Wireshark, Telephony, Hosted: VOIP Support Engineer – SIP, TCP, Wireshark, Telephony, Hosted We are expanding our support team and invite applications from highly capable, adaptable and knowledgeable VoIP Support… https://t.co/aAtvQP0jdz https://t.co/DYYRcC1su3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Senior Technical Specialist: Overview Every day at Employer, we enable hundreds of thousands of people to take on our nations most important work. Were a company founded on a diverse set of capabilities and skills, bound together by a… https://t.co/pfXBihCo7k https://t.co/29cf6bGJtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Murphy becomes a father for the 10th time: Eddie Murphy is a new dad again. https://t.co/Z1Eyeznuz8 https://t.co/fVwmZBP8CN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Data Engineer London Engineering Remote About Kraken Kraken is one of the largest and most successful bitcoin exchanges in the world and we’re growing faster than ever. We’re looking for people who constantly push themselves to think… https://t.co/9l7Sjt6gWu https://t.co/qc7nTULxT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead SAP Infrastructure Architect: NO SPONSORSHIP Lead SAP Infrastructure Architect Looking for a LEAD IT ARCHITECT with experience in SAP, Database and Middleware technology. You will work at the Corporate Technology Operations Center to evaluate,… https://t.co/pSpERrGm3w https://t.co/SrkaiaTRpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba replaces video streaming boss amid anti-corruption probe: A top-level reshuffle is sending shockwaves across one of China’s biggest online video businesses. Yang Weidong has stepped down as the president of Alibaba’s video streaming unit Youku,… https://t.co/vFmUzu6Re6 https://t.co/fdjPgJlLTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIELD ENGINEER: My Client based near Sandbach is looking for a Field Engineer to diagnose and rectify server/desktop problems. This Field Engineer would cover the local area and may require some travel up to 1 hour of the Sandbach area. The purpose of… https://t.co/7Fw5fToQIY https://t.co/mVVOOv3wyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Developer – Java Angular: Job Description Summary Are you interested in creating world class client experiences while working in a contemporary, truly-agile manner? Join the next CX Retail Lab focused on the Open an Account journey. As… https://t.co/RI8TfuAAQd https://t.co/trlf1Sh8qY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Applications Developer: SENIOR WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER This is a fantastic opportunity to join the largest privately-owned HR and Payroll provider in the UK. With offices in Nottingham, Dublin, Washington and Singapore, MHR has been… https://t.co/0bi3FHwtaR https://t.co/0zLboLjzQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain can unilaterally stop Brexit process, EU lawyers say: The British government has the power to unilaterally halt the Brexit process, the EU's top legal advisers have said. https://t.co/lPByCUCe9y https://t.co/BH0KHipl5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: About Us Employer is the data authority for hybrid cloud. We provide a full range of hybrid cloud data services that simplify management of applications and data across cloud and on-premises environments to accelerate digital… https://t.co/X7bRUeKX4p https://t.co/OWbFMS5D24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 JavaScript Developers: The Company Our client are a growing technology business within the healthcare and pharmaceutical sector with idyllic rural offices just north of Cambridge. They deliver market-leading software to clients in over 100 countries… https://t.co/NnAfgWH9LJ https://t.co/og2MBb7L69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Electrical Engr: 122325BR Job Description: Located between the mountains and the ocean in sunny Santa Barbara, CA, Raytheon Vision Systems is the industry leader in Visible and Infra-Red sensor circuits with the largest array formats, smallest… https://t.co/1Vgx7bP5iE https://t.co/rSuhKBCOxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Futures + Options Application Support Manager – SVP: Global Futures + Options Application Support Manager A leading Investment Bank has an urgent requirement for someone to Head up it's Front Office Global F&amp;O Application Support team. The… https://t.co/xfRBgg9MFV https://t.co/vbMPmBsvnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Delivery Manager: Service Delivery Manager with DCC Smart Metering in Ruddington: We are actively seeking a highly skilled, experienced and motivated Service Delivery Manager for the opportunity to join one of the most talented and dynamic teams… https://t.co/3ns1WfxnMq https://t.co/YTOYVqgzJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Our customers are at the heart of everything we do, and our business plan is designed with the clear goal of improving the service we provide to the Bristol community. As part of this, we are going through an ambitious change programme… https://t.co/nuRwxmlk35 https://t.co/3yqkim5Bdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Manager: The Infrastructure Manager is a key strengthening role within a superb Technical Services Team. It will require a competent, capable, structured and willing individual who can take on the overall management of Cloud… https://t.co/C1QxTUR89X https://t.co/LwrIYDy17e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge orders discovery in Trump foreign gifts lawsuit to begin by end of month: A federal judge has finalized the schedule for when state challengers suing President Donald Trump over proceeds from the Trump International Hotel get to seek evidence for… https://t.co/76VymPzzYM https://t.co/CAzP1kO8nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s call screening transcripts are live and they’re pretty rad: If you’re the proud owner of a Pixel handset you, like 9to5Google, may have spotted this already. The call screening transcripts feature, first noted back in November, are starting to… https://t.co/vN82j4E8xB https://t.co/blC0mKezmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snior Software Architect: IT/SOFTWARE Workato, Inc. seeks Sen. SW Arch. to be platform arch./dev.; design/setup Kubernetes cluster; design, dev., supp. Slack Workbot prsnlized. accts. tech.; dev./ supp. OAuth2 auth., SSO &amp; acct. prvsoning.; DevOps &amp;… https://t.co/BU04Cbk1bp https://t.co/GmNvXS5Kz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Mueller is about to have his say -- in a big way: Throughout his investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 election, special counsel Robert Mueller has imposed on his team an ironclad rule: nobody leaks and nobody speaks -- out of court,… https://t.co/hYChLDEMtT https://t.co/49GvoM7obk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Web developer: Graduate Web Developer A Web Developer with some commercial knowledge of HTML / CSS and SQL is required by a leading eCommerce provider based just to the West of Oxford. A salary of £25,000 is available for this role. If you are a… https://t.co/RYc9vngWnK https://t.co/J1VoM92Dz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA, Risk &amp; Compliance Manager – Information Security: QA, Risk &amp; Compliance Manager – Innovative Cloud &amp; Hosting Solutions Brand Farnborough £35,000 – £40,000 + Benefits &amp; Fun Perks We are looking for an individual to further develop our quality and… https://t.co/a8u83JaJg8 https://t.co/EgYCJqCTIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data: COMPUTER/IT Data Scientist for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) to work in different areas, such as customer projects (co-innovation, consulting, custom dvlpmt, projects w/ internal customers), dvlpmt, or research. Bach in Comp Sci, SW Eng, Elctrcl… https://t.co/SjlRJ80ZW8 https://t.co/0pcSHMYS6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal Developer (Backend) – Remote: Role: Backend Drupal Developer (fully remote) Location: Manchester Salary: Negotiable (Depending on experience) Start: immediately Are you a back-end Drupal developer looking to start the new year in a new company?… https://t.co/kbGZrMC9xK https://t.co/nZ3FncgafY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's deadline day for the Florida recount. Here's what you need to know: It was already shaping up to be an important day in the recount saga for Florida's US Senate, governor and agriculture commissioner races, and now a federal judge has extended a… https://t.co/AfWvS6lSXW https://t.co/1NNPoPuzrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: Job Title Senior Web Developer State New Hampshire Description The Senior Web Developer will perform technical and specialized work in the design, development, maintenance, and improvement of the organization’s web sites andor… https://t.co/S456i6sbdI https://t.co/Zvdubb4Eg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator – London We now seek an assistant network administrator to be based in our London office. ROLE REQUIREMENTS * Provide hardware &amp; software support to UK offices and remote workers * Significant previous Network… https://t.co/i7qXABOJtg https://t.co/lKCBQL1sdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer Cloud Infrastructure: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/ulMbN3TNOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems/Network/Infrastructure Support – Harrogate – £35k: Systems/Network/Infrastructure Support – Harrogate – £30k – £35k Greywood are delighted to be working with an international company based in Harrogate who are searching for a hard-working,… https://t.co/7rqVfIDUNR https://t.co/rQ5wvv3koG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activity Security Representative III: Req ID 100540BR Business Title Activity Security Representative III Group MCIS Location USA MASSACHUSETTS Hanscom AFB Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Security Job Duties and Responsibilities Activity Security… https://t.co/dGNnikccuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lies, damn lies, and HQ2: There are few things certain in our world except for the uplifting tendencies of technology. I’ve spent the past few years trying to prove this to myself, at least, by interviewing hundreds of thinkers on the topic. I’ve come to… https://t.co/lg9aQhg3uf https://t.co/ILR6ZCdZ4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate / Junior IT Support Engineer: Graduate / Junior IT Support Engineer £20,000 – £30,000 Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire Graduate / Junior IT Support Engineer required by a leading technology company based in Aylesbury. Due to continued success and… https://t.co/E3UtDnIDWa https://t.co/3s8EDaf6A7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – C# .NET: Full Stack .NET Developer required for an innovative digital agency in the Brighton area. Joining as a Full Stack Developer you will be in a close-knit team of developers who develop a web based application which is used… https://t.co/mxMUUkK1SX https://t.co/3MhauTM16C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Line Service Desk: A MARKET LEADING banking client based in Chester require an accomplished 1st line service desk analyst to join them for an exciting and challenging engagement. For this opportunity you will be an Ajilon employee working on a… https://t.co/GJsTW0xyz8 https://t.co/30GY80pJAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China makes opening bid to US on trade ahead of Trump-Xi meeting: The Chinese government has presented an offer to the United States to try to push forward stalled trade talks before the leaders of the two economic superpowers meet at the end of this… https://t.co/lHCYWrfHwJ https://t.co/roQzCAqDX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Engineer – 6 Month Contract – £250 per day: Desktop Support Engineer – 6 Month Contract – £250 per day Overview: A FTSE250 global financial company working on leading edge software products used by its global staff of over 1500 require a… https://t.co/vK7HM12JA2 https://t.co/5f08V8xFfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Job ID 13838-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Exciting career opportunities and a great company to work for! L.L.Bean has something for anyone who wants to build a successful career. Love of the outdoors is a common… https://t.co/atDpqSLNj0 https://t.co/LYQtiirAbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA – Contract – Slough: SQL DBA wanted – Contract – Slough Berkshire SQL Server Complex T-SQL, Data Warehousing, OLAP I am looking for a SQL DBA for a 3-6 month contract for a greenfield project in slough, my client needs help on a exciting project… https://t.co/WhCzro7hFg https://t.co/2COEHuK1rV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation/DevOps Engineer: Senior Test Automation/DevOps Engineer – Discover Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Careers Home – Life at Discover – Teams – Locations – Blog – Job Search Senior Test Automation/DevOps Engineer – P******_S1 Keywords All Jobs… https://t.co/td7g1Zu8QO https://t.co/ihgEyaTIUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer / SQL – Manchester – Contract: NET Developer Manchester 6 month contract (initially) Predominately your role within the team is to be responsible for the design, implementation and integration of remaining system features in accordance with… https://t.co/ggy1hquNwq https://t.co/uIxlI2mZis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Graduate Opportunities in Software Engineering at Ford Motor Company Ford Motor Company is aggressively pursuing emerging opportunities to become a leader in connectivity, mobility services, autonomous vehicles, the customer experience… https://t.co/HHqx2a5WFS https://t.co/bjSr2uZRm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marie Antoinette pendant fetches $36M: Marie Antoinette, France's last queen, is still able to capture the imagination of the public -- or at least buyers with a lot of spare cash -- more than 200 years after her unfortunate end. https://t.co/R7pMpJeJVl https://t.co/bDGHk4z8gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government denies Oracle’s protest of $10B Pentagon JEDI cloud RFP: When Oracle filed a protest in August with the Government Accountability Office (GAO) that the Pentagon’s $10 billion JEDI RFP process was unfair, it probably had little chance of… https://t.co/SmHARJXUNZ https://t.co/eohQYMKNP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Senior DevOps Engineer – AWS, Azure, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Terraform, Mongo DB Dublin + Remote You will be using the latest tools and technologies supporting cloud environments. You will be working with enterprise… https://t.co/qgXgat2cjz https://t.co/2yKcQsKXnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police release photo of 46-year-old suspect https://t.co/0L37LSc4Ko https://t.co/ZVn5cari5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Business / Process Change: Business Analyst – Business / Process Change Hampshire; Waterlooville area £40k – £50k per annum We are seeking an experienced Business Analyst / Business Change Analyst to work as part of the Business Change… https://t.co/neC7cDRX3z https://t.co/tpAdM56KQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer – Docker l Terraform l AWS – Blockchain! £95k DOE Are you a DevOps Engineer interested in blockchain? Want to increase your knowledge around Blockchain and Cryto working with the best? Whilst helping to scale one of the… https://t.co/96SMbOI9t0 https://t.co/wiV7b2aJmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack React-Native Developer: About Us This new Startup has a fantastic opportunity to be working side-by-side an established, leading digital marketing agency to help build out and realise new ideas/products/visions. The culture at this new… https://t.co/bC1QFTdGuG https://t.co/2nTzEGqJF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Mayer praises Taylor Swift: Taylor Swift's ex-boyfriend, John Mayer, has some thoughts about her hit album, "Reputation." https://t.co/q6XfaHKaDc https://t.co/cPvE0snRBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Telecoms – Voice: Job Title: Project Manager Suitable for: Project Managers, Senior Project Managers, Technical Project Manager Salary: Negotiable DoE plus Car Allowance Location: Home based with occasional travel to customer sites as… https://t.co/YwOOln6YMH https://t.co/snhlV1GMHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Contract- React: I am looking for a Software Engineer with strong React skills for a Market Leading SaaS Organisation company based in Manchester who boasts year on year growth in size and profitability and as they continue to corner… https://t.co/mi7Hebz8XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor to round up sex offenders for Halloween: A Georgia mayor has announced plans to round up paroled sex offenders while children in his town trick-or-treat on Halloween. https://t.co/5ks3e1zk5t https://t.co/OjMB7hEw0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level PHP Developer: Mid-Level PHP Developer Location: London or Leatherhead Permanent Salary: £35k-£45k Mid-level PHP developer looking to join a cutting edge software development company? Must Have Technical Skills: – Strong experience with PHP,… https://t.co/gdZXQqetmy https://t.co/ziz4IjAovS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Lead: QA Lead Bristol £450 – £475 BPSS Clearance The QA Lead must be hands on and previously have implemented automated frameworks and approaches in line with the tools specified for the programme. Teck Stack • SoapUI • Selenium • JMeter. They are… https://t.co/sAss42FzYz https://t.co/wuPWgX8z4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Infrastructure &amp; Operations: Head of Infrastructure &amp; Operations Permanent Location; Leicester £70,000 – £79,000 per annum Working for an established organisation, the ideal candidate will be required to join an growing organisation as the Head… https://t.co/7OgAw8GYSc https://t.co/iwSkIvut6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCR Communications Integration SME- Portable Data: Req ID 99645BR Business Title CCR Communications Integration SME- Portable Data Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Arlington Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Scientific / Analytical Job Duties and… https://t.co/4ZwuxPVGK4 https://t.co/0yxT7cVfL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Software Engineer – Nottingham: Net Software Engineer – Nottingham – C#/.Net Our award-winning client is hiring! Based in Nottingham, they are looking for a seasoned C#/.Net developer who is passionate about tech and willing to work across a range of… https://t.co/UOV9BmTEs0 https://t.co/gkWiV3evtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary IT Business Analyst: Alexander Daniels are working in partnership with a small and friendly not for profit organisation based in Coventry to recruit an IT Business Analyst on a 12 month fixed term contract. Following business change my Client… https://t.co/pvjGl2AavW https://t.co/0IHAPp7Mn2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>