<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/xM2fAh2bQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/dRyvWCPwuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/AGKykE1ABp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/AeMOZRX6Zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/WOUSvPOYBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/GfV36y1EAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/ewxoRnUgUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/Hz32i6SwH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/6bRqMD2YLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/Iev3ZOuogB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/3vcQw6i5Bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/GGTHyoSjRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/2ZJWXfkVeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/0r2xfP2epS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/ipUV4AxQjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/IM28GqFBCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/MG4tn2BKhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/ETKN1QgE3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/qCyDagXM6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/XjMQIxWlXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/QaqsIZIFzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/Xg21iD4gvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/3vcQw6i5Bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/qAk5pybdvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/f9WHPQrzim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/NCm1R3hS1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/IM0zuNX9rL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/AHSHc17xyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/ERpg5eSu2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/WqovLEV6ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/fNc4NQ7Bql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/WOUSvPOYBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/3PI5BAyeR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/etCvlKIFDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/oY7m8ZdB4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/M5GGaxloIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/BBEKgdrbUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/ei8V6mm7E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/SkjOgxcWYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/MAvbNjefde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/4K65R9qytP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/mQYftE2X2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>