<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to know  #life is to love many things. ~Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not quench your #inspiration and your imagination; do not become the slave of your model. Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A true #friend sees the good in everything, and brings out the best in the worst of things.” Sasha Azevedo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only one who can tell you 'you can't ' is you. And you don't have to listen." - Nike #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that #you can't go a day without thinking about.~Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start the New Year right... #Run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we did the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves. -Thomas Edison (via @tesschallis) #quote #run #achieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let fatigue make a coward of you."- Steve Prefontaine #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For me, like so many others, #running is the answer. Out on the road it is just you, the pavement, and your will" John Bingham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do these shorts make my ass look fast?" ~ #running shorts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll race myself, not those around me. #runningresolutions2012 via @brentkinnaird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#runningresolutions2012 to never stop thinking of new routes, new times and new distances via @georgia_simone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stretch more and drink more water, even when I don't run. #runningresolutions2012 via @amirgrin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run for a burning passion and not just burning calories #runningresolutions2012 via @lisaluvsthalawd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#runningresolutions2012 find a running partner via @cristhianrabe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To convince more friends to join me on runs. #runningresolutions2012 via @thompkia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run for charity #runningresolutions2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#runningresolutions2012 To run a race per month and have my children participate in each fun run! via @runjanisrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#runningresolutions2012 to run hard with no excuses! via @marcieamaro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run Smart and avoid injury :) #runningresolutions2012 via @tcclouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#runningresolutions2012 run for fun. No watch, no pace, no time. Just run via @natbalda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it hurts, push through the pain & keep going. #runningresolutions2012 via @hannahisaSwan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run with my heart not my mind #runningresolutions2012 via @moodymatt00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile at all runners when we pass #runningresolutions2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To run at least 6 days a week #runningresolutions2012 via @sayscye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run barefoot #runningresolutions2012 via @thatgirlruns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run more without my watch #runningresolutions2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play hard, love hard, run hard #runningresolutions2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The joy was in the act of  #running and in the journey, not in the destination." John Bingham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start it, run it, push it, sweat it, grunt it, laugh it, finish it  #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power of dreams and the influence of the human #spirit - Wilma Rudolph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few of us know what we are capable of doing…we have never pushed ourselves hard enough to find out– Montapert #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'll lean on you and you lean on me and we'll be okay." - Dave Matthews Band #friends #runningpartners #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But if you never try you'll never know...Just what you're worth" Fix You by Coldplay #inspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because it's my passion, and not just a sport. - Sasha Azevedo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run marathons #yes #for #fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live a life of my own design. I go with the flow that's uniquely mine. via  @AnnTran_ @SoCalNerium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They who have #conquered doubt and fear have conquered failure." - James Allen via @GreatestQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Skill to do comes of doing."  Ralph Waldo Emerson via @CharityIdeas #train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To settle is a choice, you can choose to run after your dreams  #life #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people say they don't have enough time to train. Others make it happen #noexcuses #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Believe that you're young enough, old enough, strong enough & so on to accomplish everything you want to do" John Bingham via #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be positive, ignore the critic, follow ur heart, invest in your passions, believe in ur dreams & get busy making them reality~ by @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow your bliss and the universe will open doors where there were only walls. ~Joseph Campbell  #life #run #change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself. ~Joseph Campbell #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only disability in life is a bad attitude. -Scott Hamilton (via @rnrgirl) #run #train #marathon #endurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A river cuts through rock, not because of its power, but because of its persistence" ~Jim Watkins #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait until the conditions are perfect to #begin. Beginning makes the conditions perfect. ~A. Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Goals determine what you're going to be." ~Julius Erving (via @sirisaac)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running is freedom. Freedom from races. Freedom from paces. Don't forget to have a free #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Naked cheerleaders  1 mile ahead"
-mile 25” via @A2Diddy  #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there something you are so passionate about you cannot stop thinking about it? #start #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman or man with outward courage dares to die, A man or woman with inward courage dares to live - Lao Tzu via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is for the LIVING. Live Yours ~ via @LoriMoreno #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We may #run a lot of miles, but it is important to take our friends with us along the way. The road will be a sweeter path.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Know your limits, then ignore them" ~John Mason #run #marathon  via @SoCalNerium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people don't know how to fit their runs in. Other don't know how they can't" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I am still standing at the end of the #race, hit me with a board & knock me down, because that means I didn’t run hard enough~Steve Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's amazing what you can accomplish when you decide you can't be stopped.” via @Kattemie #run #charity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Have great hopes and dare to go all out for them. Have great #dreams and dare to live them." Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone has special talents, and it is our duty to find ours and use them well." - John Templeton via @GreatestQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are all these people following me? #Marathon T-Shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't love what you do, you won't do it with much conviction or passion. ~Mia Hamm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chase your #passion ~Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can because they think they can. ~Virgil #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would say Santa qualifies as an endurance athlete #HappyHolidays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would say Santa qualifies as an endurance athlete #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Have great hopes and dare to go all out for them. Have great #dreams and dare to live them." Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I travel not to go anywhere, but to go. I travel for travel's sake. The great affair is to move." ~R.L. Stevenson” via @daniel_baylis #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success. ~ Napoleon Hill #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run, live, change, train, focus, help, care, laugh, friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember, your worst #run is always 100% better than the person who never tries." via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have #possibilities we don't know about. We can do things we don't even dream we can do. ~ Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you wait to #do everything until you're sure it's right, you'll probably never do much"-Borden via @Lotay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Never underestimate the power of #dreams and the influence of the human spirit.” Wilma Rudolph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most things which we think are impossible in life, is because we have never tried them. So go for every #dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you’re going to doubt something, doubt your own limits." ~Don Ward via @CharityIdeas #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know the more conservative you are, in #pace, from the beginning, the more you can push your wall back?” via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone is gifted - but some people never open their package" #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take risks, courage to try, dreams that come true, fall in love, discover the #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never #settle for mediocrity when you can have greatness"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Greatest danger for most of us is not that we aim too #high & we miss it, but we aim too low & reach it." Michelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Desire is the most important factor in the #success of any athlete." ~Willie Shoemaker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no telling how many miles you will have to #run while chasing a dream. ~Author Unknown via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody's got a laughin' place-
trouble is most folks won't take the time to go look for it" #find #laugh #love #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a #run---&gt;&gt;&gt;The greatest healing therapy is friendship and love - Hubert H. Humphrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." - Babe Ruth #determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A good #friend is a connection 2life - a tie 2the past, a road 2the future, the key 2sanity in a totally insane world" Wyse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you #sweat in practice, the less you bleed in battle. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Love #live #dream #chances #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MarathonCheeringSigns Momma said there'd be days like this. Via @kechk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Some day you won't be able to do this. Today is NOT that day." #MarathonCheeringSigns via @kevin_gillen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MarathonCheeringSigns My fave at Chicago 2011, good thing it's not 26.3 miles, because THAT would be insane. #ownit via @wendylpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ice Bath and Cookies Ahead!!" #MarathonCheeringSigns via @runnerstud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MarathonCheeringSigns "Just when you thought you was done..." mile 26.2 at my first 50k ultra via @itzmykeyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweat is sexy #MarathonCheeringSigns @RunningQuotes via @anahiboesch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forget www.Match.com, I'm looking for a man that can go long" #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really great people make you feel that you, too, can become great. ~Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is a #magic formula...It's just that the magic is different for everyone" Keith Dowling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man never made any material as resilient as the human spirit." - Bern Williams #quote via @SusanCosmos]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>