<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@Arbys's cool and nonchalant tweets suggest infection with the R0BERT.D0WNEY.JR. virus https://t.co/WVnoCOqM3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the charming R0BERT.D0WNEY.JR. virus automatically adds emoji for flowers and for chocolates to all your texts to female co-workers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This terrifying new book about bots makes Peter Benchley's 'Jaws' seem as terrifying as a bloodied finger in a joke store matchbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Arrogant Sonny Crockett" after reading @emrata's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish tuxedo-black and arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/SU3aygtBDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a Bohemian café in which
Naomi Campbell can enjoy @emrata's arrogant but stylish tweets
while peacocking in fancy clothes https://t.co/Z4QJyg9soY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Mickey Mouse" after reading @BarRefaeli's latest tweets with pleasant chocolate-brown, upbeat Santa-red and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/1KLbJgeCkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Mickey Mouse with the best of Adrian Monk and you get @BarRefaeli: cheerful and upbeat and observant and detail-oriented https://t.co/8hBevv8ZwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Entertaining Joey Tribbiani" after reading @lululemon's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and entertaining iPod-white https://t.co/YG78PkRiaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This masculine new book about computational creativity makes Patrick O'Brian's 'Master And Commander' seem as masculine as an enema]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pope is watching
If he can forgive Wernher von Braun for being so damned charismatic he can forgive @lululemon's brilliant and charming tweets https://t.co/aoJuyZvhRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Walt Disney" after reading @rogerfederer's latest tweets with avuncular Santa-red, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/9khNvOlY7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE patient humans who remind him of cats. So Hulk SMASH @rogerfederer's cool, gentle and curious tweets! https://t.co/JHQE0UJocu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Outgoing Joey Tribbiani" after reading @OfficialSanta's latest tweets with loyal Tarzan-loincloth-brown, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/b9xbnXokCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @OfficialSanta's twee and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Neapolitan ice cream made with corrugated cardboard instead of wafers https://t.co/6pcnEBodFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted Jesus Christ" after reading @ABdeVilliers17's latest tweets with inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/eH9xO4HpNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @ABdeVilliers17's honorable and well-meaning tweets remind it of Monsieur Hulot https://t.co/66i5Mfwg5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Gleeful Mickey Mouse" after reading @BreadBoi's latest tweets with upbeat sunshine-yellow, cheerful prince-purple and pleasant candy-pink https://t.co/jB0DCc0xKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Bridget Jones with the best of Rupert Murdoch and you get @BarbaraPalvin: upbeat and media-savvy and influential and powerful https://t.co/yVHy4r0fKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Long-winded Meghan Markle" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange, social-climbing Blackadder-black and pretty lamb-white https://t.co/TacP4hlc2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this nimble book about computational creativity also bought:
-   David Mitchell's 'Cloud Atlas'
-   Malcolm Beckett's 'The Human Hand'
 How very nimble!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-tongued Wernher Von Braun" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with ruthless ninja-black, brilliant emerald-green and sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red https://t.co/zA9GpKsZs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @BotOnBotAction:
1. Flash Gordon
2. Helen Keller
3. Virginia Woolf
4. Google
5. Sappho https://t.co/bl0GTrSpk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #MetaphorizeMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Sherlock Holmes" after reading @maroon5's latest tweets with dispassionate robot-silver-grey, astute sage-brown and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/NgUeys6UGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @maroon5's attention-seeking and unemotional tweets were edible they'd be Butterscotch pie made with crushed gravel instead of brown sugar https://t.co/8NuJWq468P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Engrossing Noam Chomsky" after reading @AlanCarr's latest tweets with holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white, socially-conscious Clooney-grey and arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/alXQjjeUAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This intriguing new book about bots makes Italo Calvino's 'If on a Winter's Night a Traveler' seem as intriguing as the instruction manual to Windows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a parking lot in which
Donald Trump can enjoy @AlanCarr's arrogant and smug tweets
while developing real estate https://t.co/nb47Q2IPZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Wernher Von Braun" after reading @ZombieRiot's latest tweets with brilliant Einstein-dandruff-white, charming garden-green and charismatic Obama-brown https://t.co/ltqk6KpqBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @ZombieRiot:
1. Howard Stern
2. Patch Adams
3. Champagnes
4. Tony Stark
5. Evangelists https://t.co/HG5Giq4Sf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Cold Sir Hugo Drax" after reading @Sheldon_Cooper_'s latest tweets with strategic Coriolanus Snow-white, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and cold robot-silver-grey https://t.co/7JIDsiegkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @Sheldon_Cooper_'s intelligent but arrogant tweets it pushes Noam Chomsky's book Studying Linguistics https://t.co/Llh82QfVta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Know-it-all Judge Joe Dredd" after reading @HilariousTed's latest tweets with unsympathetic Republican-red, stern Punisher-black and gruff warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/zM4StMm8ND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Judge Joe Dredd with the worst of Sam Winchester and you get @HilariousTed: unsympathetic and gruff and know-it-all and whiny https://t.co/irl5buzd2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Tony Stark" after reading @MarioGoetze's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, charming knight-silver and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Gctm1X3fkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @MarioGoetze's serene and powerful tweets is like one long lecture on running a school for gifted teens from Albus Dumbledore https://t.co/zfac1a1sIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Free-spirited Bridget Jones" after reading @ilovegeorgina's latest tweets with spunky vixen-red, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and upbeat Gumby-green https://t.co/fgI3VsbCXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@ilovegeorgina's media-savvy and powerful tweets suggest infection with the RUPERT.MURD0CH virus https://t.co/64yjd33R6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the influential RUPERT.MURD0CH virus uses your own credit-card details to buy you 1000s of fake followers (from India) on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seductive new book about Twitter 'bots' makes D.H. Lawrence's 'Lady Chatterley's Lover' seem as seductive as a wet fish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Scientist" after reading @elonmusk's latest tweets with probing NYPD-blue, curious Bart Simpson-yellow and attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue https://t.co/U38eWCgEtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @elonmusk's tweets to the equally fashionable and consciousness-raising Michelle Obama. https://t.co/Jo4weJzQcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Beatrix Potter" after reading @SaveWest1's latest tweets with artistic star-white, observant Eeyore-grey and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/MIzSvJALTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @SaveWest1: cunning and insightful and astute and detail-oriented https://t.co/HStxWRwq8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Zealot" after reading @donttrythis's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, intense espresso-black and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/h3c0vckKkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This inspiring new book about Twitter 'bots' makes T.H. White's 'The Once and Future King' seem as inspiring as a rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a secret military base in which
Sarah Connor can enjoy @donttrythis's preachy and pushy tweets
while amassing weapons https://t.co/mnmP4z6SAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Fool" after reading @kendricklamar's latest tweets with guileless angel-white, illiterate cow-brown and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/QE5F9VCCI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE upbeat humans who remind him of Bridget Jones. So Hulk SMASH @kendricklamar's media-savvy, spunky and bouncy tweets! https://t.co/yfCOcTJ8d3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Bouncy Ikarus" after reading @blakeshelton's latest tweets with eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange, ambitious Cicero-toga-white and social-climbing Blackadder-black https://t.co/10uJolLO9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @blakeshelton's sappy and hammy tweets were edible they'd be Profiteroles and chocolate sauce made with lumps of clay instead of chocolate https://t.co/bYcBkUEoV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Steven Spielberg" after reading @BethanyMota's latest tweets with media-savvy Facebook-blue, overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green and influential Madonna-blonde https://t.co/gyn1MVb1xI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cutting new book about bots makes Joseph Heller's 'Catch-22' seem as cutting as a plastic spoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @BethanyMota's influential and media-savvy tweets it pushes Rupert Murdoch's book Publishing Newspapers https://t.co/tiwoanmO3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Tony Robbins" after reading @ChesterCheetah's latest tweets with philosophical Buddhist-saffron-orange, optimistic Gumby-green and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/vWIfvOLYwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @ChesterCheetah:
1. John Constantine
2. Walter White
3. Jean-Paul Sartre
4. Scientists
5. Detectives https://t.co/N1tef2ZGag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving E.T." after reading @Arbys's latest tweets with kind-hearted Groot-brown, loyal Eeyore-grey and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/o8E9UXoneC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This stylish new book about computational creativity makes F. Scott Fitzgerald's 'The Great Gatsby' seem as stylish as a fleece ball gown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @Ibra_official's latest tweets with stylish Kate Moss-green, fashionable Barbie-pink and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/3HSfkxH75w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a Bohemian café in which
Obi-wan Kenobi can enjoy @Ibra_official's calm and powerful tweets
while promoting mysticism https://t.co/Is9RZimdqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Helen Keller" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with resolute lion-orange, tenacious warrior-woad-blue and fearless knight-silver https://t.co/Q3lOq6xFOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This upsetting new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Edgar Allan Poe's 'The Tell-Tale Heart' seem as upsetting as a smudge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Long-winded Mahatma Gandhi" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with pious Buddhist-saffron-orange, inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/VMiGUXguxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #PaintMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Nonchalant Meghan Markle" after reading @adamlevine's latest tweets with social-climbing Lewinsky-blue, calm Buddhist-saffron-orange and socially-conscious Clooney-grey https://t.co/T4Ugv2CX7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Bridget Jones with the best of Albus Dumbledore and you get @adamlevine: media-savvy and fun-loving and eccentric and serene https://t.co/sXEmAaty3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Jim Carrey" after reading @SarahMillican75's latest tweets with entertaining iPod-white, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and environmentally-conscious Tarzan-loincloth-brown https://t.co/pJ1hEcY82w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This popular new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Ian Fleming's 'On Her Majesty's Secret Service' seem as popular as a fat guy passing gas on an elevator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @SarahMillican75's stylish and urbane tweets it pushes Federico Fellini's book Making New Wave Movies https://t.co/DGbAPQrLO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Jerk" after reading @andrewchristian's latest tweets with smug Trump-orange, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/kjH8WqOcIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE observant humans who remind him of Sam Spade. So Hulk SMASH @andrewchristian's cold, detail-oriented and detached tweets! https://t.co/EOo65IPWAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Don Draper" after reading @lizzzuy's latest tweets with arrogant Thor-blond-yellow, suave Pimpernel-scarlet-red and charming garden-green https://t.co/pmw03Mxac7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @lizzzuy's pushy and emotionally-detached tweets were edible they'd be Peach Melba made with road grit instead of sugar https://t.co/LE6cAzKcJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Powerful Joey Tribbiani" after reading @virendersehwag's latest tweets with easy-going Lebowski-weed-green, good-natured Santa-red and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/GwNeHs0ugG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this fresh book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Steven D. Levitt's 'Freakonomics'
-   Cormac Dickens's 'The Daisy'
 How very fresh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Plugged In William Randolph Hearst" after reading @AustinMahone's latest tweets with media-savvy Facebook-blue, powerful Yoda-green and influential Madonna-blonde https://t.co/OMHnvYsmGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Rupert Murdoch with the best of Coco Chanel and you get @AustinMahone: media-savvy and powerful and prolific and influential https://t.co/VhDpJMlVPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Galileo Galilei" after reading @DrPhil's latest tweets with insightful Columbo-beige, revolutionary Lenin-red and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/K46zUmNu5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @DrPhil's argumentative and elitist tweets remind it of Katharine Hepburn https://t.co/LVkA3BAZYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this nimble book about bots also bought:
-   David Mitchell's 'Cloud Atlas'
-   Franz Trollope's 'The Human Hand'
 How very nimble!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Perry Mason" after reading @jcpenney's latest tweets with sly fox-red, strategic Coriolanus Snow-white and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/B7juP1GKqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a brothel in which
Oscar Wilde can enjoy @jcpenney's brilliant and insightful tweets
while scandalizing polite society https://t.co/YLSuRNhYdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Robot" after reading @davidguetta's latest tweets with dispassionate bureaucrat-grey, cold cucumber-green and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/DSMa6lKhNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Sherlock Holmes with the worst of Dr. Greg House and you get @davidguetta: dispassionate and condescending and cold and arrogant https://t.co/gRHuomaurl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Michael J. Fox" after reading @TheRock's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-tandoori-red, affable Gumby-green and social-climbing Blackadder-black https://t.co/B2Uif30ypL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a Bohemian café in which
Spongebob Squarepants can enjoy @TheRock's upbeat and energetic tweets
while blowing bubbles https://t.co/gx1OHrqYQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this friendly book about computational creativity also bought:
-   A.A. Milne's 'Winnie-The-Pooh'
-   Dennis Follett's 'The Drunken Whore'
 How very friendly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Reginald Jeeves" after reading @rickygervais's latest tweets with ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red, cunning Saruman-white and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/ZPhDbPTHmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE arrogant humans who remind him of egomaniacs. So Hulk SMASH @rickygervais's ruthless, preening and swaggering tweets! https://t.co/Gt1PDcAeHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Cheerful Piers Morgan" after reading @benlandis's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, media-savvy Facebook-blue and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/GKqQAVWmpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @benlandis's attention-seeking and temperamental tweets were edible they'd be Apple Strudel made with pus-filled zits instead of sultanas https://t.co/ahJbt8G8W3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Mysticism-peddling Sean Penn" after reading @annecurtissmith's latest tweets with attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue, socially-conscious Clooney-grey and passionate flame-orange https://t.co/nQktHpnwhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This nourishing new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Julia Child's 'Mastering The Art of French Cooking' seem as nourishing as a vending machine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @annecurtissmith's pretentious and snooty tweets it pushes films about Psychoanalysis and/or Frasier Crane https://t.co/cNBzpdCXRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Educated Joey Tribbiani" after reading @CSLewisDaily's latest tweets with easy-going Gumby-green, self-confident Obama-brown and educated priest-black https://t.co/78hR7egva2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @CSLewisDaily's insightful and brilliant tweets it pushes Oscar Wilde's book Coining Epigrams https://t.co/JHvlkZVhnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Pep Talk" after reading @ramonasinger's latest tweets with inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black, motivational Obama-brown and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/Po5iK5jkPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@ramonasinger's scholarly and eloquent tweets suggest infection with the 5CH0LARZ virus https://t.co/myaqrAV2c7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the eloquent 5CH0LARZ virus hacks your Twitter and blocks you from sending any tweets that do not scan in iambic pentameter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this dramatic book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Anthony Trollope's 'The Barchester Chronicles'
-   William Trollope's 'The Shooting Gallery At A Carnival'
 How very dramatic!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>