<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't count the days, make the days count." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are what you think about all day long." - Dr. Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It takes a lot of courage to show your dreams to someone else." - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is a lousy teacher.  It seduces smart people into thinking they can't lose." - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is wise to keep in mind that neither success nor failure is ever final." - Roger Babson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is better to ask some of the questions than know all the answers." - James Thurber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Strength lies in differences, not in similarities." - Stephen Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Open your arms to change, but don't let go of your values." - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do more than believe: practice." - William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your big opportunity may be right where you are standing right now." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we wait for the moment when everything, absolutely everything is ready, we shall never begin." - Ivan Turgenev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must embrace pain and burn it as fuel for our journey." - Kenji Miyazawa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Well done is better than well said." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The roots of true achievement lie in the will to become the best that you can become." - Harold Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is found in doing, not merely possessing." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do what you can, with what you have, where you are." - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make things as simple as possible, but not simpler." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We shall have no better conditions in the future if we are satisfied with all those which we have at present." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important thing about having goals is having one." - Geoffrey F. Abert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failures, repeated failures, are finger posts on the road to achievement. One fails forward toward success." - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To think is easy. To act is hard. But the hardest thing in the world is to act in accordance with your thinking." - Johann von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nature does not hurry, yet everything is accomplished." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most people are paralyzed by fear. Overcome it and you take charge of your life and your world." - Mark Victor Hansen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You really can change the world if you care enough." - Marian Wright Edelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious." - Albert Einstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not in the stars to hold our destiny but in ourselves." - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The way to get things done is not to mind who gets the credit for doing them." - Benjamin Jowett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can't get rid of the skeleton in your closet, you'd best teach it to dance." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Formal education will make you a living. Self education will make you a fortune." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you have time to whine and complain about something then you have the time to do something about it." - Anthony J. D'Angelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I hated every minute of training, but I said, don't quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doubt can only be removed by action." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No great discovery was ever made without a bold guess." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We learn by doing." - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd rather regret the things that I have done than the things that I have not done." - Lucille Ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To lead the people, walk behind them." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot do a kindness too soon, for you never know how soon it will be too late." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Necessity is the mother of taking chances." - Mark Twain ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every day holds the possibility of a miracle." - Elizabeth David]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Always seek out the seed of triumph in every adversity." - Og Mandino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Example is not the main thing in influencing others, it is the only thing." - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I have seen farther than others, it is because I have stood on the shoulders of giants." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A life spent making mistakes is not only more honourable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The power of intuitive understanding will protect you from harm until the end of your days." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can throw stones, complain about them, stumble on them, climb over them, or build with them." - William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Time and money spent in helping men to do more for themselves is far better than mere giving." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Accept responsibility for your life. Know that it is you who will get you where you want to go, no one else." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The sound body is the product of the sound mind." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The speed of the leader is the speed of the gang." - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Common sense is not so common." - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When it is dark enough, you can see the stars." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The less you open your heart to others, the more your heart suffers." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Better to keep your mouth shut and appear stupid than to open it and remove all doubt." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're going through hell, keep going." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sooner or later, those who win are those who think they can." - Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We make a living by what we get, we make a life by what we give."  - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's lack of faith that makes people afraid of meeting challenges, and I believe in myself." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great discoveries and improvements invariably involve the cooperation of many minds." - Alexander Graham Bell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It doesn't matter where you are coming from. All that matters is where you are going." - Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without danger you cannot get beyond danger." - George Herbert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When all is said and done, success without happiness is the worst kind of failure." - Louis Binstock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no substitute for hard work." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ideas not coupled with action never become bigger than the brain cells they occupied." - Arnold H. Glasow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Genius without education is like silver in the mine." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take time for all things: great haste makes great waste." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love without action is meaningless and action without love is irrelevant." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["While we stop to think, we often miss our opportunity." - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people grumble because roses have thorns; I am thankful that the thorns have roses." - Alphonse Karr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can adopt the attitude there is nothing you can do, or you can see the challenge as your call to action." - Catherine Pulsifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love Mickey Mouse more than any woman I have ever known." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No great man ever complains of want of opportunity." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All men who have achieved great things have been great dreamers." - Orison Swett Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At first dreams seem impossible, then improbable, then inevitable." - Christopher Reeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude. Don't complain." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Self-praise is for losers. Be a winner. Stand for something. Always have class, and be humble." - John Madden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Enjoy your achievements as well as your plans." - Max Ehrmann]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who would travel happily must travel light." - Antoine de Saint-Exupery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Snowflakes are one of nature's most fragile things, but just look at what they can do when they stick together." - Vesta Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more original a discovery, the more obvious it seems afterward." - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The harder you work, the harder it is to surrender." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can never cross the ocean unless you have the courage to lose sight of the shore." - Christopher Columbus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Progress is impossible without change and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth is the ability to fully experience life." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quality is never an accident. It is always the result of intelligent effort." - John Ruskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is defeat? Nothing but education; nothing but the first step to something better." - Wendell Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is impossible." - Susan B. Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are today where your thoughts have brought you; you will be tomorrow where your thoughts take you." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't depend on your eyes when your imagination is out of focus." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop worrying about the potholes in the road and enjoy the journey." - Babs Hoffman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our greatest glory is not in never falling but in rising every time we fall." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man is literally what he thinks." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A danger foreseen is half avoided." - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Finding a way to live the simple life today is man's most complicated task." - Henry A. Courtney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yesterday is but today's memory, tomorrow is today's dream." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone needs to be valued. Everyone has the potential to give something back." - Diana Princess of Wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things do not happen. Things are made to happen." - John F Kennedy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>