<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/feIY0QZGmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/Kwg9zKs3dJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/NvTk35IQfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/SZSnNcn5gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/5JBcbKNFGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/IGHc4TAs9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/OPQhC4h8X1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/bgGoaIJMca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/eXvO0gkR5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/W3O3ehmWqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/A0quYik44c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/nVpNWUyIkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/TobH2VvI68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/BksSqui0wA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/OEfVLcdC8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/wZl7SMcCnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/sRK5GKZzlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/GZcuUCrJNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/88ZyLolzXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/O7oLH6lQtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/EWB5chbOmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/meF5XoTAwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/wT4Tl5aC1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/UJzGwZjNsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/Vtoh5rXB7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge : " Your wife charges that you haven't spoken to her in  5 years. Why is that?" Defendant: "I didn't dare interrupt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/P9JP2uVh9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/LeBL259dpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/aX0LIlGjOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/8bPc7ExQNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/c6Vo4MxE1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/nh90EBnGXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/7p9v68Y56y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/7NjlSi8Mby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/pGN5jeAJHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/lemi2uWDup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/VLz8fSJPZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/y2BAGkjVjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/XBIZZ9ymzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/RMIVmgp1xC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/h50EF5JpLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/lHISB5egI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/o4nJIF4yF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TDdUvtPWl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/PSebbfkIQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/YmffoSCuwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/oJBcE8NM5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/9OKMKHWTl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/LxKtXaKMgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/juzvKCnzv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/doEfdgIZPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/ekBIRt1sqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/kIRHX0DzMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/rWzize6TEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/rKwGiKGxmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/oNfc9bnnxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/PfwREH2eDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/fkKLcj1qzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/ZFsmgQl4GQ  http://t.co/lT4LnyBVTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/x1qvuR8Auk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>