<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-51901 Location: Novi, Michigan Start Date: 09/17/2018 Job title Scrum Master Location Novi, MI Duration: Long The Senior Scrum Master has the responsibility of leading a mid-size team of Developers, Testers, BA and… https://t.co/KFGhPdqrQb https://t.co/venvmAacll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst: Job Description Business System AnalystBridgman, MI Posted: 8/27/2018 Category: Nuclear Job Type: – Minimum Experience: 2 Required Education: Bachelor (BA, BS.) Branch: Staffing Solutions Group Job Description Job Summary:… https://t.co/Y3t7vttNbP https://t.co/dR4r9t8OsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump changes course, calls for FBI investigation: President Donald Trump ordered a limited, week-long FBI probe of the allegations against his Supreme Court pick, Judge Brett Kavanaugh, at the request of the Senate Judiciary Committee on Friday. It was… https://t.co/sk1zDVXB6U https://t.co/nOOzYhfx6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/tvktgvdxKl https://t.co/TkACVJoxZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Mobile Developer (Connected Experiences): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the… https://t.co/8HSL1RuWnx https://t.co/nMuqTQYGZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL-Developer: ETL Developer Populus Group seeks an ETL Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide database development in the healthcare industry; develop, design, debug, test, and document ETL process for Date… https://t.co/qZdwc4KRaJ https://t.co/AN0HtaEBCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer / Electronics: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 13 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital… https://t.co/xdrUuo6CHP https://t.co/LLvdE54k8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: A financial services organization is seeking a Scrum Master to join their team in Detroit, MI. Responsibilities: Expanding Agile practices through leadership and integrating industry best practices Running daily stand-ups, sprint planning,… https://t.co/RMlWTWDGjB https://t.co/3rf7b7c7gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant principal: Girls ruin everything: A high school assistant principal in Tennessee is under fire after after he said "girls pretty much ruin everything" while addressing the school's dress code. https://t.co/Ko4QSfKrgK https://t.co/a1U98H78Ea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Job Details Network Engineer Do you enjoy coming up with creative solutions for complex problems? Join our team as a Network Engineer to support our intensive growth plans! You will work directly with our customers to meet engineering… https://t.co/KAJQspIHsc https://t.co/K4HlEXMddN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosenstein will meet with Republicans: Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein has agreed to speak with House Republicans about his reported comments discussing wearing a wire to talk to President Donald Trump and recruiting Cabinet members to invoke the… https://t.co/RVhZFSbWyV https://t.co/DoroR11PHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer I: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/9HvKIlvMky https://t.co/1VJtg1eGV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Design and Construction Technology Leader: Job Description Position Summary The VDC Technical Leader will serve as a key leader in the Firm’s Virtual Design and Construction efforts. As a member of the Corporate Global Initiatives VDC Group, you… https://t.co/dWlx8MUKIN https://t.co/uab3IiWXFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Job Details Network Engineer Do you enjoy coming up with creative solutions for complex problems? Join our team as a Network Engineer to support our intensive growth plans! You will work directly with our customers to meet engineering… https://t.co/oMS26Bl1TB https://t.co/i9RJI4WmBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reclusive Millionaire Warns: "Get Out Of Cash Now" https://t.co/5Ut3qsDIEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer – Bosch Motorsports: Company Description Bosch Motorsport North America is looking to expand their high performance team with a Software Engineer to continue to foster its North American Motorsports product development growth… https://t.co/IR3UmKGCcf https://t.co/mSPNjAJ2Se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bilingual Service Desk Coordinator: SECO TOOLS, LLC Job Position – US Position Title: Bilingual Service Desk Coordinator Job Code: JP0187 Reports To: IT Regional Service Desk Manager Department: Information Technology Location : Troy, MI Grade: S2 BROAD… https://t.co/ySOlMxCThT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Advanced: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Advanced job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS –… https://t.co/pKk7dL6PAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Job ID: ****** Service Desk Analyst Troy, Michigan Regular / Rotating Additional Job Information Title: Service Desk Analyst City, State: Troy, MI Location: MITROY 800 Tower Dr Department: Ops Service Center CRC Additional Job… https://t.co/kZq7aWYUe6 https://t.co/gUjZhF8cUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Analyst: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/2HEv3QDNkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administration – Solutions Architect: Services Back Big Data Consulting Back Hadoop Consulting Oracle Fusion Back Oracle ADF Oracle BPEL/SOA Suite OTM Transportation Back EDI Support IT Staffing Back Our Process Data Science – Staffing Mobile… https://t.co/r4DJK4hmpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Careers | A123 Systems Skip to content – Markets – Markets – Low Voltage Hybrids – Plug-In – Commercial Vehicles – Motorsports – Industrial Markets – Products – Products – Systems – Systems – 12V Starter Battery – 48V Lithium-ion… https://t.co/Ae1hFFu1ol https://t.co/1KwdTkdVNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wikipedia entry for 'Devil's Triangle' changed to match Kavanaugh's answer: Brett Kavanaugh's senior yearbook page, like his 1982 calendar, had been like a puzzle waiting to be solved. https://t.co/dcfFiWJXEY https://t.co/ITRidpvUy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/8QdIqWzIk3 https://t.co/EWszaVrodl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 26,000-pound dinosaur discovery was Earth's largest land animal: If humans had lived 200 million years ago, they would have marveled at the largest dinosaur of its time. It's name means "a giant thunderclap at dawn." https://t.co/ShDNMl6SIc https://t.co/1SJcZGNbhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the early Super Bowl favorites? https://t.co/ZBEtXjo6Vu https://t.co/jaeb8QZ7GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer / Electronics: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 13 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital… https://t.co/TPPBVVenAy https://t.co/knAVWdevKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented, passionate Software Engineer to enhance and maintain our Law Enforcement and Fire Records, and… https://t.co/Ld2CLG9nnh https://t.co/HngoGahDOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican governor calls on Senate to postpone vote: One of the country's most popular Republican governors on Thursday called for an independent investigation into the allegations made against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh and said the Senate… https://t.co/b8C8KRHkwN https://t.co/dxRfio63bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer: Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer – ENG******* in Detroit, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our… https://t.co/4ZqbNLSmIw https://t.co/7BKCNMF24d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/Letx98O2cD https://t.co/tU03p44wmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS-Traffic Project Manager I: Job Description ITS-Traffic Project Manager I Job LocationUS-MI-East Lansing | US-MI-DetroitJob ID0718-18953 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time CategoryEngineering-Traffic Why… https://t.co/tloqcfi3Au https://t.co/9CjKb8yqmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/SivdMislqv https://t.co/Lc2IWZ0KBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE ENGINEER: Career Opportunities | PICAS | Greenhouse Production Software PICAS | Greenhouse Production Software A Product of Innovative Software Solutions – HOME – ABOUT US – BLOG – NEWS – PARTNERS – PRODUCTS – ENTERPRISE EDITION – STANDARD… https://t.co/kkTv2Z7jjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer (MyBiz): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/n4olPiDGxU https://t.co/BUHlzfNkV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SOA Consulant: Oracle SOA Consulant Responsibilities: – Participate in technical planning &amp; requirements gathering phases including Design, code, test, troubleshoot, and document engineering software applications. – Ensuring that technical… https://t.co/QYBLT7GmWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US B-52s fly near contested islands amid China tensions: The US Air Force conducted two bomber flights this week into areas considered sensitive by the Chinese military, missions that have come amid heightened tensions between Washington and Beijing. https://t.co/NUJb96coBV https://t.co/hZ6jsepqmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer – 1st shift: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 10 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital company,… https://t.co/eU4dIasJCp https://t.co/DHtUxaiqvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Kavanaugh accuser has tie to firm of Christine Blasey Ford's attorney: Julie Swetnick, who went public on Wednesday with her accusations against Brett Kavanaugh, was represented in a sexual harassment complaint by the firm of the current lawyer for… https://t.co/16GQYY6mh3 https://t.co/oIQd7fNjy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: For Siemens Software Engineer Software Engineer – Syngo Dynamics: Cardiology image review and reporting software Siemens Medical Solutions, SYNGO R &amp; D US Cardiology Team, has an opening for a software engineer in the area of… https://t.co/BYVM8PNnlt https://t.co/804CkysehK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Security-Analyst—Incident-Response–Lansing–MI: We are hiring an IT Security Analyst to monitor and advise on information security issues related to the systems and workflow at an agency to ensure the internal IT security controls for an agency are… https://t.co/4w326ys5Ik https://t.co/3p1oIMHHjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK postal service tells public to stop mailing potato chip bags: The UK's postal service is urging environmental campaigners to stop sending empty potato chip bags without an envelope after the launch of a campaign urging the country's most popular chip… https://t.co/JMN3fmUuvt https://t.co/toqiUvPC5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: How to Applicants must through the UM Human Resources websit. Applicants must submit a cover letter and resume ressed to Carol Gray, Detroit URC Center Manager. The cover letter must be attached as the first page of your resume and should… https://t.co/dVqQe2FVMU https://t.co/MueIudmvBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Intern, ERP Solution: Software Development Intern, ERP Solution ========================================= We are seeking software engineering interns to join our fast paced, dynamic team during the summer of 2019. Location Troy,… https://t.co/r4wZjkSzN6 https://t.co/7iSNlPCSdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Position Title : Database Administrator Reports to : Information Technology Product Owner, Data and Reporting Location: Farmington Hills, MI I. Description : Alliance Inspection Management (AiM) is the nation s premier vehicle… https://t.co/bEvXD1ynGK https://t.co/7sDPvwKcly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal In – Building Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… We promise our customers the most reliable coverage across the country, and you’ll make sure we deliver on that promise. You’ll be a technical leader and subject matter… https://t.co/J9rgy2yGM9 https://t.co/BjseCza5R3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP to subpoena memos that may detail Rosenstein's comments about Trump: House Republicans have begun the process to subpoena the Justice Department for the memos written by former FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe that reportedly detail the explosive… https://t.co/TtaOMkI1oq https://t.co/3fneH5eMXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops engineer: Devops engineer – Detroit, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip code Find… https://t.co/8C1Z9laUa4 https://t.co/0wlHDgxbhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer I: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/eFkSyFsQDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Data Science Consultant: More than a career – a chance to make a difference in people’s lives. Build an exciting, rewarding career with us help us make a difference for millions of people every day. Consider joining the Duke Energy team, where… https://t.co/E8xevphgqD https://t.co/Uy7NaaWn0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SOA Consulant: Oracle SOA Consulant Responsibilities: – Participate in technical planning &amp; requirements gathering phases including Design, code, test, troubleshoot, and document engineering software applications. – Ensuring that technical… https://t.co/SyMZnnkTC3 https://t.co/iSO3iVWqDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer w/ PCF: Reply to ************************** with copy of updated resume &amp; best contact Information ASAP. Position: Java Full Stack Developer (Pivotal Cloud Foundry) Location: Dearborn, MI. Duration: 6-12+ months MOI: Phone &amp;… https://t.co/6CTa1JoGro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Security-Analyst—Incident-Response–Lansing–MI: We are hiring an IT Security Analyst to monitor and advise on information security issues related to the systems and workflow at an agency to ensure the internal IT security controls for an agency are… https://t.co/ImSWzXOcCA https://t.co/tbJgf0t1E4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Intern – East Lansing: Job Title: Application Developer Intern – East Lansing Location: East Lansing, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: GreenStone Farm Credit Services Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Feed… https://t.co/vtXjcyV1k7 https://t.co/8oMhyOjBKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunkin' Donuts is officially dropping 'Donuts' https://t.co/t0sU8JwOoS https://t.co/rF8pkGTXG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/cSSd4q7UPo https://t.co/5VrKTYqKnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: A financial services company is seeking a Sr. Software Developer to join their team in Detroit. Requirements: The ability to review business requirements and provide accurate technical feedback. Designing and developing Web Service… https://t.co/6R5w5XcXbm https://t.co/vt7C891zcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL QB questions rules enforced to protect him https://t.co/htfd5J7RMI https://t.co/JcmD19iKi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMM Programmer: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 10 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital company, Flex-N-Gate provides a… https://t.co/G3Hf3xAoaH https://t.co/dtDzFwQfNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louboutin wins fight to prevent red sole copycats https://t.co/ujVGy992pD https://t.co/cK1i5h67tW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer – 1st shift: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 10 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital company,… https://t.co/72GNnmRJDA https://t.co/0XJSVOjX6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst Data Scientist Detroit: **Business Operations Analyst – Data Scientist – Detroit** Locations:Livonia, Michigan Job Family: Sales New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/i4dcrEw9KH https://t.co/r4tlYkNrkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with PCF Experience: Java Developer with PCF Experience Ref No.:18-15685 Location: Dearborn, Michigan Position Type:Contract Start Date: 08/31/2018 Java Developer with PCF Experience Dearborn, MI Contract Detailed JD: Must Have Strong… https://t.co/HJ4Q2kCOmJ https://t.co/J1BGrARTFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the 15 biggest cruise ships in the world: When Symphony of the Seas, an 18-deck cruise ship measuring longer than a nuclear-powered aircraft carrier, sailed out of port for the very first time this April, it smashed yet another size record in… https://t.co/z0V6Cd4T34 https://t.co/IFoVXMU6rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Applications Specialist: Job ID : 78182BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/9rdkKuO1EW https://t.co/mS73mnbt6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Cosby learns today whether he'll go to prison: Bill Cosby will have a final opportunity to make his case to the court on Tuesday before a Pennsylvania judge sentences him on three counts of aggravated indecent assault. https://t.co/J9xOcjoQJI https://t.co/LKUlwXMyHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: We are hiring a Programmer Analyst who Plans, develops, tests, and documents computer programs, applying knowledge of programming techniques and computer systems and serves as a senior analyst in support of applications and business… https://t.co/EgVLgkVvBV https://t.co/K4oRHw6ecb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Functional Support: SAP Functional Support (PP / MM) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering Jobs – Accounting and Finance Jobs –… https://t.co/Tl26z7P8E7 https://t.co/IZDqTDK3Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5485 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=JBBRD_INDEED Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted.… https://t.co/NrSdgMct1q https://t.co/GG8Mx2WwxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell issues Kavanaugh guarantee: Sen. Mitch McConnell (R-KY) says that Brett Kavanaugh will get a vote on the Senate floor amid sexual assault allegations against the Supreme Court nominee. https://t.co/ZnzofaBI58 https://t.co/Ot97WdWUW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Rosenstein is a lightning rod: The New York Times published a blockbuster article (citing anonymous sources) reporting that Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein suggested to other officials within the FBI and Justice Department that he should… https://t.co/BE9H6goddB https://t.co/9EAEjNWJ3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java-Developer: Sr. Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Sr. Java Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software application design, development, testing and deployment utilizing the following: Java, J2EE, API,… https://t.co/ruF3laY5m5 https://t.co/MHPHUzgcxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Breastfeeding better for babies' weight than pumping: Research has already shown a link between breastfeeding and lower obesity risk for babies. But a new study finds another association: "Breast is best" for them even compared with giving babies… https://t.co/ct5zeYc934 https://t.co/CJs9VbtrMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer w/ PCF: Reply to ************************** with copy of updated resume &amp; best contact Information ASAP. Position: Java Full Stack Developer (Pivotal Cloud Foundry) Location: Dearborn, MI. Duration: 6-12+ months MOI: Phone &amp;… https://t.co/Cq4Ks0GMpS https://t.co/8dM3szJmyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developers///only Green Card And Citizens Can Apply: Android developers///Only Green Card and Citizens can apply Michigan Center, Michigan TechnogenInc Jobs Toggle navigation Failure Message Sign In Sign Up Career Portal How to Sign up to career… https://t.co/B25DExAK0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/9MwMxHZ4J4 https://t.co/PYNlHb3ZdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Lead: Career Opportunity: Test Lead- Farmington Hills, MI Are you thrilled to work on the latest in in-dash navigation and services for cars? TomTom s Custom Systems teams are challenging, fast-paced environments where people are empowered to make… https://t.co/qzUFxGBTJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer (MyBiz): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/CkxgIQ2RRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business One Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/2OhozW6Clx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump's global insignificance is about to be exposed: Trump is a master of New York-style showmanship. The United Nations General Assembly, therefore, should be his finest hour: hosting world leaders in his town. https://t.co/3GINv9mBC1 https://t.co/71kuwz5f7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/LKfXhNt8CX https://t.co/G9Zhzc9eJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maintenance PLC Technician: now Maintenance PLC Technician (Hourly) =================================== Company Name: Michigan Dairy Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Non-Exempt Position Summary: Support programming, troubleshooting, calibration,… https://t.co/zLo092V5RE https://t.co/rsWx18ku26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: Connected vehicles and connected navigation is a domain in which many innovations take place at a rapid pace. The System Architect needs to stay current with these innovations and the asset developments in the various TomTom… https://t.co/EJRUDmdsRh https://t.co/VvrQoLI2O8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bourdain on Kenya: 'It's dynamic, it's changing, and it's incredible' https://t.co/NOBO92yQDO https://t.co/g4Gn0CkgyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Intern: About Us… GreenStone Farm Credit Services is over an $8 billion financial services institution with over 500 employees in 36 locations throughout Michigan and northeast Wisconsin. GreenStone provides short term and long… https://t.co/JvmsxXpRXV https://t.co/ntrGtV3E36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Auburn Hills, MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Software Developer The Software Developer is responsible for leading configuration projects on multiple credit application systems used in the end to end… https://t.co/KxUupNy9F2 https://t.co/nqbEeVhTbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Alliance Inspection Management (AiM) is the premier new and pre-owned vehicle inspection partnership in North America that combines breakthrough technology with deep industry experience to provide a trustworthy, independent bridge… https://t.co/erDbVIFfEL https://t.co/Ggk8mhUHgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Gronk threatened to retire to avoid trade https://t.co/WAb71U7ovJ https://t.co/J2EMzy8D2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal In – Building Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… We promise our customers the most reliable coverage across the country, and you’ll make sure we deliver on that promise. You’ll be a technical leader and subject matter… https://t.co/gh2sr5e2NY https://t.co/8ZOPEyXHZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quotation Specialist / Application Sales Engineer: Careers | Grand Power Systems – About – From the CEO – About GTI – What’s New – Press Releases – Product Releases – Contacts – RFQ – Contact Us – Directions – Careers – ************ – Specialty Magnetics… https://t.co/TZjThP5QqU https://t.co/FpfjyMRSYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/xIwoC8AmtU https://t.co/LSGy7SZc1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Syngo Dynamics: Cardiology image review and reporting software: For Siemens Software Engineer – Syngo Dynamics: Cardiology image review and reporting software job – Research &amp; Development – Ann Arbor, Michigan Skip to Main Content – –… https://t.co/krClanr45U https://t.co/B4JqLu7cnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Parts Unknown' enters uncharted territory: As someone most at home in a pair of broken-in jeans and a faded t-shirt, Anthony Bourdain once joked that putting on a suit to go to an awards show felt like making a court appearance. https://t.co/fRJNCUSdhY https://t.co/fFdgHDexXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Technical Lead: Country: United States Work Location: Auburn Hills State: Michigan Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Lead and manage the Software development for Embedded Controls Programs… https://t.co/7JxXoVrQZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Trainer: Global Information Technology is Professional IT training and consulting services corporation that has been in business since 1999. Global Information Technology committed to providingstudents with the necessary skills and attitudes to… https://t.co/tRURAlR0Fb https://t.co/xhkVsM0nUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Center for Autonomous Vehicle Development – AV Sensor Performance Engineer: Center for Autonomous Vehicle Development – AV Sensor Performance Engineer – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home… https://t.co/UVyytkY7mT https://t.co/tbMkrjoUIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Intern: About Us… GreenStone Farm Credit Services is over an $8 billion financial services institution with over 500 employees in 36 locations throughout Michigan and northeast Wisconsin. GreenStone provides short term and long… https://t.co/lbT1wpXCW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Open Dealer Exchange, an affiliate of Reynolds and Reynolds, is looking for a Database Administrator with broad database knowledge and experience to join our team. The role of the MS SQL database administrator is to proactively… https://t.co/KB4kCYe4BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Job ID : 73348BR Location : US – Michigan – Kalamazoo : Job Description Position Summary: This Technical and Software Support Representative will be primarily responsible for supporting Technical Support, LIS… https://t.co/xWHJuPHeEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Applications Specialist: Job ID : 78182BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/hQc65YH1xL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>