<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ultshanator @JonHeyman 10/5 rights, plus I bet he would want the club to pick up his option..and that might screw the deal right there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman I would do that deal with the Cardinals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaysfan9293 @JonHeyman Well that's the question..sell what?  Our pending free agents won't get us much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david_draper10 @kdog_NL @JonHeyman Pipe dreams favourite argument?  Anything can happen.. lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdog_NL @JonHeyman I don't need the false hope of a second wild card spot to prevent a perfect opportunity that would benefit this franchise for the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheToughBretts @thejaysnation @AndrewStoeten Positives!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdog_NL @JonHeyman So you expect the Jays to play 20 games above .500 ball in the second half?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman They can't disrupt the "awakened fanbase" has been the narrative lately.  Well if they keep losing it will happen anyways.  Sell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Enjoy your break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregorMLB Keep playing like this and they won't have to worry about the "awakened fan base" from 2015 till now.  They'll be gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Jays fans who showed up in 2015 https://t.co/PpFu34qmr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Shades of Vernon Wells putting up numbers when the game was out of reach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Rebuild and piss off a fanbase that has come out since 2015
Continue with this group, wallowing in mediocrity, slowing lose that fanbase.hmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 If there was ever a day to tune into Jays therapy, it will be today.  Can't wait Mike lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Why are people even entertaining trading a young 2b that's often injured.  What MLB team takes that on right now? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Cry because we don't sign free agents, also cry that we over payed when they don't perform.
LF - injuries to Alford and Dalton didn't help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ To suddenly lose command and issue so many walks in a short stretch.. wondered if his back flared up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Can't live and die on every game in a baseball season.  You'll drive yourself nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Quite a few blowouts in a short stretch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro While taking a series against arguably the best team in the AL is encouraging, the Jays need to string together more the a few series wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 @FAN590 Everyone back on the bandwagon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevenbanks17 @ari_shapiro @BlueJays Feast or famine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro  https://t.co/SgZuXyjzLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Jk lol hopefully this offence gets going for real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Its like that partner you threaten to break up with,suddenly they start acting like it used to be, but we all know it doesn't last for long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Hopefully this isn't a tease job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheScaryNature: This is how the heart of a shark beats https://t.co/BTlRFQbuY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Prospect porn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro So is this what Shapiro means by "window of competitiveness"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baseball_Jenn Maybe a fastball in the butt might clear up this misunderstanding between teams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mauerback @Wilnerness590 At least they can do that well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Too bad we aren't good right now.  It would be a nice rivalry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I'm curious what the big Dome renovation will entail..though I wish the team would be instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Relax everyone, Wilner says it's still early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Nothing a deadline trade won't help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro We used to destroy high fastballs.. seems so long ago :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydpparsons @ari_shapiro Imagine they blew it up knowing full well the dome was basically sold out in sept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydpparsons @ari_shapiro Yup.. the business of baseball trumps all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydpparsons @ari_shapiro I'm dedicated,  just share a longer term view then most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro The sacrifices we make for more home runs ;p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Just no blisters please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HunterAtkins35 Can we stop with the no emotion, robot style "old school" baseball bullshit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mav_five @Ken_Rosenthal Moving Donaldson and Haap would set us up nicely (theoretically)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mav_five @Ken_Rosenthal Difference is you had a wealth of talent ready to take over.  Jays only have 2 worth a damn and they are 3 years away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN https://t.co/HYAu4p6llq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Russian headlines is big $$$ for CNN..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mav_five @Ken_Rosenthal Agree 100%. But when a media company owns the team, selling hope to keep butts in the seats is more important then realistic opportunities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal Selling just enough hope to keep the fans in the seats and watching on tv..but not enough reality to contend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks @ScottyMacThinks crowds are great but will they be here in two seasons if this team stays the way they are now?  And we missed an opptunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @jgoldstrass Lol, I know rebuilds aren't a guarantee..or free agent retools for that matter..the big club performing to their career averages solves it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @jgoldstrass Good discussion.  Fair and logical... still doesn't put my mind at ease :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @jgoldstrass I'll listen now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Good question I heard on the radio just now, is the business of baseball hindering what the Jays can do moving forward?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro And just pathetically wallowing in the bottom third of the league pretending to have a shot at the 2nd wildcard for 4 months of a seaon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I don't want them to a field a team of aging fan favourites based on ratings and "the awakening of baseball fans" ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro It is a loaded question, especially when you factor in the owner being in the media business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Seriously, ask yourself, what does this team do well, average and what are they absolutely terrible at?  Then you'll have your answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Yankees had been struggling almost as bad as the Jays recently.  Something had to give between the two teams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Does InfoWars have a sports reporter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buster_ESPN do you think it would be a mistake for the Jays not to get ahead of this rebuild instead of "retooling" a slow old core?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRiccio590 (3)..division.. AL East and it's dead last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRiccio590 (2)..like the Phillies back 2010 and on.. against core they kept adding to only to finish 3rd with the Mets, Marlins and Braves in their ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRiccio590 I think rebuild talk steams from the fear that if we don't get ahead of it, we stand a chance at turning out ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 (2). Cubs philosophy or just the best player at the time and see where the chips fall with development?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 draft question.. while the pervious regime drafted pitchers predominantly, is there a focus on position players.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fortaustins @Wilnerness590 Lmao Leaf fans making baseball trades again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luluhop @Wilnerness590 Classic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 So a .500 team :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro You can play small ball all you want, but it doesn't get runs home (squeeze bunts not included)..hitting with risp does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Knack for scoring clutch goals.  Rebuild is over apparently.  Let's get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RapSheet @buffalobills should trade McCoy to the Cowboys :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro @JaysJournal I heard Shapiro talked about renovations for the dome today. Any details?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Wasn't he benched recently?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Sanchez.  Future Yankee 1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyStewart10 @DRUDGE_REPORT That series is such a slow burn.. he was fantastic though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheChadSmith2 @MLB Scum bag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanHirsch Advanced metrics have him doing into in 3.5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Definitely have confidence on paper...😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Pat Hentgen. Starting pitching was a strength last season, debatably the reason for making the playoffs. This year it's been a liability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch Is it me or the kids just big these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baseball_Jenn What did I miss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Heard his weight is down significantly since the start of the season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Based on this series, I bet Houston is loving that Liriano deal right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Lol nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueJaysAddict Working out of that jam is a huge confidence boost that's been missing.  Kudos to Gibby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro What's the metric stat called for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I wonder how many home run derby winners followed up with a second half slump?  Or am I crazy to even suggest it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten @gabelerman Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabelerman @AndrewStoeten What about the ACC?  Leafs and Raps have designated, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabelerman @AndrewStoeten Good point.  Hopefully it's on the list for the incoming renovation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten It would be cool to have a Blue Jays hall of fame somewhere in the dome..if they don't already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten how many players constitutes a core to build around?  Should position variety play a role?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DumaraosC @AtheistRepublic Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billclinton @BarackObama Is balloon a code word like pizza?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillDixonish Can't be an atheist and run for president.  The sheep would never vote for him.  Look at Sanders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AstrosRants: Wanna hear a Rougned Odor joke?
Here it is then:
Rougned Odor plays on a Major League Baseball team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrySoetoroESQ @oneredpaperclip @ArianaManchestr @malo_j @mr85009 @zalphaprime @FlatEarthCity @djboptics Meow https://t.co/aoAsfUEkoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@everythingbbird If the Jays just want to compete and not contend next year, sure..pick up his option and hopefully that's his finally swan song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Finish the year strong.  Give some kids a look.  Enjoy Bautista's final two months.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>