<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/blHmNymu3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/IY4dhfdtFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/2ZLQJH2LkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/xSWGcUMIW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TLNrVz3I1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/3kB1K7x8OZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/YXe3kEoMyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/G4d6Mhlgnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/h6rITzVPio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/XY0yhOPdZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/0Drfb2yQez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/FxFLyI05hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/9s3NOTBztV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/i7M2tYrohL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kYtMpaD9wI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/yIRQAPe76L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/fupjgBtlLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/FGy4Qpiyna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/xrKGeyD8Q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/ZYcx2HXmSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/OYXVYidoh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/3zUKdKxYRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/GpwIYBVXgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/NH5npGoBcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/vznqdgIoWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/MqdWnv9Vn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/stIUnku6HG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/XTttYwK3br]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/2rmRwKaoZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/XZEes8jjOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/mvfMPkfrT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/JYpTkDJgQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/Op2UUsu9vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to get thin is to re-establish a purpose in life. - Cyril Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/BXNIaXGUDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/Eush6aFxwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/MUtTjJIHDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/gVQNtj0ZiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/zoML3R3KmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/qjVtWsrPJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/3eUDEOooEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/qTNwysFgG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/QHWEvQznxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/fAgoDBeP2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/day9ElW6Bo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/9abQcp6qjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/WTIOdYCVjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/lr3KgnDNwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/ekLhSLe9fE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>