<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/hB50UOfMfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/x3qaqObeJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/QvpXZo6YQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/DjTAylYV3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/HJF0vIZP7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/zR3Au9fzQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/XixVuFScRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/u8NQnM0KfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work is the presentation of our capabilities. - Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/nsHMg1h9q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Introduction to Ray Bradbury  http://t.co/ig6OoXDL9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/WAyZ3ffvBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/wSntA3bvlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/OcKnsoXRmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/Y9cz1V8Suu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/RIc1XULS9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/Ljqp0RSBZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/ejBfhg2hhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/3cE4LmQJOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/zqfvPal88b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/ymPKzZ4a4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/aYKGcZ1rTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/89GliTQdbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/8ncvnKD8HO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/9YA7elinO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/5mmEXYkMoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/fUP09ytPed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/jRpZG0j3fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/eWyxrbc5xO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/5RA8xD5Idy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/fDY9qP6jxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/URuVstThzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/qgChS95aAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/5IK4vDgP5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/xl9ia5en0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/XlAsvJR1ay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/xIboyngPA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/4KpmA6FtTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/3KfniseGs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/s78HVN2iMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/6esav6TfCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/PPRERSa7Da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/HQYpBJe3pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/czS6dYYrWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/FZQjx0uPBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/RjRIrX73PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/t41ePdarXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/Zt7WRBCekr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>