<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just took a #TellyBreak to enter my work in this year's @TellyAwards. http://t.co/bsuqpnPpht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For YOU too! http://t.co/qPcqdmq43Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 700 Club with Kenneth Copeland - April 28, 2015 | http://t.co/K7u8kHuTHR (beta) http://t.co/UFJ35YdVDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all my NFL football fans that are also my gospel music fans. Terry Bradshaw sings with The Isaacs! http://t.co/WuAmUQTtOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on out to Eagle Mountain Church! http://t.co/a5oSdZyYf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HE IS RISEN!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is! Watch the Blood Moons Special right here! http://t.co/5MhpLldC0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resurrection Sunday this weekend! Enjoy! http://t.co/Koa8xfJOBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this Friday night on http://t.co/P0Ggpx7Z6U at 8pm CDT http://t.co/MZo8b3s6jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make plans to watch this TV Special I just recorded with Pastor Mark Biltz! http://t.co/oH36GUt92F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Great Is Our God! In Hebrew and in English...Enjoy! http://t.co/XndkJVZKTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will shake all the nations, and the treasures of all the nations will be brought to this Temple. I will fill... http://t.co/xDE1GY13wa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[July is MIRACLE MONTH! http://t.co/7jOh8lvzrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Eagle Mountain Worship https://t.co/AizCVOhRFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Phil Driscoll LIVE at SWBC! https://t.co/TlrDcD7Jtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we celebrate our Founding Fathers declaration of our Day of Independence! What about the rest of us now?... http://t.co/8oxuZFGmgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: SWBC 2015! https://t.co/SGxIzP1R0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! Check out my official UNO site @ http://t.co/2YPf19BOYy. It’s my complete identity online. Follow me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Bailey (Haslet, Texas) - My UNO Site @ http://t.co/2YPf19Tqn8 http://t.co/uyl2JagLcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed "A Night of Miracles" with Living Rivers Millenial church this week! More pics from the healing line to... http://t.co/nCe24Daecq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I call heaven and earth to record this day against you, that I have set before you life and death, blessing and... http://t.co/m198xl0T3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff here at #SWBC2015!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the Spirit who gives life; the flesh profits nothing. The words that I speak to you are spirit, and they are life.  (John 6:63 NKJV)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the 1940's the Marine Air Corps Station had their Base hospital in the very spot Eagle Eagle Mountain Church... http://t.co/nbjn19QYQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the hardest things for me to learn... http://t.co/5vtEhra6sV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destiny! http://t.co/6BddCswmiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering today.... #NARA http://t.co/2yi9g3WabU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no boundaries to healing! http://t.co/BsSBkpPruo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Sounds of miracles https://t.co/XHFhrl72Bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BishopJakes: Your FAITH moves God, rebukes the devil, rebukes diseases, gives you courage, access promises! http://t.co/tOCAJo0ymx http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He sent out his word and healed them, snatching them from the door of death. (Psalms 107:20 NLT)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For in him we live, and move, and have our being; as certain also of your own poets have said, For we are also his offspring.
Acts 17:28 KJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For in him we live, and move, and have our being; as certain also of your own poets have said, For we are also his offspring.
Acts17:28 KJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/b3xYaijVs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allow the Word of God to change you! https://t.co/DAft0LYUjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep calm and still believe in your miracle! http://t.co/YmSZF93KGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is prayer your steering wheel or your spare tire? http://t.co/OqiljnPnpb http://t.co/F1SMpiaQaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking this Sunday at Victorious Life Church in Conyers, GA!
Join me as we live in the... http://t.co/f1xkMlrxuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The LORD replied, “Listen, I am making a covenant with you in the presence of all your people. I will perform... http://t.co/UgAT6SZgSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest! The dishes will wait!
http://t.co/OqiljnPnpb http://t.co/AcMcBdx1iW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgiveness, a vital key to your healing! http://t.co/dnGTBVV1AW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["History will be kind to me for I intend to write it."
~ Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take some time to read a pastor friend of mine's book on The Blessing. I especially enjoyed reading about Jim's... http://t.co/7k7KObT7Jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[***SCAM ALERT***
Do NOT accept a friend request from a ministry page posing as me. It is NOT me and I am not... http://t.co/DN9zeQnGX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a video from my wonderful wife Teri. Watch as she reveals more about living from the heart! http://t.co/M61f8GA8QT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Love is patient and kind. Love is not jealous or boastful or proud or rude. It does not demand its own way. It... http://t.co/uPmWODEKCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved doing church with Mark Hankins this week! http://t.co/kAGU91O8Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honor to lead service today with Kenneth Copeland Eagle Mountain Church! http://t.co/1Wz9gRs6u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MartianMovie: Help is only 140 million miles away. Watch the new trailer for #TheMartian, in theaters Oct. 2. #BringHimHome
https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crux of Jesus' message wasn't about world evangelism, changing the world or the reality of hell. He simply... http://t.co/RvKU8Boe2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revival History flashback:

W.E. SANGSTER 
(1900-1960)
William E. Sangster was one of the great British Methodist... http://t.co/26Rkal2WY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Don’t you realize that in a race everyone runs, but only one person gets the prize? So run to win! All athletes... http://t.co/CjBNgVfPQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracle Month!! http://t.co/7TL3FnG7pE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Great is the Lord, and greatly to be praised; and his greatness is unsearchable.”
Psalms 145:3 KJV https://t.co/MLer6pvv9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good input. Always remember though to keep honesty and integrity in ALL your communication! https://t.co/5slC5vSw8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philmunsey: Never met anyone who didn't need encouragement. I don't pose or impose, but even "successful" people need it.
#encourageMEA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Lessons From The World's Fastest Growing Congregation https://t.co/vPmGil8Idd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You will be secure under a government that is just and fair. Your enemies will stay far away. You will live in... https://t.co/SRmscPWkLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dallascowboys: Almost GO TIME! #DALvsWAS https://t.co/OWVBpL0jNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Believe!! #WFAACowboys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing song by this 10 year old. "I Look to You"
https://t.co/OqiljnxM0B https://t.co/sb1dkpA40I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always use your faith for the miraculous but make using your faith for God's abiding presence on your life  the priority!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Neither skill nor knowledge is needed to go to God, he added. All that is necessary is a heart dedicated... https://t.co/5bY47YhUPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sweetheart https://t.co/kvMB7tIojq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which scripture should you read at the Thanksgiving dinner today? Watch and find out!  
Happy Thanksgiving to all... https://t.co/Nqi2r7Fih4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Einstein on the presence of Jesus. https://t.co/QhtCy5DjOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God Bless America. https://t.co/lMngxS6hmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted my notes from the 4 classes I recently taught on
 "How You Can Be Led By the Holy Spirit" in the Notes... https://t.co/9AHaGkBB7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be Led By the Holy Spirit #4 https://t.co/SX9MBOvi7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be Led By the Holy Spirit #3 https://t.co/WUfCDVW8AB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be Led By the Holy Spirit #2 https://t.co/6TRNktTNU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be Led By the Holy Spirit #1 https://t.co/6DFhk9bVFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is Lord! https://t.co/FQxAIxkCXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would the church look like? https://t.co/gjd4Oz20tX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have an appetite for the IMPOSSIBLE! https://t.co/2XFUqXUK1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John G Lake...what a heritage we have! https://t.co/PtjdtgxR8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azusa Street 1907 https://t.co/9y6oE70JOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I declare! https://t.co/a7D1XXaRkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sickness is NOT the will of God!
https://t.co/OqiljnxM0B https://t.co/n3FIodcXYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting perspective. Thoughts? https://t.co/QaX4YRfvNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's name is not "I Was".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Radtke bringing it @MnstryInstitute  #MIGlobal16 https://t.co/rxBEL9Mx7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming to Wales! https://t.co/CBpRzSQtbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great halftime show!  #PepsiHalftime #SB50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh...#SB50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016: The Winds of Change! https://t.co/iSyRx3Ve11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Part 2 Pastor John Kilpatrick shares in detail the day the revival broke in Pensacola. Story after story of... https://t.co/w6ILXc4xMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Part 1 of Brownsville Revival Stories Pastor John Kilpatrick shares personal stories from his past! Listen for... https://t.co/oWIkaXHZgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Message to the World by Evan Roberts

THE Power of the revival in South Wales is not of men, but of God. He has... https://t.co/1r8Jog2Ekx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the God of great wonders! You demonstrate your awesome power among the nations. Psalms 77:14 NLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BerniceRich Always nice to hear when your words make sense! @thetimshow @DonniePetty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! https://t.co/DycfkaVZGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope https://t.co/17CghC9KhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us in Wales March 6-7! https://t.co/KS4YDiJKxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! https://t.co/B7tAmMZ0TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are not going to move this world by criticism of it nor conformity to it; but by the combustion within it of... https://t.co/kdnWr8DcpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your giving immunizes you against covetousness. ~Jesse DuPlantis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first belly buttons? https://t.co/wv61eTwDvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you compromise to keep you will eventually lose."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Sing, O childless woman, you who have never given birth! Break into loud and joyful song, O Jerusalem, you who... https://t.co/52XoFKHyIX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>