<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, I talk to other guys but I don't talk to them like the way I talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I confess that I'm starting to like you, would you do it too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird how you say that you hate the person who broke your heart. But when they run back to you, your arms are wide open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving him wasn't the mistake...thinking he loved me was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actions prove who someone is, words just prove who they want to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll keep my head up and smile, just because I know you want to see me fall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact is that I love you. I love your imperfections, and the parts of you that are nearly perfect. I love all of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of the days spent on this planet Earth. I've found one thing that is wroth the tears, struggle, pain, heartache, breath, and that is... you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feeling you get when you find the perfect song that describes how you're feeling at that exact moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's impossible to give your heart to someone when the last person you gave it to doesn't return and is still breaking it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, you can t reach for what s in front of you until you let go of what s behind you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is such a big word, it really should have more letters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some say that love is a hoax but deep down they still believe. There's still a glimmer of hope that allows them to build new relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your dreams turn to dust, vacuum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wished I had cherished you better when you were mine, but it's all too late now.. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physically we're miles apart but mentally you're in my heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can change a person but someone can be the reason for a person to change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I try to do my homework twitter just happens to interrupt and throws off my focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never chase them, quickly replace them. Mistakes? Nahh, I don't retrace them. I just move on and mentally erase them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brick by brick, we started crumbling Will I find you when it falls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it's love when your feelings don't leave even if the person does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don t like me, remember that it s mind over matter. I don t mind and you don t matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take someone for who they are, not who you think they should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lust is wanting to sleep with someone. Love is wanting to wake up next to them in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say when you meet the ONE you just know, well what if they don't just know back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to enter a relationship is with your eyes wide open and your heart slightly ajar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgiveness is the first step you have to take to begin healing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I like you. How about you, do you like me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you have to wait for something, the more you will appreciate it when it finally arrives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best accident I've ever had was... when I fell for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difference between promises and memories We break promises, and our memories break us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy: Do you have any raisins Girl:No Boy: How about a date s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a soul mate, just not everyone finds them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that feeling you get when you're on a roller coaster Well I get that feeling whenever I see you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let your past dictate who you are, but let it be a part of who you will become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss you. But I am not going to start the conversation unless you talk to me first. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when so many people have hurt you and there's that one person you want to trust but you just cant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know we re friends, lets be more. I can t stop thinking about you, I can t stop thinking of what else could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to understand how to live through the worst parts of life so you never take the best parts for granted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a line between caring &amp; interfering. There's a line between trying &amp; forcing. There's a line between loving &amp; controlling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just waiting to see who is going to walk out of my life next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Giant Spider On The Wall, Please die. Please die. Please die. Please die. CRAP! Where did you go Sincerely, Terrified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After awhile, waiting gets boring. Your crush doesn't seem so attractive anymore, and you realize you need to stop wasting your time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the hardest person to forgive, is yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at your chest, a little to the left. There's where I will always be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bigger the explanation, the bigger the lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday we will meet again. When we have our second chance at love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave you my heart, you gave me your lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty isn't about having a pretty face, it's about having a pretty mind, a pretty heart, and a pretty soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once u've been hurt, u're so scared to get attached again. U have this fear that every person u start to fall for is going to break ur heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't treat me like #2 when I'm treating you like my #1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopeless romantics are only hopeless in the eyes of those who don't believe in romance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to talk to you for awhile. I need you to miss me. I need you to appreciate having me in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What lies before, and what lie behind us, are tiny matters compared to what lies within us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have your chance, say what you want, because second chances are really rare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I see you everyday I fall in love all over again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try to expect nothing, but be open for anything. Don't look for happiness, but don't settle for anything less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know exactly what to say to make me feel like everyone else is lying and you're the only thing thats true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some people in life that make you laugh a little louder, smile a little bigger and live just a little bit better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No comment" usually translates into "Oh, if you only knew."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things happen in a flash, and you can never change the fact that it happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, it's just impossible to please everyone. So stop living for others &amp; start living for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish I could go back and change what happened between us...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything I like is either illegal, immoral, fattening, addictive, expensive, or impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly boy, when are you going to realize I'm crying because I'm in love with you and I know I can never have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heart wants most what the heart can't have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the male, I'm the female. You text me first. End of story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The harder you fall, the higher you bounce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't make things easier. It just makes them worth fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls have their insecurities and boys have their egos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a weakness, but I have two. Everything you say and everything you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you like waffles :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-Wakes up feeling refreshed- *Looks at alarm clock*, AM. *Goes back into deep sleep* .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing for the impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m the type of girl who can be so hurt but still look at you &amp; smile and is willing to brighten your day even if I can t brighten my own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart have been in bits and pieces, but I gave you the best of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For us girls, the little things matter, just as much, if not more, than the big things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I text you, that means I miss you. When I don't text, that just means I'm waiting for you to miss me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thosefriendsthat you can just see yourself with when your  raising hell in the retirement home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never matters how you met, if you love each other enough to try to make it work, it will work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1If all you see is problems, maybe it s time to adjust the direction you re looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a humble person, really. I'm actually much greater than I think I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A boy gave a girl roses: real ones and one fake one. He said, "I'll love you until the last rose dies."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People change. And sometimes they change to another side which you are totally unfamiliar with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish you would just swallow your pride for once and admit that you really do miss me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for always being there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said "I ll love you forever.".... Who knew forever ended so fast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's easier to pretend you don't care, than to admit it's killing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretending that I don't miss you makes me miss you even more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life stops when you stop dreaming, hope ends when you stop believing, love ends when you stop caring, friendship ends when you stop sharing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry I mistook all our laughs, long nights, sweet texts and inside jokes as you caring. I'll think twice before wasting my time again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and you can do anything or nothing and have the best time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2We all have that one friend that loves to embarrass themselves and you in public, but you wouldn t trade for anything in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say when you die your life flashes before your eyes. Make it worth watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you see your ex and you don't know whether you should say "Hi" or just ignore their presence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need an instruction manual, I'm perfectly capable of screwing it up without printed help, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not that we aren't meant to be together, I think that we're just not ready for forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know how good you are at something until you try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just need to forget about the boy who forgot about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing in life is finding someone who knows all of your flaws, mistakes, and weaknesses and still thinks you re completely amazing.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>