<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life. -Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mother_know: Sleep mode on! :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/oEqapFSxSF https://t.co/BmIpktQb5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of complaining about your circumstances, get busy and create some new ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SMALL changes can make a BIG difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Look who's staring back at you https://t.co/X2V7ijjTK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership is not about titles, positions or flow charts; it is about one life influencing another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And whether or not it is clear to you, no doubt the world is unfolding as it should. -Desiderata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time changes everything. https://t.co/4ITpfIFM4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is never a better measure of what a person is than what he does when he's absolutely free to choose. - William M. Bulger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fill your mind with truth, your heart with love, your life with service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things turn out best for those who make the best out of the way things turn out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would you attempt to do if you knew you could not fail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good instincts tell you what to do long before your head has figured it out. - Michael Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather be a failure in something that I love than a success in something that I hate. -George Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing could be better :) https://t.co/KrEy7On4B6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want something different You Gotta do something different. - Nathaniel Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace meets us where we are, but doesn't leave us where we are found.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If through a broken heart God can bring His purposes to pass in the world, then thank Him for breaking your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't take life to seriously :) https://t.co/lmDH3Ng4Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen:
- Every day.
- To everyone.
The difference is in how people deal with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_HQ: Sound like a great plan :)

Get your hiking tee here --&gt; https://t.co/TtvbpwmWHS https://t.co/ZjyQ7k1Lw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of happiness is to count your blessings while others are adding up their troubles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone you will ever meet knows something you don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thought. https://t.co/Gquds96ngG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be happy not because everything is good, but because you can see the good side of everything. #optimism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray hardest when it is hardest to pray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomanDoItAll: Do you follow this rule? ;)

Get your pink tee here --&gt; https://t.co/VKFBowk8JQ https://t.co/xSgbXRwP7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth above all else. https://t.co/DZRpVvt5dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand disappointments in the past cannot equal the power of one positive action right now. Go ahead &amp; go for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude. -Dr. Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like photography - develop from the negatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True. https://t.co/tXOeU3wZxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The art of being wise is knowing what to overlook. -William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline is just choosing between what you want now and what you want most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love &amp; kindness move mountains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending… :) https://t.co/1GLdMcBeWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born with the ability to change someone's life - don't ever waste it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I BELIEVE IN BEING STRONG WHEN EVERYTHING SEEMS TO BE GOING WRONG. - Audrey Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't sit back and let things happen to you. Go out and happen to things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live is to short to take it seriously. https://t.co/9IT9axWDk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every saint has a past.
Every sinner has a future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things worth having are worth waiting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be courageous https://t.co/hUA4lvQ73S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every minute you are angry you lose 60 seconds of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile is the lighting system of the face, the cooling system of the head and the heating system of the heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count your blessings, not your problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to be irreplaceable, one must always be different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: If you don't believe in yourself, no one else will!

Get this inspirational tee here --&gt; https://t.co/6zrU9KROdY https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most reliable way to predict the future is to create it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mother_know: In that order! :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/NERh9Ed2bO https://t.co/MQtymBkSBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this thought. https://t.co/HjFFBrGpz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually all things fall into place. Until then, laugh at the confusion, live for the moments, and know everything happens for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to have it all figured out to move forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't let praise or criticism get to you. It's a weakness to get caught up in either one. -John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You deserve it :) https://t.co/St88KTkTep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find someone who will change your life, not just your status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being powerful is like being a lady. If you have to tell people you are, you aren't. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know the key to success, but the key to failure is trying to please everybody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best advice I've ever heard. https://t.co/mNNhhjvXyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let someone else's opinion of you become your reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you must decide exactly what you want to accomplish, then resolve to pay the price to get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You become what you believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about breaking our personal limits and outgrowing ourselves to live our best lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree! https://t.co/UrwGWaVnSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what comes up in my life, I know that 'This too, will pass'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind yourself that you don't have to do what everyone else is doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't go back to yesterday - because I was a different person then. - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak. Courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude: recognize the good in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look back when you know you shouldn't.
Don't stress over things that don't matter.
Don't worry about thinks you can't control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[forgive others not because they deserve it but because you deserve peace. https://t.co/HDBH4dUdj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll never leave where you are until you decide where you'd rather be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: It has begun... :)

Get your t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/bx1KmQXxxU https://t.co/wnINB4IMMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mother is a person who seeing there are only 4 pieces of pie for 5 people, announces she never did care for pie. - Tenneva Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from the past, prepare for the future, and perform in the moment. - Mike Van Hoozer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be beautiful. https://t.co/R139ys17Pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those that talk down to you are just trying to walk tall by making u feel small. Rise above]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone you meet has something to teach you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with those who see greatness in you, even when you don't see it in yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man's like, take a good look at how he treats his inferiors, not his equals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do, not what you say you'll do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's more fun than doing what people say you can't do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has ever made himself great by showing how small someone else is. - Irvin Himmel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every good thing that has happened in your life happened because something changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree, it will live it's whole life believing it is stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank your past for all the lessons, and move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God sometimes takes us into troubled waters not to drown us, but to cleanse us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: How did you know? 😊

Get this pawesome T-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/9cSVPmuyBV https://t.co/HA2htu50cY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the first step in faith. You don't have to see the whole staircase, just take the first step.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignore the fear and push on. https://t.co/cEVK6cVBO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What worries you masters you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment means staying loyal to what you said you were going to do, long after the mood you said it in has left you. #commitment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A happy person is not a person in a certain set of circumstances, but rather a person with a certain set of attitudes. -Hugh Downs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell someone they matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you do matters, but why you do it matters so much more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worry is a down payment on a problem you may never have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our experiences shape us.  Appreciate them, for you wouldn't be the person you are without them. https://t.co/Gj9mnjxIlO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>