<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[10 US cities that could gain the most from smart city infrastructure https://t.co/6SF0TPrF9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect more IOT attacks in 2018 https://t.co/9kOzA0LwUS by @ITWeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers find another smart toy that's easy to hack https://t.co/NnGOzHsvLN by @danielwcooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What keeps business executives awake at night? 
Securing your (and your customers’) data, and Seamless and secure digital experiences https://t.co/lWiGHQw7f6 by @Telstra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast’s new xFi Advanced Gateway router could be a smart-home hub - Business Insider https://t.co/Rw5Uq4jg3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 million banking app users at risk https://t.co/fqZc9TxEWb by @NatTechNews https://t.co/RcwMXqYIP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT Spending On Track To Pass $1 Trillion 12/08/2017 https://t.co/x6rZnPCT1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Christmas Shopping: Beware Of Fake Apps &amp; Data Theft - Information Security Buzz https://t.co/a88Mevvxqy by @Info_Sec_Buzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satori IoT botnet with zero-day powers and over 280,000 bots in 12 hours. Protect your IoT devices NOW https://t.co/LpPTv52JqW by @DeviceAuthority @rao_cherukuri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT can help smart cities solve major traffic problems, Latest Views News - The New Paper https://t.co/a5HhB2mt4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Register now to attend our webinar: Delivering Trust for IoT with HSMs https://t.co/6EaVM16ZFL https://t.co/A74RfrHvXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meow! Facial recognition reaches pet doors https://t.co/BWDCrvMuk2 by @NakedSecurity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally some decent new trains on South West trains. Immediate impact by new operator. Well done,  they are great!! @SW_Railway https://t.co/dI731n7TAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five key trends to watch in 2018 as cybercriminals continue to innovate - Help Net Security https://t.co/KIetUJyWsz by @helpnetsecurity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satori IoT botnet with zero-day powers and over 280,000 bots in 12 hours. Protect your IoT devices NOW https://t.co/evoj08WfKz by @DeviceAuthority @rao_cherukuri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Internet of Things Impacts Health IT Infrastructure https://t.co/GyD93keHfi by @HITInfrastruct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Senate bill would require jail time for data breach cover ups https://t.co/qvkjhXsta9 by @scmagazineuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten IoT predictions for 2018 from Cisco’s Maciej Kranz https://t.co/JFnAeflpde by @InternetofBiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Areas The IoT Will Impact You Without Your Even Knowing https://t.co/Kvgq3J05gI by @danielnewman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security and costs holding back those looking to implement IoT projects - Help Net Security https://t.co/C9e4TPX4KN by @helpnetsecurity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Joins the IoT Security Foundation Executive Steering Board https://t.co/BtNXtgtOks by @PRNewswire @IoT_SF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you attending BIOMEDevice Expo today in San Jose? @DeviceAuthority will be there to discuss medical device security. Contact us to set up a meeting: https://t.co/6CbUdUIHO0 https://t.co/Xda4igpWJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Yahoo and Equifax hacks, cybersecurity goes mainstream https://t.co/k0oqPicm2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey Shows US Cybersecurity Attacks Costing Orgs More Money https://t.co/ot0irjj7br by @SecurityHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The installed base of wireless IoT devices in agriculture reached 17.0 million in 2016 https://t.co/SOVnQwYdYj by @iotnow_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @DeviceAuthority Executive Chairman @AlbertSisto is speaking about Cybersecurity &amp; Privacy at tomorrow's event 'Connecting the Dots: U.S. and International Issues and Regulatory Developments on Connected Cars/Autonomous Vehicles' in Washington DC. https://t.co/2fIKU3NViG https://t.co/nBuMr9ezf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently @fbnilsen is showing a demo using @PTC @ThingWorx AlwaysOn with @DeviceAuthority extension for securing an Industrial machine #IoTSF2017 @IoT_SF https://t.co/oAPGyWoKwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applied IoT Security for Healthcare and Industrial at #IoTSF2017 conference. @IoT_Lockers going through various use cases where robust security is required and how to do it. There's no tricks - we take the pain out of IoT security for our partners and customers. @IoT_SF https://t.co/gtptyWPW3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 IoT security trends to expect in 2018 https://t.co/8ubgmIw78p by @Brian_Buntz @iotinews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you attending BIOMEDevice Expo on Wednesday in San Jose? @DeviceAuthority will be there to discuss medical device security at Silicon Valley's premier Medtech showcase. Contact us to set up a meeting: https://t.co/sVggdaSUKw https://t.co/UFRXnpYOMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Technology Mega Trends That Will Change The World In 2018 https://t.co/dHQDhl6fyl by @bernardmarr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Whether in healthcare, auto industry, agriculture or appliances in the home environment, IoT devices generate an unprecedented amount of data, which – as in the case of the blood sugar monitor – is often of a sensitive and personal nature” says Gartner https://t.co/zZIibAPipk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you ‘suitably paranoid’ about your home devices’ cybersecurity? https://t.co/Qo6iRsHsAe by @financialpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @DeviceAuthority at the annual @IoT_SF conference in London on December 5th. Hear from @IoT_Lockers on Applied IoT Security for Healthcare and Industrial. Other speakers include @intel @Thalesesecurity @PenTestPartners @IBM + more. Register now: https://t.co/tRzUIGiPjL https://t.co/IToCnsvJYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Securing the IoT takes strategic investment https://t.co/iPyJcRs7lQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Slow Ride in the First Self-Driving Chevy Bolt https://t.co/FTWyyCZ5pl by @technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Over half of all IoT devices will live in connected spaces' https://t.co/zNY2bfOo5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @DeviceAuthority at the annual @IoT_SF conference in London on December 5th. Hear from @IoT_Lockers on Applied IoT Security for Healthcare and Industrial. Other speakers include @intel @Thalesesecurity @PenTestPartners @IBM + more. Register now: https://t.co/oVlzhLNGjk https://t.co/cWQ7hT4kLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity: A Marketer's Problem? 11/30/2017 https://t.co/iXdVkUVVVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good guidance for first steps in IoT security, but speak with @DeviceAuthority if you need robust, automated security for critical verticals like Healthcare and Industrial!

Don't let poor IoT security turn your devices against you https://t.co/iI0udLnTPZ by @iotagenda https://t.co/N1VHXsrQu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet manufacturers who are monetising the IIoT today - hear from @DeviceAuthority on securing your infrastructure, @PTC on the new manufacturing &amp; service journeys of the IoT and @InVMA_IoT on new methods that are changing the environment https://t.co/lsOdPcsCk8 #IoT #Industrial https://t.co/UaJdsH75XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top 3 hot spots for federal IoT security https://t.co/dGUPJllXE4 by @csoonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak password settings leave IoT devices vulnerable to attack https://t.co/ADZEenvYCB by @deccanchronicle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @DeviceAuthority at the annual @IoT_SF conference in London on December 5th. Hear from @IoT_Lockers on Applied IoT Security for Healthcare and Industrial. Other speakers include @intel @Thalesesecurity @PenTestPartners @IBM + more. Register now: https://t.co/TF6WMfX23F https://t.co/1BZ68qnXZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reaper IoT Botnet Leaves Millions of Devices Vulnerable to Hacking https://t.co/tafpfhp1IG by @rao_cherukuri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Device Authority's KeyScaler delivers Automated Password Management with @AxisIPVideo Cameras https://t.co/qc9GJ4RctI https://t.co/3GBwPt7G38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applying US-CERT IoT Security Best Practices to Healthcare https://t.co/427Ni2zoQv by @SecurityHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #cybersafebusiness strategy for the Internet of Things https://t.co/uIFuebyw0a by @GetCyberSafe https://t.co/oJ6Fg3MkBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT for healthcare means actionable and meaningful data https://t.co/46fOWcBzsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet manufacturers who are monetising the IIoT today - hear from @DeviceAuthority on securing your infrastructure, @PTC on the new manufacturing &amp; service journeys of the IoT and @InVMA_IoT on new methods that are changing the environment https://t.co/QVOg4Dm8qn #IoT #Industrial https://t.co/ls235NArjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @DeviceAuthority at the annual @IoT_SF conference in London on December 5th. Hear from @IoT_Lockers on Applied IoT Security for Healthcare and Industrial. Other speakers include @intel @Thalesesecurity @PenTestPartners @IBM + more. Register now: https://t.co/MWGhW9F0yZ https://t.co/H9YYdPOkd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cybersecurity Guide to Purchasing IoT Devices This Holiday Season https://t.co/vLDbdZJLF3 by @nextadvisor https://t.co/JtMAZpNWL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT lottery: finding a perfectly secure connected device https://t.co/8ZTh4TiLTp by @Securelist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By 2021, the world will have seen its first $100 million class-action lawsuit against a medical device manufacturer for negligence due to a cyber attack causing the death of more than 25 people connected to networked medical devices while hospitalized. https://t.co/fuFAc0PlAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet of Things predictions for 2018, ready for business https://t.co/ZIJM4WLCqj by @digitaljournal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet-connected toys putting the privacy and safety of children at risk https://t.co/JGqtRwoWR7 by @Jayjay_tech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet manufacturers who are monetising the IIoT today - hear from @DeviceAuthority on securing your infrastructure, @PTC on the new manufacturing &amp; service journeys of the IoT and @InVMA_IoT on new methods that are changing the environment https://t.co/ZiW6IL9JZR #IoT #Industrial https://t.co/QXxo1gdfBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Health IT predictions for 2018: Al, blockchain, robotics and a $100 million class-action suit https://t.co/2iE5UUfeqQ by @SiwickiHealthIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to get a handle on IoT security https://t.co/hJv7Vo7WSs by @IoTiNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assessing a sustainable IoT future: Why security and connectivity barriers must be overcome https://t.co/og74oF8PJy by @IoTTechNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red, White or IoT? https://t.co/R4Pznry8Rn by @ENGINEERINGcom https://t.co/dJCpOhFjPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PKI as IAM for M2M and IoT https://t.co/zJKLuu2Pwm by @InfosecurityMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How an IoT sensor is helping Australian milk reach China faster https://t.co/rizPFWKHlS by @zdnet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Device Authority signs global OEM agreement to power Comodo CA IoT security service https://t.co/6BX3E6Zw7p by @totaltelecom https://t.co/jJvVK4z6iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Device Authority Signs Multi-Year Global OEM Agreement to Power Comodo CA IoT Security Service https://t.co/0eAr2EFa59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delegated Security Management (DSM) - Providing high assurance device authentication for IoT platforms, network and power efficiency, and simplified integration with KeyScaler https://t.co/O0TZ6hhmaQ https://t.co/MSWQgMkHPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Data is the new oil': F-Secure man on cartels, disinformation and IoT https://t.co/FuGFYpfdPk by @TheRegister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trends and innovations in Industrial IoT https://t.co/QFCZc9bGB4 by @TheManufacturer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Industrial Internet of Things market: state and outlook 2021 https://t.co/273cCvQCr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to get a grip on enterprise IoT security https://t.co/wJNyT8oESk by @IoTiNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connecting the industrial market: is there an app for that? https://t.co/gbXANoWzq9 by @iotnow_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How an Engineer Used IoT to Save His Avocado Farm https://t.co/kRkHnJ3RQF by @ENGINEERINGcom https://t.co/BNt9tRQCjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Device Authority signs global OEM agreement to Power Comodo CA IoT security https://t.co/ZrZuUDPBRQ https://t.co/pGgMJ2LZVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving from everyone at @DeviceAuthority https://t.co/RZcR9oAE9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confidence in IoT security is low - IoT Agenda https://t.co/eRWMaERO8A by @iotagenda @gemalto https://t.co/AUVgBtTWIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber paid hackers 100K to cover up cyberattack affecting 57M people - Business Insider https://t.co/xkZYV4U85c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Recommendations for IoT – Are you ready for 2018? https://t.co/3TIfDvoBQs by @AlbertSisto @DeviceAuthority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @DeviceAuthority Delivers Advanced Device Security for IoT Platforms https://t.co/vKeJDYgmgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delegated Security Management (DSM) - Providing high assurance device authentication for IoT platforms, network and power efficiency, and simplified integration with KeyScaler https://t.co/yk8pXsDwIV https://t.co/H8fRd5ixWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Healthcare is a Major Target for Cybercriminals | 2017-12-21 | Security Magazine https://t.co/ITjKyFPLk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Code Used in Zero Day Huawei Router Attack Made Public https://t.co/V4hnG0Jra1 by @threatpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How PKI has evolved to solve the IoT security issue https://t.co/KEZGWyKPmO by @IoT_Dobson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ransomware of IoT: the new security nightmare - Information Age https://t.co/Vpeg5zfoDi by @InformationAge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated PKI is the foundation for IoT Security https://t.co/b0bcccpvGL by @rao_cherukuri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Multifaceted Approach to Autonomous Vehicle Cyber Security - IOT Journal https://t.co/SdExpnrfqk by @iotjrnl https://t.co/CJtTwiavGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delivering Trust for IoT with HSMs with @Thalesesecurity + @DeviceAuthority https://t.co/Iy0l4ZJJ5L Sign up for our webinar on February 15th with Adam Erickson and @johnrgrimm https://t.co/PRNEimDl3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are your medical devices secure? Join @PTC @ThingWorx and @DeviceAuthority on Jan 25th to learn how to drive business results and continuous innovation by transforming your medical device product design, engineering and security practices. https://t.co/7FkCAm1TwQ https://t.co/hYzCIdff4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 top cloud security threats for 2018: The dirty dozen | CSO Online https://t.co/nqxelQN2GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Connected Christmas Ever! Or Is It? https://t.co/3wD83M5IaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six IoT trends we'll see in 2018 https://t.co/wZFAzLWc4B by @iotagenda @defshepherd https://t.co/9L6p4Zz8J9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everything is connected, the art of network planning gets complicated https://t.co/wDRwBWv4Wv by @iotagenda https://t.co/We4nXnHE5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our 2018 webinar series has launched with an array of IoT topics including medical devices, HSMs, lifecycle management and IoT device hacks. Speakers include @Thalesesecurity @intel @Inteliot @ComodoNews @PTC @ThingWorx @PenTestPartners - Sign up here:
https://t.co/aIo2CtHt8S https://t.co/zWc82n5z6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are your Connected Medical Devices and Data compliant with GDPR and HIPAA? https://t.co/CkrceRg8mW https://t.co/qumfJ4dePr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @DeviceAuthority recognized as @SCMagazine Innovator in Access Control for IoT for second year! https://t.co/wN5lMKMdaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting the Internet of Medical Things' Demands for Networking | HealthTech https://t.co/bKHPloSlyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Recommendations for IoT – Are you ready for 2018? https://t.co/ZqAMtYBN9V by @AlbertSisto @DeviceAuthority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time to deal with IoT security is now | Network World https://t.co/A979a58X6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Top 8 IoT Trends For 2018 https://t.co/6tc7hjs8C6 by @danielnewman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Few Simple Tips To A Safer Smart Home During The Holidays https://t.co/Lf6kP0wqCM by @haroldstark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 2018 could be decisive year for IoT https://t.co/oca1gyXwAZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>