<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBC_TopGear: Holy mother of carbon fibre, it’s the 1250bhp Lamborghini Aventador ‘Carbonado’ by Mansory #FrankfurtMotorShow http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow! got this song stuck in my head...The Fox http://t.co/opZ5Rc5v8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @erichrich: When a Taurus man is in love, he is a prime example of a gentle, compassionate and loyal lover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats my friend Weilong Xie, rising top designer &amp; his team in #London for #bubble #machine #dress worn by Gaga http://t.co/zAu8uqtAHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Samantha Bea! Straight talk with Russian insider. #howitsdone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night's @TheDailyShow was seriously one of the best! Welcome back Jon. Jon &amp; John re: Middle East = just brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So looking forward to launch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another epiphany. I love it when a plan comes together :P It gets better as we get closer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home sweet home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm going to be sore tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St. Marks Summit http://t.co/C2dDXGLnun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off for a hike in the mountains. It's been a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking home it was like "fake fake fake, omg, fake!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went out to grab salmon donburi. I passed so many  arguments and heated conversations. Prefer the… http://t.co/koE7DTRazB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a pho kinda Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Model S Sedan Destroys Safety Tests ... Literally http://t.co/3rN1osp7So Congratulations @elonmusk @teslamotors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the rooftop deck, Keg steakhouse #Yaletown. Another beautiful sunny afternoon in Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw a couple checking out new electric vehicle charging stn @ English Bay.  Next stop @teslamotors Car giants could only wish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[199 days to go until the biggest pride parade in history! @Sochi2014 #GoTeamCanada @CDNOlympicTeam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rode 29km twice around the #seawall came home ate #fiveguys bacon cheeseburger, fries &amp; #dq ice cream. I think we are even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paralympic @hailfabio the rule is ridiculous and should be changed immediately. Definitely not in the spirit of the Olympics! #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paralympic use opportunity, save face &amp; do the right thing. Fast track rule change &amp; let @Arlenv1 compete. For #Olympic sake!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigspence of @Paralympic tells @Arlenv1 &amp; athletes if they have hope for cure, they can't compete #WTF #shame #IPC #unacceptable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lazy Sunday. Should I stay or should I go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cadillac unveils Ciel concept - BBC Top Gear http://t.co/rmmqaKYLGA via @BBC_Topgear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cadillac reveals Elmiraj concept - BBC Top Gear http://t.co/h1F8Vscilq via @BBC_Topgear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's what I've been working on. It's about time and its coming soon to an App Store near you. It's… http://t.co/C2rDUhbauX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT Please follow @Calemazoo It's about time and it's coming soon to an App Store near you! #FF #TGIF #innovation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is truly a gift. Our time is limited so make every day count and never take tomorrow for granted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You didn't get a chance to enjoy life to the fullest &amp; were taken too soon. My prayers are with you and your families. RIP my friends RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body strong. Heart healed and strong. Mind strong. Emotions a bit fragile but hanging on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Priceless! Cartwheel Fail Vine http://t.co/MSq7HYfgxW via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21km ride, now rapid chest workout. Re energized! This is how it should be all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escaping for an afternoon ride. It's going be foggy and chilly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look back and thank God. Look forward and trust God. He closes doors no man can open and he opens doors no man can close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From feeling lonely to hungry to happy #singlefriday http://t.co/QURGo0Po2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it's foggy out when you hear fog horns in downtown Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a restless night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snuck out for a lunch time bike ride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving. Spend time with family and friends, and tell them how much they mean to you. #Life and #Time is #precious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could definitely put a smile on @MileyCyrus face. Just sayin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we as humans don't truly appreciate what we have until it is taken away from us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are hard to find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 soda drink per day = 50lbs of sugar per year. #wow #Sugar = &lt; #diabetes #Alzheimers #cancer http://t.co/BevvNtMg13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secrets of #sugar http://t.co/BevvNtMg13 What they don't want you to know. #Obesity #diabetes #Alzheimers #cancer #science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put you high up in the sky and now, you're not coming down. It slowly turned, you let me burn and now, we're ashes on the ground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited! http://t.co/YDixq3Vade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling full and comfortably numb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I take it as a compliment that I'm harder to deal with than some asshole bf? An asshole is simple. Leave him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting hungrier by the second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bundling up to go get YoPo cafe. Can't believe it's this cold already Vancouver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I could summon ramen right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ever find yourself lost in the dark and you can't see, I'll be the light to guide you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about grabbing the reigns and directing it. If not you are just holding on for your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robinwilliams " #Canada your the nicest country in the world. You're like a sweet apartment over a meth lab" #TheCrazyOnes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching two of my former clients star in the premiers of their new shows tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to record 2 shows and watch a 3rd and your pvr can only handle 2 #seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need the night off. My mind is going to mush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Calemazoo #toinfinityandbeyond ! Are we having fun yet? Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been working day and night I haven't left my office for days except to eat and sleep. A shower and shave would feel good right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday working, still going but going good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to make mistakes or not succeed. Life is about evolution and how we grow from our experiences. #Persistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Chun Yi: Making of a Legend which is 1/2 in Chinese so I only understand 1/2. There you have it, my Sat night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying a nice btl of Robert Mondavi Napa Valley Cabernet Sauvignon my ex brought back for me from LA. Perfect dinner for one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and the most amazing spinach salad. Something is up, everything tastes incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating the most amazing steak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#groceries work out to about $25 per bag in Vancouver #random #observation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So tired so hungry. Drove 9hrs to Lilloet and back as a day trip with my mom #bucketlist #qualitytime #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I lived in Roman times I would have been a Thinker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@PaulGAllen: Polar Bears above the Artic Circle on Devon Island, Canada this afternoon http://t.co/lV24fREcP6” Oh Canada!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jack: Maybe this is why Warhol stuck to soup cans: http://t.co/XhVntO0Rv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tbt http://t.co/wwwUcbc9mL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[29km of fresh air and inspiration. http://t.co/fDSi57dDeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading out for a bike ride, twice around Stanley Park. Anyone want to join in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Another trailer for my little movie 'Muppets Most Wanted' http://t.co/NW7q3QqqSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn I think you got into my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I close my eyes and imagine us dancing together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pnpss @calemazoo I am biased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On reserves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the use of having business hours if you are going to just randomly close early! Fckng #yopocafe did it again!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can't be friends with you I can only be friendly to you." - ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's a series of problems we have to solve. One, then another, and another and another until at last we die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fox - London http://t.co/1EJKxWYGWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banksyart London http://t.co/MqoRLu8h87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banksyart London http://t.co/lVKwnir9HT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banksyart London http://t.co/dzByqCBF2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banksyart London http://t.co/ldRYsWwdJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banksyart London http://t.co/5Nx3NEGPMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enough said. http://t.co/NDUz8Z6DU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ever find you're the most talented person in the room, you need to find another room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11-12-13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you'all just going to have to find the rest...and I'd hurry up if I was you because the basements slowly filling with pudding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another amazing achievement for Weilong Xie, rising top designer &amp; his team XO in dress worn by #ladygaga http://t.co/RoAX8OVMQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FeedTexas: Be kind whenever possible. It is always possible - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home safe dry warm how fortunate. Pray for Philippines and give give give what you can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SunTzuSaid: When envoys are sent with compliments in their mouths, it is a sign that the enemy wishes for a truce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look closely at the present you are constructing, it should look like the future you are dreaming" - Alice Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing @JoshLeviWorld killed it tonight! You are mature beyond your years. Vote #levination #xfactorusa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray for the Philippines! Bunker down and stay safe my friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it wasn't for offshore winds &amp; our location would Vancouver be covered in smog &amp; have poor air quality? #illusion]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>