<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#GhostOctopus  #Okeanos https://t.co/g9uyLELJ6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case you were unclear on the importance of today's bilateral announcement to #cutmethane and #actonclimate, https://t.co/5YZ2JvbH7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GinaEPA: Proud to carry out @POTUS commitment to reduce #methane emissions &amp; join our Canadian colleagues to #ActOnClimate. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kate_sheppard: I don't really care who "won," but it sure was nice to see climate policy discussed substantively in last night's debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No credible plan to combat climate change can ignore methane emissions" say @ddonigernrdc, @NRDC https://t.co/SPzYlTjrrV #cutmethane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It has become clear that it is time for the EPA to take additional action to regulate existing sources in the oil &amp; gas sector.” - @GinaEPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau and Obama announce agreement to #CutMethane, and U.S. commits to regulate existing sources! #actonclimate https://t.co/4qpDwiFeg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every day that passes w/ the Supreme Court below full strength impairs the ppl's business..." -President Reagan https://t.co/RxMGTTWHKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: “The more I look at Earth…the more I feel more of an environmentalist.” Welcome home, astronaut @StationCDRKelly! https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The post-aPostalypse well underway down the street. Hope you got everything out of there, @kansasalps. https://t.co/eMCBUAp1mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders stopped at Harbour Lights too. More his style than Henry's or the Bottleneck, I'd imagine. #RCJH #LFK https://t.co/xyAIR1CBOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, that's surreal. Good barber shop. #RCJH #LFK
 https://t.co/GoTyogEBII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: BREAKING: Oregon just passed the historic #CoalFreeOR bill — a huge victory for clean energy! https://t.co/bq7bxcFhCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As of last night, Oregon plans eliminate coal from its energy mix entirely. #actonclimate https://t.co/1hcT8Zwixm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nate Silver, don't you make me start worrying about you.   https://t.co/284vh4pCOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @repjohnlewis: The Vote is precious, it is almost sacred. I gave a little blood to guarantee that every American has the right to vote. …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How we waste a third of all of our food: 
https://t.co/kXN6Zq8MFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hitRECordJoe: And this is definitely the baller thing to be tweeting about the night you win an oscar. Congrats pal! https://t.co/DijHT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let us not take this planet for granted. I do not take tonight for granted." @LeoDiCaprio's Oscars transcript/video https://t.co/QfWuEMsnLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome for @LeoDiCaprio to use his long sought for Oscar speech as a platform to #ActOnClimate. That's as impressive as his performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: “Climate change is real. It is happening right now. It is the most urgent threat facing our species.” — @LeoDiCaprio https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bruneski: "Climate change is real and it's happening now. We need to find leaders who speak for all of humanity." Great job, Leo. Congr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biding time at the office for a few while the storm pushes through.  https://t.co/Fa2VSY2WuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GinaEPA: New info shows methane emissions from existing sources in oil &amp; gas sector are substantially higher than we previously underst…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @onEarthMag: Interactive: Explore how and where humans are making coastal flooding (a lot) worse. https://t.co/9P2Yw977Ls https://t.co/j…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #oceans news this week: China's box office records  shattered by a movie about mermaids fighting evil businessmen https://t.co/YgvPayIyHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Revkin: Defining terms good start in hashing out clean-energy paths. @BillGates's take on "miracles" https://t.co/E3suy2dIKy https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: “The people of Flint got stuck on the losing end of decisions driven by spreadsheets" https://t.co/0E8MFllfiW #FlintWaterCr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to go check this out--I'm guessing it's in the featured spot where the absurdly large LL Cool J portrait was. https://t.co/QI1YkHkQeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Koch brothers' rumored campaign is a desperate reaction to the success of electric vehicles. @NRDCSwitchboard https://t.co/aU2b8WRQjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Join @VAIPL to show your support for the #CleanPowerPlan &amp; for climate action in #Virginia: https://t.co/FGTwryAzPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can pause the Clean Power Plan, but you can't pause clean power. #actonclimate https://t.co/oY8TEbG7HK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennKesslerWP: In case you were wondering: When the Court divides 4-4 the lower court opinion is affirmed without creating any Supreme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the hammer of Thor, I deny everything. https://t.co/k3M0RDVBS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenFranken: The Supreme Court’s decision yesterday to pause implementation of the #CleanPowerPlan is a disappointing step in the wrong …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GovInslee: Deeply disappointed in #SCOTUS decision to pause feds' Clean Power Plan. We'll continue to #ActonClimate in WA &amp; believe CPP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican primary voters are asking what their candidates will do to #actonclimate. https://t.co/emfaAdVsyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NOAAFishMedia: Marine species in Northeast U.S. showing their vulnerabilities to climate.
https://t.co/ndyLuJpk61
@KuffnerAlex @URICRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: you wouldn't like @MarkRuffalo when he's angry.  https://t.co/fdU3bainuD https://t.co/w2xexXNdyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @christackett: 300 Union Plumbers Spent The Weekend Installing Water Filters For Flint Residents For Free https://t.co/ZueBBsx2mA via @t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So what’s really at stake in this year’s election? Well, among other things, the fate of the planet." Krugman'd.  https://t.co/sFXc2mFnkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Join Robert Redford &amp; tell @POTUS to save our wild lands from fossil fuels:  https://t.co/ZCfM1s0qbz https://t.co/RZmAM0V9E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CVSummit @Oceana https://t.co/hQPa6GibvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Dansen says working to #protectourcoast is "the most joyous fight you could possible have." #cvsummit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coastal leaders and organizers celebrating 100+ resolutions in city halls across the Atlantic w/ @Oceana #cvsummit https://t.co/8Pz8Lv21ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not a matter of if a spill will happen, we all know, but when." @katewalsh at #cvsummit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA beer industry working to react to climate impacts on hops. https://t.co/qM3wXycpC2 #RaiseaGlass #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else been holding back the impulse to dramatically yell "hold the door" at people entering buildings in front of them today? #GoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: "That kind of extreme heat is not only an inconvenience, it kills people" - @DrKimKnowlton @NRDC https://t.co/XWLm54KiBj vi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WABADC: @JohnFCross Thank @DDOTDC! They went in overnight. 

(L Street is not so well cared for, alas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my @WABADC, dedicated bike/ped lanes around 15th st construction just in time for #BiketoWorkDay2016? Well played https://t.co/oZEHmS611Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goodmanme Consider this white male student government eagle scout convinced!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @postgreen: Why this could finally be the election where climate change matters https://t.co/1dSPF5yRCI https://t.co/GdELKG3Rdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great breakdown of @HillaryClinton's platform:  https://t.co/35c2qjK4b9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: "This was a man-made disaster. This was avoidable. This was preventable." - @POTUS on #FlintWaterCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch I mean, it's no Con Air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worrying more about climate change than they used to. Is it odd that this is a source of relief to me? https://t.co/MxZUb8xCoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnDingell: Luckily, Carly Fiorina's latest failed business deal only resulted in two people losing their jobs. Not another 30,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PressSec: Briefing prep always goes better when CJ Cregg is in the house cc: @AllisonBJanney https://t.co/asp25hnRf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll from @BloombergDotOrg - major public support for #CleanPowerPlan in states where AGs are suing to block it.  https://t.co/SxVLnvbb5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BarackObama: For the health of our children and grandchildren, we have to #ActOnClimate. https://t.co/pJz7ODyr3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BarackObama: Fighting climate change will save Americans money at the gas pump. #ActOnClimate https://t.co/ePl93jLYTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: In the United States, 20 pounds of food per person goes uneaten each month:  https://t.co/SzP878r5y6 #StopFoodWaste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LizHeyd: Historic #climate agreement's missed opportunity: addressing a major threat to #oceans https://t.co/3agui93hV1 via @NRDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It turns out a few people agree with me. #ActOnClimate  #EarthDay2016  https://t.co/7aL67mfVqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierraclub: This #earthday, the signing of the #ParisAgreement marks "a turning point for humanity." https://t.co/awzYjpbbFA #ActOnParis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KristenGrennan: .@StateDept John Kerry signs #COP21 agreement for US with granddaughter in arms! #ClimateAction #EarthDay https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uscan: This is a historic moment. But make no mistake, this is the beginning, not the end. this is the floor, not the ceiling.  1/2 @Rh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tcktcktck: "We need to turn these promises into real action. The world is watching." @NRDC's @RheaSuh responds to today's #ParisAgreeme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: UPDATE: Leaders from 171 countries have signed the historic #ParisAgreement! #EarthDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press conference starting now: Civil society's role in the #ParisAgreement. https://t.co/it2T6DR84R #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: And we’ll cut the global carbon footprint today so climate chaos doesn’t overwhelm our kids tomorrow.

#ParisSigning #ParisAgr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really digging the synth beats behind this recap of the #ParisAgreement and I think @LeoDiCaprio is too. #EarthDay2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children currently taking over the UN general assembly hall. https://t.co/ONVevYXlfQ #ParisAgreement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We'll hold our leaders to account. We'll hold each other to account." @RheaSuh on the #ParisAgreement. https://t.co/lDtGBnvYer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know what I'm doing this morning! #EarthDay2016  https://t.co/VhWYslhcwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCardin: On the @DSenFloor calling on my colleagues to finally wake up and #ActOnClimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone trying to listen without running into copyright blocks, KEXP is all Prince right now. https://t.co/lRW3cI8AC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now cracks a noble heart. Goodnight, sweet Prince."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Upworthy: 40% of food in the United States is wasted. We can all do our part to prevent food waste. — @AdCouncil
https://t.co/8B7Ou3hWWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: It’s time to act! Tell world leaders to follow through on the #ParisAgreement: https://t.co/juCA3znoIj https://t.co/x2UoCQhrB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decades of advocacy, hundreds of countries, millions of supporters. Let's do this.  https://t.co/BemjiJxRMp #EarthDay2016 #ParisSigning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCSolutions: New @NRDC @ACEEEdc study shows low-income households may spend 3 times as much on energy: https://t.co/x2AugoMmOH https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aletweetsnews: Lady Liberty arrested at the Capitol. #DemocracySpring https://t.co/jkdx1tPzyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @patricey: happy birthday to you @JohnFCross  https://t.co/22HiHy9Ym4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legal defense of the Clean Power Plan: Consider yourselves briefed. #actonclimate  https://t.co/lg8JVg6PiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substance over process and reasoning over drama.  https://t.co/0ineRqcDoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: New report: Kansas has 27,000 #cleanenergy jobs | https://t.co/Eaw2tafLaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why on earth would @DCPoliceDept ever announce this publicly? Be careful out there, bikers and walkers. https://t.co/nm3zfh8mDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eilperin: Obama on how Garland had to sell his comic book collection to attend Harvard Law School. "It's tough. Been there." https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garland is about to get nominated to #SCOTUS - now it's the Senate's duty to consider him.
 #doyourjob  https://t.co/K7PLSQLILs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlyssaRosenberg Judge Doom, thank goodness, was unavailable. https://t.co/halejZE7zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dropping Atlantic drilling means "standing up to Big Oil and protecting our coastal communities"  https://t.co/dTSfZ7SuEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @nancypyne and everyone who fought for this! https://t.co/FKlVfgJmGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SecretaryJewell: BREAKING → Next 5-year offshore proposed plan protects the Atlantic for future generations.SJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19% chance to win it all? I'll take it. Rock Chalk. #RCJH https://t.co/Gk5AMYFZeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fivefifths: Everybody remember: it's ok to disconnect, not consume every news, not develop takes, grieve, and do what you need to do to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change is like "gas on a fire" when it comes to global security issues. https://t.co/R4TNbM2tKV #CleanPowerPlan   #ActonClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: UPDATE: Mid-Atlantic region has released 1st ever playbook to guide ocean decisions. https://t.co/TUefXCIUn0 #oceanplanning #MidA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sobering when a dystopian fiction writer captures the moment so well. On Trump, hate, America, humanity:  https://t.co/LmIgIt5aHD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>