<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoodfordCKNW980 That's a real shame. I hate to hear of these layoffs and cutbacks, and they seem to be getting more and more frequent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look Dion, it's not you, it's us. We need to work on ourselves right now. We just need some space. #tmltalk #yyz https://t.co/IQiayhkZym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DamoSpin: A year ago, would have been thought impossible for Leafs to move contracts of Clarkson, Kessel and Phaneuf. But they somehow …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love your tweets and photos at the bottom of the page, Brent. What a steal for $2.4 million! #vanre #vancouver  https://t.co/WGrVslsNE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scoopercooper: Unprecedented detail of an apparent attempt to launder money in #vanre https://t.co/kQ1iOIzicy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KathyTGlobe: Digging into this was fascinating. The legal/crazy way Vancouver's RE market is getting stoked:  https://t.co/lFFJB9Ang9 #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong wind storm in Vancouver right now. Whitecaps in the Strait, lights flickering, windows rattling. Surprised there was no wind warning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: It's wet out there, but at least #Vancouver is beautiful in the rain. Happy long weekend! https://t.co/Hpf4kRDZgp https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This! #tmltalk #keepthedreamalive  https://t.co/ZW38ZuOr0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainblack_vbot: I don't think I could take a more stereotypical Canadian photograph... https://t.co/MPJ8buCWdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another bleak day for #cdnmedia. The Merc was an institution and the first paper I applied to after j-school. #RIP https://t.co/HrwMC5KK1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we've reached the #NHLAllStar break and #Canada's 7 teams are all in the bottom 11. That's just sad. #nhl #hockey https://t.co/JVwHoc0qND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Proud to support #BellLetsTalk. RT this photo of @ClaraHughes_ to donate 5¢ to #mentalhealth programs in #Canada. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WendyHartley: These veteran journalists are so darn smart. We need to keep employed veteran, experienced journalists in this country. #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKofsky @Chris_Holling It's a great system. We use it quite often at our forums!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bizarre video shows how the "world's first crowd-funded real estate brokerage" pitches #yvr to China: https://t.co/zCTOO0Cobh #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Vancouver ranks third most unaffordable housing market in world, worse than New York and London: https://t.co/tAeX2zJv8j #vanpoli #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: We found this old TV commercial for #Expo86 in #Vancouver. The '80s were epic. @MyVancouver @HelloBC @VancityBuzz https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amrikvirkbc: Had a great talk on #BCTECH with the @BoardofTrade this morning.  They get why tech is important in BC https://t.co/s7x4UM…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Say hello to our friends at @TorontoRBOT! We're excited to welcome the Minister to B.C. and #VBOT Feb. 11! #cdnpoli https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a selfie with @MikeyPlumb before his audition. Proof that I knew him before he became a star! #Vancouver https://t.co/qTsnUuQJjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thoughts are with #Postmedia journalists today. I remember trying to focus and work amidst Sun Media newspaper layoffs in 2007. Not easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: JUST IN: Premier @christyclarkbc to give #BCBudget address at @BoardofTrade Feb. 17: https://t.co/b6WAwiKQST #bcpoli http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes. Oil price falls below $28 a barrel, or less than the cost of an actual barrel: https://t.co/POhoB6uVoi https://t.co/RPDUIfgaW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposed property tax surcharge would put cash in the hands of #Vancouver residents: https://t.co/1BnWX3arGH #vanpoli #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting piece on #Vancouver's starring role in car commercials, courtesy of @CBCTheNational: https://t.co/RTl7h6I3LK #yvr #canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billburr Hey Bill, just for the record I liked your shoes tonight. Don't let that #canadianheckler get under your skin! #JFLNW #ItsBurrTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're at the Orpheum and ready to see @billburr! Thanks @JFLNorthWest for bringing him to #yvr! #JFLNW #ItsBurrTime https://t.co/rlm9zX8HNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the talk about transportation, transit and infrastructure in the news, this should be a hot ticket! #bcpoli https://t.co/UkHM4ShjgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got rear-ended while driving an Evo earlier tonight. Shout out to @EvoCarShare help staff for making a bad situation fairly painless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new business cards just arrived and they look awesome. #newname #newlogo #gvbot https://t.co/RXUwG38M7g https://t.co/tQusZRahbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spinning the classics tonight on Beach Avenue. #wutang https://t.co/wXcB8EA4pI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bethanyjchan: Loving the new logo everywhere at tonight's event! @BoardofTrade #gvbot #cypprogram]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @miaandrew: CYPx tonight! Excited about the guest speakers and gaining new insights #cypprogram @BoardofTrade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A King in His Castle: How #DonaldTrump Lives, From His Longtime Butler. https://t.co/Q5OnZh4JLu #uspoli https://t.co/xF6Iej68cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: NEWS: #GVBOT CEO pitches SkyTrain investment in 2016 Federal Budget: https://t.co/7J6phFuWew #bcpoli #vanpoli #yvr https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials flee #Vancouver for more affordable cities: https://t.co/xIdDEXkFbx via @business #vanpoli #VanRE https://t.co/LNbI7V5nNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's a study on empty houses that doesn't count a bunch of empty houses? Got it. Typical for #vanre discussion.  https://t.co/9XNzjc5Q9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndreaWoo: Overheard in the newsroom: "A house that literally burnt down last week is now on MLS for $2-million." #VanRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KathyTGlobe: Great digging and reality check on vacant homes study by @Goldiein604 https://t.co/IKtDDetjbl #VanRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this photo of #NorthVancouver taken from the Lonsdale Wharf in 1917. Zoom in and look around! https://t.co/LK8W5duEFi via @VanArchives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdelmanVAN: LIVE on #Periscope: Live: Edelman Vancouver Trust Barometer panel discussion!  https://t.co/rFHKh7jGt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Lots of Twitter traffic at today's #gvbot event as our panel of experts dissect the 2016 #EdelTrust survey. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Our expert panel featuring local media, business and academic influencers discuss the #EdelTrust 2016 survey. #gvbot http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have @johnclinton122 back at #gvbot to share #Edeltrust 2016 results. Always a thought-provoking event. https://t.co/YSJfgPeebF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Our #redesign of Sounding Board is now out! Find it inside @bizinvancouver or at https://t.co/vdVieoWhZK #gvbot #yvr http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: India's High Commissioner to Canada speaks to the #bcbiz community March 15. https://t.co/aUo0vzGXUO #gvbot #bcpoli https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the top of vancouverlookout. Part 3/3. #urbangrind #vancouver @ The Vancouver Lookout https://t.co/1wgrqQHDWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the top of vancouverlookout. Part 2/3. #urbangrind #vancouver @ The Vancouver Lookout https://t.co/5h4K2zllz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the top of vancouverlookout. Part 1/3. #urbangrind #vancouver @ The Vancouver Lookout https://t.co/VAvQeDawZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcbiz #bcpoli #BecauseIts2016  https://t.co/oV9qzbApJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is. Excited to unveil this #redesign. Thanks to the team at Glacier Media for their help! #GVBOT https://t.co/LnRarT2uHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In addition to our new logo, we've also redesigned Sounding Board. 12,500 copies now in the mail! #Vancouver #GVBOT https://t.co/3is059iups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep thoughts by @justinbieber. https://t.co/tSCAMbbVYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: We are deeply touched by this fundraiser for @NEWS1130's Tammy Moyer. Please share + donate: https://t.co/AWVvjO1ZGu http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spring sunshower in #Vancouver. You can actually see rays of sunlight bouncing off the rain… https://t.co/tVR1EJwJ0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total attendance for today's #GVBOT event with @MichaelEPorter = 1,048. This guy is a business strategy rock star. https://t.co/7jwLa2QLsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Thank you! We look forward to continuing to work with @MetroVancouver in the best interests of our region! #gvbot https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what I like to see! #gvbot https://t.co/tLpzp7Xos5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Meet the Greater Vancouver Board of Trade: https://t.co/zmXl9wFgM1 #bcbiz #vancouver #globe2016 #gvbot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Hundreds of people filing into @VanConventions East to hear @MichaelEPorter's keynote to @BoardofTrade. #bcbiz #yvr https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mandymwu: On Mar 10 @EdelmanVAN presents the #EdelTrust survey results at @BoardofTrade. Register now: https://t.co/i7qvhMlp0j https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: .@bchydro CEO Jessica McDonald speaks to #Vancouver media following her second annual @BoardofTrade address. #bcpoli http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't say enough good things about @EvoCarShare. A fantastic made-in-B.C. car-sharing service. Great work, @BCAA! https://t.co/O40QxGkvqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted in the West End. https://t.co/ioFxoeR3y6… #vancouver #publicart https://t.co/19FJweD1O8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im pretty sure this mattress store on Broadway has been closing since I moved to Vancouver six years ago! #yvr https://t.co/I26RaO8RXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I guess that plan backfired, huh? Don't worry @Bell, I think only a couple million people watch The National. https://t.co/IcwCo6wCOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS: #Vancouver @BoardofTrade calls for provincial ride-sharing strategy: https://t.co/gmqT5YVmAT #bcpoli #vanpoli https://t.co/XcsIVjS9GH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Awesome @pinkshirtday volunteers are giving away free hugs outside @LondonDrugs in #Vancouver today. #pinkitforward https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainblack_vbot: @WoodfordCKNW980 now engaging @MetroVancouver chair @GregMooredotca on reg'l unity, transit, affordability. #vbot https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: .@MetroVancouver Chair Greg Moore takes the stage for his 3rd annual address to regional business leaders at #VBOT. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: JUST IN: High Commissioner of #India to Canada to speak at #Vancouver @BoardofTrade: https://t.co/aUo0vzGXUO #bcpoli http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NespressoCA I am unable to DM you our account number because you're not following me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NespressoCA Absolutely. I share an account with my partner, I will send you our details in a DM. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NespressoCA Hi! I'm the guy who had a shopping bag with $70+ of capsules stolen from me in Vancouver. Wondering if you can help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yvrairport: So long @IronMaiden! Was a great treat to get a final glimpse of  #EdForceOne taking off today. https://t.co/bs0SbAShdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: New Sounding Board is out today! Find it inside this week's BIV or online: https://t.co/B3GC9nxpYF #bcbiz #vancouver http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[¡Hola, Amigos! Wish you were here. #cancun #mexico @ Royalton Riviera Cancun https://t.co/eWLs63bHfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost two hours later and we've escaped the chaos of the Cancun airport. En route to paradise! https://t.co/ctwul7GaN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our chariot has arrived. Seats 1A and 1B. Can you tell I'm excited for the beach?! @ Vancouver… https://t.co/E3z0IYLFDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next stop: Mexico. Going to see my little sister get hitched! Adios, Vancouver. See you in a week. 🛫 https://t.co/XX21HY7pBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. I want one! The future is clear with Google Cardboard Plastic: https://t.co/UROU9sVcg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes at #GVBOT, where @rcmpgrcpolice Commissioner Bob Paulson is speaking to #Vancouver media. #bcpoli https://t.co/6f2iuKM5H8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Thanks @CityofVancouver's Chief Digital Officer @jessieadcock for meeting with our Civic Affairs Committee. #vanpoli http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fruit juice on the right, all-purpose cleaner on the left. This looks like a lawsuit waiting to happen @Walmart. https://t.co/x96a45eCAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phanyxx Very true! Or stuck in the middle of nowhere with no cell service. I'm glad it didn't happen during a trip to the interior or U.S.!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yourbuddySean It was a grey Honda Civic with the licence plate PAPPY C! @justinbeddall 2/2 https://t.co/DuzWZMVhmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yourbuddySean Just barely. But as I was waiting for the tow truck I actually took a photo for you and @justinbeddall... 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I've had better mornings. https://t.co/TyVoRupBzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BardishKW: Powerful energy: a room full of female entrepreneurs! Thanks @WECldouglas @SmallBusinessBC @BoardofTrade https://t.co/zutHRY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: We're honoured to host Canada's #SmallBiz Minister @BardishKW in Vancouver today. Time to talk #bcbiz + #cdnpoli! https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brentonwalters Yep, that's a fair comment. I personally prefer the terminology "on-demand" as well. (Hi Brenton. Hope you're doing well.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: Is it time for #ridesharing in Greater Vancouver? Our report to #BCgov: https://t.co/NWYoV0vOyY #bcpoli #vanpoli https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't eaten Honey Nut Cheerios in at least a decade. Yet suddenly, out of the blue, I want some. Right now. https://t.co/phDDDUq11D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoardofTrade: ICYMI: Our policy paper on innovative transportation options for B.C.: https://t.co/DNfu7kjjem #bcpoli #bctech #yvr https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenni_sheppard I've been watching from my perch all day. Feel badly for the people stuck in it on a long weekend. https://t.co/PDP8ERUznc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1130reporter @NEWS1130Traffic I posted a few photos earlier. Still gridlocked. Motorists not getting the memo. https://t.co/PDP8ERUznc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtnbvan The notice says they have an exemption to work 7 a.m. to 10 p.m. Friday-Monday. I don't think motorists are fully aware yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtnbvan Yes, taken about 15 minutes ago. It has looked like that all day. It narrows to one lane in/out of the city. Take Granville Bridge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Easter weekend and construction at Burrard + Pacific is in full swing. Avoid the #BurrardBridge! #vanpoli #yvr https://t.co/atqWP7abCi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>