<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[More Asian-influenced #snacks are emerging in the US: https://t.co/AzcwHF9tnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cultured #butter! Browned butter! Flavored butter! Butter, butter, butter! https://t.co/0X90YMRmcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's get down to brass tacks: How would a 20% tariff on Mexican imports impact our ability to eat #avocados?!
https://t.co/SOno4rUBR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olive oil may be heart healthy pick by many ppl for now, but @terravia's Thrive algae oil has 75% less saturated fat https://t.co/k5r4oUn46y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pairing a brand w charity of good cause not only can lift sales, it can lift staff morale: https://t.co/5gf1LVOVY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meal kits emerge as a surprising threat to #meat sales https://t.co/Yq3IurNHPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinkable soup has #foodwaste reduction over green juices: https://t.co/acrMJEfwDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes learning the wrong way can be more effective &amp; memorable when it comes to #foodsafety https://t.co/VTpWfCi214]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure #farmers are pivotal to food in US, but the most significant force is @Walmart bc it sells 24% of food, says @DanRGlickman at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Referencing pivotal scene in the movie The Graduate @DanRGlickman says the future isn't plastics anymore it is food &amp; agriculture #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atleast a third of food produced globally is lost or wasted Leo Abruzzese says at #FoodTank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is more important to business success: the product formula/features or the branding? @nutpods weighs in https://t.co/sIiZkFGVf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't build wall around malnourished child bc economic impact ripples thru their family/community/country @RogerThurow says #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In US 12.7% of homes are hungry and poor nutrition is the cause of half of the deaths of children under 5 yrs says @JsonHuffman at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FERNnews: "In order to have political leverage you have to become an expert in the entire Farm Bill." --@katmerrigan #FoodTank #farmbil…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clairenaugust: "We have the lowest rate of child food insecurity right now in history. That's largely because of SNAP." - @mattmherrick…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forces of darkness...sharpening knives against #organic" support in farm bill are "cruising for a bruising" @katmerrigan says at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next farm bill needs to tie crop insurance to goals like soil protection &amp; give urban #agriculture own line @katmerrigan says #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we are a food secure nation, we are a secure nation @mattmherrick says at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@chefjoseandres argues school nutrition is a national security issue bc it relates to military's ability to find healthy recruits #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturer claims hydrogen-infused water can help w #inflammation and other ailments https://t.co/EzvLdPrcIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#technology isn't always the answer. We also need to put #culture  back in #agriculture says @DaniNierenberg of @foodtank  at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ag research must be a priority in federal budget bc when we help #farmers we help all our communities @RepJimmyPanetta says at #FoodTank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At my Alma mater to learn about the future of food at #FoodTank. https://t.co/VXpPHqndQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are high amounts of #fiber or other nutrients enough to overcome high #sugar in foods and justify #healthy claims? https://t.co/uXBcm2zJtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If perfection is in the eye of the beholder, the under-30 crowd sees imperfection as perfection: https://t.co/Gmd1CpphZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodQualityNews: MT: @frankyiannas Enjoyed co-chairing Consumer Food Safety Education conf. Videos: https://t.co/bBw5LkZfXP  https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In wake of regulatory freeze, FDA reminds industry that it isn't the only one that can issue compliance guidance: https://t.co/Hnd4Am2oZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The consumer has never been confused" by use of 'milk' on non-dairy products @CalifiaFarms says https://t.co/QkwccfNJAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even as other #superfoods gain popularity, it isn't over yet for #kale chips, says @RhythmSuperfood exec https://t.co/IfSNjhAkZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCPDPG: Our former #FCPDPG webinar host @frankyiannas gives more #foodsafety insight in @FoodNavigator piece: https://t.co/GclBOyBj04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where will the next generation of healthy #snacks be? @EWatsonWrites investigates: https://t.co/AzcwHF9tnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like #butter, check out these emerging flavor-enhancing trends uncovered by @packaged_facts: https://t.co/0X90YMzKOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will President #Trump's tarrif idea on Mexico impact the food and beverage industry? https://t.co/SOno4rUBR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @terravia's Thrive Culinary Algae Oil is, well, thriving: https://t.co/k5r4oUEFv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonsebastiani: With so much $ in the marketplace —brands need to be more selective than ever when choosing a partner @forbes #cpg https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KateScarlata_RD: All new! Digestive Health (Coffee Chat #1) https://t.co/0ilxkrIr40 via @YouTube Today we talk about FAQs with the low…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premium packaging from companies like @CalifiaFarms is leading innovation in beverage https://t.co/Q8lS7duPlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dietary supplement #NDI guidance could be stalled, AGAIN, w Trump administration freeze on regs, guidance docs https://t.co/ysxNe26Eng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make most out of TV home shopping channel appearances, think about them as marketing not sales @PraimGroup says https://t.co/vz0QVWUQAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to choose a cause for good that best fits your brand: https://t.co/5gf1LW6xmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of all shoppers don't perceive #meat as high in #protein: https://t.co/Yq3IurNHPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More #fiber! Less #sugar! The secret to cold soup maker @ZupaNoma success: https://t.co/acrMJDXVfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for cheery orange colors to beat back winter blues? @BASF has a new natural orange to replace yellow 5 &amp; 6 https://t.co/g77e47MADo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: A look at FDA's 4th Annual 2016 Scientific Computing Days from 2016. The 5th Scientific Computing Days Symposium will be Sept.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget dry handouts detailing #foodsafety strategies If you want employees to keep something in mind, make it rhyme: https://t.co/VTpWfCzCSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some #foodsafety experts fear they're losing the battle against food borne disease. Here are 4 tools that could help https://t.co/VTpWfCi214]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is driving @Nutpods remarkable growth? Hint: It is unsweetened, versatile &amp; has unique packaging https://t.co/sIiZkFpkny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight over use of terms milk &amp; cheese on non-dairy alternative continues to rage: https://t.co/xgvjug5PDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With #sugar in the public health crosshairs, @yumamifood bests on umami to sell #snacks https://t.co/5MRo1Mp4U7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many Americans erroneously think natural sugar is safer than added sugar @AtkinsInsider study finds https://t.co/W5JWv1dAed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beet the rush on this new food trend: https://t.co/TkmkJXPbFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Nut meats are gaining traction as #plantbased, protein-packed, flavorful alternative to animal products https://t.co/rz1jiQvGLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers want brands w relatable stories -- a strategy that helps little cos compete w big guys @Nutpods exec says https://t.co/sIiZkFpkny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#foodsafety is more pressing for @US_FDA than if using 'milk' on non-dairy products confuses ppl @CalifiaFarms says https://t.co/Qkwccfw8cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showing products on TV home shopping channels can elevate value in eyes of consumers, retailers @PraimGroup says https://t.co/vz0QVXcrsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New beta-carotene color from @BASF can help clean up labels https://t.co/g77e47uZLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RTD packaged #coffee category is leading beverage #innovation https://t.co/Q8lS7duPlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freeze on guidance docs could give Trump administration way to influence implementation of FSMA &amp; Nutrition Facts https://t.co/ysxNe1P3vI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 of 5 Americans don't know what causes a blood sugar spike, complicatng weight loss efforts @AtkinsInsider study https://t.co/W5JWv1dAed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FDA, #EPA aim to protect #health &amp; #environment while preventing barriers to #innovation as it modernizes #GMO regs https://t.co/KGNCsylffn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free-from claims dominate labels, but it turns out consumers also care about what is in food/bev, @mintelnews finds: https://t.co/EPn9hwOU5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Seafood provides important nutrients to pregnant women &amp; young children, yet most moms don't eat recommended amount https://t.co/p9oPqIr4Ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super-charged nut-butters &amp; squeeze pouches help propel nuts &amp; seeds on to the center stage in 2017 https://t.co/rz1jiQvGLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans' growing interest in Asian flavors inspired @yumamifood's latest launch: https://t.co/5MRo1MGFLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dairy Pride Act is a waste of gov't resources, @Change petition claims https://t.co/xgvjufOef8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Cauliflower is everywhere! https://t.co/63G5kGihFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AtkinsInsider puts sugar goggles on high schoolers, office workers 2 reveal high hidden #sugar in unexpected foods https://t.co/W5JWv1vb5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UglyFruitAndVeg: "I have decided to stick with love. Hate is too great a burden to bear." Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. #EraseTheHate #Lov…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it ok to use milk in nondairy products if it is modified w words such as almond, coconut? @CalifiaFarms weighs in https://t.co/QkwccfNJAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: Ever thought about the potential of home shopping TV for your brand? @ECrawfordwrites reports for @FoodNavigatorUS https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OprahWinfrey &amp; @KraftHeinzCo  to help eradicate hunger by donating 10% of profits of new joint venture to charity https://t.co/bpxjPGZBBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fight_BAC: Stephen Ostroff @US_FDA announces new online tool https://t.co/fKZ0UEdmrm #foodsafety2017 https://t.co/VBJoT1UDVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could an #icecream social hosted by @DippinDots help connect dots between Spicer &amp; the press? https://t.co/SY9AJ4kQn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the rise in unsweetened drinks, innovations in sweeteners remains relevant in beverage:https://t.co/Q8lS7dMqKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV home shopping has sig impact on mrktg beyond the live air time @PraimGroup says in this wk's #SoupToNuts #podcast https://t.co/vz0QVWUQAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you thought Nutrition Facts final rule &amp; #FSMA rule were safe from regulatory freeze, think again: https://t.co/ysxNe1P3vI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StuffSomersSays: Now guac is really going to cost extra. https://t.co/jXlSXyQkyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At #foodsafety2017 conf aplea for funds to conduct observational studies on impact of #foodsafety messages to masses and American behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Request from #foodsafety leader for efforts at state and city levels to be showcased on national agency websites #foodsafety2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankyiannas: Dr Ostroff, Acting Commisioner, FDA, "food safety culture is important on the farm &amp; in the home." #foodsafety2017 https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good&amp;bad #foodsafety news from @US_FDA: 85% ppl wash hands after handling raw meat but only 6% thot raw veg could have germs #foodsafety2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ostrich meat, mung bean snacks, mamaki tea - so many #innovations in food &amp; beverage. Find out who is leading charge https://t.co/hepaEjYGJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA seeks comments on how genome editing impacts plants for food as part of #GMO regulatory update process https://t.co/KGNCsyCQDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the top health claims consumers consider when buying food/beverages? https://t.co/EPn9hwOU5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@US_FDA asks drs and retailers to post easy-to-read #seafood chart &amp; info to encourage more American to eat fish: https://t.co/p9oPqI9tdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joewhitworth: Hard to judge as we are better at finding now with new tech https://t.co/xA8m9XaF2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 #foodsafety tools from @frankyiannas: enclothed cognition, learn from right &amp; wrong way, make it the norm, make it rhyme to keep in mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US cannot test or inspect away food safety risks. @frankyiannas suggests we need new tools to boost #foodsafety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we winning the battle against food borne disease @frankyiannas asks at dc conference.  The mumbled answer: no. #foodsafety2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to #foodsafety the "soft stuff" is the hard stuff @frankyiannas says about emergence of food safety culture #foodsafety2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nuts &amp; #seeds will take a starring role in the American diet this year, predicts @packaged_facts https://t.co/rz1jiQvGLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattdpearce: If science has to undergo political review in order to be seen, in what world can it still be trusted as science?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the next phase of #healthy snacking high #flavor? https://t.co/5MRo1MGFLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ASRCAdReview: Posts by Celebrity Endorsers Revised to Disclose Material Connections to FitTea Following NAD Inquiry
https://t.co/0Hq9MT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Change petition calls out "absurdity" of legislation to prohibit use of milk, cheese on non-dairy alt products https://t.co/xgvjufOef8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a mid-morning #snack? Check out these new trends from Winter Fancy Food for inspiration https://t.co/XOJqJg1n9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AtkinsInsider hops on anti-sugar bandwagon w new campaign talking about hidden #sugar in high #carb foods https://t.co/W5JWv1vb5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OprahWinfrey teams with @KraftHeinzCo to launch new refrigerated line of foods, raise funds for charities https://t.co/bpxjPGI0Kc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families are the future for #glutenfree, says @canyonbakehouse, which is one reason it sells a larger bread loaf https://t.co/mecb7OkihI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>