<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart hey buddy - dont worry about it! you're under no pressure! here's the link to available pieces:

http://t.co/VZYxHLvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These two will become parrots http://t.co/BIHCiJp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be an owl. 24" x 24" http://t.co/pGqxf4cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm happy to be starting some new art tonight after a nice two week break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmhays thanks mate, just doin what i love! (after regular work hours, that is.. :S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmhays thanks for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BabeoPerro thanks for the follow - i relate to your quote!! except i dont know what irreverence is. ill look that up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garybizzo hello - thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NadiaSecreto thanks for following!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronnie_yunker thanks for the follow, nice bg!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart twenty bucks a piece my friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFolliott haha thx for that buddy! these sushi paintings are movin fast! :)

how are youuuuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart ya! Jon@jonshawpaintings.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart ya buddy! Send me an email with the ones (no dot means available) and a transfer would work fo
Sho! Sets of 3 have been popular!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got about 30 sushi paintings left of the original 100! Check out the remaining ones:... http://t.co/gi1HINpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do you like PUFFINS!!??

http://t.co/vxgn5oiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BIGTRAVdotCOM I have no idea what the hell u just asked me ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluefuze I use paper with holes in it, and paint through it so it stencils over!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm painting and chilling at cuppa joy coffee 11-6 all weekend for the AIOM art walk. Swing by to chill and see new stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deliber8lyAskew thanks!! It was a great weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenmitchell thanks mate! It was an awesome weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End result from 3rd annual whistler paint-off competition. Note the sign at the bottom :) http://t.co/ZBn5j3vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a wrap! http://t.co/36BT9JSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding some more feather subtletie. Two hours left, it's all little details now :) http://t.co/Cc5gBFSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished for the day. Add some more touches tomorrow!! http://t.co/8Pdrqg6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistler paint-off: 4 hours in http://t.co/2hmGH01e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistler paint off - 2.5 hours in http://t.co/HCigFJYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistler paint off - 1 hour in http://t.co/rlPC40aU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting up the paintin in whistler! http://t.co/dHScLQ1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This show is on pender island in September. I can't wait to be out there for the opening! http://t.co/779GJaZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shut_up_n_paint: Cool to see a name I recognize in my @OpusArtSupplies newsletter! Congrats @JonShawPainting on your upcoming demo!  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtProfiles hello - thax for following me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha just doin what needs a-doin :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all can - there's just obstacles or roadblocks. I work fulltime but make my art at night :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy oh my thanks so much! i was just doing what i love doing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started a new flamingo-go-go http://t.co/736CKZUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy hey there, thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katherinesoucie thanks for the follow! nice background!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's one of my parrot pieces I am currently working on, with some new ink and paint applications. It's about... http://t.co/EXC48SpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanessaFineArt helllo!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aymikaznak awesomeeeee!! tell her i say hiiiii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aymikaznak oh thanks! yes, thats @birdonawireart on main street. Karen is a great person - thats where i sold my first vancouver piece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy guacamole the response to my painting at Greek Day was amazing - I love everyone of you who stopped to chat and admire :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aymikaznak hey there thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smokin busy at Greek day with my painting today - I might run out of cards!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you plan to hit up Greek Day on Broadway today, come find me and my giraffe canvas working at Broadway and Balaclava :) I'll give u a hug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy hey - i got some in progress shots on my facebook page - http://t.co/IGJnS0R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigger pieces like this one need to be painted on the floor :) http://t.co/Bx4Jtx7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First stages but this one will turn out cool!! http://t.co/9Bv5GUSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's looking more like a parrot http://t.co/WXJmzWyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to add some colour patches! http://t.co/PMdjNbFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdelaideDamoah hey there thx for the follow - nicccce brushstrokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be working on my giraffe painting at Greek Days this Sunday (starting 3pm) on Broadway - if you wanna see it... http://t.co/wWUcoEvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some giraffe progress from this eve - almost time to add some paint applications again! http://t.co/cRq4J5wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmandaGAdams very good - same ol - lots of art, exercise and eating. pretty much the best stuff ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmandaGAdams yeeeea budddddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icequeen057 thanks for teh follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parrot Study #3. This one is a bit bigger, 24" x 24". I love the gesture of it. I'm having lots of fun with this... http://t.co/nPd7yIo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very early stages for one of many new parrot studies. 16" x 16". colours are a bit off in this pic, but the pose... http://t.co/r3svgzSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my biggest animal study yet, at 36" x 48" . Soon I will apply some collage elements to it. This piece is... http://t.co/SPWOKI6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a commission piece i finished recently, and it just arrived at its new home in England :) http://t.co/BTExx7Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JadeVarden thanks for following!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling shirts at the corner of main and 17th for car free day!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started this parrot!! http://t.co/PN2mfplO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More progress :) def liking this painting so far http://t.co/b2ZvcYkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy me either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy thx! Stoked about this one. Biggest yet (3x4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's where this painting is at currently- starting to fill in! http://t.co/aLVtpJk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some progress on this new piece from last night. Gonna make some good progress tonight too! It's bigger so it'll... http://t.co/BzTd73mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPlaces are u referring to the carfree day event? If so - yes plz! I'm there this Sunday, 12-5, at main and 17th :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato keep yer eyes peeled I plan to do a number of em in the coming weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miooooo how u been, mio? Had a mini mount a fine art reunion here about two weeks ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPlaces my bad were at main and 17th this Sunday!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jbarr @mvilleniagara cheers mate - the sushi paintings mostly sold! (25 out of 100 remain). Chek it here - http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariannebanton i like ta mauve it mauve it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my art (and t shirts and cool prints!) are at CarFree Day sunday @ Main and 17th - I'll be doing some cool drawings there too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariannebanton yea buddy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract #2, stage two. Bojingle!! http://t.co/FcSBum7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workin on an abstract piece at harmony today. First stages. Bazzam! http://t.co/1uT6aQwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double that good buddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are looking for something to do this (beautiful) long weekend, I will be in booth 36 at the harmony arts... http://t.co/faFbIrt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are looking for something to do this (beautiful) long weekend, I will be in booth 36 at the harmony arts... http://t.co/92bAt51N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final documentation - come see this colourful guy (or purchase!) in person at Harmony Arts starting tomorrow!  #HAF2012 http://t.co/ULCNTede]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloomMarket thanks so much for the supportive words! stoked for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radjuli good luck mate! im lookin forward to it myself...packing also aaaaaah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done! Final, better documentation photo coming tomorrow. #HAF2012 http://t.co/SDqE3Qr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrapping up pieces for Fridays show - just varnished a number of new works http://t.co/JThiXewo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv im happiest when my work goes to good places :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv most definitely for sale :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv A few weeks ago it won first place at the annual Whistler Paint-Off during the Art Walk. Special memories of a great weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm more excited to exhibit this piece @harmonyartswv this weekend than anything else! #HAF2012 http://t.co/pCFsHUdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopin to finish this piece tonight :) diggin the upper right cluster http://t.co/7nUTXUm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece is final-documented, and ready to show @harmonyartswv starting this Friday in Ambleside! #HAF2012 http://t.co/HNBp6nwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completed fresh batch of painted sushi! #HAF2012 http://t.co/cVtXhlJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely exhibiting this piece this weekend at Ambleside #HAF2012 http://t.co/PcViHKyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harmony Arts starts in just a few days. This long weekend I'll be in Ambleside Park chilling with some art for four days! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbjustason thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harmonyartswv: We've updated our Art Market page to be a bit easier to navigate when filtering by category. http://t.co/TBiACXRH #HA ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha what a champ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JVandepolderand vice versa! ill write it down and come see you too. Are you flying all of your work out from ON for this show??]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>