<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 254: PLEASE COMPLAIN TO SAN MIGUEL TO STOP SUPPORT OF DOG MEAT TRADE – CLICK THIS LINK http://t.co/USXacT9AX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 254: PLEASE COMPLAIN TO SAN MIGUEL FOR THEIR SUPPORT OF DOG MEAT TRADE – CLICK THIS LINK http://t.co/USXacT9AX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peggyrussell: @PeterEgan6 @moonbearJill Could I impose on you to RT this link - the Gobi bear - I feel terrible that I didn't know http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new dog portrait series about the silence of animals - and the silent feelings in ourselves  http://t.co/juOlzz5ngu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 253 – DEPRESSING DAY IN PARLIAMENT AS I GET TRIPLE WHIPPED http://t.co/ZpuOftkr7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tracey_crouch: Yesterday I voted in favour of a motion stating that the badger cull should not go ahead. For the full transcript... htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tracey_crouch I was at the cull debate and SO admire your spirit. I'm not Tory but well done for going against the cull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demoralising vote pro the badger cull in parliament- 299 v 250 but we know the goverment party were under whip. Boo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 251: TWELVE REASONS BADGERS ARE RELATED TO HIPSTERS http://t.co/VYNkCNHVp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VICEUK Twelve reasons badgers are like hipsters http://t.co/VYNkCNHVp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Londonist Twelve reasons badgers are like hipsters http://t.co/VYNkCNHVp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of humour before I head in to Parliament to lobby my MP against the Badger Cull.........http:/ http://t.co/VYNkCNHVp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop the dog meat trade. support @Network4Animals and write to the president here: http://t.co/zT55YiMnD3 http://t.co/a1JgPA0HLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if all animals weren't sentient. New evidence shoes dolphins call each other by their names...http:/ http://t.co/YXZZQ8b9mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 303: HOW EASY IS IT TO BUY ILLEGAL PANGOLIN SCALES IN HANOI? I TRY AND FIND OUT. http://t.co/8WyT0cMB9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 300: WHY I NEED TO BE CAREFUL ABOUT CLIVE http://t.co/hlXwa1xokz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jo_barefoot: All you need to know and believe, truth from @MartinUsborne : http://t.co/ZZm7qYCkM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 297: A SMALL THOUGHT ON KINDNESS http://t.co/P4ww0mt253]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 296: RESCUING 7 BABY TORTOISES. DO SEVEN RIGHTS CORRECT ONE WRONG?? http://t.co/C4VDqdxShN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tracey_crouch are you available to be interviewed about the badger cull? I'm writing a book about wildlife welfare and saw you in debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorServais thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessWhite99 @pupaid thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog post here: http://t.co/cL0YylOEFA DAY 293: DEEP IN THE JUNGLE, BUT WHERE ARE THE PANGOS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: If you want to help stop the dog meat trade Two charities you must support my http://t.co/CnVHH9pDqG and @SoiDogPhuket they…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 294: RELEASING WILD ANIMALS FROM JUNGLE MARKET GOES A LITTLE WRONG  http://t.co/wkco6nPy0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pupaid: SO CLOSE to 40,000 signatures pls keep RTing for these poor puppy farm dogs http://t.co/hXWoAXfdam #wheresmum http://t.co/kdIQx…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A VERY IMPORTANT POST FROM A BLOG READER REGARDING GREYHOUNDS IN EUROPE / UK : http://t.co/eOEgcACfH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 291: FOUND IT! OUTSIDE THE HQ OF ASIA’S MOST WANTED #ILLEGAL #WILDLIFE  #TRADER read here - http://t.co/biMQKd9js2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks also to @HungerMagazine and Luke Evans for the mention on Hunger TV. Click here: http://t.co/3iLpxaA2pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs in Cars, Nice to Meet You and A Year to Help all mentioned by @TheWeek read here: http://t.co/qosRZSajkB http://t.co/3uFMZYPQqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 289: SPOTTING MY FIRST ILLEGAL PANGOLIN TRADE TRUCK http://t.co/mFj3QBbL4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iddley ha! You are wonderful!! Thank you a million!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @myLaurenHansen: Our @theweek photo blog ventures into original content with @MartinUsborne's haunting, emotive photographs of dogs http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheWeek: Check out these hauntingly beautiful photos of dogs from @MartinUsborne: http://t.co/cUvKKgp72i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 287: #PANGOLIN EXPERT SENDS ME OUT ALONG MEKONG RIVER TO TRACK #WILDLIFE #TRADE http://t.co/fiwRmrC4oR http://t.co/LS16VmBVYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Podenco Martin is now with his wonderful new family in Belgium!!! read more … http://t.co/Zs4f4uRIgX http://t.co/IdrjSvlVPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW BLOG POST: DAY 283: I’M OFF TO LAOS TO GET CLOSER TO #PANGOLINS http://t.co/SZ5CFlMiW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeanP thank you, very kind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeanP @pupaid @marcthevet yes, I must make it to that. I know marc, incredible what he does!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The silence of pigs in pens http://t.co/wgpIeCQ75t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeanP yes I know those great organisations.., and also @AllDogsMatter !! See you on Heath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SerenaCowdy yes I saw he's a pangolin fan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning on the mekong river I witnessed the site where hundreds of pangolins were illegally smuggled from thailand to laos. Grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mafaldabulli nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SerenaCowdy Thanks! Such a terrible story out in Asia with the pangolin trade and no-one in the west seems to know. tragic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hic_clix_pix: One man's amazing year saving animals here http://t.co/gFdiMAHuoC  and his amazing photography here http://t.co/ZNAMSZyLT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't already please join YTH FB page for pics &amp; discussions about my year long project helping animals http://t.co/eOEgcACfH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 280: DOGS AWAITING SLAUGHTER WEIGH HEAVY ON MY MIND AS I VISIT RESCUED PANGOLINS IN HANOI http://t.co/WtyfIyxnX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wayneford: @Detritusphoto I like "Juliette," but agree with you about @MartinUsborne's book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 279: TWO PUPPIES SAVED FROM DOG MEAT TRADE – CAN YOU HELP ME NAME THEM? http://t.co/bPhTpXN6wJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 277: UP PANGOLIN CREEK WITHOUT A PADDLE http://t.co/Sd9KDGBaVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nydailynews: Woman fired, even after donating a kidney to her boss! http://t.co/rMq2alv5tu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @boobygraffoe: Get them in front of a mirror and they go on and on and on…. http://t.co/tI72PirM8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @boobygraffoe: Kim Jong-un makes further threats to America. http://t.co/RTQTKatgyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @boobygraffoe: Large increase in the number of invisible people opening bank accounts. (pic via @BestEarthPix) http://t.co/ko2heJoMTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @boobygraffoe: "Who ate all the flies?" http://t.co/jtbtbEkjTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edielush I'm your 1000th!! I'm flattered!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marianimalover Thank you Mariana - I might be coming soon actually! TBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the pain I'm seeing out here I'm desperately f***king grateful for what I have- to my wife, family, friends and dogs...thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marianimalover thanks for being in touch. just in the middle of planning our honeymoon in mexico! Where is the shelter located?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAR_updates indeed. Horrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iddley I really appreciate that. I'm not great at asking strangers like that so its really kind of you to push it. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper @AllDogsMatter ha! Perhaps that's next! But tomorrow's event should be v fun and its for a wonderful charity!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those of you in London tomorrow check out @AllDogsMatter's Pup Idol! http://t.co/IaYqGHb7C0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAR_updates so tempted to buy and rescue but that just adds fuel to fire. Torn #EndTheDogMeatTrade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iddley yay!! Is she an animal fan??? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs waiting for throat cutting in Vietnam restaurant cell, can't bear it. Sorry, grim but true http://t.co/xwibq7wi46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonSugdess set up, with 3-4 lights each and 1 week planning every shot. Thankfully not many dogs left in cars in UK !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 274: MEET ‘LUCKY’ THE #PANGOLIN  http://t.co/sUO7T1zucx #vietnam @SavePangolins @wspauk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hackneycitizen: East London publishers Hoxton Mini Press launch Kickstarter campaign @MartinUsborne #Hackney http://t.co/uyL3xBZB0X via…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For updates on our new books all about east london please follow @HoxtonMiniPress http://t.co/0QK655NJfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoxtonminipress new books finally about to launch! watch our intro video here http://t.co/2N7udL4WEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 'Fox About Town' book featured in @Telegraph article about the fantastic @NazraeliPress One Picture Books. http://t.co/Nf5lVv1yGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 348: ENTERING A PIG FARM UNANNOUNCED. OOPS http://t.co/UHFw68u78M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheodoraLuca: "As things go more #virtual there's something incredibly important about the #book as a beautiful object" @MartinUsborne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheodoraLuca great you found your way to @HoxtonMiniPress. Our Kickstarter campaign launches on Monday. pls help spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarovanStudios: Rescued a fledgling pigeon from bring pecked to death by magpie on the road. Add to #yeartohelp list @MartinUsborne htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 346: GOING UNDERCOVER INTO A SPANISH PIG FARM - PLEASE PASS THESE IMAGES ON http://t.co/j2CazAOcij http://t.co/OydVBN90yl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 343: THE DIRTY FACE OF SPANISH PIG FARMING  http://t.co/QBykLl2KHM http://t.co/koQnZK5Drp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieASharp sounds terrible. I need to read more about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarovanStudios amazing! where did you find it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 340: THE LONG (BUT BRIEF) JOURNEY OF AN EU PIG FROM BIRTH TO DEATH  http://t.co/2hlkCaLGQv http://t.co/0RSzsN2zQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 336: I HAVE A DREAM....... that one day #badgers will not be shot http://t.co/mxeUG9UK9o #stopthecull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RSPCA_official: Petition to #stopthecull is so close to 300,000 signatures. Please sign &amp; RT! http://t.co/Ho3KzwfBuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Badgergate: #stopthecull petition above 300,000 - biggest petition ever by a long way. The UK public have spoken - badger cull must be …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 335: OH BUGGER, THEY’VE STARTED RANDOMLY SHOOTING BRITAIN’S MOST ICONIC ANIMAL  http://t.co/mfGBVHNIXU #badger #stopthecull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop puppy farming and com to pup Aid tomorrow. Sign the Pup Aid e-petition #wheresmum http://t.co/cqQDTCwzOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 333: TAKING PIGS FOR A WALK IN LONDON IS HARDER THAN YOU THINK. http://t.co/rKsQO0WEZt http://t.co/LA2eYqRPX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 331: TEN FAST FACTS ABOUT PIGS…OINK OINK!  http://t.co/baV63e6BtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jo_barefoot: 'We don’t need to teach compassion so much as to stop unlearning it.' @MartinUsborne http://t.co/Az7HKQIO6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoorSpelling thanks Phil. that was shot on the beach in Northwest Wales - same as my fav image of Shep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SmoothYeti: In celebration of International Dog Day. The Silence of Dogs in Cars by @MartinUsborne http://t.co/kSNtJGS6j0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hellokel thanks! Glad to hear you found your way to Year to Help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @transparentcts: In Nice to Meet You, @MartinUsborne shoots portrait of dogs photographed through a material http://t.co/TIjxfKw3YE http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarovanStudios fantastic. well done you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarovanStudios: @MartinUsborne saved 6 ducklings from abandonment http://t.co/9tQHjfJh1w &amp; rehomed them at http://t.co/eIgTRD69S1 http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EFTuttle thanks for sharing emily!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 325: INTENSIVE FARMING IS THE GREATEST CAUSE OF SUFFERING ON EARTH – DISCUSS  http://t.co/202fvX6h6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thanks to Katherine Carver for the great interview about Year to Help! Read it here: http://t.co/jhmMVFyJq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciwf Intensive farming is the greatest cause of suffering on earth - thoughts?   http://t.co/a3457XSb0M]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>