<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Developer, Tools Reporting: Card Services Job Talent Network Form Join our Talent Network! Thank you for your interest in Alliance Data! Please fill out the information below to receive updates on available opportunities. *First Name *Last Name… https://t.co/UQuLEXqefO https://t.co/Zg1ADrocpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Scrum Master: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-PA-Fort Washington Posting Description Aon Is Looking For A Scrum Master As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by delivering innovative and… https://t.co/I3OrEOuijZ https://t.co/sdWDj0NUkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – TS/SCI Required: As a Software Engineer at Synergist, you will work with a team of developers on a specific project critical to one of our customer’s needs. You’ll be an active contributor on an Agile Software development team to… https://t.co/wQyvuVWS10 https://t.co/vWEAr4l5Xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal System Engineer: Boeing Intelligence &amp; Analytics (BI&amp;A) is a leading provider of strategic capabilities to the United States Intelligence Community. We help Customers identify and develop strategies to counter the strengths and exploit the… https://t.co/hi8Babkn0b https://t.co/ezQZKSWzTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer/Data Ingestion Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Reston, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/6/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/KGgF1lSLFb https://t.co/tgdlgA8u5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include… https://t.co/IzBTX3moLI https://t.co/FGG5UtQvmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist I: IT Specialist I Job Description and Duties This position performs work within the IT Project Management and Business Technology Management domains. IT Project Management is the management or oversight of all phases of project management… https://t.co/8GE8H7LLQn https://t.co/enGoASCs5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla seeks to dismiss securities fraud lawsuit: U.S. court document: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Tesla Inc on Friday asked a court to dismiss a securities fraud lawsuit by shareholders who said the electric vehicle maker gave false public statements about… https://t.co/8d1NxEFwqH https://t.co/NBmDypPkUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Expert: Cybersecurity Expert Job Summary IRG is looking for a dedicated and meticulous cybersecurity specialist to join our growing team associates. In the role, you will operate independently and as part of a team to ensure our clients’… https://t.co/jrIz8VwAHw https://t.co/iAUZJXIL5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent's WeChat drops 'sugar daddy' dating website: BEIJING (Reuters) - China's top social media app WeChat has removed "sugar daddy" dating website SeekingArrangement from its platform, after a recent surge in the popularity of the U.S.-founded service… https://t.co/P1K2NWJsGa https://t.co/iqM4DG5E1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Services – Irvine, California Software Development Engineer II – Design, develop, implement, test, &amp; document software apps, tools, systems &amp; services. Multiple job openings. Equal opportunity… https://t.co/38SopMB9HK https://t.co/8s3QMskPgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Engineer: QualitrolTech Inc. seeks Sr. Integration Engineer. Duties are to design and develop integration software codes and packages based on web Methods Integration Server &amp; related software platforms. Education Requirements:… https://t.co/qNFzPoAkbJ https://t.co/CIZBL6BJta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Tesla flies in new battery production line for Gigafactory: FRANKFURT/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Tesla Inc has flown six planes full of robots and equipment from Europe to California in an unusual, high-stakes effort to speed up battery… https://t.co/fh7a3O2c4v https://t.co/fyVyWhHD1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazilian electronics company Multilaser files for IPO: SAO PAULO (Reuters) - Brazilian electronics company Multilaser Industrial SA on Thursday filed for regulatory clearance to launch an initial public offering, according to a securities filing. https://t.co/n32ejeMBwa https://t.co/srbHmRjHRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Analyst, Marketing Analyst: PayPal, Inc. has the following job opportunities in San Jose, CA: Director, Data Science 1 (Req.#09-581): Design, dvlp &amp; maintain predictive statistical models used for risk mgmt. Innovate &amp; improve PayPal’s fraud… https://t.co/sJCrMei3hf https://t.co/qbTMSPGIlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: You. As a Project Manager, you’ll be an expert in delivery planning and project management a go-to person to figure out how to make a great idea a reality. Youll work directly with a variety of clients and be responsible for the planning… https://t.co/B7RMlX85E6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FMV Instructor/ Developer: FMV Instructor/ Developer job in McLean, Virginia, United States | Intelligence jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp;… https://t.co/oycaEjKdGH https://t.co/5aMkJ4kocx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= AWS Solutions Architect Cloud Computing Stafford, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a AWS Solutions Architect that is passionate about developing and executing… https://t.co/JIV1UwcTbE https://t.co/x7pP8zgQ4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Publicis starts test phase of 'Marcel' internal network aimed at performance boost: PARIS (Reuters) - Advertising group Publicis will unveil its internal collaborative network "Marcel" on Thursday and hopes to have 90 percent of its staff using it by… https://t.co/cB0RNWkfDW https://t.co/Kim3Gj9Y6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Operations/Systems Analyst – ORCA: Metron | Careers |Associate Operations/Systems Analyst – ORCA Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/7BPDQqO0KT https://t.co/TI1sZxBlqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Development Manager: Java Development Manager McLean, VA Prestigious Organization is seeking a Java Development Manager. This position is part of the Investments and Capital Markets Division Business Technology Organization. The position will be… https://t.co/FpPBzXFt4K https://t.co/y8fKemwM6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Front End Software Engineer: Division: Digital Factory Business Unit: Product Lifecycle Management-PLM Requisition Number: ****** Primary Location: United States-Alabama-Huntsville Assignment Category: Full-time regular Experience Level: Mid… https://t.co/A0SrP4bnZX https://t.co/h65Ntkp9Fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber shuts Arizona self-driving program two months after fatal crash: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Uber has shut down its self-driving car operation in Arizona two months after a fatal crash involving one of its vehicles, the company said on Wednesday. https://t.co/DDo6CtIkxB https://t.co/fwra25d4Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Specialist: COMPUTER/IT Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) wrk in crss-fnctnl dvlpmnt or tstng team w/ focus on QA &amp; tst rltd tasks w/in prdct creatn prcss. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd &amp; 5 yrs exp req’d… https://t.co/4KzZtJbiIh https://t.co/qRmN77A75w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber ends Arizona self-driving program following fatality: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Uber has shut down its self-driving car operation in Arizona two months after a fatal crash involving one of its vehicles, the company said on Wednesday. https://t.co/Euyt6WS9dr https://t.co/WVNdMMVpcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber firms warn on suspected Russian plan to attack Ukraine: (Reuters) - Cisco Systems Inc on Wednesday warned that hackers have infected at least 500,000 routers and storage devices in dozens of countries with highly sophisticated malicious software,… https://t.co/BocfnfooV2 https://t.co/Jx5m3BEeHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile payment firms struggle to dethrone cash in Southeast Asia: SINGAPORE/HANOI (Reuters) - Bui Mai Phuong is an avid online shopper, ordering anything from clothing to personal-care products from her smartphone. But she prefers to pay with cash. https://t.co/tuoGafHV0J https://t.co/llldw6is2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn unit aims to raise $4.3 billion in biggest China IPO since 2015: TAIPEI/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Foxconn Industrial Internet , a subsidiary of the world's largest contract manufacturer Foxconn , said it plans to raise 27.1 billion yuan ($4.26… https://t.co/MXNGtgclYb https://t.co/QnyKXgHheD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Grand Lake Mental Health Center, Inc. Claremore, OK Desktop Support Technician. We are currently seeking a Desktop Support Technician with at least three (3) years of experience in computer repair and maintenance. Some basic… https://t.co/DdLlwHzQcd https://t.co/pQjyUJLhCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Senior Project Consultant-Development for SAP Labs, LLC (South San Francisco, CA) under suprvsn, wrk on small to midsize prjcts in dvlopmnt org w/modrte lvl of rsk &amp; cmplxty. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd field &amp; 6 yrs… https://t.co/lNZt0REaES https://t.co/xeDxnqMeQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Staff Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Responsible for ensuring software components are expertly designed, tested, debugged and ready for integration into the product line. Build out new applications and features… https://t.co/3qHDC0tTny https://t.co/8DaRpIZ0Bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's Zuckerberg arrives for grilling by EU lawmakers over data leak: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Facebook boss Mark Zuckerberg has arrived to meet leaders of the European Parliament to answer questions about how the data of millions of Facebook users… https://t.co/1wsrbE1t45 https://t.co/qtFGQVoqyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Algorithm Developer – Engineer: We are looking for an experienced algorithm developer to come on board to lead development of technology that will play an important role in how people will find jobs in the future. Our international team gets along very… https://t.co/Pl3GbapwgF https://t.co/vs46xEMtX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber pulls up in Japan with taxi-hailing service: TOKYO (Reuters) - Uber Technologies plans to launch its first taxi-hailing pilot service in Japan that will connect passengers to other taxi providers, as it seeks to expand in the country where the U.S.… https://t.co/fpyUi6HJtT https://t.co/7ER9DIpJAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. will lift sales ban order against China's ZTE: WSJ: BEIJING (Reuters) - The U.S. government will lift an order banning U.S. companies from selling components and software to China's ZTE Corp , the Wall Street Journal reported on its Chinese… https://t.co/fjt2WPtQSY https://t.co/RgWqyjq5p9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Micron to buy back up to $10 billion of shares: (Reuters) - Memory chipmaker Micron Technology Inc said on Monday it would buy back up to $10 billion of its shares, in conjunction with its newly announced plans to return at least 50 percent of free cash… https://t.co/2CBFx1AFfK https://t.co/GIUHSHwJqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: COMPUTER/IT Senior Project Consultant-Development for SAP Labs, LLC (South San Francisco, CA) under suprvsn, wrk on small to midsize prjcts in dvlopmnt org w/modrte lvl of rsk &amp; cmplxty. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd… https://t.co/xuT39hXFrW https://t.co/IkQkxVXMVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst / Software Engineer: COMPUTER Miri Infotech Inc. seeks Programmer Analyst/ Software Engg. In Fremont, CA for design, develop, test &amp; support s/w projects in C#, https://t.co/zjXQhVObQU, https://t.co/r7mq3XiKT5, SQL, HTML, XML.… https://t.co/bjq8UYYulc https://t.co/EXeMasCzki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Analyst: QA ANALYST Oracle America, Inc. has openings for QA Analysts positions in Redwood Shores, CA. Job duties include: Develop, apply, maintain, and improve quality methods, procedures, and standards for company products. As a member of the… https://t.co/B09EELmQE7 https://t.co/cFVwctO6oU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineer IV #AMZ2547: https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Services, Inc. – Austin, TX. Support Engineer IV – Provide technical support, including fielding &amp; handling customer issues via phone, chat, &amp; email. Multiple job openings.  Equal Opportunity… https://t.co/OWpKuQxU6Q https://t.co/ajQPTOJ5A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Model 3 price hype helps Tesla shares bounce: (Reuters) - Shares in Tesla Inc jumped more than 4 percent on Monday as investors were encouraged by the company's placing a $78,000 price tag on the fully-loaded version of its Model 3 sedan. https://t.co/FIlILOuGmB https://t.co/3SQFI3t84g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/ufKL3mGzef https://t.co/avTdiFwKhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab to partner with Maybank for mobile wallet in Malaysia: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Ride-hailing firm Grab will partner with Malayan Banking Bhd (Maybank), Malaysia's biggest bank, to drive the usage and adoption of its GrabPay mobile wallet, the companies… https://t.co/59s99dDa4U https://t.co/ddZNCvUTbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Systems Analyst II – Epic Cupid: Clinical Systems Analyst II – Epic Cupid (45800) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 45800 Job Description At Stanford Health Care we’re… https://t.co/nZn87e9bBU https://t.co/kW7HnMdDOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Deployment Specialist Principal: Location: Springfield, Virginia Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Office Job Summary The Systems Deployment Specialist Principal is responsible for installation of new Windows\Unix based… https://t.co/rD0HmDJbQV https://t.co/MN8gjd4pbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redshift Application DBA: Redshift Application DBA Ref No.: 18-21647 Location: Peapack, New Jersey Role: Redshift Application DBA Location: Peapack, NJ Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Should have strong exp. working with Redshift… https://t.co/yOL0rDnT8c https://t.co/49IqtFPm8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: R0001570 Front End DeveloperJob Responsibilities * Work with different development and QA teams to code HTML/CSS mockups, test, and verify projects through development process. * Oversee site optimization for SEO, cleaner and concise… https://t.co/4tOIJmsCZP https://t.co/sAdDA3YNkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer, Senior Consultant (Chicago): Big Data Engineering Sr Consultant / Manager is a member of the delivery team. This role leads architecture, design and implementation of projects focused on collecting, aggregating, storing, reconciling… https://t.co/MavR7GKTNN https://t.co/ywsaAFziLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: OCR ensures compliance for international trade through a comprehensive solution that improves operations, complies with government regulations, saves money and provides a competitive advantage. OCRs solutions enable global corporations to… https://t.co/IGdCOQlG8J https://t.co/wK3Wuuqf33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build/Devops Engineer: Build Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time position Job Description: 10+ years of software development, build infrastructure engineering experience Expertise in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery Experience with build… https://t.co/4KPn7iZNUc https://t.co/Uq70wmqHd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain to tackle 'Wild West' internet with new laws: LONDON (Reuters) - Britain will tackle "the Wild West elements" on the internet from cyberbullying to online child exploitation by introducing new laws for social media companies, digital minister… https://t.co/SyGOAOvgvZ https://t.co/XQ7h6IvVsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Manager Scrum Master: Are you an experienced development team lead who is looking for a challenging role in a fast paced environment? Do you have a knack for problem solving? Are you able to multi-task and influence for technical excellence?… https://t.co/WkSKLD4aU3 https://t.co/j2ckUXM67r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title Computer Security Analyst (ISSO): Job Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 3 weeks ago(4/19/2018 9:16 AM) Requisition ID 2018-3278 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development company headquartered in… https://t.co/fp1Sbuy2Ft https://t.co/fcVrquhzh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Web and Mobile: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is… https://t.co/GdmRAtJTNc https://t.co/T0Mh28OeYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Infrastructure Engineer – Senior: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented API Infrastructure Engineers – Senior Level for our Plano, TX facility. USAA API Infrastructure Engineers create and maintain critical infrastructure services for our… https://t.co/4a6SzOmu3e https://t.co/YZ9wsR52o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Management Trainee: If youre looking to jump-start your career with a clear path to advancement, then the Enterprise Management Training Program is for you. Whether you see yourself in sales, business development, customer service or operations,… https://t.co/KAfOrgF3bv https://t.co/8Pe5uIlWZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: The challenge Digital marketing is advancing at a dizzying pace and companies are turning to the Adobe Marketing Cloud, the leader in enterprise marketing software, to stay ahead. Solution Architects help Adobe Marketing Cloud… https://t.co/QlqTvE2sUJ https://t.co/51twvj8nxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Information Security Advisor: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Information Security Advisor Senior for our San Antonio, TX facility. Provides thought leadership while managing multiple initiatives. Collaborates with all levels of… https://t.co/hmAGcNyun6 https://t.co/JkG6cRP6Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! * Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/OmjDxEmEP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Database Administrator – DBA 4:   Job Description – Senior Oracle Database Administrator – DBA 4 (18009321) Senior Oracle Database Administrator – DBA 4 Requisition ID : 18009321 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US Citizenship… https://t.co/U0MYTB4UrN https://t.co/IgJyLT30rZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Database Administrator Infrastructure Washington, District Of Columbia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Database Administrator that is passionate about cutting edge… https://t.co/bSGcy19GvW https://t.co/XLpEHKpRIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer with AWS CLI: We are one of the most successful lifestyle companies in the country and we need a Sr. DevOps Engineer with in depth MySQL and AWS knowledge to join our infrastructure team. We have a massive road map ahead of us,… https://t.co/rTfWLb686t https://t.co/fMp5FPSEtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proxy adviser ISS recommends votes against two Tesla directors: BOSTON (Reuters) - Proxy adviser Institutional Shareholder Services recommended on Friday that investors cast proxy votes against Tesla Inc directors Antonio Gracias and James Murdoch. https://t.co/lCXA9GetCa https://t.co/YxnKrRG1v6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Consultant/Developer #AS-LCD042018: ThoughtWorks Inc. seeks Lead Consultant/Developer in Chicago , IL &amp; various unanticipated U.S. locations. Requirements: Bachelor’s in CS, Computer Engineering or related + 5 years post bachelors experience in job… https://t.co/i2fxH5Rcfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple pays Ireland first tranche of disputed taxes: DUBLIN (Reuters) - Apple has paid 1.5 billion euros ($1.18 billion) into an escrow account set up by the Irish government to hold 13 billion euros ($16 billion) in disputed taxes, Finance Minister… https://t.co/k7EDoeHc7y https://t.co/ZFbLCQ8K8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMOTE Regional Sales Manager: Pittsburgh, PA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Regional Sales Manager with experience in security sales, please read on! We are the leader in third-party risk management and cyber threat intelligence,… https://t.co/T64yhgs8ZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18258 Location: Plano, Texas Job Title : SharePoint Developer Location : Plano, TX Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Responsible for specific architecture and technology decisions such as… https://t.co/DrINlyc6tu https://t.co/TSr3ejgX7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica files for Chapter 7 bankruptcy: (Reuters) - Cambridge Analytica, the firm at the center of this year's Facebook privacy row, filed for voluntary Chapter 7 bankruptcy in a New York court late on Thursday. https://t.co/MxxiB4355e https://t.co/FSKjzeDNce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer: * What youll be doing: * Working on a team alongside other talented engineers, designers and content creators developing quality software that is used by some of the worlds largest technology firms, fixed income asset managers, and… https://t.co/WRwM4AzyNM https://t.co/dnp3X7sYI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead Java: To provide senior level IT technical lead services, including the direction, evaluation, selection, configuration, implementation, and integration of new or existing technologies and tools. This position is for an NGA technical lead… https://t.co/DTP7jK7dmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBOL Developers: COBOL Developers Location: Pontiac, MI Job Code: 1739 # of openings: 8 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/9c8uIVUxyq https://t.co/NV6uyQrnSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instacart faces new challenge with Kroger/Ocado tie-up: LOS ANGELES/NEW YORK (Reuters) - U.S. grocery delivery company Instacart suffered a new setback on Thursday when Kroger Co , one of its major U.S. customers, announced a partnership with British… https://t.co/12SDU5IRmb https://t.co/tKpDCkpn6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayPal in advanced talks to buy Sweden's iZettle: Sky News: (Reuters) - PayPal Holdings Inc is in advanced talks to buy Swedish payment group iZettle, Sky News reported on Thursday, citing sources familiar with the matter. https://t.co/nP1rLtg0nZ https://t.co/Q6UW8IKACU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley startup peddles 3D-printed bike: (Reuters) - After a career that included helping Alphabet Inc's Google build out data centers and speeding packages for https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc to customers, Jim Miller is doing what many Silicon Valley… https://t.co/W2qm3R6F99 https://t.co/bVxXZqYF8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Engineer: Nuvi aggregates hundreds of millions of pieces of social content that are created every day via Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, and just about every internet publishing outlet on the web. We help the worlds leading brands and… https://t.co/6QwThzQlgh https://t.co/ZevwkE04Go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Engineer: 114565BR Job Description: The Raytheon Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) Business has many exciting programs currently under development with key programs located in Richardson, Texas. The Raytheon Intelligence, Information… https://t.co/M90UTtWklK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube to launch new music streaming service on May 22: (Reuters) - Google's YouTube said on Wednesday it will launch a new music streaming service, YouTube Music, next week and unveil soon a premium service that will charge more for its original shows. https://t.co/elnNWY1AGn https://t.co/NvDS0C54v9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Soros' bet on Tesla could see other investors follow suit: NEW YORK (Reuters) - If Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk needs to raise even more money, there may be a way. https://t.co/ZzfwA30ee1 https://t.co/P3kzwRxmDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Specialist: IT Support Specialist CCHS is looking for an IT Support Specialist to join our team of caring professionals here in the Kanawha Valley. This position will be a full time position with some travel required between our various sites… https://t.co/009oUqDNLd https://t.co/bRbT81Uqwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Data Science: PayPal, Inc. has the following job opportunities in San Jose, CA: Director, Data Science 1 (Req.#09-581): Design, dvlp &amp; maintain predictive statistical models used for risk mgmt. Innovate &amp; improve PayPal’s fraud prevention &amp;… https://t.co/uhHWSrdgIe https://t.co/jxXCdJXSLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. net neutrality bill advances in the Senate: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Senate voted 52 to 47 to advance a bill that would reverse the Federal Communications Commission decision in December to repeal landmark 2015 net neutrality rules. https://t.co/DzxbMLTXiA https://t.co/guGZeq259Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix's next act: feeding the service with its own movies: LOS ANGELES (Reuters) - As Hollywood studios unleash their summer blockbusters into theaters, Netflix Inc is trying to give film buffs a reason to stay home. https://t.co/dqgVRaqidJ https://t.co/nlmLZKiWW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET / SQL Server Developer (Presentation Layer): C#/.NET Developer (Presentation Layer) In search of a C#/NET Developer with focus on the presentation layer and conversational user interface. In addition to C#/.NET, applicants must have or quickly… https://t.co/k9D7fZUz1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon cuts Whole Foods prices for Prime members in new grocery showdown: (Reuters) - https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc and Whole Foods Market are making a surgical strike in the already brutal grocery price war. https://t.co/3SBjmxBhju https://t.co/TakSBZp9Sy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber attack delays Atlanta mayor's first budget pitch: (Reuters) - Atlanta's 2019 budget process has been delayed by a March cyber attack that scrambled a swath of government data, temporarily closing courts, halting bill payments and slowing other key… https://t.co/nQ4fBtNH6r https://t.co/WaigvnZbsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter changes strategy in battle against internet 'trolls': SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Twitter Inc on Tuesday revised its strategy for fighting abusive internet "trolls," saying it would use behavioral signals to identify harassers on the social network… https://t.co/kEFLqidlbD https://t.co/typ9ZD54L7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering – Multiple Positions: ENGINEERING Atlassian, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks: 1) Principal Trust Engineers to collaborate and craft deliverables as part of technology team working to build infrastructure and scale that drives technical… https://t.co/svDuZfhony https://t.co/9SIg5ZsWZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Positions: Sr. Systems Administrator (Sacramento): Responsible for managing all service delivery resilience, efficiency, and audit programs as well as ensuring engineering standards and products are integrated across the ESX estate. Responsible… https://t.co/oXd9hzMHQ5 https://t.co/qT0CDATjfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Technician: Network Technician About University at Albany: Established in 1844 and designated a University Center of the State University of New York in 1962, the University at Albany’s broad mission of excellence in undergraduate and graduate… https://t.co/QMVQYneqYG https://t.co/025c5eBrvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Director Solutions Design: Job ID: BDP-******* Description: As the healthcare industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable healthcare for… https://t.co/Fxac98vXzS https://t.co/GRxkWIPCur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, IT Business Partner: Under Armour is all about performance. Because what we make empowers athletes in every form to push themselves, to turn good into great, and to stay hungry for whatever comes next. And this is exactly what we expect from… https://t.co/Gwh0uW6wlY https://t.co/xNh0m6qIH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Municipal Assistant Project Manager: Discipline Municipal Job Location(s) US-NJ-Mt. Arlington Type Regular Full-Time Use your browser ‘Back’ button to return to job listings Responsibilities * Site Investigation &amp; Due Diligence includes the review of… https://t.co/kvnoxdDaZo https://t.co/K4ifdwIcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Sales Manager #171688: Technical Sales Manager Zilker Technology, Austin, TX. Software solutions. Requires BA (or foreign equivalent) in Software Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, or related + 5 years experience software… https://t.co/aYFfSHcMgi https://t.co/Fj1ByFLj0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Symantec says investigating reporting of certain accounting measures: (Reuters) - Symantec Corp said on Monday it is investigating company's reporting of certain non-GAAP measures including those that could impact executive compensation programs, stock… https://t.co/s7907g3GhY https://t.co/1IhAR3CkWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Designer and Technical Manager: Website Designer and Technical Manager The Office of Public Relations at Saint Vincent Archabbey and Seminary currently has an opening for a part-time temporary Website Design and Technical Manager. This position… https://t.co/041Q2lsfiw https://t.co/NJdvHsURKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Data Interchance (EDI) Manager: Littelfuse, Inc. seeks Electronic Data Interchance (EDI) Manager in Chicago, IL to dsgn, dev &amp; spprt B2B Intgrtr app btwn LFUS &amp; trdng prtnrs. Reqs BS in Elctrcl/Elctrncs Engnrng, IT or rltd + 3 yrs exp; 3 yrs… https://t.co/waD9g2ifoX https://t.co/egz6wWyUEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer II – Embedded #2018-43845: Engineer II – Embedded sought by DISH Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Maintain and develop Set-Top Box (STB) software; design, develop, and test embedded C/C++, QML, and JavaScript code for the User Interface of the… https://t.co/AcE2V5Z2Bm https://t.co/7WD9JNzeOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thieves suck millions out of Mexican banks in transfer heist: MEXICO CITY (Reuters) - Thieves siphoned hundreds of millions of pesos out of Mexican banks, including No. 2 Banorte, by creating phantom orders that wired funds to fake accounts and promptly… https://t.co/ckpvkgKnF3 https://t.co/ZZwDmdlzjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Test Engineer: Job Posting Title Sr. Software Test Engineer Summary This role is for mPower test engineering team that consists of White-box and black-box test engineers. Charter of this role will be to test C++ based Game Development Kits… https://t.co/XgQFj9dOqh https://t.co/4heC7Nkc1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HSBC says performs first trade finance deal using single blockchain system: HONG KONG (Reuters) - HSBC Holdings Plc said on Monday it has performed the world's first trade finance transaction using a single blockchain platform, in a push to boost… https://t.co/w18n2fBPJ8 https://t.co/6DLkiPiTAc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>