<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Support Engineer: Java Application Support Engineer at Fiserv, Inc. Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations –… https://t.co/73m10LO5nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27896 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 12 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Core Java… https://t.co/jMPmME3AFy https://t.co/uqKmDyPt1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Full Stack Developer: **Sr. Java Full Stack Developer** Locations:Charlotte, North Carolina Job Family: Information Technology New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/6qBkil9V5A https://t.co/LSzJQESCK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer: Apply now Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer ============================================= Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business:… https://t.co/744QmXN7ul https://t.co/ggAEe6QZho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: SR. LEVEL JAVA DEVELOPER – AUSTIN Excellent opportunity in the Austin area to capitalize your career with a global, Fortune 50 Company. Our client is seeking a high-achieving professional that can create innovative software in an… https://t.co/MpCqg3FtIU https://t.co/riiTieXiic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Microservices Developer: Sr Java Developer Ref No.: 18-23246 Location: McLean, Virginia Position: Sr Java Developer Location: McLean, VA MUST HAVE SKILLS – Solid Java and Spring framework knowledge – Expertise in producing and consuming message with… https://t.co/trWzf3ocYz https://t.co/7bkOuntSg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Des Moines, Iowa – United States Job Start Date – 03/26/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview The Java Developer is part of the CORE team within the Consumer Lending Technology Group. This role… https://t.co/zbDpn8BFM4 https://t.co/CjsEl4kJR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer SSO: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be responsible for providing software design and development, and second line production support for our external customers’ single sign-on suite of applications supporting Verizon’s… https://t.co/Jcm6ueEJLk https://t.co/raXGJnhsd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer at American Express Java Developer Palo Alto, California, United States Contract Do you have the ability to put together unique cutting-edge customer facing solutions that increase business value and customer engagement by… https://t.co/rBaK6tvldm https://t.co/1uTDrvuDBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job ID: ********-11836-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: Senior Java Developer ClaimXperience is searching for a dynamic and creative Senior Java Developer who has the knowledge and experience to help shape our industry… https://t.co/eVcog0SX28 https://t.co/2rX1YjgyDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer Java: Lead Software Developer – Java, #15690BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance… https://t.co/2ZkATJ9OBI https://t.co/wWWxvXoNIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverview Job Description * Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field and 3 years experience building… https://t.co/ZM3yMwCVzP https://t.co/gOqf170RCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-RNC finance chairman's former mistress sues him over hush money: The former mistress of former Republican National Committee Finance Chairman Elliott Broidy, who signed a $1.6 million agreement that included a confidentiality clause to keep their… https://t.co/qRZNroUBWV https://t.co/yhznhzmTbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer in Coppell, TX at Brink’s – Careers Home – About Brink’s – Veterans – – Featured Careers – Driver-Messenger – Cash Logistics Processors – Corporate – All Jobs – Join Our Talent Network SEARCH OUR JOBS Keyword:… https://t.co/bDUFy5X8xZ https://t.co/Z2at0zFXqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer: Java Fullstack Developer Ref No.: 18-29063 Location: San Antonio, Texas Hello, Greetings for the day! We have an urgent requirement for Java Fullstack Developer with Angular JS in San Antonio, TX. Please let me know if you are… https://t.co/6E8YHxqLhT https://t.co/xAFT0BdEQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger, Mickelson plan $10M match-play battle https://t.co/oxyKN2t1eo https://t.co/GUT2QGYHPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer: JAVA Developer Ref No.:18-10346 Location: Sunnyvale , CA Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/08/2018 Title: JAVA Developer Location: Sunnyvale, CA Job Type: Contract Job description Java Development: Expertise in Core Java Concepts… https://t.co/NTIOXAPxCk https://t.co/wAgOFaqvQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – Scenario Analysis / Analytics: Summary: The Java Developer for engineering works in a new product area related to financial analytics. The initiative will focus on scenario analysis for risk-return measurement at the instrument… https://t.co/rIe8vMDVBn https://t.co/tRA5spPvzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump's wish for Supreme Court may take him down: Despite what many of us want to believe, President Donald Trump is the front-runner in 2020. If you supported him in 2016, you have little reason to regret your choice -- he's working hard to… https://t.co/SsS2oez2AE https://t.co/LCmGpurycB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Washington, DC Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment… https://t.co/iyYvYKerDF https://t.co/y9Mr8LQlvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API: Java API Ref No.: 18-24345 Location: Monterey Park, California Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 10 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Java API Programmer… https://t.co/2Q6yilcT50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Java Developer: About Avaya Avaya enables the mission critical, real-time communication applications of the world’s most important operations. As a global leader in delivering superior communications experiences, Avaya offers a complete… https://t.co/gBZ8I3AUbr https://t.co/HUx53ELML1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's #MeToo swipe updates his 2016 playbook: President Donald Trump understands what got him elected -- a willingness to throw caution and decorum to the wind and to assail what his supporters see as rampant political correctness. https://t.co/ybkYHbGdWn https://t.co/7RZkk0Py08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt resigns as head of the EPA: After months of scandal and more than a dozen separate investigations into his lavish spending habits while in office, Scott Pruitt has tendered his resignation as head of the Environmental Protection Agency.… https://t.co/65ZM8BTh4o https://t.co/cEI1Et509B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer | high traffic, end-user facing web application (built and maintained by a group of five Agile teams): Sr. Java Developer | high traffic, end-user facing web application (built and maintained by a group of five Agile teams) – CareWorks… https://t.co/xsuw7ivzHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In photos: How 1968 changed America -- for better and worse: In modern United States history, few years are remembered with such mixed emotion as 1968. The year began with the Tet Offensive and the Mai Lai Massacre in Vietnam, turning points in the… https://t.co/SPnbI814Et https://t.co/x8jN40VOC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/YcICW3rIIk https://t.co/9zFZZDwBY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with React/Redux: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Java Developer with React/Redux Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX Campus Java Developers are engaged in all phases of the software development lifecycle which include; gathering and… https://t.co/xd9bp7CpzZ https://t.co/RiLUwAxaOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heather Heyer's mom: My world was demolished: Before the events of August 11 and 12, 2017, Charlottesville was, for those who knew of it at all, a college town or a weekend getaway from Washington, DC. Or, for the history buffs among us, the home of our… https://t.co/sNW6HdopnQ https://t.co/9SHH9YnkLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer (Server side): Senior Java Developer (Server side) at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact… https://t.co/HogT3DK1WI https://t.co/9gOVNxlCt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California wildfire smoke reaches NYC: Take a look at this forecast model from the National Weather Service. It shows how the smoke from the wildfires scorching California is traveling thousands of miles. In this case, all the way to New York City --… https://t.co/6P6jM7jCJC https://t.co/wmPlA0Vjlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the launch of NASA's Parker Solar Probe Sunday morning (update): Tomorrow, August 11th, NASA is scheduled to launch a historic mission called the Parker Solar Probe. The spacecraft will launch on a ULA Delta IV Heavy rocket from Launch Complex 37… https://t.co/7tviA5al3s https://t.co/vhaXACbSKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java DEveloper: Java DEveloper Ref No.: 18-32517 Location: Hoboken, New Jersey JD – Candidate must have excellent Java/J2EE skills with minimum 8-10 yrs of experience into application development and designing. Experience in AngularJS, NODEJS and MongoDB… https://t.co/AGudeNXJoD https://t.co/4qGuGINJF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Java Full Stack Developer 5:   Job Description – Technical Lead – Java Full Stack Developer 5 (18016458) Technical Lead – Java Full Stack Developer 5 Requisition ID : 18016458 Location : United States-Virginia-Springfield US Citizenship… https://t.co/fX3thQd8L8 https://t.co/KuGKKEjtBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer (JAVA) – ArcSight – Provo, UT: Sr. Software Engineer (JAVA) – ArcSight – Provo, UT Tracking Code ******* Job Description At Micro Focus, everything we do is based on a simple idea: The fastest way to get results is to build on what… https://t.co/SVZAdMTV23 https://t.co/noYnZfsKMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C#/ASP.NET/JavaScript: *NO THIRD PARTY CANDIDATES WILL BE CONSIDERED* SOFTWARE ENGINEER – C#/****************** LOCATION: Arlington, TX OFFICIAL TITLE: Software Engineer WHY JOIN OUR TEAM * Industry leader * Casual workplace * Great… https://t.co/vKMBWi1TMH https://t.co/QbLqYhkcp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer: Job Details | Syneren – Home – About Us – Certifications – Company – Contact Us – Customers – Solutions – Services – IT Services – Mission Planning, Acquisition and PMO Support – Science and Weather Data Support – Systems Engineering –… https://t.co/TVVvTmFpmS https://t.co/eDgxL0HSn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimmel's Trump question silences Kanye: Kanye West returned to "Jimmy Kimmel Live!" for the first time in five years. https://t.co/LfYgYZ1kw7 https://t.co/ykLaXpriLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Tesla engineering lead Doug Field is back with Apple: Tesla confirmed in July that instead of returning from a six-week break, senior engineering VP Doug Field had departed the company. The timing was interesting as it came during Tesla's push to… https://t.co/0pZlUeTdKB https://t.co/2B1GwVFfou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Java Developer (w/ UNIX/LINUX): Sr. Specialist Java/J2EE Developer (w/ UNIX/LINUX) The Global Institutional Accounting and Risk Solutions Information Technology team is seeking an experienced Developer. The candidate should expect the… https://t.co/OAL9AZ2b0Z https://t.co/mw6gNUpTIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-33527 Location: NYC &amp; SFO, California Java Full Stack – ADM x 8 positions $120 to 145k range / exceptions can be considered on case to case basis for a little higher salary if needed. SFO /… https://t.co/wXu6VfCytI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer – Axius Technologies – San Jose, CA | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Java Developer… https://t.co/ggnjSLb2ZN https://t.co/X8oceYiPaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Irvine, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/14/18, Posted Date – 06/14/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverview Duration 6-12 month Interview : Phone/skype Description We are looking for a talented Senior Java… https://t.co/ApjuBtLMVk https://t.co/wA2hfliiLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung's smart home devices can pick up Spotify streams from your phone: Samsung just announced the Galaxy Home, a clear competitor to Apple's HomePod, and the speaker will be powered by Spotify. The company also announced a new partnership that'll tie… https://t.co/oP4QnaSXS1 https://t.co/9F3FVCIP7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Tech Lead: Java Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-31128 Location: Montvale, New Jersey Position: Java Tech Lead Location : Montvale, NJ Duration: 12 Months Experience- 6-8 Years Minimum Role- Java Technical Lead Technology- Java, Hibernate, Spring, REST… https://t.co/BsorQXCEqp https://t.co/CXk5c4WsTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer VXML / Java Script: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions in… https://t.co/I9qlgvHfAb https://t.co/1Wocz2rRxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the best time to invest in China. Here's why https://t.co/RTeIIcmpJX https://t.co/lRE9QCjyOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Location US-CA-Encino Posted Date 2 months ago(5/10/2018 6:53 PM) Job ID 23599 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Republic Indemnity is a subsidiary of Great American Insurance Group – we market… https://t.co/ww0R01JIJV https://t.co/4sRnPzJs7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Note 9 hands-on: All about the S Pen: Hello, stylus, my old friend. I've come to talk with you again. Today Samsung unveiled the Galaxy Note 9 -- the latest in its flagship big-screen phone series. Like its predecessors, it comes with a… https://t.co/uLRLCQ3CRO https://t.co/aXo7dZl97R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java ui developer: java ui developer Ref No.: 18-31252 Location: JERSEY CITY, New Jersey Hi, My name is Neha and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc. I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available for a… https://t.co/oCUzZWYJcP https://t.co/8RFBFR5oXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java – Columbus: Responsibilities: Expertise in application, data and infrastructure architecture disciplines Advanced knowledge of architecture, design and business processes Ability to work collaboratively in teams and develop meaningful… https://t.co/hmjgtw2waF https://t.co/ps7TtqVzkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core JAVA Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right away.Your… https://t.co/sDjO8RXi6L https://t.co/EZX1NiZtag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Level Agile Developer (React/Vue, JavaScript, node.js, C#, MVC): Who is Markit Digital We design, develop, and host data rich, full featured, and high traffic web and mobile applications for financial institutions, brokerages, and media clients… https://t.co/S2nHCi2rTB https://t.co/QqupTbIjhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrities target Ivanka Trump on Instagram: Celebrities including Amy Schumer and Chelsea Handler have launched an Instagram campaign targeted at Ivanka Trump, urging the US President's daughter to act on the administration's family-separation policy… https://t.co/201VfsoOxT https://t.co/7BCoOCCsZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer – Java, Spring, UI: Job Description Principal Developer – Java, Spring, UI This person will be a resource with expertise in App Engine and DBaaS environment setups and deployments, AngularJS UI development, API development and… https://t.co/zx0CqYsrL2 https://t.co/vWYMKeBSJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Description As a Java Developer and member of the Serco software development team, you will share responsibility for the design, development, automated tests, builds, and deployment of application solutions and delivery of the company… https://t.co/MKFbvmNxCW https://t.co/KdHTvzgokF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Meanstack Developer: Overview **ONLY US CITIZENS** Sr. Java Meanstack Developer Location: Rockville, MD Rate : Depends on the number of years of experience – Demonstrated experiences in MEAN stack (The MEAN stack is MongoDB, Express.js,… https://t.co/v0DuDHKgF0 https://t.co/aCzIDXhHe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineers: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn Jul 16, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #479: IT Job Code: #479 Title: Java Software Engineers Job Type: Direct Hire Job Location: Reston Virginia Job Description: Sterling Computers is looking to… https://t.co/xRzXkndkrI https://t.co/NJctd40GIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen's powerful song earns golden buzzer on 'America's Got Talent': 14-year-old rapper Flau'jae, whose father, rapper Camoflauge, was killed days before signing a record contract, performed an original song dedicated to her father's legacy on "America's… https://t.co/lgT1DF2ddu https://t.co/GyhWhQ6dTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s Pixel 3 XL could come with Pixel Bud-style headphones: Today, a Ukranian tech blogger named Luchkov may have leaked images of the white version of Google's Pixel 3 XL. These look like the real deal, though they include a bit of a puzzle. The… https://t.co/bIa051PmJF https://t.co/nFhlyCqIF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Sr. Specialist Developer – Java: Job Description Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for data, workflow, logical… https://t.co/OAsy9JX0CW https://t.co/yIb0X7DWY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Mid Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 (18005011) Mid Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18005011 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/1p5fzKqQrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Engineer (JavaScript, REACT/AngularJS): Menlo Park, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Location: Menlo Park, CA Title: Front End Developer We’re looking for a JavaScript expert with React / AngularJS experience. We’re building a… https://t.co/S8VgqY8H2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job ID: ********-11836-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: Senior Java Developer ClaimXperience is searching for a dynamic and creative Senior Java Developer who has the knowledge and experience to help shape our industry… https://t.co/rroRRcoOAD https://t.co/bYJvCoyN1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer (OO, RestFul, DataStructure): Principal Developer-&gt;&gt; Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical… https://t.co/tcFqKUsgMq https://t.co/TbpbZh9TNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: We need to talk about InfoWars: YouTube, Facebook and Apple have taken steps to remove content associated with InfoWars and its founder Alex Jones. CNN Opinion asked a group of contributors to weigh in on the implications for both free and… https://t.co/jNtLelZ8ly https://t.co/iKYfPEwwCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Angular Developer: Java Angular Developer Ref No.: 18-30026 Location: NYC, New York Java Angular Developer FTE Location: NYC, NY Job Description – Good knowledge of Core Java with JDK 8 features – Framework: Spring, Spring Boot, Spring Data,… https://t.co/DknJFQYlon https://t.co/HpNUimfCGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: OJ Simpson says 'Being a felon ain't all bad' https://t.co/1pCecRDI0S https://t.co/gCUy7UipeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer (Java): Overview Job Description: As a Senior Software Engineer, the ideal candidate will have designed, developed and implemented solutions that include not only the code that services business functionality but the underlying… https://t.co/ls940dopRh https://t.co/FQkuJUkwoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer (Java): Job Description PSI Title: Senior Web Developer (Java) Work Location: DC – Washington Description Essential Functions and Job Responsibilities: The successful candidate’s core responsibilities will include, but not to be… https://t.co/3Mu20Ky0RK https://t.co/43V4ZD9Beh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-13192 Location: Honolulu, HI Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/25/2018 Position: Java Developer Location: Honolulu, HI Type: Contract Roles and Responsibilities: – Strong communication and leadership skills –… https://t.co/54dQdB3rtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33567 Location: Weehawken, New Jersey 1.Should have 7-9 years (B3) of experience on Core Java, J2EE architecture, Java Design Patterns, Struts. 2.Should have experience working in Spring suite – Spring MVC,… https://t.co/lj4RDVKymh https://t.co/8mD01lJ419]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Manafort's work for Ukraine fit neatly with Putin's agenda: The one searing image out of the first week of the Paul Manafort financial fraud trial in Virginia is the mug shot of the defendant's $15,000 ostrich skin jacket, described by some as a… https://t.co/sdODpWJuXr https://t.co/Zcvj067eQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/RiJd9v2fKr https://t.co/qLE1DYl1Ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MoviePass will limit customers to three movies per month https://t.co/RD2acCf3vc https://t.co/acOjPlTKw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Math: Score one for the good guys: Oh what a week it's been. Apple is now valued at one trillion dollars, the NES Classic is still selling like hotcakes, one plucky hacker garnered a seven figure income from a single ransomeware attack, and… https://t.co/4ZgVzDvN3G https://t.co/qatOi1jINB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Javascript Developer w/AWS – IoT Development: CirrusMio’s business team is seeking to hire a highly motivated senior-level Javascript programmer who is passionate about creating the next big thing. The ideal candidate will display innovative ideas… https://t.co/SqOTLNn96L https://t.co/QfPfPqCYaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Princ’l Architect, Application Development – Java: Job Description Designs technical infrastructure for applications and assists in defining application tools. Develops the applications architecture and blueprints which reflect business logic of the… https://t.co/SJVhSm9xPO https://t.co/5Tcm7CXnql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 (18005436) Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18005436 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton… https://t.co/mcuqKvub0q https://t.co/3DSwCq8PDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoid these foods due to outbreaks and recalls: At least six multistate foodborne illness outbreaks are going on now, according to federal health officials, prompting recalls aimed at preventing further problems. https://t.co/xgCzHy3vcd https://t.co/BQ0kpc1TQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: Glendale, CA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a JavaScript Developer with 4+ years experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 1. Based in Glendale, we are digital data collection company that is setting a… https://t.co/0JWFo4Luos https://t.co/HfDA7sYAYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Level- Software Engineer- Java/C++: Mid Level- Software Engineer- Java/C++ ====================================== Req #: ******Location: Austin, TX USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job… https://t.co/jLcJkh2Sfu https://t.co/r3JIQpBA6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise. Agilent enables… https://t.co/Upp7cuFcZx https://t.co/WvjYDOuS7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer in Jersey City, New Jersey, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core… https://t.co/7NCPLb1igZ https://t.co/bsYFj299Sg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java: Java Ref No.: 18-30629 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 8 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Sr Java Developer based in Atlanta, GA… https://t.co/hPRvhkRCyq https://t.co/Hs5PTS3azT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 arrested in alleged assassination attempt of Venezuelan President: Six people have been arrested after Saturday's apparent assassination attempt on President Nicolas Maduro in the Venezuelan capital of Caracas, the nation's interior minister said on… https://t.co/yDFN4Vu4Yd https://t.co/qbSuWFD4lt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Core Java Developer Gainspeed: Nokia is a global leader in the technologies that connect people and things. With state-of-the-art software, hardware and services for any type of network, Nokia is uniquely positioned to help communication service… https://t.co/17g3UOkYrO https://t.co/M6RvjsvCby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Principal, Java Development: Job Description – Consults with internal business groups to provide application software development services or technical support. – Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior… https://t.co/R7atGIZKp0 https://t.co/OebyObxnXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Software Developer, Expert w/Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-44200 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description The DPS Team is looking for an… https://t.co/xy9WiH4BAZ https://t.co/sNsnpUsaHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior / Principal Java Developer: Summary CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our products in several new areas. The Sr. or Principal Java developer will work on developing new middle tier/server side functionality for the system. This… https://t.co/Y3cPUjT3p1 https://t.co/RwXrq2pYZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Java Architect Ref No.: 18-33276 Location: West Chester, Pennsylvania 10+ years of experience fielding software systems as a software developer and at least 3+ years of experience designing software systems as a software architect… https://t.co/DbxB0kqXuM https://t.co/QQcHgz97fH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump escalates old fights this week and starts new ones: At the end of a week in which President Donald Trump appeared more ready than ever to pick fights with his adversaries — both real and perceived — it was perhaps fitting to have the UFC's… https://t.co/cj6j6tkDyO https://t.co/A2tuOjKyP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Angular: ******/Java Developer with Angular Ref No.: 18-30762 Location: Mc Lean,VA, Virginia LEAD-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Should have hands on experience in UI development Should have knowledge in Core Java, HTML 5,… https://t.co/b4ImF6Coio https://t.co/l9UhPXuhBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/AWS Enterprise Architect: Job TitleJava/AWS Enterprise Architect – ID:31769 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsCloud, MicroServices, AWS, Java/JEE, Docker, CI / CD, event sourcing, CQRS, NoSQL LocationPlano, TX Date Posted06/28/2018 FOR… https://t.co/fdSwV5TR8Y https://t.co/ewSSnhhZ66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Portland, protesters hurl rocks, police say 'disperse': Police in Oregon's largest city were bracing Saturday for the latest dueling political rallies in Portland, asking people not to bring weapons and warning that screening checkpoints and… https://t.co/UlWU8xDtPd https://t.co/7M5tQEsvdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SELENIUM CORE JAVA: ******/SELENIUM CORE JAVA Ref No.: 18-29942 Location: Bellevue – Washington, Washington Selenium-L3 (Mandatory) Core Java-L3 Appium-L2As a Senior Test Engineer you should able to devise Test Strategy, review test plan, traceability… https://t.co/iS4a0mqn3Q https://t.co/dJ5kvgpED8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer Agile JAVA/Angular/Python Developer and Integrator: This position is in the BNY Mellon Information Lifecycle Management group, responsible for building and buying solutions to support Cyber Security Data Masking, Records Management,… https://t.co/YkLwlsSYL7 https://t.co/6hgIAtkWBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-30113 Location: jercycity, New Jersey Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java Developer with the client based in Multiple… https://t.co/sabMNQB7Da https://t.co/CEYOnpcrRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildfire claims lives of great-grandmother, two children and firefighters: The fast-moving Carr Fire has claimed six lives as it tears through Northern California. https://t.co/ZuxWL8WQxY https://t.co/H8cavC1VpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. We are looking for a Lead Java Developer to join the Wireless Ecommerce Team. Join our Information Technology team where you will work on old and new technologies and find ways to meet our… https://t.co/54awz1lkOn https://t.co/gLGoHKZ4AM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>