<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhispersNewsLTD: BREAKING: Boris Johnson Rushed To Hospital With Suspected Head Up Arse https://t.co/G3wE5Luiwk #borisjohnson #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jennaaclaire: man I had no idea you could buy this.  I’ve just been using drugs and alcohol https://t.co/RziVhnvoY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Haha clever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 CC will naturally die out here. Not fast enough but inevitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Haha perhaps I missed the joke? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 What rate of taxes would you apply?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 So how would it work in Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ElodieBurke @AmazonUK Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ElodieBurke @AmazonUK You want socialism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamonnBlaney @conorthomas89 I'm all for PPPs but good lawd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath Hi Vickee :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseless whining. https://t.co/zeinRepkfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disturbing. https://t.co/i2OfgPlnLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashlingplunkett Ok. So do you mean 6-6?

I think then in the interests of fairness you would then have to apply 6+6 to any kind of criminal case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashlingplunkett I'm not trying to catch you out by no means. Just curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashlingplunkett However that doesn't really answer my question. Representative of the population only makes sense if you feel women can't be represented by men and vice versa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk Did you seek any recourse? Quite honestly if this was true it would be completely damning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk https://t.co/3aO6vgTB7C

Hi John, do you deny the contents of this article?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashlingplunkett Why does it need to be balanced? Should every jury be 6+6? To serve what purpose? Do you think women are biased towards women and men are biased for towards men?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 That's fair. They both equally deserve to be in court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Again was it all towards the player? Sure there was nasty stuff but the majority I saw was against the IRFU for hiring him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 That's fine but let's not say A is not good because B still goes on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell While I doubt it was a good time for GG, at least it reminded other players of the furore if they decide to dope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell But I don't see it as bullying Grobler. The questioning was more towards the employer, not the employee. As for this journo standoff, I'm not really fussed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell I don't think the ire was directed at Grobler, but more so the IRFU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Moving the goalposts there Conor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. https://t.co/3aO6vgTB7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @cianodo One of many answers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @cianodo The reason given will be drinks sales but it really takes from the atmosphere. Stadium is 50-60% full when the teams emerge from the tunnel. The place should be buzzing for it but it's dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AVIVAStadium The deep voice that does the security notices on matchdays is impossible to hear on the PA. It's been like this for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @cianodo They need to do a Croker and stop people taking drinks to the stands. No reason it can't be done in Aviva.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Overthehillprop @threeredkings :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy Incredible result. Benetton are missing as many as Scarlets are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shill CRAIC in Galway. https://t.co/0L3f3GM0yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've gotten 4 retweets. My cut is now 10%. @threeredkings https://t.co/QTgOAtItuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Dubya See Dubya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also known as shilling. Shame. Shame. Shame. Shame. https://t.co/fgeMqsKslZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Don't hey-yo me chico!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But. I'll take 5% cut. I'm an INFLUENCER. @threeredkings https://t.co/QTgOAtItuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want premium rugby content? Pay for it. Throw a cupa bucks over to THE BAD GUY @threeredkings .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @threeredkings: Just savage work from Earls to make up the ground on this chase. He's absolutely fucked after it too. That's what leavin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BeauxisDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie Hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @timoconnorbl It all depends on "Yionel" at 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan Lefty loonies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian...meet Boucherie Ovalie! https://t.co/tOhx2G6gwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 Nah Brian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's tempting to reply. Resist the baiters. Not worth your time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS The pontificating tone is the best. He has as much legitimacy as I do. Waving around awards like S J*nes does changes nothing. A*cough got a pro-l*fe award handed it to her recently. It's meaningless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS The other...meh who cares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Which is why I use an asterisk. Even a mention of their name equals money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When E*an and K*mmage inevitably reignite the ragebait with Grobler selected, ignore them. Don't like. Don't engage. Do nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mortgages prices would surely go up thanks to this. Yeah cheers for that https://t.co/BKQBE862nS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lionel Beauxis. Is it 2007 again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WelshDalaiLama: Wow Ric Flair's fallen on hard times https://t.co/8KR7R86P7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjRossouw87 Otherwise it looks like your original content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjRossouw87 You should credit him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulieAMcDowall: How cheap journalism works: I go to Chernobyl, do research, and write about it for The Guardian. Then the Daily Mail ta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CaptAndrewLuck: Dearest mother —
I write with most distressful news. The men have been hoodwinked. The deserter McDaniels is on the lam…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie @mikeneglia @conorthomas89 @ireland To campaign in another country. What a waste of money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She has stood outside clinics. Pretty reprehensible behaviour in itself. One wrong doesn't justify the other but it appears she us well able to dole it out. https://t.co/VxLTOi162f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bwhahaha https://t.co/DM53gpKKBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghdoyle @keithbelfast @brokenbottleboy I think you may have been duped Darragh. Per screenshots from her father she's here to campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @Office_Zombie @ireland I thought there were disclosure laws on this but perhaps they only apply to political parties and not interest groups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie @conorthomas89 @ireland Exactly. Foreign funding should be denounced regardless of side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie @conorthomas89 @ireland I do think it's disconcerting to see Americans pay to send her over. Other side at it too no doubt. Not good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ireland This is precisely the attitude that you don't want though. You're not going to convince anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HardRockCafeMCR You have some cheek serving us this rubbish tonight. A bottle of Budweiser from a multipack, cold nachos (cheese didn't even melt on them) and SD picture. SD picture in 2018. £15 and I feel robbed. This is the last time I'll be coming here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Sexton. I am not worthy of your greatness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @threeredkings: A 42-metre drop goal after 40 phases of carrying. Legendary stuff. What a moment #FRAvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Waters. Still irrelevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheTweetOfGod: Sarah, if I answered prayers your boss would have already died 50 billion times. https://t.co/4BVD5CPZtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eamonnhs: Forget Ireland v France it’s all about Mayo v Kerry @MayoGAA up mayo https://t.co/tFeFBbEZzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Not enough intensity Tom. Not NEARLY enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan Lousy SIXMAS weather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 I'm surprised she didn't get more stick from that lazy Internment article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianmoore666: To be fair - this is wildly inaccurate; his whole head should have been up there. https://t.co/1wyD7qpO4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjRossouw87 Have you tried Guinness Storehouse website?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gergilroy @paddylogan13 Bad blood between Brennan and IRFU I imagine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @offtheball Good to hear you on the airwaves again Cian!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup WONDERFUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can this be a Patreon benefit? @WrestlingSoup https://t.co/KJPEx42JaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're planning to visit any questions don't hesitate to drop a DM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DJ you're welcome at the RDS for a Leinster game. I'm a Munster fan too but I frequent the RDS due to geography. :D https://t.co/J1FZOd12Hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell @threeredkings Conway has good leverage with Zebo leaving. Hopefully he'll get a good contract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docathail I wish people would stop engaging. He's an odious twerp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docathail Apologies! E**n then? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop feeding E*en. Don't @ him. Don't type his name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Roarzz: Guys stop being shocked when Brazil's leading GAA writer puts out an article that's complete nonsense about rugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad Nobody should @ him. He is an immediate block.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad The issue is the author. An odious twerp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug @RnRRugby If I could change the World Rugby rules...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug @RnRRugby That's interesting Simon. I think in the interest of fairness international teams should be allowed to retain 24/25/26th men in reserve for matchdays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is your Dublin event?! :) https://t.co/0KULyhDCRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage @CorkSeashell I looked through it and it does what it says. Bots and trolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland Repealthe8th @Office_Zombie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie @AmnestyIreland @SIPOC Hellllooooo...Karen...? I see you have been tweeting....still waiting on an answer as to proof ProLife isn't funded by foreign sources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Hopefully this list only extends to trolls and not to those with a legitimate/respectful argument.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>