<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Harinordiquay is such a legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 are you playing at home today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicrawley @domdunnett what time mate? Havingan early tea the now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @aspy87 @rustyboy2310 i'll take them! might be able to go now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 if no one else takes them I will buy them and try and flog them on (said I would take them likes).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 feeling rotten so not going to try to get to jetpacks. Can't make Bon iver either but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckWendig: Cancer's a real fucking prick is the real lesson. Hope we find in-roads toward chopping that dragon's head off someday  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to hear about Steve Jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jo_Caulfield: I know we're only 3 days in but I think this is turning out to be the BEST British Potato Week EVER!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brewdog: Our bit on Channel 4 News if you scamps haven't seen it yet. Row brewing with CAMRA - http://t.co/xmXmPfaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally getting round to listening to Emily haines' album. It's no Metric, but still very nice indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicrawley @domdunnett I am very keen for a bailie bar #beer chaps. It's only right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FRabbits: Currently listening to For Emma, Forever Ago for the 2nd time ever. Wanna know how many times I've listened to Enema Of Th ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely devastated for Dan Carter #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Euan Murray is abusing Stevens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrazYoung aye, but he put it over the upright. That was straight betwixt the sticks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How hard is it to judge if a pen goes over??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruaridh_jackson hard lines mate, hopefully you'll be back for the next round!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrazYoung all will be forgiven. The guys have started at double time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can shove yer chariots up yer arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking #SCOTLAND c'mon!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: At #mcfc Carrington. Football's brutal. Somebody's already parked in Carlos Tevez's space...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Swanson?!? @CraigLevein, go fuck yourself San Diego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIYAAA! @alicrawley @domdunnett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant sleep dammit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carlos #Tevez. what a wee boaby!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OliverKayTimes: Mancini says in post-match press conf that Tevez will never - never - play for Man City again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently listening to Azeda Booth. Not going to change the world but great background music to work to! A bit like Postal Service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 you are baws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @aspy87 @rory_g_macrae keen for @wwpj at the liquid rooms on the 6th oct?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sickipediabot: I'm half ambidextrous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah genius!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrychappell: Cav doesnt make a single national newspaper front page. Meanwhile Cameron watching/Balls playing footie makes Telegra ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real Estate Gets Techie - PR.com http://j.mp/r0E0ly (via Instapaper)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @millarmind: Proud doesn't even begin to describe how we feel. Rod Ellingworth, he dared dream we could do this. http://t.co/tJuKqTwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for travel writing http://j.mp/rcKdoH (via Instapaper)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2007 all over again. Should have won. Didn't #rwc #scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair enough argentina were miles offside, but that was the crappest platform for a drop goal I've ever seen. #scotland #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parks that was absolutely ridiculous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squeeky bum time #scotland #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the support into the rucks boys! #Scotland #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been baw deep in #spotify and #aweditorium tonight. Got some new choons! Scotland game tomorrow bright and early #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What. A. Try. #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrackenBrewDog: Just dared a sausage dog to eat a giant airport sized Toblerone whole. I'm hoping the effect will be Stegosaurus-like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy ahead of me chowing down on a White magnum. #jealousy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Tips for Surviving & Thriving at Networking Events http://j.mp/p8FQEi (via Instapaper)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibs have been so bad over the last year, I don't have it in me to mock hearts for their loss to Ayr last night #spl #communitescup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicTrades: Greece: emergency kebabinet meeting! Doner who's attending but crisis hallooming, going to be an Athens chainsaw Moussaka ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: David Goodwillie stays in the squad despite his upcoming assault trial. I don't let off field issues dictate who I pick ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: Mackail-Smith ahead of McCormack. Why score 9 goals in the Championship when you could score 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to see @TetonGravity "One For the Road" at the bongo club on thursday night. who's fancies it? looks mint! http://t.co/8WzHDShm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 yeah not too bad, knackered now though! How was yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 eeeeh it was chunky like my calves! #chegwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmcnairn your team looking good on MOTD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 good time in englandshire thanks. how was your weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310  well game been on. ridiculous decision, should have been a yellow. Meeking should have gone for challenge on Hammill though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeah well game been on. ridiculous decision, should have been a yellow. Meeking should have gone for challenge on Hammill though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching #sportscene. the standard of refereeing in the #spl just now is beyond a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some louie theroux gold on right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having just listened to the most recent album from the cribs, I now know why I didn't hear of its release. It's baws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TweeterAlliss: Well done to Greece and their magnificent past 10yr funding strategy. They went shopping in Harrods and got the bill  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what a pish crowd #hibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Hibs team tonight probably the most open I have ever seen. hope we're not on the end of a battering!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[paying a massive price for not referencing as I went along #schoolboy.
Nearly done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sorry that would be Portugal. The Man #braindead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listen to Portugal. A Man to get me through this frakkin' essay. #brutal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rory_g_macrae Alas, I will be in Yorkshire for the weekend, at a thing for Elizas stepdad's 60th.Will be around on sunday night tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 should be fit. Always thought of myself as more of a #chicharito myself. Naaat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Adams on #laterjools, yeaah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae That I hate country girl? I despise it. did you make it out for pints?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ, Country Girl by Primal Scream. I really hate that song. No Idlewild or Frightened Rabbit? Really?? #scotlandsgreatestalbum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mull Historical Society! yes Nevin #scotlandsgreatestalbum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae sorry ginger bear, canny tonigt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learned that @UglyDuckling are playing sneaky petes on Monday night. #yaldi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBig_Sam: Job done. Big Sam has once again straddled the magnificent steed of tactical bravery and rode it majestically into the s ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bryan ruiz- what a finish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ouch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all blacks are bottle merchants. hope im wrong but this has France world cup winners all over it #RWCFINAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@MirrorFootball: Mario Balotelli rescued by fire brigade after setting his house alight with fireworks http://t.co/prN2qSVg” @rory_g_macrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dying #hungparliment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn @domdunnett expensive night guys. Bundered like a chump. Prospective sofa replacement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#eurothone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 what the fuck is HIGNY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@domdunnett chedd me cheddar, cheddar me chedds! #megadrill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its October, and #Messi has score 16 goals this season...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some epic barracking going on #primeministersquestions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really surprised to find myself enjoying #NoelGallaghers new album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NathanPresley: It's sad how Wile E. Coyote is remembered for his violence, and not for his brilliantly realistic paintings of tunnels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paddypower: We've decided to refund all losing match bets on Wales. Only fair as Warburton decision was wrong - wales would have won ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bloody hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cheers for killing the game ref. wanker #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Wales #rwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rustyboy2310 @rory_g_macrae let's just do the tap for one then meander in. Already set to JC to meet there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 well Tom do you want to meet stocky tap at 8 and we can decide from there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rory_g_macrae Queens arms? want a decent beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rory_g_macrae no worries open to suggestions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DubstepSong: RRRREREREER WUUUBWUUUBWUUUB RERE WUBUBUB WUBUB WUUUUUB BRRRRRR BRRRRRR WUUU WUBUBUBUB BRRRR WUUUUUB WUUUB UHUHUHUHUWUUU ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 Y.E.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just came home to a postcard from @OfficialMannah ! Thanks mate, glad to hear your having a great time enjoying river beers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 I did indeed suit up! Your maybe coming for beers? Rugby for you tomorrow?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>