<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GailSnyder Hey we are practically neighbors. I am in Longmont. I am promoting accumulating silver at silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/weoWC
 via @addthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagerly promoting the cure for our economic woes. Take a look at SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPFinn  Looks like we are "birds of a feather"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping people get their websites on first page of google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilkThisCashCow Looks like your shopping business is a good idea. Much better than MyPowerMall. Make it a great day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting my day with checking out the news re. swine flu out break etc. Nuggets really clobbered the Hornets. WOW! Now on to my e-biz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teamarete My computer won't accept anything with "tiny" in the domain name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teamarete Father Sky and Monther Earth are taking care of us all. Everything is just as it should be !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nwJggS599 Hello, Jamie - How is the new job going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teamarete I agree -- The most important things in our lives are invisible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stanzst Hello, doctor! Just found you in my email. I am a retired Family Physician from Michigan. Now live in Colorado. How are you doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonPerna  Hey Jason.  Just getting started with Twitter. Tell me somethng about your self and write an interesting profile about YOU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronseal Hi thanks for the follow. How long have you been marketing online?
 Ron Smalley, Longmont, CO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigbankrecords  Need help promoting on the search engines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDEntrepreneur  We are into helping others promote whatever they want on the search engines. My niche is SEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindymcasey Happy Birthday to Jayce! Im starting to get more people signing into my veretekk sites. Maybe the crash is coming together !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[adding a link to my ganodermacoffee.com website and ordering some more gano Mocha.  Yum !  http://ganodermacoffe.com/ronsgano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Hartrick  So how are things in Japan? Economy doing well? - Ron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenniferdoe  Sounds like you are enjoying life ! Good for you !. What are you doing at UCLA ? Teaching or learning or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweeterstore  Entrepreneurs should be acquiring hard assets like silver.
Check this out to get yours:  http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GPMTrading  Do you trade silver? It is more rare than gold because of the demand by commercial silver users....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldbullionnews I just figured out that a trillion dollars in 100-dollar bills if taped together would go around the earth 38 times !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldluvr  Buying any precious metal is a good idea. When you want to sell your gold for dollars you can use where do you go to do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking out my new followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allenth How are gifting systems working for you. I had no response so gave up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealTigerWoods  Good show, Tiger!  Looking forward to watching you at the Masters.... Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sent my tea bag to 1600 PA Ave. Did you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheftut  I looked at and registered for m2e . But there is no real info yet. In general I avoid pre-launches like the plague.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1incomementor So what is your online business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSuccessGran  Getting acquainted.  You are all about the most important thing we have to do in Life :  Help one another . . . !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking abour investing in precious metals as a defense against inflation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refining my list of followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindymcasey  Hey Cindy!  Check this out: http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdgruener   You got me - what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laineyspawtique Maybe a glistch in the system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tsger Are you aTiger Woods fan? I think he is on his way back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrownUpGirl OK - I get it but plan to use bit.ly to get some shorter ones. Are you trying to make $ online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikepfs I predict Obama won't get re-elected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still working to improve my site. Changed my username from FreeBizLeads to SilverSaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweaking my twitpage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@affiliate_me How do adwords help you in your marketing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on my art blog helping people create better paintings and drawings
http://artyblog.wordpress.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelellison I am a Trivita affiliate under Lorne Timchuk. I think my arthitic stiffness and discomfort it better w Nopalea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikepfs Ya - and he says "its not about me" but we know it IS all about him and his desire to Socialize the US of A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariancumer Francisco! How are things in Puerto Rico? We are just getting started on summer.  seofrontrange.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrownUpGirl  Question : Why are you using tinyurl to link to your business?
Ron (freebizleads)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alovelylady2  Hi - take a look at TWELLOW.COM to find groups to join
Ron Smalley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billoreilly_i HEy, Bill We listen to you every day! This twitter thing is not your style. I suggest you forget about it or let staff do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allancurtis Hello Allan - I used to live in Flint, MI. How are things going in Brighton?  SEO is my niche.  Look like you are helping a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweeting Barack Obama to quit with the health care thing and quit putting our grandchildren in debt.  Join me, please.!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama No one in the USA wants socialized medicine and that is where we are headed with your crazy Hurry Up! approach to the issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workfromhomeexp Want to be on the first page of Google? http://seofrontrange.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunklyer So how is your Vereekk going now? Getting ready for 2.0?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eMoneyMaking  Already have a cat. I help people get on first page of Google.
Interested?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flefebre I can help you get on first page of google thanks to Veretekk
ron-smalley.veretekk.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking my tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@homebizchicks  Yes - I agree that there will be a rise in home business online.
My niche is SEO. at  http://seofrontrange.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just achieved #1 for BEST HOME BASED BUSINESS TRAINING TOOLS AND WEBSITE on Google of 1,010,000,000 listings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raczilla Looks like you are doing well - saving and earning silver? http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben14864 'Mornin' to you Ben  http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CCEditor http://silversnowball.com/1438  Good Morning to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyOlexa Hey Kelly are you protecting your wealth with silver?
http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddDickerson SEO is my niche.  What is yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul__Jones What is your one most favorite online business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MittRomneyUSA  I certainly hope you run again in 2012. I like the firmer tone
you are displaying in your interviews. Gingrich for VP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my leanology.net/13242759 on the first page of Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promoting my TriVita business at :   http://free-page.net/web/leanology.htm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoachKenoDavis  Are you thinking about the devaluation of the dollar? Might want to look at http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSchwind @CCEditor U saw a UFO !?  I have heard other credible people say the same.  What did you see?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiXiTWarecom  Sounds like I might be able to use your services. I will go to your website later today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gorwood Hello - we are almost the same age. I can help you with online marketing of your business. I need your member number to get in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hypervre  Right back atcha!  Whaats a "hypervre" and why should I want it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TamelaWV You are a busy gal and your kids are blessed to have you. Let me know if you are interested in http://leanology.net/13242759]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoldMarket How about earning free silver coins?  http://silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/1HWJZ4
 via @addthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/K7huG
 via @addthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mad_kadster How is your business doing. SEO is my niche. http://seofrontrange.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDEntrepreneur Get found on Google!   http://seofrontrange.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marcys2Cents What a great hummingbird photo!  I am an artist and instructor http://create-great-art.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Grade or not to grade. That is the question - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/pl4Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it a good idea to invest in gold/silver coins? | Gold Silver Coins http://bit.ly/Qj6BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrooFtCollins So, how are things in Ft. Collins? Longmont is nice and cool this am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindymcasey Thanks Cindy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellzballer But what if you started receiving free silver dollars in addition to the ones you are buying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos Of Gold Bars, Usa Gold Bars, How To Buy Gold Bullion Bars ... http://bit.ly/TacY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coin Mentoring - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/RXVMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Eagle | Buy Coins http://bit.ly/JCj3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Buy Gold . Langhore PA 19047. http://bit.ly/16uTW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SILVER COINS AND BULLION - WEAK U.S. DOLLAR | Silver Snowball Program http://bit.ly/JYqWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mess That Greenspan Made: John Law, Alan Greenspan, Ben ... http://bit.ly/uMqxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Eagle Silver Coin Alert | American Eagle Silver Coin http://bit.ly/BvzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing Tips For Beginners - Silver Coins http://bit.ly/15BF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Treasure Hunt Coming to Woodbury (ClearysNoteBook) http://bit.ly/e6Dou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Coins and the Short-Term Buying Opportunity | Silver Coin ... http://bit.ly/10GP2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy : Ms 70 SIlver and Gold Coins | CoinWeb - Coin News, Articles ... http://bit.ly/2kt9Oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to buy GOLD from FOX | Bullion Review http://bit.ly/4LjZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Path: A Definite Case of Socialism http://bit.ly/lygWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone buy &#39;09 silver proof set? - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/18FCx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citrine&#39;s Blog: Random Bracelets and Necklaces for Fobs http://bit.ly/CYHwv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>