<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump slams FBI, DOJ leaders ahead of memo release https://t.co/sRWMsUi8vu https://t.co/6gfOqPNhYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Weather: Forecaster predicts Britain facing snow this weekend and into next week - https://t.co/LT21CGlX0D https://t.co/yysDY0SSf9 https://t.co/GvJahjrce4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calais migrants: Five shot in mass brawl - BBC News https://t.co/hLwlfe3IUo https://t.co/QmJXSxUXQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Palm Beach yoga instructor not guilty in death of twin in Hawaii, reports say - Sun Sentinel https://t.co/ZQ5y9hCgQh https://t.co/bkpu9dkL69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: The big questions before the Nunes memo is released https://t.co/KQbwMGtsYn https://t.co/aYyY4Dmdig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa gold mine: All 955 trapped workers freed - BBC News https://t.co/41yGIu01Oq https://t.co/P00pufYVH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Crash Outside Shanghai Starbucks Injures at Least 18 - New York Times https://t.co/kFXKF1Dvo8 https://t.co/luHf0qePwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchin: Nunes 'neutered' confidence in House committee https://t.co/arsarwauao https://t.co/0HbyKFnSpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Himes: Memo is a 'second-rate hit job' https://t.co/XTwat3M7U4 https://t.co/Q82YUXd3RF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida's Ban on Felons Voting Ruled Unconstitutional by Judge - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/egSKH6nQkR https://t.co/ZLfRnJb0cH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fidel Castro's oldest son commits suicide, Cuban state media report - Fox News https://t.co/ehOvxQTMv4 https://t.co/xMfmi6ZtBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper: Nunes memo is a phony drama https://t.co/Z1khhLTI9o https://t.co/CmmXFRNZO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['In the long run, weasels and liars never hold the field' Comey tweets https://t.co/xYhCPLT52n https://t.co/8CjMmggA3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punxsutawney Phil and 7 other famous groundhogs you should know - Fox News https://t.co/PlncDu0rSi https://t.co/CzaDALCA5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple iPhone sales miss, but profit still breaks record anyway - CNET https://t.co/aNkkTIrvAz https://t.co/2KTtcKnCgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI still has 'grave concerns' about Nunes memo, source says https://t.co/0wbLsL6ajC https://t.co/xnv01xbwry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Carson warned about family involvement at HUD, emails show https://t.co/RBzcPZqBIK https://t.co/7aOevdmPlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen in 'Slender Man' stabbing gets 40 years in mental hospital - New York Post https://t.co/1HXpXXkDh0 https://t.co/i4YdgN4tha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: The incredibly simple reason why Trump will OK memo https://t.co/X8AcCl315X https://t.co/eET9Z9ae1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitt Romney set to announce his intentions in Utah's Senate race - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/aGinUduPoc https://t.co/UM7qWzupH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pennsylvania GOP leader defies court order on gerrymandering https://t.co/MSDkERvnSx https://t.co/PHUjSPF8lA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump rallies Republicans: 'We're just getting started' - The Hill https://t.co/w2PPRXR9qd https://t.co/HwwMIHnkTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Of course it sucks for Joe Manchin. Here's why https://t.co/MmjJTDDr8y https://t.co/DNowocxvIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aides believe Christopher Wray could step down if GOP memo alleging FBI surveillance abuse is released https://t.co/8YRGtGYunW https://t.co/8UFXTzAfR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obstruction Case against Trump Still Has a Way to Go - National Review https://t.co/8nE3mGBStx https://t.co/9hka5L7OAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two students shot at Salvador Castro Middle School, one in critical condition. Girl in custody - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/MjNCfhoPVS https://t.co/vfNoBa542t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WSJ: Alphabet, Aramco planning data centers in Saudi Arabia - Seeking Alpha https://t.co/ICt4doC6FC https://t.co/zrr9kRVUuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama tells Ellen to 'forget what they're saying in Washington' https://t.co/8FoAK1oeAS https://t.co/cXqOAP46dB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta boy, three, 'beaten to death over a cupcake' - BBC News https://t.co/NR3XCri5pL https://t.co/lB5myFPz0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President has told friends the GOP memo alleging FBI abuses would expose bias in the agency, sources say https://t.co/u6h9fZAC8t https://t.co/UM3IPpxp7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NJ weather pattern turns cold, stormy in February with more snow on way - https://t.co/tdxSzJzQdt https://t.co/DgoOqlDgSr https://t.co/0n8OFwKMzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She filed a complaint against Larry Nassar in 2014. Nothing happened https://t.co/tvxiW5kdwm https://t.co/sznnXHcXcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Warriors could set up talks with LeBron James if max deal is available - ESPN https://t.co/9qUzpRNETu https://t.co/qXFVigHjNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump is on a Nixonian collision course with FBI https://t.co/0lOvTz5jcY https://t.co/8Jw5WLQIyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: 2018 has been 2017 on steroids https://t.co/OrC4WTb4RO https://t.co/pVdoz87p1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's 'Please None' Budget - Bloomberg https://t.co/L4pfA7aPZP https://t.co/03sx8HmPM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was There `Deliberate' Attempt to Be Negative?: Brexit Update - Bloomberg https://t.co/eqAzzwCZT6 https://t.co/skAGJOODU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst erupts over Nunes' memo denial https://t.co/o16fAIaIk3 https://t.co/XjYvMOjSuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticizing Pelosi, Pence launches White House into midterm fray - https://t.co/IQl5Ig4Oxz https://t.co/01zANF9VUD https://t.co/i5PcPPNhUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass graves in Myanmar point to latest slaughter of Rohingya: AP - CBS News https://t.co/GcDbjK2W3E https://t.co/WyvgHJi1B1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pelosi: What do Russians have on Trump? https://t.co/M5tYiF9xdl https://t.co/wZ249ummif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Robert Forrest Jr.? Nashville Mayor Megan Barry Admits Affair - International Business Times https://t.co/o3kzAm242q https://t.co/PPtZokYqm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Cuomo presses Rep. Steve King on Watergate claim https://t.co/pvkAeOv3If https://t.co/0wgEbwNybO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Trump Spokesman Believed Hope Hicks Was Considering Obstructing Justice Over Trump Tower Meeting ... - Slate Magazine https://t.co/3vVQD5EFOH https://t.co/MRQ7Rys08m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker says Nunes is acting as agent of the White House https://t.co/zv38QfVphl https://t.co/agz4mqFFVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Jones: Campaign was up to no good https://t.co/OXNa33Tw1T https://t.co/lgb6Ssr6I5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nashville mayor Megan Barry admits to having an affair with the officer who ran her police detail - Washington Post https://t.co/dzYguEROWB https://t.co/z1sQ1hFZrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels' signatures under scrutiny https://t.co/tKv3gMWErA https://t.co/3XoemxL0BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Megan Barry admits affair with former head of security - https://t.co/ErpwMl6wUK https://t.co/jnjcWACXUr https://t.co/P5B9giBgnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper to Rep. Nunes: You've fooled us once https://t.co/Oh8KpbNd1I https://t.co/X32YpMLLiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nashville Mayor Megan Barry admits to extramarital relationship with top police security officer - USA TODAY https://t.co/Bb8hPINj4s https://t.co/nBPydgQmVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Democrat just out-fundraised Ted Cruz https://t.co/lniY6khxL1 https://t.co/faCuS14z0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Why the Nunes memo really isn't a partisan fight https://t.co/W0thbPSKBp https://t.co/jQSSUbntDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence criticizes Joe Manchin in West Virginia for voting against tax cuts - Washington Times https://t.co/QeKMiWiegG https://t.co/LSUmGgs0am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: How a porn star taught a law class on Kimmel's show https://t.co/SNfl0toR89 https://t.co/LNINWG1TCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gowdy: FBI should explain 'secret society' https://t.co/XOTXHUSROa https://t.co/WjtMqbMjkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Trump asked Rosenstein if he was 'on my team' - CNN https://t.co/BsJEBYsOu0 https://t.co/Z70G50TaZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who oversees Robert Mueller https://t.co/PTXCiPrxjM https://t.co/o3Tblk9rqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenya TV shutdown: Court suspends ban imposed over Odinga 'inauguration' - BBC News https://t.co/9ULmWMOefv https://t.co/xCtiq0B2YR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clapper: It looks like obstruction of justice https://t.co/aohnkg36t0 https://t.co/k0GuaJsJUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In San Francisco, Thousands With Pot Convictions Will Find Their Records Cleared - New York Times https://t.co/z6MK9lL5GA https://t.co/XhLTE6MqAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI agent who sent anti-Trump texts co-wrote draft of letter reopening Clinton email probe https://t.co/mifnv6d8t2 https://t.co/pWCHwvZO2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mnuchin: More Russia sanctions coming in 'near future' https://t.co/CUdyt2is7o https://t.co/Ev0JGdxLuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NBA player Rasual Butler, 38, killed in car crash - Yahoo Sports https://t.co/d1atidZChz https://t.co/cXlQlF1FqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philly Congressman Brady Won't Seek Another Term - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/Oojs3wQp3G https://t.co/3QVvXdW3CI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a wave of Republicans leaving Congress https://t.co/Vga2kzeIAk https://t.co/tD3xtMEc5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law enforcement, intel agencies concerned about Nunes memo https://t.co/qTG74tWnb6 https://t.co/LeehR0SVSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Dept. won't retry Sen. Bob Menendez - CNN https://t.co/wsKCBwVydL https://t.co/KwizPB24P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Hill: Victims thrown from truck https://t.co/BC2KrxIvJp https://t.co/QYzRqqhtk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amtrak train carrying GOP members to retreat collides with truck - Washington Post https://t.co/fs4hvsS0tj https://t.co/Pkjwglugpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea to parade its missiles https://t.co/RGPZ3odYiM https://t.co/QBfqvg5xWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man dies after sand tunnel collapses on him at north Florida beach - Sun Sentinel https://t.co/rX27gVKtka https://t.co/UBL6EOphjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FEMA shocks Puerto Rico by ending food shipments today https://t.co/4rtkFyf9Mp https://t.co/4z7GUXhKw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly: Memo should drop soon https://t.co/Wvkm7ivsvN https://t.co/3BDwrwef1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now We Know What Was in That Tiffany &amp; Co Box Melania Trump Gave to Michelle Obama - Fortune https://t.co/R3N1xVNNLX https://t.co/dCDGltDH8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Tech student accused of having assault rifle and trying to buy ammo - CNN https://t.co/AB98O4XAEZ https://t.co/XeynmEI0dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders says Pelosi should smile more https://t.co/KBr2uOtVZ9 https://t.co/fOCbrntI0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first couple reunites on the world stage https://t.co/BKgN7S60JP https://t.co/uKh1MxZ9pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrested Virginia Tech Student Tried Buying 5000 Rounds Of Assault Rifle Ammunition - International Business Times https://t.co/Un6vONrX8I https://t.co/f8K3LIBz6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump repeatedly offered to forge common ground, only to use language that could offend his opponents https://t.co/mGkYu7bhIG https://t.co/d5cBgN3RTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman calls for police to arrest undocumented immigrants at State of the Union - SFGate https://t.co/5bgc62r4LL https://t.co/OiUGzuqngA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Huge 6.2-magnitude earthquake rocks India, Pakistan and Afghanistan - Daily Star https://t.co/PjRSmUSqck https://t.co/DdUIwxrhkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapper: One hand reached out, other made a fist https://t.co/5em8PHGJF3 https://t.co/hKCjtyOdti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact-checking website crashes during State of the Union https://t.co/MCUsdsg0z1 https://t.co/2Rd28oW7Pv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump overheard saying he'll '100%' release Nunes memo https://t.co/WqcxxXmAIe https://t.co/E3uO0QxXdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Joe Kennedy III tells Dreamers: We will fight for you https://t.co/qVOXPpt3zi https://t.co/BfR345kJhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Mr Market loves President Trump's tax cuts - Economic Times https://t.co/I755pdf6t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: 6 takeaways from Trump's first State of the Union https://t.co/SI4pcmwoys https://t.co/kPtdjXzH59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs order to keep Guantanamo open - CNN https://t.co/agyAPfdTpB https://t.co/ezoeaVjMtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: 'Americans are dreamers, too' https://t.co/o5J7ZJ1kDX https://t.co/h3lPUYvufR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: This is why we stand for the National Anthem https://t.co/tIs5gATPLF https://t.co/5dyttMdTW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest tax cut in history? Not quite. https://t.co/yLBvQsJicW https://t.co/vHkgnmgNy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President hopes to strike a unifying tone after a divisive year https://t.co/p51XooEznc https://t.co/cOVT7Osbqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read excerpts of Trump's State of the Union address - CNN https://t.co/KDttLq2uUO https://t.co/noOFEVKxuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump arrives separately from the President https://t.co/o5ZQ4u08cW https://t.co/PzDW1gcakz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Mississippi Gov. Barbour arrested with gun at airport - https://t.co/IQl5Ig4Oxz https://t.co/0rbzOSFZ1c https://t.co/O1sipmPYrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's lawyers argue Mueller has not met threshold for presidential interview https://t.co/WtN3vdBDwJ https://t.co/jNSFEJQr5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warrants in Las Vegas mass shooting reveal name of additional 'person of interest' - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/4gIU9xcIL1 https://t.co/FHhKRek3pD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump hopes for unifying State of the Union after divisive year https://t.co/A6I6Q8fXhE https://t.co/3tdp6Y2DCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems direct outrage over Nunes memo at Ryan https://t.co/KdJDwGvGmL https://t.co/EPNztaXfga]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>