<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Many things about tomorrow, I don't seem to understand, but I know who holds tomorrow and I know who holds my hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love isn't when you can name a million things about someone. It's when you can't find the words to describe how you feel about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need someone that sees what's good about me. I need someone that sees the bad, and still wants me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being strong doesn't always mean you can handle what's thrown at you. It just means you're prepared to ignore whatever it is that hurts you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's love is perfect. God's love is beautiful. God's love is precious. God's love is wonderful, and God's love is for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there when the world stops running, I'll be there when the storm is through. In the end I wanna be standing at the beginning with u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is a light that shines from heart to heart." ~ John Denver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the way you can always make me feel happy, the way you care, the way you understand, the way you love me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might not be the best at showing my emotions, but I hope you know that I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love to see you smile, but I love it even more when I know I'm the reason you smiled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how hard and fast you fell for me. What really matters is how long you're willing to stick around for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to be great to get started, but you do have to get started to be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I miss you, I close my eyes and see your smiling face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within my heart, God is there, to light my life and help with despair. I know through Him I can do anything, because He is always there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over-thinking ruins you. Ruins the situation, twists things around, makes you worry, &amp; just makes everything much worse than it actually is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I just don't wanna answer my phone or reply to texts. It doesn't mean something's wrong, it just means I want time to myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go in the search for love... Let it finds u... It will be the best gift you will ever receive and it's straight from God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God designed ONE person special for you. Just be patient until that person shows up in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect guy is not the one who has more money or the most handsome one you'll met. It's the one who knows how to makes you smile everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very easy to Hurt someone and then say "Sorry". But it's really very Difficult to get Hurt and say "I am Fine".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look back and thank God. Look forward and trust God. Look around and serve God. Look within and find God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe everything happens for a reason and since I met you... I believe it even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow your heart, but be quiet for a while first. Ask questions to your heart, then feel the answer. Learn to trust your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do your best. That's all you can ask of yourself. If you did your best and things didn't work out, you don't owe an apology to anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a strong person. But every now and then I would like someone to take my hand and say everything will be alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before I go to sleep, I think of you. When I fall asleep, I dream about you. I wake up the next day and it starts all over again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday I wake up and the first thing I think about is you, then after that I go through a whole entire day just thinking about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not looking for someone who has everything. I'm looking for someone who has the time to spend with me more than anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, I may not understand why everything is happening in my life right now, but I just wanted to say I trust you and love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes...when he hugs me tight...I feel like he's trying to make our hearts touch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, when I say "I'm okay", I want someone to look me in the eyes, hug me tight and say, "I know you're not."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My attitude is based on how YOU treat me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you call it love when you're crying more than you're smiling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appearance captures your attention; Personality captures your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl's laughter is much more cheerful than a boy's, but a boy's cry is much more meaningful than a girl's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might feel worthless to one person, but you are priceless to another. Don't ever forget your value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the guy, you are suppose to chase after us. We pretend not to notice you because we want to see how hard you're willing to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter if the guy is perfect or the girl is perfect, as long as they are perfect for each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kadang, meski tahu kamu bisa saja mencintai seseorang yg bukan dirinya, kamu tak akan pernah bisa mencinta seperti kamu mencintai dirinya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes jealousy is just a way of telling someone you care too much to let them go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving someone isn't about what you can give them, it's about making them happy.. weather it's with or without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will always, always, always, always, always care about you. I just may not tell you.. but I will always do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how stormy the day, God will always eventually send a rainbow to your way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes listening to music with a headset is just the best way to ignore the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up... If you are willing to try the possible... God will help you through the impossible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm afraid if someone else catches your attention, you'll ignore me, maybe even worse... replace me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never feel bad about your choices you make in life, never regret your mistakes. Mistakes are to be made, just learn from them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when everything feels just so right when he/she around you and nothing else seems to appear or bother you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when your heart skips a beat or beats faster and slower at the same time when you just think about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when you look online all day for love quotes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aiqingfenxiang: 爱情是灯，友情是影子，当灯灭了，你会发现你的周围都是影子。朋友是在最后可以给你力量的人。]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were like strangers who knew each others very well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could stop. I wish I could just look at you as a friend, because that's all you'll ever see me as.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All things happen in God's perfect time... Hold on to God when everything else seems hopeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kesetiaan berarti ketulusan untuk menyimpan satu nama tetap di hati, kemudian berjanji untuk tidak mengkhianati.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you GOD for allowing me to see another day. I'm not live for myself, but to live for you. Lead me, help me do better than yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone truly wants you, nothing will keep them away. They will do everything they can just to be with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I need to cry in front of you so you can understand how much you hurt me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need any promise, I just need you to prove it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he really loves you, he will have time for you no matter how busy he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't text me because you're bored. Text me because I'm the person you want to talk to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find someone worth your tears, worth your laughter, worth your heart, and loves you as much as you love them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is just a word, unless someone comes along and gives it meaning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is greater than the need, and so much bigger than the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It might seem like the hardest thing to do, but you have to forget and let go the person who forgot about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know why, but even when we stop talking, just for a little while, I start to miss you right away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes in life you have to step out of your comfort zone. If you ever want to get anywhere in life, you have to lose your fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what you may be going through, there is always someone going through worse. Be grateful for your life and look at the positives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good boyfriend can't fix all your problems, but he can promise you won't face them alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bersyukur akan apa yang kita punya lebih baik daripada bersedih akan apa yang kita tidak punya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might laugh with other guys and I might text other guys, but none of them will ever mean as much to me as you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're happy, you enjoy the music. But when you're sad, you understand the lyrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't just thank God when everything is going right. Thank Him even when things may be challenging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people that will accept you for who you are, are the ones that will be with you forever, no matter what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl is beautiful, it sometimes just takes the right guy to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care if we talk about absolutely nothing... I just want to talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care if I'm tired. Staying up late texting you is better than sleeping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart has never felt like this before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want someone who will stay with me no matter how hard I am to be with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I first met you, I honestly didn't know you were gonna be this important to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you without reason and that is reason enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need to be popular just to win someone's heart. Be yourself. Because in someone's eyes, you are already special.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the effort that makes the girl smile. It's the willingness of guys to make those crazy efforts just to make her smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With faith you can press on during the dark times. Have faith and it will light your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U don't lose if u get knocked down, u lose if u stay down. Just don't lose hope. When u're down to nothing, God is up to something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl says "don't worry about it", you'd better worry about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see you're sad. Even when you smile, even when you laugh. I can see it in your eyes, deep inside you wanna cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only you will always have your back. That's why you should only rely on yourself to make you happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banyak rintangan dalam hidup ini, tapi Tuhan akan memberikan apa yang kamu butuhkan, bahkan kadang lebih daripada yang kamu inginkan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need someone to tell me how much they love me. I need someone that can show me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl cries for a boy it simply means she misses him. When a boy cries for a girl, he loves her more than anyone ever could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not that I want to be the only one in your life, I just want to be the only one that matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I speak to you, I realize how lucky I am to have someone like you in my life. You make me love you more and more everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not be able to remember &amp; return all ur kindness. But God sees, counts, &amp; multiplies all that u've given &amp; done with sincerity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've finally found that life goes on without you and my world still turns when you're not around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do right now is talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I miss you, you're still not missing me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't smile to make your day better, try to make someone else smile to make their day better and brighten yours in the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst feeling in the world is when you can't love anyone else because your heart still belongs to the one who broke it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best ways to make yourself happy is to make other people happy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>