<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Town &amp; Country Magazine Uninvited Monica Lewinsky From An Event Because Of Bill Clinton - HuffPost: HuffPost Town &amp; Country Magazine Uninvited Monica Lewinsky From An Event Because Of Bill Clinton HuffPost Town &amp; Country magazine disinvited Monica… https://t.co/th6yTd8gWO https://t.co/YCYk4khpe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Business Systems Analyst – Automated Testing: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Cleveland, OH Job Type: Product/Pricing/Analytics Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/12/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Serve as a subject matter expert in… https://t.co/WQRB2qpr3c https://t.co/oeMs6rKSC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Business Process Engineer (Prospect-to-Customer) (P-Mod): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely… https://t.co/os9zIqBy2D https://t.co/CoVJIMDDOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 75713BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians, Sales, Services, and Solutions Position Type Full Time Relocation… https://t.co/wfmHuGsi8F https://t.co/WbtYanagNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller questioned Novartis payment to Trump lawyer Michael Cohen - Washington Post: Washington Post Mueller questioned Novartis payment to Trump lawyer Michael Cohen Washington Post Special counsel Robert S. Mueller III's team sought information last… https://t.co/DlimL5RULG https://t.co/9hGBhaqmOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care… https://t.co/37xwUUiDia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump makes it explicit: Negative coverage of him is fake coverage - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump makes it explicit: Negative coverage of him is fake coverage Washington Post A generous interpretation of President Trump's views on “fake” news… https://t.co/jfXQBNBAnb https://t.co/ZHeIUQfjz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Agile Coach: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care coordination… https://t.co/XoyZ2w7Oac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mormon Church breaks all ties with Boy Scouts, ending 100-year relationship - Washington Post: Washington Post Mormon Church breaks all ties with Boy Scouts, ending 100-year relationship Washington Post The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints… https://t.co/7FFNYGKxkF https://t.co/mg9tZmfms7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haspel to pledge never to restart CIA's brutal interrogation program - Washington Post: Washington Post Haspel to pledge never to restart CIA's brutal interrogation program Washington Post Gina Haspel is expected to tell the Senate Intelligence Committee… https://t.co/tnsov3nZcX https://t.co/ik46bw8OW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Performance Tester: SAP Performance Tester Ref No.: 18-18500 Location: Dublin, Ohio Position: SAP Performance Tester Location: Dublin/OH Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Strong experience SAP Performance Tester. https://t.co/QnAjGn59T7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 big announcements from Google I/O 2018 - TechCrunch: TechCrunch 8 big announcements from Google I/O 2018 TechCrunch Google kicked off its annual I/O developer conference at Shoreline Amphitheater in Mountain View, California. Here are some of the… https://t.co/8wmhK3ElSc https://t.co/znNMJGBVwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: LendKey is solving a complex challenge to improve lives with lending made simple by helping financial institutions compete in the digital age and provide a delightful customer experience, while providing borrowers with the simple,… https://t.co/NgWAFx4Q4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer III – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 217648 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving many of America’s… https://t.co/zwTwP7f3zW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria blames Israel for air strike near Damascus - BBC News: BBC News Syria blames Israel for air strike near Damascus BBC News Syrian state media says Israel has launched an air strike against an army position south of the capital Damascus. The Sana… https://t.co/PXVwG5GHj5 https://t.co/xbVIwr92VF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Civil Engineer: Civil Engineering Project Manager * Manage project teams to create land development plans.for our commercial, institutional, and energy clients. From a hospital parking lot, natural gas plant, pipeline or well pad, to an… https://t.co/P71rzZrSpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Marketing Specialist: Are you interested in driving forward digital initiatives with a world-renowned medical center? Are you an experienced CRM specialist or analyst who is looking for an exciting change of pace in a healthcare setting? Our client… https://t.co/DVIPIbhAiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage Engineer (cisco MDS): Storage Engineer Santa clara ca Fulltime position Job Description: Provide hands-on server, storage administration, system maintenance and operations support. Build, configure, and troubleshoot vSphere. Diagnose and correct… https://t.co/Egx9lVDMYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has lost control of Trumpism - CNN: CNN Trump has lost control of Trumpism CNN Washington (CNN) Donald Trump can't control Trumpism, if he ever could. And the proof is in West Virginia, where, win or lose, the candidate who best represents the… https://t.co/4qYbe0ADuY https://t.co/qtvTpRP706]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-15708 Location: Columbus, Ohio Title:- Java Developer Location:- Columbus OH Contract Role Foundation : Core Java, Foundation : Java Web Services Java Webservices Thanks and Regards Tarun Arora Sr. IT Recruiter… https://t.co/ClUfvjAYrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Operations Manager: IT Operations Manager / Cincinnati , OH Overview: At TQL, our rapid growth and success has been dependent on our ability to deliver cutting-edge technology with an emphasis on performance and reliability. As the IT Operations… https://t.co/0elOZnQ07F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP activists are already rallying volunteers to stave off Democrats this fall - Washington Post: Washington Post GOP activists are already rallying volunteers to stave off Democrats this fall Washington Post GREENWOOD, Ind. — The midterm elections are… https://t.co/ZQ1vc5myNi https://t.co/ybyeXCAdIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea's Kim wants to talk to Trump about mutual nuclear issues, says Chinese media - Washington Post: Washington Post North Korea's Kim wants to talk to Trump about mutual nuclear issues, says Chinese media Washington Post TOKYO — North Korean… https://t.co/H2QhvbIZQw https://t.co/9Wbvhpe6GR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Schneiderman, Accused by 4 Women, Quits as New York Attorney General - New York Times: New York Times Eric Schneiderman, Accused by 4 Women, Quits as New York Attorney General New York Times Eric T. Schneiderman, the New York State attorney general… https://t.co/sal06ibVBZ https://t.co/eIg2UBP8Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Comcast prepares all-cash bid to gate-crash Disney-Fox deal - sources - Reuters: Reuters Exclusive: Comcast prepares all-cash bid to gate-crash Disney-Fox deal - sources Reuters (Reuters) - U.S. cable operator Comcast Corp is asking investment… https://t.co/hdS3w8IlTs https://t.co/UHJcbOse1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Software Engineer, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and… https://t.co/W3mIuPZX8H https://t.co/Yukbt3hi2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met Gala 2018: Best dressed looks from Rihanna, Amal Clooney, Lena Waithe and more - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Met Gala 2018: Best dressed looks from Rihanna, Amal Clooney, Lena Waithe and more USA TODAY Considering the dress code of the 2018 Met Gala was… https://t.co/BSOUtR6UDl https://t.co/qauvEeKmKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer | Microsoft Stack: .NET Developer | Microsoft Stack Columbus, OH 04-11-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread… https://t.co/gnSakhHfih https://t.co/4IrewPPVIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain's critiques of Trump have president's supporters angry and firing back - Washington Post: Washington Post McCain's critiques of Trump have president's supporters angry and firing back Washington Post As Sen. John McCain (R-Ariz.) remains in his… https://t.co/OluYsnre3W https://t.co/iwLBWDyt4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Weighs In on West Virginia Senate Race in Sign of Republican Anxiety - New York Times: New York Times Trump Weighs In on West Virginia Senate Race in Sign of Republican Anxiety New York Times WASHINGTON — President Trump intervened Monday in the… https://t.co/SaD6tBC2Xs https://t.co/QuCl6JXVuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New DHS policy could separate families caught crossing the border illegally - CNN: CNN New DHS policy could separate families caught crossing the border illegally CNN Washington (CNN) The Trump administration has decided to refer every person caught… https://t.co/ceSQoVXknH https://t.co/MhL4SFBIF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing college grads dragged off stage, school apologizes for being 'inappropriately aggressive' - ABC News: ABC News Dancing college grads dragged off stage, school apologizes for being 'inappropriately aggressive' ABC News The University of Florida's… https://t.co/i5D56Lv2sG https://t.co/CLkXeZyXTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Melania Trump's complicated White House life: Separate schedule, different priorities - Washington Post: Washington Post Inside Melania Trump's complicated White House life: Separate schedule, different priorities Washington Post Donald and… https://t.co/WYgTeMnZ5G https://t.co/sOmJ4JZQKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Miracle' child comes to life from brain injuries after parents sign organ donation papers - USA TODAY: USA TODAY 'Miracle' child comes to life from brain injuries after parents sign organ donation papers USA TODAY Jennifer Nicole Reindl has a simple… https://t.co/TygwuaURna https://t.co/LvdidLaJiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: Oracle DBA Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 04/09/18, Posted Date – 04/09/18 Primary SkillsOracle 12C,Oracle database administration,GRIDTax TermsC2COverview Must-haves 6+ years of hands-on Oracle database administration… https://t.co/XpufhF0eGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gina Haspel, nominee to head CIA, sought to withdraw over questions about her role in agency interrogation program - Washington Post: Washington Post Gina Haspel, nominee to head CIA, sought to withdraw over questions about her role in agency… https://t.co/0yf9jo2XQV https://t.co/8OrsP6TrW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Grc consultant: Who are we looking for? A mid-senior level SAP consultant to manage a critical activities in project. The Individual should be passionate about technology, experienced in managing cutting edge technology applications.… https://t.co/jlFXAf6Cq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* C++ Software Engineer, Mid Key Role: Participate in software design and implementation for advanced intelligence and weapons systems analysis projects. Serve as a part of a… https://t.co/HK9PLSx6iK https://t.co/RhzXiYV3h2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grieving parents of teen killed in Parkland school shooting use 'graphic activism' to confront the NRA - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Grieving parents of teen killed in Parkland school shooting use 'graphic activism' to confront the NRA Los… https://t.co/J6MlHLAfBr https://t.co/6uvMvaqxNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Lead: DESCRIPTION: Employer ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth. We are seeking a… https://t.co/TrD4NZdzaq https://t.co/kE3LVeojSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highway sniper who shot 2 idolized Nikolas Cruz, sheriff says - https://t.co/p7DV2HB4So: https://t.co/p7DV2HB4So Highway sniper who shot 2 idolized Nikolas Cruz, sheriff says https://t.co/p7DV2HB4So A sniper who targeted cars on a Georgia highway left… https://t.co/QT5ehU5x0J https://t.co/BqTg52i3Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Software Engineer IILocation: Columbus, OH As a Software Engineer II, a typical day might include the following: Work as a member of an agile team to enhance and improve software written in one or more of the following languages:… https://t.co/zvogawTXkR https://t.co/TnLuN8skGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Communications and Marketing DevOps Lead: Customer Communications and Marketing DevOps Lead ================================================= Apply now Date: Apr 10, 2018 Location: Blue Ash, OH, US, 45242 Company: Kroger Company Name: Kroger… https://t.co/5VXtLJ3QzN https://t.co/xkcM3oJsGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Team Takes a More Aggressive Stance on Mueller Probe - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Trump Team Takes a More Aggressive Stance on Mueller Probe Wall Street Journal WASHINGTON—President Donald Trump's legal team is striking a more… https://t.co/b8qmsErU5a https://t.co/Ib4g21tnti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nunes, in spat with Justice Department, threatens Sessions with contempt over Russia materials - CNN: CNN Nunes, in spat with Justice Department, threatens Sessions with contempt over Russia materials CNN (CNN) House Intelligence Committee Chairman Devin… https://t.co/IAHRqcxBHc https://t.co/GWwLd1iKgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nikki Haley on Trump, "confusion," and speaking her mind - CBS News: CBS News Nikki Haley on Trump, "confusion," and speaking her mind CBS News Our SUNDAY PROFILE this morning is of Nikki Haley, our outspoken Ambassador to the United Nations. She talks… https://t.co/HuE2F4aN32 https://t.co/Wyhw3MnpDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani says Trump doesn't have to comply with a Mueller subpoena and could invoke the Fifth Amendment - Washington Post: Washington Post Giuliani says Trump doesn't have to comply with a Mueller subpoena and could invoke the Fifth Amendment Washington… https://t.co/HF232OrxJ4 https://t.co/zGt6SNZ0Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump campaigns for Senate candidate, derides immigration laws at Ohio tax roundtable - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump campaigns for Senate candidate, derides immigration laws at Ohio tax roundtable Washington Post CLEVELAND — President Trump… https://t.co/IZeMlcQuFL https://t.co/yAJHg9QC7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: Business Intelligence Analyst / Cincinnati , OH Overview:We are seeking an entry to mid-level Business Intelligence Analyst that possesses both technical aptitude and incredible customer service skills. You’ll be working… https://t.co/ditYHN0wns https://t.co/2lHjS8NHHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran's president: US ending deal will be 'historic regret' - Washington Post: Washington Post Iran's president: US ending deal will be 'historic regret' Washington Post TEHRAN, Iran — Iran's president is warning President Donald Trump that pulling… https://t.co/P0SqZ5wyhg https://t.co/SsYzTjE9am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT: Joe Biden says John McCain 'concerned about the state of the country' - CNN: CNN NYT: Joe Biden says John McCain 'concerned about the state of the country' CNN Washington (CNN) Former Vice President Joe Biden recently took a trip to Arizona to visit… https://t.co/NYaFuNUEJr https://t.co/8Fa5RNfTYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Software Engineer: Are you an ops person with a penchant for software development? Then we might be looking for you. If you have experience with Hadoop, public or private cloud, we might be in love. This position is with one of our clients in… https://t.co/0e0PZXIgh1 https://t.co/xTfsYmeyRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Cox, Travis Allen court state GOP delegates before endorsement vote for California governor - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times John Cox, Travis Allen court state GOP delegates before endorsement vote for California governor Los Angeles Times… https://t.co/1RnrkBlP2b https://t.co/r13rxfLZJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Cardinal Health at Home is a best-in-class provider of medical supplies to patients in the home. It is comprised of two separate operating segments: Edgepark, a leading direct-to-consumer (DTC) medical supplies provider and… https://t.co/g7oKrtxCdl https://t.co/5rqhTW2RYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House: China's demands to US airlines 'Orwellian nonsense' - Politico: Politico White House: China's demands to US airlines 'Orwellian nonsense' Politico Amid high-level negotiations on trade, the White House on Saturday called China's demands that… https://t.co/ziLznU3MQo https://t.co/GSSUwzxnIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At His Ranch, John McCain Shares Memories and Regrets With Friends - New York Times: New York Times At His Ranch, John McCain Shares Memories and Regrets With Friends New York Times PHOENIX — When former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. traveled to… https://t.co/9N4hssoikE https://t.co/1Ax8ENFLXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homicide suspect kills Indiana police officer in shootout, dies from injuries - New York Daily News: New York Daily News Homicide suspect kills Indiana police officer in shootout, dies from injuries New York Daily News A man who killed a police officer… https://t.co/0K5Q7tECf3 https://t.co/37GnMZ8S5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ending protection for Hondurans was unnecessary - CNN: CNN Trump ending protection for Hondurans was unnecessary CNN Raul A. Reyes is an attorney and member of the USA Today board of contributors. Follow him on Twitter @RaulAReyes. The opinions… https://t.co/sBMiwnraoa https://t.co/9ulVJdezcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Operations Software Engineer: Are you aa recent grad with an interest in development and ops? Then we might be looking for you. If you have experience with Hadoop, public or private cloud, we might be in love. This position is with one of our… https://t.co/LZfBZzSUuY https://t.co/qV8ORdtV0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George HW Bush released from hospital after treatment for infection - Washington Post: Washington Post George HW Bush released from hospital after treatment for infection Washington Post Former president George H.W. Bush has been discharged from the… https://t.co/wRBy9eNov6 https://t.co/DOkZznZXWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer | test driven development, paired programming re-factoring code: Application Developer | test driven development, paired programming &amp; re-factoring code Columbus, OH 04-11-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years,… https://t.co/mHSIw0w1yQ https://t.co/W3fTggpNJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Operations Specialist: Overview CFNA is a limited purpose federally chartered private label credit card bank and a longstanding credit provider in the automotive service and tire industry. We provide private label credit card solutions for… https://t.co/j7EW2n7Tyc https://t.co/ciqfUL1aiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa bans nearly all abortions as governor signs 'fetal heartbeat' law - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Iowa bans nearly all abortions as governor signs 'fetal heartbeat' law USA TODAY DES MOINES — Iowa's governor signed legislation Friday prohibiting nearly all… https://t.co/ZLB8cS3NC7 https://t.co/iDmunFGjlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: DESCRIPTION: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Employer currently has an opening for a COMPUTER SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR to support contracts on Wright-Patterson AFB in Dayton, OH. The successful candidate will work with a… https://t.co/9QMf2OMIwl https://t.co/u1TswLGl49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's eagerness for a deal with North Korea leaves future of US troops in South Korea uncertain - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Trump's eagerness for a deal with North Korea leaves future of US troops in South Korea uncertain Los Angeles Times… https://t.co/Qj1pUEDg5s https://t.co/5B2xXk3Ohe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo self-driving minivan involved in crash in Arizona - The Verge: The Verge Waymo self-driving minivan involved in crash in Arizona The Verge A self-driving vehicle operated by Waymo was involved in a crash in Chandler, Arizona, on Friday afternoon,… https://t.co/2conR8mtmH https://t.co/laXCRZPNUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence's doctor resigns after reports of concerns about Jackson's conduct - CNN: CNN Pence's doctor resigns after reports of concerns about Jackson's conduct CNN Washington (CNN) The White House physician assigned to Vice President Mike Pence, Jennifer… https://t.co/eqvZYp41qi https://t.co/B2cQWmmowL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance and Release Specialist: Quality Assurance and Release Specialist / Cincinnati , OH Overview: Join our scrum team with a focus on Quality Assurance and release planning for our Core Product Development Team. This position will work on… https://t.co/t4jl46pyG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway Comes for April Ryan in Latest White House Attack on Top Black Journalist - Newsweek: Newsweek Kellyanne Conway Comes for April Ryan in Latest White House Attack on Top Black Journalist Newsweek Top White House adviser Kellyanne Conway… https://t.co/SFiKewUt8N https://t.co/Cj0Ab8Waod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani tries to clean up his hubris-inspired mess - Washington Post: Washington Post Rudy Giuliani tries to clean up his hubris-inspired mess Washington Post I disagree with the prevailing wisdom that Rudy Giuliani committed one giant blunder… https://t.co/mvLWBrf9gV https://t.co/huxfjjbTk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii's Kilauea erupts. Evacuations underway as lava threatens communities. - Washington Post: Washington Post Hawaii's Kilauea erupts. Evacuations underway as lava threatens communities. Washington Post After authorities had warned for several days of… https://t.co/Jl5YvGs8Rs https://t.co/lkXgr8aga1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local election results 2018: Mixed picture for Labour and Tories - BBC News: https://t.co/lhxy8Rqpfd Local election results 2018: Mixed picture for Labour and Tories BBC News Labour and the Conservatives have both lost control of key councils in local… https://t.co/6Zqc6G7fQ9 https://t.co/GgbrVE3J37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Custom Application Specialist: Custom Application Specialist About Us: Cincinnati Sub-Zero Products, LLC, a leading manufacturer of Patient Temperature Management Devices and a Global provider of Industrial Test Chambers is in need of DYNAMIC talent to… https://t.co/7x2E4k2Xyp https://t.co/Y1ghMxJ3jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greitens impeachment to be considered by lawmakers in special session - CBS News: CBS News Greitens impeachment to be considered by lawmakers in special session CBS News JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. -- In a historic move, Missouri lawmakers announced Thursday… https://t.co/l6Ldc25vFe https://t.co/tdgMZYeT3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blankenship blames 'the establishment' after Trump Jr. criticism - The Hill: The Hill Blankenship blames 'the establishment' after Trump Jr. criticism The Hill Don Blankenship, the controversial Republican candidate for Senate in West Virginia, responded… https://t.co/5C0O1Z1EnV https://t.co/lT508DGsM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser From Chinese Base Aimed at US Military Pilots In Africa's Skies, Pentagon Charges - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Laser From Chinese Base Aimed at US Military Pilots In Africa's Skies, Pentagon Charges Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/s938tuffA2 https://t.co/T8DcivDqoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: Family found dead had recently moved to Grand Forks neighborhood - Grand Forks Herald: KDLT News Update: Family found dead had recently moved to Grand Forks neighborhood Grand Forks Herald Authorities were at the scene of a Grand Forks residence… https://t.co/Z9CMy1TT9d https://t.co/vO3OLJBZ3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk's conduct, Tesla stock slide make $700 million profit for short-sellers - Reuters: Reuters Musk's conduct, Tesla stock slide make $700 million profit for short-sellers Reuters NEW YORK (Reuters) - Short-sellers who had targeted Tesla Inc logged a… https://t.co/7kOKsg3cnv https://t.co/a5Z9hnILVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body found after nine officers injured in Connecticut barn explosion - New York Daily News: New York Daily News Body found after nine officers injured in Connecticut barn explosion New York Daily News A body was discovered among the charred remains of a… https://t.co/XdgXjYHotN https://t.co/N82QscOBaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Architect / Architect Project Manager: is seeking qualified Architects for immediate openings. DLZ is an award-winning, full-service architecture and engineering firm with over 600 employees located in 22 offices. DLZ has built long-standing… https://t.co/1nCpF9uyGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Adds Clinton Impeachment Lawyer, Bracing for a Fight on Multiple Fronts - New York Times: New York Times Trump Adds Clinton Impeachment Lawyer, Bracing for a Fight on Multiple Fronts New York Times WASHINGTON — President Trump hired on Wednesday a… https://t.co/Jx3VjalYEw https://t.co/HXH6HOSRk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Consultant: Developer Consultant What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At the heart… https://t.co/DxechADMIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico Air National Guard plane crashes on its final flight, killing nine on board - Washington Post: Washington Post Puerto Rico Air National Guard plane crashes on its final flight, killing nine on board Washington Post A Puerto Rico Air National… https://t.co/USwlk5dVea https://t.co/4VTBARpNLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica to File for Bankruptcy After Misuse of Facebook Data - New York Times: New York Times Cambridge Analytica to File for Bankruptcy After Misuse of Facebook Data New York Times Cambridge Analytica's offices in London in March. The firm… https://t.co/ncNPg8ZMkl https://t.co/iNfbEgVWre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las Vegas police release video footage recorded inside gunman Stephen Paddock's hotel suite - Washington Post: Washington Post Las Vegas police release video footage recorded inside gunman Stephen Paddock's hotel suite Washington Post The officers sweep… https://t.co/P93S3lff1F https://t.co/XGyPaD5suw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano teen arrested in ISIS-inspired plot to commit mass shooting at Frisco's Stonebriar mall - Dallas News: Dallas News Plano teen arrested in ISIS-inspired plot to commit mass shooting at Frisco's Stonebriar mall Dallas News This story is being… https://t.co/ZYDPHFUay3 https://t.co/JtC9MB2t3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainians Stop Investigating Manafort After Trump Sells Them Missiles. A Win-Win for All Involved. - Slate Magazine: Slate Magazine Ukrainians Stop Investigating Manafort After Trump Sells Them Missiles. A Win-Win for All Involved. Slate Magazine The… https://t.co/6kkxMvU7Dc https://t.co/YsuRwFxk5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa Lawmakers Pass Ban on Most Abortions, Aiming for Court Fight - New York Times: New York Times Iowa Lawmakers Pass Ban on Most Abortions, Aiming for Court Fight New York Times Iowa lawmakers early Wednesday passed a bill that would outlaw most… https://t.co/W82WyXlHOv https://t.co/R5DQR4MCo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harold Bornstein: Exiled from Trumpland, doctor now 'frightened and sad' - Washington Post: Washington Post Harold Bornstein: Exiled from Trumpland, doctor now 'frightened and sad' Washington Post They came knocking because of loose talk about the… https://t.co/xIZ2ORetRq https://t.co/yzVC9XPlq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacist is guilty in Charlottesville parking garage beating of black man - Washington Post: Washington Post White supremacist is guilty in Charlottesville parking garage beating of black man Washington Post CHARLOTTESVILLE — One of the white… https://t.co/67NsaLhwka https://t.co/qeyUhDaCjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst, Software Engineering (SAP MM Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/v2BTIIplEA https://t.co/9AxLk4d7mB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager-IT: At TalentLaunch and our family of companies, we believe that when you match the right person to the right career, the possibilities are endless. Its a little process we like to call unlocking unrealized potential. At TalentLaunch we… https://t.co/fHkhHO32fR https://t.co/bbdt1lSTYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Allays iPhone Worries, Adds $100 Billion to Buyback Plans - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Apple Allays iPhone Worries, Adds $100 Billion to Buyback Plans Wall Street Journal Apple staved off recent concerns about the future of its iPhone… https://t.co/VnNk9Pt1e9 https://t.co/Sfvu5nCJuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's mission to connect people now includes dating help - Washington Post: Washington Post Facebook's mission to connect people now includes dating help Washington Post SAN JOSE — At Facebook's annual developer conference, chief executive Mark… https://t.co/Ke4L5gWTHp https://t.co/QjARD1Xyyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Level 1: Software Engineer Level 1 Join a team recognized for leadership, innovation and diversity Honeywell Intelligrated is seeking a Software Engineer to join our growing team based out of the West Chester OH office. A Software… https://t.co/g7Wfp8hpx6 https://t.co/Uu3UXJ8SfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School claims 'Modesty Poncho' was not meant to be worn by students, but to 'remind' them of prom dress code - Fox News: Fox News School claims 'Modesty Poncho' was not meant to be worn by students, but to 'remind' them of prom dress code Fox News A… https://t.co/zs1hwYJjjz https://t.co/7saRUPsvES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP candidates don't want to talk about Stormy Daniels. Neither do Democrats. - CNN: CNN GOP candidates don't want to talk about Stormy Daniels. Neither do Democrats. CNN (CNN) In any other political environment, headlines about the President of the… https://t.co/h7sFHR5onL https://t.co/CWjIVrlVqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parkland father files lawsuit against 'coward' school resource officer - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Parkland father files lawsuit against 'coward' school resource officer https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC "I want to expose that coward so… https://t.co/cOqU5BJf9q https://t.co/SndXHa1sqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 most intriguing questions Robert Mueller wants to ask Trump - Washington Post: CBS News The 7 most intriguing questions Robert Mueller wants to ask Trump Washington Post Now we know what special counsel Robert S. Mueller III wants to ask President… https://t.co/reHVH3RZDk https://t.co/sR7a6xeZw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATION DEVELOPER: Full Job Description can be obtained from the link "**************************************************************************************************** The description below may contain some unreadable words or sentences, so you… https://t.co/XxWpgADvXe https://t.co/cb64WDSzpS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>