<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnP_CBC Pierre Poilievre is the slipperiest politician in Canada. Can't stand his arrogance and half truths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broken but not out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is in life's common denominators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pchiddy congratulations! Go Canada!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday night @ home, tortellini, spinach salad, vodka oj, watching men's world figure skating Lol does that make me gay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really got to stop wearing my heart on my sleeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is a candle in your heart, ready to be kindled.
There is a void in your soul, ready to be filled.
You feel it, don't you?” - Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#JusticeForTrayvon anywhere but #Florida. #StandYourGround law should be repealed. #Boycott travel to #Florida and have your say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squirrely_Ninja @TransLink current zone system is flawed. Paying by distance travelled is fair and reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found some balance with a hard day of physical labour today. I could go for a day or two like this every week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink #Compass pay as you go &amp; more will use it. More users + more revenue = less cars + less gauging taxpayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thoughts and prayers go out to those affected by the events in Lac-Megantic, Quebec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshade scandalbrewing my new fave! http://t.co/Sk7k6BdxIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know how many are being hurt and what is being damaged for big oil? Who are the elite that are making millions on it? @CTVNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In need of a break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil is just too much to handle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for a football match. Brazil 1: 0 Spain 2 in under 3 min]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vikkiwkl: At @MyVancouver staff meeting. Congrats Debbie for 25 years at Tourism Vancouver! #tourism http://t.co/Ukl1myTP6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Her #Majesty the #Queen and the #Royal stable. So nice to see you so happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great brand strategy session today with our new CBO, Larry Donen @jamjartweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta pay accountant before affording tickets to @BrunoMars in Vancouver. Going broke first. Success and payout, second. Onwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[260 push ups plus a bunch of other stuff while watchin @BrunoMars on the @NBCTheVoice. Wish I had tickets to Vancouver show :'(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking up live Dungeness crab and spot prawns for dinner. TGIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the gym after much procrastination. Feels good. Now to keep it up. Persistence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scandalbrewing discovered your lager last night. Amazing! Where can I buy a case in Yaletown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a nice day! Making progress. Moving forward. Persistence is paying off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC Conservative Art of War strategy: talk up being the most transparent govt while being most secretive. It's a smokescreen #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shizen Ya Japanese on West Broadway in #Vancouver is a must try. All organic, all fresh, all delicious! Mmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent start to the week. Gym time then dinner with the love of my life. Onwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine what I would do if I could do all I can? - Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great intelligence for tech start ups @kevinrose Foundation series on #Vimeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC: gov't in coming weeks, "I can't comment on an ongoing RCMP investigation" #deny #deflect #delay #dishonest #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How convenient #Duffy doesn't show up to #senCA committee to answer questions. Another delay to #truth. #shame #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @richardbranson: If you’ve got it – use it! Why business must exist for a higher purpose than just profit http://t.co/vUGdL4rKCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Just as ripples spread out when a single pebble is dropped into water, the actions of individuals can have far-reaching effe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovin the tasty collaboration in kitchen these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Angeloistic serious?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bo Laksa King: #fabulous #Malaysian #Burmese food in #Vancouver @ 2546 E. Hastings #cheap #tasty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bchesky: Every day, there are 3M mobile phones activated and 370k babies born. That's a nearly 10:1 phone to baby activation ratio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcmpgrcpolice why is it a @senateCA decision whether to hand over #duffy #scandal to #rcmp? Is the @senateCA above the law?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnP_CBC Where is the #rcmp in the #duffy #Senate #pmo scandal as #senators and the #pmo act as if they are above the law?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @leisure: “@jkottke: I've found it, the world's best Vine video: https://t.co/pv6Otlc4QD” WAIT. WHAT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: You go to jail in Russia for being gay. Someone better arrest those nesting dolls. They're ladies inside other ladies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAtlantic: China's population is equal to the population of the Americas, Australia, New Zealand, and Western Europe—combined http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @levie: 3 days in and still no Hyperloop. If this was a photo sharing app, it would have millions of users and already be acquired by no…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brian_wong @yvrairport welcome back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scobleizer perfect! Just sent you an email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scobleizer can I send a car to pick you up at YVR and drive you to your hotel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@brian_wong: @DilankaWettewa it knew” haha perfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoungFlip7 this guy is brilliant! Follow him on #ANW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does washing your hands with hot water clean better than cold? #whatiwanttoknow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 blondes walking side by side down bike path. 1 deer staring at me as I ride towards them. "Yes! You are on a bike lane!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drsanjaygupta big pharma doesn't want us to know about medical benefits of #Weed oil. They would be out of business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drsanjaygupta early 1900s Bayer sold oil but big pharma couldn't patent &amp; control sale of it so manipulated govt to demonize use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad but relieved. Tomorrow is the start of a new chapter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimGunn love your Yoda moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop, look both ways and proceed with caution. Some of the best advice ever given yet so many forget to do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screw Putin! #Kealys #Moonshine #Premium #Vodka #Diamond filtered in #BC #Canada. Liquid #Happiness no #prejudice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Kealy's Moonshine is dangerous! So smooth and delicious it goes down so easy. #premium #vodka #diamond filtered in #BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Banks are hazardous to ones health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PnPCBC Sochi Olympics is the perfect opportunity and stage for athletes and countries to stand up against intolerance in Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Among human beings trust comes about, not from expressions of wealth or fame, but from our showing affection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennisthetang seems legit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GanzHydraulus: Run when you can, walk when you have to, crawl if you must, just never give up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudden rain storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the bright side, the Stanley park seawall was nice and quiet today. Twice around and home again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks, oil, agra, pharma &amp; govt.  Control the money, fuel, food, drugs &amp; regulations &amp; control the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#big #banks and their untouchable executives are richer and more powerful than ever after barely a slap on the wrist post 2008.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I make a bank deposit after 5pm, it posts tomorrow but #banks can withdraw anytime over night &amp; post retroactively. It's not right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['08 crash was caused by massive &amp; unaccountable fraud by elite bank executives on the backs of the 99%. Not one has seen jail time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going on 33 days without rain #Sunny #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Vancouver sets record for sunniest July on record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abs are made in the kitchen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tutticontenti: Fox News anchor #LaurenGreen is further proof that #Fox only hires bigoted illiterates. And there are people who watch t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Week 2: tracker screwed up on 2nd one. More like 29km. Week 1: 3  days @ 21km and 4 @ 29km. http://t.co/2Rz911gR5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacular night for fireworks. Oh #Vancouver oh so gorgeous! http://t.co/bF8gAijrn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyGWeir Sochi is an opportunity for the world to stand up to intolerance. Go, compete, be proud. Don't let Putin &amp; his thugs win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to predict the future is to create it" - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Putin an ignorant, scared thug who should be charged w crimes against humanity. #boycottRussia w your wallet &amp; influence change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing worse than being blind is having sight but no vision" - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was is over. What is is now. Now focus and make the future worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Card giants earn $5-7billion on the backs of #Canadians /yr.  An average of $175/Cdn. Time for caps on CC fees @JimFlaherty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding balance. Rode 110 miles last week. Going for 125 miles this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A step in the right direction. #UAE ruler of #Dubai pardons Norwegian woman jailed after reporting rape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boycottDubai until rape laws are changed #BoycottFLORIDA until stand your ground law repealed. It's time for #Justice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dubai #Florida places w ridiculous laws. Perhaps if more of us said NO &amp; stopped traveling there, they would sit up &amp; listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver thanks for the follow up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 6 - daily regimen riding around #Stanleypark. So blessed to live in #Vancouver w this out my doorstep. http://t.co/bPVgJ1TFPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver how much is it costing for each of these electric car stations at Sunset beach?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is it. Gotta make this one count!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. Had to repost. Have a great weekend everyone! http://t.co/HCN5vd74FR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurGriffiths "Vancouver is great at promoting itself as a big city but in reality, not so much"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @ArthurGriffiths. Nice to hear your story, unfiltered and candid. Thanks also to @kharecom for the invite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to @kharecom interview @ArthurGriffiths, former owner of @VanCanucks. Should be an interesting conversation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marioalv_ haha thanks! What are you using?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marioalv_ I galaxy 4 is pretty nice. Also Motorola just came out with one. I need to do some research]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marioalv_ I need a new phone and was waiting to see what they would do next.  I think #Apple missed the mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been with #iPhone since 1st week it was launched but I think this relationship might be over #Apple #epicfail disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twilight tonight on my bike ride after work http://t.co/Z3JSLQfyzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice day for a ride http://t.co/JDtlKfE1zI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>