<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/8dMbjMKW5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/jp89mEKaPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/9elIK4emzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/v1KANVMiI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/jcMxH6IHok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/vZU9y8kj4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/Sit6dH6bsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/WkQ7xsJyqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/Z9m8J56gLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/LV0D83mqDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/7fkiWnQVFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/SQDhPvVJYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/w0ikzyB9cQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/4fDWRWuQRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/ZYNpOWWWRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/6ut9B8UWac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/8sRD9eZq9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/DetwRe6ack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/OHLjN6z3LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/fPny35Hay3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/uIXyJHFQFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/AoGHRqGzfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/jCwE9utYH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/3QTJrxBOot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/yfmkOfyx2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/rTNsUI5hQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/NeDkuG5mUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/dgSxl2A2it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1noevE2tPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/sdNPL8y01L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/XpwMxisKPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. - Marcia Wieder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/Im3xjaJNza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/9yfblf4sQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/y1flc8gQQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/SXyQMQETiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/6t3MDOU9zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/CfSvqoMuO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/SDbsNOddN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/QOC10xkchU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/LhLERBbULF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/dscJP5TJt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/ztUl5U1E64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/vZU9y8kj4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/w2GBwLne2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/16MqPQH1Cy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/wGSwykkC5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/iy8pRbHaoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>