<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SimoneBeauvoirs: Feminists must fight against the capitalist fetishization of monogamy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Negro revolution is controlled by foxy white liberals, by the Government itself. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In retrospect, all revolutions seem inevitable. Beforehand, all revolutions seem impossible.   Michael McFaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeopleYouNeed: Sober people, they will empower you by showing you that life is best lived without all the mindless intoxications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easier to pass a camel through the eye of a needle than for a rich man to enter the Kingdom of Heaven. ~Jesus Christ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nonviolence is fine as long as it works. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BiIIWilson: It's never too late to say no to alcohol. I drank heavily for many years but I was still able to quit for the Revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power never takes a back step only in the face of more power. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JPMorgans: Investment bankers are liars who evade the truth about the markets eventual doom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can give you freedom. Nobody can give you equality or justice or anything. If you're a man, you take it. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not ready to die for it, put the word 'freedom' out of your vocabulary.~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even call it violence when it's in self defense; I call it intelligence. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rosa__Luxemburg: Perpetuate the revolutionary flow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be peaceful, be courteous, obey the law, respect everyone; but if someone puts his hand on you, send him to the cemetery. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who stands for nothing will fall for anything. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikhaiIBakunin: Those who do not want revolution are no anarchists, the masses want revolution and anarchy is the will of the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe that banking institutions are more dangerous to our liberties than standing armies. ~ Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dear__Teenagers: Make revolutionary friends and work on political projects with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who accepts evil without protesting against it is really cooperating with it. Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who passively accepts evil is as much involved in it as he who helps perpetrate it. Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WealthyFacts: According to MSU, wealthy individuals are far more attracted to the history of kings and queens than the history of popul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workers of the world you have nothing to lose but your chains nothing to gain but your freedom. Workers of the world unite. -Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow the revolution will already 'raise itself with a rattle' and announce with fanfare, to your terror: I was, I am, I will be!" - Rosa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Malcom___X: African American slavery will not end until members of the community revolutionize their social instincts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The basic law of capitalism is you or I, not both you and I." - Karl Liebknecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["History is the only true teacher, the revolution the best school for the proletariat." - Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For to be free is not merely to cast off one's chains, but to live in a way that respects and enhances the freedom of others. ~ Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: Lockheed Martin managed to get US subsidies to help sell fighter planes to Poland at the end of 2002/beginning of 2003.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most heroic word in all languages is revolution. -E Debs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rosa__Luxemburg: Revolt for yourself, for your life, for your future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a revolution started with the actions of a few. -W Marsalis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revolution is not an apple that falls when it is ripe. You have to make it fall. -Che]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnK_Galbraith: The stock market induces mindless production because growth is its only motto regardless of the direction of this grow…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who make peaceful revolution impossible will make violent revolution inevitable. -JFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every generation needs a revolution. -Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeopleUDontNeed: Delusional Dreamers, you know the brainwashed people who spend their lives dreaming of achieving the lives of capitali…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the people understood the banking system, there would be a revolution tomorrow. ~Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is the oxygen of the soul. ~Moshe Dayan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2GetFired: If your superiors say you work too slow, tell them 'At least I work, look at the lazy CEO on the golf course'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hero-worship is strongest where there is least regard for human freedom. ~Herbert Spencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom in capitalist society always remains about the same as it was in ancient Greek republics: Freedom for slave owners. ~Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there is state there can be no freedom, but when there is freedom there will be no state. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Voltaire: Revolt against religion and you will find yourself more intellectually, socially, culturally active.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is what you do with what's been done to you. ~Jean-Paul Sartre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom lies in being bold. ~Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Fox News: a media company dedicated to distorting the news and spreading maniacal fears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Necessity is blind until it becomes conscious. Freedom is the consciousness of necessity. ~Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. ~George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeizeWallStreet: Physical protests must be designed as efficiently and cheaply as possible; the movement cannot afford wasted resources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only free men can negotiate; prisoners cannot enter into contracts. Your freedom and mine cannot be separated. ~Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as part freedom. ~Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reasons2BLazy: Being unproductive is a great way to make the corporations suffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let freedom reign. The sun never set on so glorious a human achievement. ~Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves. ~Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is never voluntarily given by the oppressor; it must be demanded by the oppressed. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing worse than rebellion is the thing that causes rebellion. ~Frederick Douglass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikhaiIBakunin: Anarchy is the revolutionization of the relationship between the self and the community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rebellion is the only thing that keeps you alive! ~Marianne Faithfull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find rebellion packaged by a major corporation a little hard to take seriously. ~David Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Francis__Assisi: Instead of spending your life seeking more luxuries, seek political freedom for all human beings, finance the commune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without democracy there is no freedom. Violence, no matter who is using it, is always reactionary. ~Friedrich Ebert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reactionary: a man walking backwards with his face to the future. ~Aneurin Bevan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeizeWallStreet: Build up SWS by loosening people's traditional loyalties to a 'free' society in which bankers are free to rob the peop…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reactionary is a somnambulist walking backwards. ~Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Freedom from fear" could be said to sum up the whole philosophy of human rights. ~Dag Hammarskjold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RebellingSlave: I will stand steadfast in the face of capital and I will denounce it bit by bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World wide capitalism kills more people everyday then Hitler did. And he was crazy. ~Ken Livingstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's immediately profitable is the only kind of logic that capitalism understands. ~Susan George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: The average Coca Cola addict drinks 3 bottles per day, that's 219000 calories of corn syrup fat per year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have two evils to fight, capitalism and racism. We must destroy both racism and capitalism. ~Huey Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under capitalism, man exploits man. ~John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Exploited Women: women that are conditioned by the mass media to hate their bodies in order to cajole them into buying…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The basic law of capitalism is you or I, not both you and I. ~Karl Liebknecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this country, capitalism triumphed over democracy. ~Fran Lebowitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Disney: a corporation which works hard to brand children before they develop any kind of revolutionary instinct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find capitalism repugnant. It is filthy, it is gross, it is alienating... because it causes war, hypocrisy and competition. ~Castro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For capitalism, war and peace are business and nothing but business. ~Karl Liebknecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnK_Galbraith: The stock market will crash because the people are sick of the bankers banking on a docile populace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascism is capitalism plus murder. ~Upton Sinclair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism without bankruptcy is like Christianity without hell. Don't bailout the bankers! ~Frank Borman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoIIstonecraft: The revolutionary girl works to spread the spirit of resistance in everything that she creates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism is war; socialism is peace. ~Karl Liebknecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism is the legitimate racket of the ruling class. ~Al Capone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2SpotTraitor: Traitors to the left tend to be extremely attached to one capitalist indulgence or another: pornography, fashion, fanc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism has destroyed our belief in any effective power but that of self interest backed by force. ~George Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History is a tool used by capitalist politicians to justify their intentions. ~Ted Koppel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reasons2DropOut: A college degree represents a four year prison sentence in which you are prepared for a lifetime wage-slavery sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy no longer works for the poor if capitalist politicians treat them as a separate race. ~Frank Field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A capitalist politician's goal is always to manipulate public debate. ~Dean Koontz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Huey_PNewton: The people will rise and seize power!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising men and capitalist politicians are dangerous if they are separated. Together they are diabolical. ~ Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These capitalists generally act harmoniously and in concert, to fleece the people. ~Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DearConservtive: Conservatism is fascism; they both serve the interests of capital at the expense of the well being of humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guiding principle is not to manufacture the goods everyone needs, rather to earn profits for a few capitalists. ~ Ulbricht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is impossible for capitalists and laborers to have common interests. ~Samuel Gompers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalists are no more capable of self-sacrifice than a man is capable of lifting himself up by his own bootstraps. ~Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberate the minds of men and ultimately you will liberate the bodies of men. ~Marcus Garvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadicalOrSlave: Are you disgusted by those individuals who treat personal success like the only factor that matters in all existence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time we liberate a woman, we liberate a man. ~Margaret Mead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is better to die on your feet than to live on your knees. - Emiliano Zapata]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>