<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/iwWc7TIRkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/AhURY7AnMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/lV1hbchQYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/Br7EoPAL0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/sdKKQh5uYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/StLJ7wyR4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/ciaFsOT52P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/Q4VHWrXPO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/F3WNqHqEtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/aX7MtdCEGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/fwxXilZ7rM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/hkU3kAOkqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/4R8ENNDTGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/VZnzKcJ4XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/STu5G8avLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/Jh8TsaGdkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/2WdETNBztc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/bht28VsM1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/8bsHUxHVLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/jtUscLrZVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/V3WZOpBmk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/JHkrdaTLTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 12 - And so it begins...  http://t.co/7Cw9lc2qEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/kuHJQV0zOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/Vg50m8ZLnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/EF2jeAxu5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/kKDT5E2BNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/jCwE9utYH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/RAU79h0fyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/1a5cqjxDbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/veelmh7wxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/pYamlev4tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/Xfq7e1vEO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/jLRbql0zrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/XeMf0tgGXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/72mrqZbTJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/Hmfj5c6h6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/tKDlyAdCyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/w0ikzyB9cQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/YF1I6bHoAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the confidence that makeup gives me. --&gt; Tyra Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/qWjObcxnWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/AubXipv6ww]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>