<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/94FXdKbStG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/xEM0GbBnNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/uBdgtzCAqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/AqUqIYrBXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/2MYezl2f1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/yToOvC0fXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/r4skxOS9Lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/9oXoGxaSYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/QJB8WOfwWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/PKSTkmsvRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/2a9baVkyfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/3knTBXxIgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/vt1Uk0kz9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/Ctsn1gl18S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/SG7aakWm8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/SELzJ6uCSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/xgVbcogvzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/jjM2CzdR2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/X4LehTfRjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/5iW6bOTsKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/pqD2NwZDEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/X7mqTCTSET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/oAf4aW9C0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/yLtuna9wdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/jrggBPXsri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/FYLs41k9Eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/SPlK0qEyYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/QyoG3010TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/xEM0GbBnNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/DXgZG2MBPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/3aDOHNrmJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/FKXzjhFV8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/O6HWZNM1om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/X4LehTfRjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/tlbkz1HVLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/4NQVTH4GPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/wspSAKMQoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to being a good manager is keeping the people who hate me away from those who are still undecided. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/adUjJoNesT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/7I5oyrk3k0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/wudKXx3gbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/25S8auT2c7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD?  I prefer the term intellectual Bad ASS!  http://t.co/X8hTWHTGAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/GwcZug2Iz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/Ctsn1gl18S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/SJmgASQHj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/9nbnNIByKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/IlkB29QxnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>