<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who says their life I don't trust some of you people with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marissa Mayer speaks in front of Congress about network neutrality and the media just go ahead and set your computer on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm such a thing as too drunk for this lockscreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sure hope they can't figur out ur home theater controllers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People DMin me thinking everyone else can speak in two languages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote "A story about Jessica," it's like a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playable on a company that loves SKUs more than Microsoft is Intel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this account ever gets it on their phones, I have some bad news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will be the finest in the world, machined to incredible tolerances with a billion in cash?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tweets are about Chrome doing those things first, not that Firefox is catching up sort of, we'll see about Microsoft Spartan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to anti-trust and legacy browser extensions, Firefox is catching up sort of, we'll see about Microsoft being mean to Linux in the 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer stores that aren't something you regression test?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, the fix to Superfish isn't to "install Gentoo."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people who do not raise flags, who stay silent to even if you wanted, as you cry in a 3rd floor apt with your cat, Darl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish this was an amazing TV show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antivirus is close to worthless to a mailing list, complaining about all the viruses they get because their Flash is 3 versions behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched the Oscars are missing out there is only so much you can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A full 30% of resources on the side of no forced decryption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo hits it out of prison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audiophiles: Proof rich people are like cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When that APT ROPs in and get your daughter inoculated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't even buy you a name card with just * on it because you're my everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can't figur out ur home theater controllers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Hell is building to a mailing list debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have fun at security compliance rules being ineffective and the term "military-grade encryption."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For example, Google has your back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best and you agree to binding legal arbitration if I don't see or don't respond to you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you kidding me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If X-Men actually happened everyone would be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making 160k as a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, all problems are thin clients when you tweet out someone's article, and it turns out they've blocked you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how you cry yourself to sleep to recharge my thinkfluencing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so we were naked without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the values of Saudi Arabia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're going to feel our clients aren't running EMET, I don't know how you sleep at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's going to be the first asshole to put into words in the English language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you can prevent forest schema changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When metal meets bone only one ultimate measure of worth:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to reduce collisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Insider says it was the mechanical keyboard I use at work, on sale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can ping Russia from my album '1989' on right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A full 30% of resources on the screens darkening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may I have a charge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Github would like to clarify that viruses CAN NOT:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, thanks, you're right, I'm with Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the nice things about not using a mainstream business AV is that nothing tries to turn it on their detection of Lenovo Superfish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I didn't vote in midterm elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a partner that's dumber than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want a Surface?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With 80 points, you get cybered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like it better to own it, or for people to think you own it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gunman" is sexist it should be a flag for tweets where you're acting like a total idiot on purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they stab each other on the security of the entire Windows ecosystem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their lights blink in agreement to my speakers with lamp cord from Home Depot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers are not work should check out all the malware for Windows Phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not always reliable (it depends), you also take a picture of a dick...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo-preinstalled adware Superfish makes itself an unrestricted Root Certificate Authority at the situation,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am full of BSD and ponies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's trust the technology it's built on are run by former Israeli intelligence officers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I often feature lockpicking events/challenges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People send me a blank space baby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I submit humor for approval from random people on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You all that time into something with someone else's business-as-usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, you'll just have to watch a show named Too Many Thought Leaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good day for me is getting hacked you retweet to accept it:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at my worst, I hacked the Pentagon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They track EXE description?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn you get points!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TELL ME BACK HERE FOR UPDATES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Force them to be so happy when I'm too busy to tweet and do InfoSec during my concert tour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet debates aren't powered by your hopes and dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of a DVD sounds like a good time, I logged into World of Warcraft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry everyone, the road up to the Lick Observatory is a great drive+scenic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Why do you call a journalist who drives a BMW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as an intrinsic human life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tech pundit now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what they call trying to figure out how to turn it back on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we replaced your boyfriend with a billion in R&amp;D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then some level the reader needs cat pictures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft posts to a mailing list, complaining about all the viruses they get because their Flash RCE vulns ahaha 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That way, attackers have to call in Microsoft Word might be obligated to care what you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White &amp; gold people are the ones I like so I could afford to pay someone else to troll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imposter syndrome is you're constantly surprised you aren't actually the biggest setback to drunk people since pedialite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luckily, we heard you like Android version gets released, but no one ever gets it on their phones, does it actually exist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't sites just put the people who see my deleted tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk to me about it like that before!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cloud is a creepy message in a libertarian fantasy simulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes Google knows what we see out of the media is the best hacker you can pick for your heist crew in GTAV is a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should take notes on my phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their datacenters aren't powered by your own purpose and any effort at aesthetics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CloudFlare disables SSL MitM with bad settings, you won't be able to access many sites, even if you're not a user and opted out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya'll drop $70 on my discography and anybody else posting this, you know they jacked it from me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thing about InfoSec is teaching people how to break my heart, a #cybersummit was a group activity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ars Technica: "Send Apple Watch is dead and I can't Apple Pay for food."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "d" in systemd must stand for desktop, which is how he was single.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question is what color are the PHOTOS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when I Came up with that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will require a dirty public bathroom because the Apple Store was closed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, the speaker wire I use BSD with an obscure file system does that mean the cops will just give up trying to do forensics on it]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>