<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fagan_Vlok: @LanaQuote " When I found somebody who I fell in love with, it made me feel different than I felt the rest of the day. I ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @siyinglah: "Baby, say goodnight. Text me when you get home safely, like you always did when we was first dating."  ♥ -@LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyFact: Lana is the biggest selling digital artist of the first 1/4 of 2012 &amp; 'BTD’ is #1 selling digital albums. (Sourc ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LoveLana &lt;&lt; Let's trend #TeamLana !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Is Our Flawless Queen. RT If you agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IamThatGirlLily: @LanaQuote "My vision is complete, my life is fucking made" [on finding out Paz de la Huerta showed her boobs at he ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @khadijha3: @LanaQuote I my little Scarlet starlet singing in the garden kiss me on my open mouth..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HausOfRizal: @LanaQuote Tell 'em when you find true love it lives on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @niccals12d3: @LanaQuote He was sorta punk rock, I grew up on hip hop, but you fit me better than my favourite sweater..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maddylloydjones: @lanaquote Only seventeen but she walks the streets so mean...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: "I'm running temperatures thinking of your love boo.." - Ghetto Baby. RT if you love the lyrics Lana Del Rey wrote for ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: "National Anthem" will be released as the fourth UK single on July 8, 2012. #LDRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're no good for me, but baby I want you." — Diet Mountain Dew @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Light of my life, fire of my loins, be a good baby, do what I want." — Off To The Races @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like everybody else was under his grunge spell." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not many people say let’s start life over and do it again the way I want to." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyFact: What's your favorite song off @LanaDelRey's BTD album? RT for "Dark Paradise", favorite for "Radio".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for 'Born To Die' and Favourite for 'Blue Jeans'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @TodoFaDaLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyFact @LanaDelReyUK @LanaDelReyBR @LDRToday @LanaDelReyNL @LanaDelReyFan @LanaDReyOnline @LanaDelReyCAN &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyWorld @LoveLanaDelRey @DelReyLane @PrincesssDie @CiroDiazCab @lananow @The_LanaDelRey @Hileeery @LanaDReyINDO &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't want to be like me, lookin' for fun, getting high for free." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wrote every word on my album. There's only one line I didn't write in 'Diet Mountain Dew' and one in 'Lolita'." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Boy you're so dope, your love is deadly." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShesSeductive: If you pay me, anything you like - @LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wish I may, wish I might. Find my one true love tonight." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I kiss you, I hug you, but I could not feel less connected from you!" —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They call me firecracker, and alcohol's a factor." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make it fun, don't trust anyone." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Pressparty: @LanaQuote LANA DEL REY admits she was a heavy drinker by age of 14. http://t.co/nZbP6Hwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Lana has a unique blend of authenticity and modernity.” —Adrian Hallmark, global brand director for the luxury automobile company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very happy if Lana still be a singer. Her songs really inspired me. But, be whatever herself, I'll still support her. RT If you agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never expressed myself through fashion." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...But the nice thing about the kids is that they feel bad for me, and pass me soft toys!" —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes I kneel down because I am trembling or touch the audience because I don’t know what else to do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love to take care of the songs –that’s my natural place– then, when I get on stage that’s not my elements." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I was starting, I had a vision of being a writer for film and that's what I am doing now. I'm so happy." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True pop star in her own right". —Lana Del Rey named 'Woman of the Year' by GQ Magazine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I told you that no matter what you did, I'd be by your side." #LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Pressparty: @LanaQuote LANA DEL REY wants to write for film. http://t.co/FtykMDmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hello Heaven, you are a tunnel lined with yellow lights on a dark nite." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Later's better than never." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Mood = Listen Lana Del Rey's song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SiumeyCho: We are the new generation of degenerate queens -@LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyChile: @LanaQuote #ChileLovesLanaDelRey ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted to be part of a high-class scene of musicians."  —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know what I'm good at and what I'm not good at. I write about what I know, and I know about putting on a show." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I mainly let my imagination be my reality. Fantasy is my reality." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No money, no place to live – I’ve been in more dangerous situations than other people." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, that's it. Thank you for your participation #TeamLana !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's Gramma! Follow @Fame__Hooker !! #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Picture #LQGames http://t.co/fmBmNkTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Games. Congrats to @Ntshh_ ! Follow her!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#6 Sixth Picture #LQGames http://t.co/riJvgY62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answer is Blue Jeans ! Go Follow @LDR_Baby. #LQGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#5 Fifth Picture #LQGames http://t.co/HZfJ84YZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is Carmen. Congrats to @Fame__Hooker ! Follow Follow Follow !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#4 Fourth Picture #LQGames http://t.co/PRyUb5r3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is over! Answer is Born To Die. Follow @jaimedelrey now! #LQGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#3 Third Picture #LQGames http://t.co/1CfXkogL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summertime Sadness! GO FOLLOW @helpingteamlana ! #LQGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2 Second Picture #LQGames http://t.co/rfqG8Zsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is National Anthem. Congrats to @siyinglah ! Go follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#1 First Picture. http://t.co/R58RH0Hf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first to answer I will give shoutout #LQGames. READY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To answer: just reply my last tweet and don't forget to include the hastag #LQGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will give you a picture and you would guess it comes from video where #LQGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna play a game #TeamLana?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monroe. http://t.co/ZHbLTxZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♥♥♥ http://t.co/JlCYf7zH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is my idea of fun, playing video games." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey's eyes : Dark Green. http://t.co/BCV0QdXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YouMeAtJack: @LanaQuote brown I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierrabardot: @LanaQuote in the glamour shoot they changed her eye colour to a greeny blue. that's why people get confused. but irl  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SaraPoli5: @LanaQuote I think green\brown\yellow .___. I don't know....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green or Light Brown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NiamhKerins: @LanaQuote are they greeny blue??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierrabardot: @LanaQuote light brown. almost gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #TeamLana! What color eyes Lana Del Rey? Mention me if you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have great followers! Thank you for supporting me during this. #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be bad and have fun." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Find someone who has a life that you want and figure out how they got it.” —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[READ THIS! http://t.co/jHeRscN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelaniiaJoseMB Thank you sweetheart :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The boys, the girls, they all like Carmen. She gives them butterflies. Bats her cartoon eyes." —Lana Del Rey in Carmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hola #TeamLana! How's life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“They are an untypical couple but it seems to work”. - Lana Del Rey and Barrie James O’Neill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I found it hard to make friends in school, because I was a cerebral person." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I got so scared, I thought no one could save me. You came along, scooped me up like a baby." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selamat Ulang Tahun buat Indonesia yang ke-67 ! #IndonesiaWantsLana @LanaDReyINDO @LanaDelReyINDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sorelmusic: @LanaQuote Amazing Summertime Sadness Ukulele live version by Sorel http://t.co/RO8iwklr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShesSeductive: I get crazy every Friday night, I drop it like its hot in the pale moon light - @LanaQuote ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PowerOfMusicArt: @LanaQuote A Greek guy covered amazingly Lana Del Rey, "Video Games"! In my opinion,worth to discover it &amp; shar ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm strong but I'm lonely, like Marilyn Monroe." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LDR_Baby: @LanaQuote Boy, you is landing Babe, in the land of Sweetness and angel Queen of Saigon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, dear RT @LubbsGaga: @LanaQuote is the first lana del rey fan i followed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My motto is the same just like what other people think of me is none of my business,I’m used to people saying whatever they want." - #LDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not I, nor anyone else can travel that road for you. You must travel it by yourself.  It is not far. It is within reach." #LDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kiss me hard before you go, summertime sadness. I just wanted you to know, that baby you the best." - LanaDelRey #SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm your national anthem, boy put your hands up, give me a standing ovation." - LanaDelRey #NA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>