<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade War, Thailand, World Cup: Your Friday Briefing https://t.co/x7SIEAKS3H https://t.co/bwonI9fimx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Thousands of Migrant Children, Shelters Are Becoming Makeshift Schools https://t.co/SkDsxsHN7F https://t.co/eqvhBtNeVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Its Stars Shone at the World Cup, P.S.G. Scrambled to Avoid Financial Punishment https://t.co/QxGUoTWNUG https://t.co/u2VqKtfgZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Yemen, a Pause in Fighting Raises Hopes for Peace Talks https://t.co/osnB72yEjV https://t.co/yPtMIaEvqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.P.A. Chief Scott Pruitt Resigns Under a Cloud of Ethics Scandals https://t.co/pu8iWrlsS4 https://t.co/6200JJ15FN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Imposes Sanctions on 3 Top Nicaraguan Officials After Violent Crackdown https://t.co/UN7g5jO4u0 https://t.co/7WOpBfTF3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India, Thailand, Mexico: Your Monday Briefing https://t.co/2emhQEbC9H https://t.co/pUFRs2vraP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel’s Secret Operation to Recover the Watch of a Legendary Spy https://t.co/WBDnKzB2z6 https://t.co/tuYgrg8Myp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A City Founded by Alexander Hamilton Sets the Stage for Its Next Act https://t.co/kpqfzB82u1 https://t.co/8Ce9YlueWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3,000 Migrant Children Remain Separated From Parents; 100 Are Under Age 5 https://t.co/YzF3kwVi46 https://t.co/fTZT94Klnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.P.A. Aide Questioned Deleting Sensitive Meeting Details. Then She Was Fired. https://t.co/mU8liq9rBY https://t.co/H7qOgAxiKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turmoil at Lincoln Center: Infighting, Money Troubles, Scrapped Projects https://t.co/FGnetzeWHg https://t.co/tveccJhscp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the World’s Greatest Soccer Players Gather, Scouts Stay Away https://t.co/4ANhgLyEBZ https://t.co/OOEI3IEjRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of a Ban, Transgender Military Recruits Hit Endless Red Tape https://t.co/BDfmHcWp4e https://t.co/8Dsygrv3aY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sponsors of Migrant Children Face Steep Transport Fees and Red Tape https://t.co/rGKD9kjrpu https://t.co/sgQpMWKaO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warriors Forward Kevin Durant to Sign Two-Year Max Deal https://t.co/ww0uPn2zRP https://t.co/PbIomDysr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novichok, Migrants, Serena Williams: Your Thursday Briefing https://t.co/LjtvXN8kUy https://t.co/eKhF3SMIYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Americans Evacuated From China Over Mysterious Ailments https://t.co/76ipfOMDcf https://t.co/ZNpJ6wCvkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. ‘Heat Wave’? Irish ‘Drought’? Unfamiliar Words for Unfamiliar Times https://t.co/l1xLThgpUu https://t.co/P44GB4Qhoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Britons Were Exposed to Nerve Agent That Sickened Ex-Spy, Britain Says https://t.co/27ZLQAdrrl https://t.co/c4WGcJzWTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In France, Police Killing Unleashes Familiar Riots and Recrimination https://t.co/Vshm8zZTzz https://t.co/0f3C4viraJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migration Deal Rescued Merkel’s Government. Now, She Has to Save the Deal. https://t.co/znqoBioK77 https://t.co/jynkxzgaH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests Across U.S. Call for End to Migrant Family Separations https://t.co/uUXKIYEIGm https://t.co/qmouSXsDw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thailand, Hong Kong, World Cup: Your Thursday Briefing https://t.co/cO5CsG09pF https://t.co/tG8jDCbh9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The E.P.A.’s Ethics Officer Once Defended Pruitt. Then He Urged Investigations. https://t.co/ZZDI9VKMMx https://t.co/NqldAuKI6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Shows Police Officer Firing Stun Gun at Unarmed Man Sitting on Curb https://t.co/0XxQQJaDhO https://t.co/09xkjv7TtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Photo of a Bag, and a Fresh Push for Clues in Central Park Blast https://t.co/1lQgnNw7iU https://t.co/QQ8OEKG220]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump’s Policy Decisions Undermine the Industries He Pledged to Help https://t.co/DSOK16vNEu https://t.co/5vHd8ZpnYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criminal Convictions Behind Them, Few Have Had Their Records Sealed https://t.co/Fcbh3rbb0J https://t.co/K15Snklpgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wang Jian, Co-Founder of Chinese Giant HNA, Dies in France https://t.co/Yc7c9Dyz9G https://t.co/MvuA1Qwsfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two More Suspects Arrested in Slaying of Lesandro Guzman-Feliz, Bronx Teenager https://t.co/TTWGlxhrgh https://t.co/d3sH2trHvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What It Costs to Be Smuggled Across the U.S. Border https://t.co/gdDXOztApg https://t.co/UGUItkZ33L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Frosty Summer for Alan Dershowitz on Liberal Martha’s Vineyard https://t.co/oWyNDP3t7j https://t.co/8unTvMMmzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Judges Exemplify the Choice Trump Faces in a Supreme Court Pick https://t.co/DQih2YcVsr https://t.co/oDA5LUsHWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trooper Is Killed Answering Call to Home of School Principal https://t.co/qGnj9aw3XE https://t.co/DXUXfPuMtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Arrested in Cleveland Terror Plot After F.B.I. Sting https://t.co/d6IAms7FTQ https://t.co/6yFTuv17Jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Declines Dirk Nowitzki’s $5 Million Option for 2018-19 https://t.co/fMekD0c9Hv https://t.co/uNEEUjea0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are the Biggest Stories in American Politics This Week https://t.co/MqLxREdzyt https://t.co/dkLfTNwgrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Firebrand Leftist Far Ahead in Mexico’s Presidential Polls https://t.co/LryMqPSgXa https://t.co/YijcH8Cqgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fox-Inspired Tweetstorm Touches Many of Trump’s Favorite Themes https://t.co/GHh0UbRDxX https://t.co/yJ4pJ9sTUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Shaken’ Rosenstein Felt Used by White House in Comey Firing https://t.co/QbX1u6TOd7 https://t.co/UCHfgBpNzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Today: Where the Corpse Flowers Bloom https://t.co/ic4J6vVeqQ https://t.co/PKKTOsSv3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$16 Million vs. $4: In Fatal Police Shootings, Payouts Vary Widely https://t.co/qgfnn6u0bq https://t.co/RoitCG0oNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accused Gunman in Capital Gazette Shooting Left a Trail of Conflicts https://t.co/0hBF1GuFYK https://t.co/wBj9TQS70t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron James Opts for Free Agency. Next Stop ... Lakers? https://t.co/KnvQpe3zYd https://t.co/jZJ5aKk2FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maryland, Amazon, World Cup: Your Friday Briefing https://t.co/8MyhjpiInM https://t.co/XlGAdqGN9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Reverses Obama on Affirmative Action https://t.co/pZhucWNTTD https://t.co/NaslvrSxeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Najib Razak, Malaysia’s Ex-Prime Minister, Is Arrested Amid Corruption Inquiry https://t.co/imQvk5e2EE https://t.co/fJ3FX4Ts8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 People Dead in Shooting at Maryland’s Capital Gazette Newsroom https://t.co/WlECSE9kQy https://t.co/1phTrCU71C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former E.P.A. Aide Says Pruitt Asked Her to Help Find Work for His Wife https://t.co/8U9ivTyB3e https://t.co/2zaWBD9WAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DeMarcus Cousins Gives the Warriors a Fifth All-Star https://t.co/1iOxDuP2AI https://t.co/WtNSKYUCGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple Is Charged in Plot to Bomb Iranian Opposition Rally in France https://t.co/AxaFKVAfqG https://t.co/1gFJgFr5n4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Softens Demand That Countries Stop All Iran Oil Imports https://t.co/cl4hATJyUh https://t.co/hNk0mhZ3Gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Pointed Letters, Trump Demands More Defense Spending From NATO Allies https://t.co/l7gypwbtvF https://t.co/OUA77feKEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Faces New Sex Assault Charges in Manhattan https://t.co/xgYpIg9ATi https://t.co/kPiWKooOKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio Spurs Almost Ready to Cut Ties With Kawhi Leonard https://t.co/MEABGOs7Uk https://t.co/dVwGS6NHf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Hints at Cooperating With Federal Investigators. Or Does He? https://t.co/jDm4nVaj59 https://t.co/jJZSUcguJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC Parts Ways With Investigative Reporter Brian Ross https://t.co/63vLoqNZUk https://t.co/qxqJJSA9uE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bridgewater Plans to Become a Partnership as Ray Dalio Takes a Step Back https://t.co/2nRyDFyEbx https://t.co/tBQ1wmNw4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Aide to Roger Stone Is Subpoenaed in Russia Investigation https://t.co/9dshB0d8tU https://t.co/OUmd7xqiyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mavericks Closing In on DeAndre Jordan, Three Years Later https://t.co/73E3OfauCu https://t.co/SiOe2SIOGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands Protest in Hong Kong on Anniversary of Handover to China https://t.co/cgc4fMhHjY https://t.co/mWb45Rvoav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Cameroon English Speakers Fight to Break Away, Violence Mounts https://t.co/0JmgMUzxeo https://t.co/71ShfE8aAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Its Stars Shined at the World Cup, P.S.G. Scrambled to Avoid Financial Punishment https://t.co/QxGUoTWNUG https://t.co/ls1RCqpXGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunman’s Rampage Turned Quiet Newsroom Into Chaos https://t.co/4quzWY5mbu https://t.co/9E54iNxkfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We Are Putting Out a Damn Paper’: Capital Gazette Journalists Kept Working After Fatal Shooting https://t.co/Qdc2WdXpyt https://t.co/dHLgidkZIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Backs Softer Restrictions on Chinese Investment https://t.co/XUZxlfKayp https://t.co/73G1gJskU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Putin Will Hold Summit Meeting, Officials Say https://t.co/kbOYeAAiiN https://t.co/AosC9QZG9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Upset in the Making: Why Joe Crowley Never Saw Defeat Coming https://t.co/bU76bggHZu https://t.co/5BD1k4UhNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Leave My Husband Alone’: Elaine Chao Confronts Immigration Protesters https://t.co/lWvsOdc078 https://t.co/WPxTL50Da0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Yemen, a Pause in Fighting Raises Hopes for Peace Talks https://t.co/osnB72yEjV https://t.co/XBJ2QcDKkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India, Thailand, Mexico: Your Monday Briefing https://t.co/2emhQEbC9H https://t.co/IuIH6gD0xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shine Likely as Next White House Communications Director https://t.co/EKfDfimseg https://t.co/en0wt5acz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Cites Difficulties in Meeting Judge’s Timetable for Family Reunification https://t.co/ywrnuV9b9M https://t.co/rpJPp4YSXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer Who Shot Antwon Rose Is Charged With Criminal Homicide https://t.co/4atrZhoHHk https://t.co/SKWNmY4Wus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Motors, Migrants, ICE: Your Friday Evening Briefing https://t.co/t0YNnKrVQ0 https://t.co/nhUJFUvmDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bronx Mourns Teenager Killed in Vicious Attack https://t.co/tBVQXF2uO4 https://t.co/VnXSxcLr3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind Lincoln Center’s White Travertine Facade: Infighting and Indecision https://t.co/FGnetzeWHg https://t.co/TulDko7ZUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Spymaster Steps Out of the Shadows https://t.co/1vuK8IXJA4 https://t.co/PuQO4MbE0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gang ‘Hunting’ for Rivals Is Said to Have Mistakenly Killed Teenager https://t.co/7uyvEDrAZy https://t.co/Bkq7FEFebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sponsors of Migrant Children Face Steep Transport Fees and Red Tape https://t.co/rGKD9kjrpu https://t.co/097hWRQJK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warriors Forward Kevin Durant to Sign Two-Year Max Deal https://t.co/ww0uPn2zRP https://t.co/1NDoB1FakK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Taps the Brakes on Its Global Push for Influence https://t.co/BaZNkluYdX https://t.co/fVQqNwlyI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Won’t Yield ‘Even One Inch’ of South China Sea, Xi Tells Mattis https://t.co/NPCVloLpSH https://t.co/CjxXnfbT9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Human Trafficking Report, State Dept. Warns Against Separating Children From Parents https://t.co/xLzhAOQQ7y https://t.co/cj9pELuOGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Americans Evacuated From China Over Mysterious Ailments https://t.co/76ipfOMDcf https://t.co/iTPFjG7za0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How McKinsey Lost Its Way in South Africa https://t.co/6V0vnroJTf https://t.co/ulIxRqDOaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump May Soften Sweeping Plan to Restrict Chinese Investments https://t.co/innE4dGyEp https://t.co/s5OzTQ4uMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The E.P.A.’s Ethics Officer Once Defended Pruitt. Then He Urged Investigations. https://t.co/ZZDI9VKMMx https://t.co/gz5TxYKU5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What It Costs to Be Smuggled Across the U.S. Border https://t.co/gdDXOztApg https://t.co/1pqw46JiCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Implores Voters to Back South Carolina Governor on Eve of Runoff https://t.co/dye9NlSWng https://t.co/M3oPegf9zW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Schools Chief to Depart After a Short, Rocky Tenure https://t.co/nDTx3pijxQ https://t.co/qs0JWKeMiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Officials Suspend Handing Over Migrant Families to Prosecutors https://t.co/gGa2STMKqm https://t.co/EdHaxzD3dU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of U.N. Agency for Palestinian Refugees Warns of Cuts https://t.co/tMHKBosDVl https://t.co/Xc0aTeyCp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas Declines Dirk Nowitzki’s $5 Million Option for 2018-19 https://t.co/fMekD0c9Hv https://t.co/XgZPUET960]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are the Biggest Stories in American Politics This Week https://t.co/MqLxREdzyt https://t.co/qB9X9IJYJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What My 6-Year-Old Son and I Endured in Family Detention https://t.co/D7c29i35PE https://t.co/WmAcCJWaCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurning the Elite, Mexicans Favor a Leftist for the First Time in Decades https://t.co/LryMqPSgXa https://t.co/b4XyAnc5yL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China Got Sri Lanka to Cough Up a Port https://t.co/FKGmsgZIyZ https://t.co/FUgaz9AuYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Shaken’ Rosenstein Felt Used by White House in Comey Firing https://t.co/QbX1u6TOd7 https://t.co/J3PuAPJaSl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>