<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern: Software Engineering SQL, JavaScript: Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript Tracking Code ******* Job Description Please note that our internships run in perpetuity throughout a students degree program, therefore you must live within… https://t.co/ezcgDX0Mvw https://t.co/7rpQwIrZL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer/Architect (.Net, Full Stack, SQL Server, Cloud): The Alternate Investment Services – Client technology group’ is a collaborative development team with the goal of delivering a uniform, responsive user experience to clients. ‘ We are… https://t.co/AXZdN81NC8 https://t.co/ecyfkqrASi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan stuns Colombia in World Cup opener https://t.co/iFOUvalUZb https://t.co/SdRtuvjL9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer/Architect (.Net, Full Stack, SQL Server, Cloud): Job Description The Alternate Investment Services – Client technology group is acollaborative development team with the goal of delivering a uniform,responsive user experience to… https://t.co/g2qA3iaw8T https://t.co/vrYcxTK54R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatens China with new tariffs https://t.co/KusBwX72AY https://t.co/OwGzuVtB9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Database Administrator: Location US-NC-Research Triangle Park Job Description Biogen has a large SQL environment with thousands of databases under support, the successful candidate will need to be organized and able to work with multiple… https://t.co/0uAYpwt1Ao https://t.co/9umJa3qamm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marijuana affects sex drive in different ways: In the movie "Annie Hall," the titular character likes to smoke a joint at bedtime because, she says, it relaxes her and helps get her in the mood for sex -- even though her boyfriend claims it cheapens the… https://t.co/1iXzCtLR9C https://t.co/vtgB2A9m3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer NoSQL: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, NoSQL Developer with Java skills to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a strong developer… https://t.co/I2LNpE4naE https://t.co/pqauP3GWjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead SQL Server DBA: Job ID 13713-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Leon Leonwood Bean (L.L. Bean) founded his business on a passion for the outdoors, a profound belief in honesty, and an unwavering commitment to quality and customer… https://t.co/DrjwDxeaRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's family separation policy has GOP starting to panic about midterms: Just five months before the midterm elections, Republicans are scrambling to distance themselves from the Trump administration's widely panned "zero tolerance" immigration policy… https://t.co/Yd7mKE4mXP https://t.co/eoZsa1hYVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job ID: ********-10050-LEK Company Name: Argus Description: LCI is an industry leader at analytical and technological services to the financial industry. Founded over 25 years ago, we handle over 1.3 billion accounts a year for the… https://t.co/9jlxOG3jAQ https://t.co/ptI1Y95Xwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia's plane catches fire https://t.co/vpdKT3SeDR https://t.co/Qhhyn6MqMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2016-11597 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description The Database Administrator will be responsible for the… https://t.co/mRLjkMb3QF https://t.co/v2BgWuXk0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL SSIS Developer: MS SQL SSIS Developer Ref No.: 18-23310 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- MS SQL SSIS/SSAS Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More… https://t.co/LMD44ArkNE https://t.co/QuWuPfCM8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/kOenOnlGHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer NoSQL: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, NoSQL Developer with Java skills to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a strong developer… https://t.co/nMmfzgARrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: The MSR Portfolio Management team is currently searching for a Technical Data Analyst with associate level experience with relational database structures, SQL, Visio, Excel and/or MS Access skills. Business Objects or Reporting tool &amp;… https://t.co/jswZBpdvJm https://t.co/3jvKf4Nwq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer (Full Stack – VertX, No-SQL, React, Cloud): *At American Express we place an enormous emphasis on users and usability. We sit at the intersection of commerce and experiences and are rare in our business model where we are one of only a few… https://t.co/ZgNzXIGOGt https://t.co/szMUyGtAE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooks Koepka becomes first repeat champion in 29 years https://t.co/PzbyOe9NfC https://t.co/EwgpynFDNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer in Alexandria, Virginia, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers… https://t.co/5xQRUYWQEN https://t.co/jEDoET1TA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA: MYSQL DBA LOCATIONS: PITTSBURGH, PA/CLEVELAND, OH LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED MYSQL DBA TO ASSIST WITH ENTERPRISE MYSQL DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION PROJECT. * The candidate must have experience with the following technologies: * MySQL Architecture,… https://t.co/CpsrqHWuRs https://t.co/RRPkZYO8YH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Top Chef' host: I could have been that child torn from her mother: I was two years old when my mother left me in India with my grandparents to come to the United States. She was fleeing an abusive marriage, and needed to find a job and a safe place for… https://t.co/ejVaRrufng https://t.co/uHpdrwLtgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing: SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security – Interactive – Events – Careers… https://t.co/bQZFq0vMt8 https://t.co/CLsXyTJQXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr-Data-Migration-Consultant-with-Oracle PL-SQL-and-ETL: SR DATA MIGRATION CONSULTANT WITH ORACLE, PL/SQL AND ETL HOPEWELL / PENNINGTON, NJ Project Description: Seasoned ETL Engineer with strong PL/SQL, Informatica Power Center and ORACLE skills is… https://t.co/6o2a16Y0wE https://t.co/HjmediMnbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first lady's spokeswoman says Melania 'hates to see children separated from their families': In a rare statement on a policy issue, first lady Melania Trump weighed in through her spokeswoman on the immigration crisis taking place at America's borders. https://t.co/FNXkzoxFB8 https://t.co/DhKnspIvWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Georgia State University, Georgia – United States Job Start Date – 07/05/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview The ideal candidate will be experienced in writing SQL Stored Procedures, Query… https://t.co/Q8DkNx5NKd https://t.co/CGwbBI86PS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Report Developer (.Net, SQL): Job ID: EMO-******* Description: Located in one of the following locations – Austin, Houston, Richardson or San Antonio, TX this position is responsible utilizing .NET and SQL Server for creating reports, insights… https://t.co/rq8I40ilTW https://t.co/MchrpGdmE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Business Intelligence: SQL Server Business Intelligence (BI) Responsibilities: – Providing direction on the new SQL Server Data Warehouse (DW) SQL Server BI tool – Making sure all data elements in the Enterprise Data Repository (EDR) were… https://t.co/MMlybTM7Zc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst II(excel, SQL, Healthcare): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: – Analyze health management programs including: data collection,… https://t.co/WoFmR71R51 https://t.co/r3P6Cl0tht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Application Development Advisor: Job Description Job Description As a SQL Server Software Developer, you will be responsible for end to end, full-stack development of both internal and client facing applications for Wellpartner’s Contract… https://t.co/ps6QhEXxai https://t.co/xBGdt0q8Lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Mysql Dba: One of my client is looking for Lead Sr. / Lead MySQL DBA . If interested then please send me you resume ASAP. Sr. / Lead MySQL DBA Duration: 12+ Months Location: Milpitas, CA Rate:- Open Requirements Ensure performance, security, and… https://t.co/lRFOONtwR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two years ago, this radio man lost this voice -- it hasn't returned: If you're scanning through radio stations, you may soon hear a familiar but oddly mechanical voice reporting the latest news from Capitol Hill. https://t.co/QJJBmg6wb1 https://t.co/spbYjERghG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Advansoft International SAP Services Partner Risk Free Implementation SAP Implementation IT Project Implementation Follow Us on : Toggle navigation Careers – Home – About Us – Services – Industries – Careers – Clients – Training –… https://t.co/MCeqsMaLtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olympian: This is what it means to be an American: I am an American. https://t.co/PHu8JZnszi https://t.co/xovrJJOcPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to work in core components for the Ariba cloud that includes application, persistence, meta-data, object model framework, common data server, customization and UI frameworks. Bach… https://t.co/1DLPGfYnDY https://t.co/HMpAV2yWbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tour de France rider expelled after punch https://t.co/1d1ZYDhkPL https://t.co/nN4XqhS7GH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As fallout from the Putin summit grows more toxic, Trump makes an all-caps threat against Iran and launches false attacks on Mueller: President Donald Trump is lashing out in all directions as the fallout from his summit with Vladimir Putin becomes ever… https://t.co/iOp1kCEPNc https://t.co/DfqAL0jthl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian ayatollah profiting from $95B hedge fund, Pompeo says: US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo delivered a scathing speech on Iran's leadership Sunday, accusing Tehran's ruling ayatollahs of spreading violence across the Middle East and lining their… https://t.co/VkmHb6jzVT https://t.co/1JeEY5EJtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Appl Support Developer/Analyst, Windows Server Admin, SQL Admin, Scripting: Specialist Appl Support Developer/Analyst, Windows Server Admin, SQL Admin, Scripting Maintains and supports applications and their operating environments. Coordinates… https://t.co/7R1mCTFGne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/sql developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/sql developer – ID:31484 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL/SQL, Billing LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/13/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for GIS… https://t.co/fEyqryInUM https://t.co/4k1q4QUVwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer SME: SQL Developer SME – 18-02550 Ref No.: 18-02550 Location: Greenwood Village, Colorado Akraya is looking for a SQL Developer SME for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Ajay at… https://t.co/KzSliJn7AM https://t.co/061vjG2kmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. SQL Database Administrator: Greensboro, NC 27408 #2018-26522 Description Overview The Fresh Market currently has an opening for a Jr. SQL Database Administrator at our Corporate Offices in Greensboro, North Carolina. Responsibilities – Provide… https://t.co/ndg1u07F77 https://t.co/MUY55V6R2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Careers Center | PL/SQL Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/Glk4i026SV https://t.co/0igF1R5hym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedian to congressman: Go ahead, call us sluts: Rep. Jason Lewis was elected in 2016 to serve the people of Minnesota's 2nd Congressional District. https://t.co/LJoSE7AjVB https://t.co/p8PCgMLIgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper: The spin has just begun: The FBI is in possession of a recording between President Donald Trump and his former personal attorney Michael Cohen in which the two men prior to the election discuss a payment to a former Playboy model who has… https://t.co/4M2hZF3UlM https://t.co/Jal4Bzg18h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's accused of using sex, lies and guns to infiltrate US politics: The young Russian gun enthusiast was struggling. Maria Butina had twice applied for visas to attend the National Rifle Association's glitzy annual meeting. But she said she was twice… https://t.co/PyxRrET6sQ https://t.co/kOG3nqP4h6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Job Title: Lead Java Developer Location: Omaha, NE Job Number: JO-1807-27788 Description ProKarma is hiring a Lead Java Developer in our Omaha, Nebraska office. You will help lead large scale solutions as part of a global development… https://t.co/cpdJcGVGMD https://t.co/UvGxQXAno3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst GRS Strong SQL: Job Description Technical Business Systems Analyst – GRS – Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business,… https://t.co/yaNGWBMuhK https://t.co/wLwakh5bpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA/Architect: Job TitleSQL Server DBA/Architect – ID:28818 Duration9 – 12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSQL, SQL Server LocationEl Segundo, CA &amp; Las Vegas, NV Date Posted07/18/2018 SQL Database Administrator/Architect As a Sr. Database… https://t.co/kTK84T9uo4 https://t.co/LxeWx5D33l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worries linger after EPA changes coal ash rules: Concerns are rising for residents living near coal ash ponds after Andrew Wheeler, the acting administrator of the EPA, rolled back regulations on the storage of the toxic waste. CNN's Sanjay Gupta reports. https://t.co/r3EDfVoIM8 https://t.co/jEjLAalnd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Markit Digital is looking for a talented SQL Server Database Developer/Analyst who is interested in working with large, complex data sets. Our growing development team is looking for folks eager to take on the challenge of… https://t.co/do7cMGyZVW https://t.co/m7zT2GjlSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why we should ditch the 'perfect woman' myth https://t.co/QC9IXrnRlk https://t.co/jaPcR2T0iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Reporting, Metrics, and Dashboard Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/17/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* SQL Reporting, Metrics, and Dashboard… https://t.co/Er0ouMp19A https://t.co/Ug76XoqsHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: 7/6/2018 SQL Developer Tracking Code 10751 Job Description Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the… https://t.co/qocfYH43SK https://t.co/lwLsoJFOS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most remote places on Earth: The problem with exciting destinations is that you're unlikely to be the only one drawn to them. https://t.co/d7panzN7wP https://t.co/nFJ6gQQ1Ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep.'s chilling warning on Trump and Russia: In a New York Times op-ed — headlined "Trump Is Being Manipulated by Putin. What Should We Do?" — Texas Republican Rep. Will Hurd writes of this week's summit between Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin: https://t.co/1uWLsOhm4G https://t.co/eF6xLfLect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer, Web-Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-42206 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Develops, codes, deploys… https://t.co/7DBeZDdD0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Sr. Software Developer (.NET) Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with… https://t.co/qD2ScCA3Dw https://t.co/aSqPgM8bzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avenatti says he had 'lengthy' talk with Cohen this week: What began as a coincidental encounter between Michael Avenatti and Michael Cohen on Monday evening evolved into what Avenatti is calling a potentially "critical" meeting. https://t.co/PRhNL9fOkw https://t.co/OkYCabn3l2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: SQL Server Database Administrator Ref No.: 18-31038 Location: San Francisco, California SQL Server Database Administration, Infra &amp; Data Security : IT IS_AMS_Oracle Database Administration L3 Oracle Database Admin… https://t.co/NZCXmb4C0z https://t.co/ECwkDy2ll3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Job Description Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible… https://t.co/IimPA7aszn https://t.co/fATZEHRCeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Webmaster/Technology Systems Specialist: Kanawha County Schools has an opening for a Webmaster/Technology Systems Specialist to design complete web data processing systems. Experienced in web design for forms, active server pages displaying, and… https://t.co/3ravCHGclu https://t.co/qvMrVBzUs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows moments before boat sinks: When choppy waves began crashing against two duck boats in a lake in Missouri, Jennie Phillips-Hudson Carr started recording. https://t.co/TgfHWAhBfM https://t.co/mmrynAQTYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist, Data Scientist Associate, Senior Application Developer: Capitalogix LLC has multiple openings to work in our office in Coppell, Texas. Senior Data Scientist to translate business needs into data reqs to prototype, develop &amp; launch… https://t.co/DX2AOdsSPX https://t.co/HoDgDcLOX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSULTING SOFTWARE ENGINEER – SQL Server / ETL / DW: Lead SQL Server database, ETLand cube development design and development in Business Intelligence Team data warehouse and analytics environment Essential Functions: – Develop guidelines for other… https://t.co/Mx7WoD2QJj https://t.co/BDwmyOUOJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhatsApp adds new restrictions after India killings https://t.co/UkJAPHLdhc https://t.co/YFIC82Q8P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: ******/SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-31083 Location: San Diego – California, California Ensure all database servers are backed up in a way that meets the business’s Recovery. Troubleshoot SQL Server service outages Configure SQL Server monitoring… https://t.co/AkuItHeSLJ https://t.co/tQDIuPiXiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior OBIEE Developer: Senior OBIEE Developer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network –… https://t.co/dRAPBClFo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Senior Consultant 3rd level support VMware/Netapp/MS SQL: IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept –… https://t.co/a8mLiWROo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPER – MIS DEPARTMENT: TRAX International Careers – Home – Our Services – Our People – Our Leaders – Careers – About Us Returning Applicant? Login Now New Job Search SOFTWARE DEVELOPER – MIS DEPARTMENT Job Code:2017:0405-058 Location:White… https://t.co/NPUFr33X9f https://t.co/A4bOWE2Ukz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer with .Net: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Ref No.: 18-28424 Location: Tempe, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for PL/SQL Developer with .Net in Tempe, AZ or Santa Clara, CA. Please Let me know if you are… https://t.co/Hns5izyAnS https://t.co/2G1d5yfO6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graham: I don't care what Trump and Putin talked about: Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) says he's less concerned with the topics President Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin discussed in private, and more concerned with any agreements the two may have… https://t.co/Y6Az5A5YSI https://t.co/KyZV69KVId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer NET, C#, SQL Server Exchange Traded Funds: Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server ‘ Exchange Traded Funds The Exchange Traded Funds Technology Team creates application-layer solutions to streamline and improve the… https://t.co/QAl439lCCx https://t.co/bogDB7r6IA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids ruthlessly mock ancient cell phones: Today's kids are surrounded by technology, but can they figure out how to operate a simple 'dumbphone' from the 2000s? https://t.co/96R2KWLokP https://t.co/Mw8e2Yf9FH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police investigating man's rant against lesbian couple: Oregon police are investigating after a man hurled threats and homophobic slurs at a lesbian couple in a rant caught on video. https://t.co/LxN0eJlO0A https://t.co/DJuKUtjYZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst, IT: Business Systems Analyst, IT in Coral Gables, FL at Beacon Health Options Return to *********************** | Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation – Careers Home – We are Beacon – Benefits – Featured Careers – Clinical… https://t.co/dLU1e2Q1ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer C#/NoSQL/API: Data Engineer (C#/NoSQL/API): [Chicago/up to $110,000] Our client is seeking a several Data Engineers who will be passionate about problem solving and technology. Job Description * Develop, maintain, test, and troubleshoot… https://t.co/RdFOmHCldt https://t.co/kzTTpqyPuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer | Oracle, C#, T-SQL, https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, LINQ, WCF, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery: Full Stack .NET Developer | Oracle, C#, T-SQL, *******, MVC, LINQ, WCF, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery Columbus, OH 07-15-2018 Location:… https://t.co/23zZKiVHPN https://t.co/3sUmdE3t35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Architect/DBA Lead: Our direct client is looking for a SQL Server Architect/Lead to provide leadership, guidance, and coordination for large DBA support teams, including coordination of complex database design, development,… https://t.co/KXSLLiIj4O https://t.co/DpP07u4o0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-43302 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MS SQL Server Database… https://t.co/MWXNZ22V1H https://t.co/wRvGYblNd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer Columbus, Ohio. Design, develop, &amp; maintain various MFTS platforms.  Duties: Design, develop, and maintain various managed file transfer system (MFTS) platforms. Review platform architecture to align with… https://t.co/hr6ioEhvRj https://t.co/tOTHpMkITi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Analyst/Developer: Company Overview For 29 years, clients in the private and public sectors have relied upon SOS International LLC (SOSi) for critical operations in the world’s most challenging environments. SOSi is privately held, was… https://t.co/OS26TuvIoA https://t.co/7eAidShZbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to handle multiple saving goals https://t.co/KwH9IDdYGt https://t.co/jb79nXsWAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Overland park, Kansas – United States Job Start Date – 06/27/18, Posted Date – 06/27/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12+ months contract. Phone and Skype. Candidate must have atleast 1 real time project in… https://t.co/B7JW6RwHWe https://t.co/KfDSKy9mkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Title: Senior SQL Developer Location: Downers Grove, IL, US, 60515 Company: Univar USA Requisition ID: 7682 It starts with great chemistry. Univar is more than a distribution company – we’re a leading, global partner dedicated to… https://t.co/tUy8IZowUz https://t.co/JrLweiPODW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSRS SQL Server Reporting Services: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services Ref No.: 18-27583 Location: columbia, Maryland Key skills required for the job are: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services-L3 (Mandatory) As a develoer, you are responsible for… https://t.co/aZKVE3aPhy https://t.co/M9oTtMl7HJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama says men have been getting on 'his nerves' and urges 'empowering more women': Former US president Barack Obama is urging more women to get involved in social movements and governance "because men have been getting on my nerves recently." https://t.co/YgK98kFt0h https://t.co/GZeAeiTwIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5227 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=****** &amp; codes=JB-Indeed… https://t.co/sZAaevkrMb https://t.co/3MX0I4Wwtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst GRS Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/8IIHQCcIP4 https://t.co/fo9HoDtS49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cop fires through own windshield during chase: Las Vegas Metropolitan Police released this bodycam footage of an officer chasing two men suspected in a shooting hours before. https://t.co/R2RDNKvyqu https://t.co/uoWP4UgWhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II Order to Cash / Finance: Job Description Business Analyst II – Order to Cash / Finance Job Title Business Analyst II – Order to Cash / Finance Requisition ID ******** Duration Location Greenville, WI 54942 Other Location Description… https://t.co/so0esdIgtq https://t.co/jNlvKjZiEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: At least 4years of experience in Oracle PL/SQL development. At least 4 years of experience in software development life cycle. At least 4 years of experience in translating functional/non-functional requirements to system requirements.… https://t.co/UBJFJtufUL https://t.co/dc5TmXTwzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary was right: Trump is a puppet: On the heels of the World Cup final and the eve of Trump's summit with Russian President Vladimir Putin, in Helsinki, Finland, Hillary Clinton took a jab at her former presidential campaign rival. https://t.co/z8q2xqqPZA https://t.co/E9qyvvPKAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian national charged as secret agent: 6 things the documents show: The Justice Department on Monday charged a Russian national, Mariia Butina, also known as Maria, with conspiring against the US as a secret agent. https://t.co/GZJmB8mw3v https://t.co/NJRjFpTw3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP BO Admin: SAP BO Admin Ref No.: 18-26785 Location: Hoboken, New Jersey Experience in Data Warehousing, Business Intelligence using BIBO 4.2/4.1/4.0, SAP BO 3.1/3.0/XIR2/6.5, BO Designer, DeskI, InfoView, WebI, Crystal Reports, Oracle 11g/10g/9i/8i,… https://t.co/glkMRhrTeY https://t.co/53hUlrR5EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead SQL Server DBA: Job ID 13713-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Leon Leonwood Bean (L.L. Bean) founded his business on a passion for the outdoors, a profound belief in honesty, and an unwavering commitment to quality and customer… https://t.co/NUomIRS8Tc https://t.co/D7W4xAZPAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL SERVER DBA (BOSTON, MA) An exciting opportunity for a SQL Server DBA to join a global leader in secure payment technologies. You will be responsible for configuring, troubleshooting and maintaining the company’s production and… https://t.co/dWszx6qjIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented PL/SQL Developer to join our team in Lorton, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. We are looking for a SQL developer who will be… https://t.co/sGzjTOAVcA https://t.co/HwNZNpHd0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch 'firenado' turn into giant water spout: A couple in Blythe, California, filmed this wildfire along the Colorado River. The extreme heat from the wildfire created a vortex known as a firenado. As the firenado spun off across the water it turned into… https://t.co/wSHQwTFQmy https://t.co/d2EU0ZckIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer/SQL Developer (Business Intelligence): Overview * Develop, test and deploy various ETL jobs * Participate in data conversion and data migration efforts * Create Stored Procedures, Functions and Views from scratch * Model and then implement… https://t.co/YYKWKBr2Hq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>