<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Lyft, Inc. has the following openings in Seattle, WA. Software Engineer (SWE) (multiple). recblid 39ypo69ybe7dhq7o3w6ctpa635ui1b https://t.co/4P4y8POQOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Developer: Software Engineer/Developer Expedent Corp Irving, TX. Develop Design, implement, review, repair &amp; improve Existing Code Required Java, C++, VB, Oracle, Linux .NET. C#, https://t.co/gzetm9tqoA, MVC, MS SQL Server, Can work… https://t.co/UGHyzTV7xa https://t.co/p0Kjtlshyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Information Security Analyst: Join our Winning Team as a Senior Information Security Analyst At CARFAX we are constantly EXPANDING our product and technology offerings!  This means we are continually bringing new, innovative products to market… https://t.co/h5pjfMjTvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer III – CBO Data Center: Client Reference Code: 213989 JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Engineering team is responsible for the implementation of… https://t.co/04mJrURGU5 https://t.co/noSFt6VdKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator 1:   Job Description – Systems Administrator 1 (18003111) Systems Administrator 1 Requisition ID : 18003111 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/hYlW1ZmPR4 https://t.co/Q09b2Cj3NI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Computer Systems Architect: Req ID : 429253BR Job Code/Title : E1804:Comp Systems Architect Stf Job Description : Position available to join a "hands-on" Systems Engineering team with the ability to help shape the future. Candidate must be… https://t.co/FelFKnv5aN https://t.co/y4cQntQz1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: Engineering Staff System Engineer Develop/maintain firmware to control RFIC &amp; handle interface w/ wireless baseband; Validate and debug RF transceiver devices on customer platforms. Work site in Irvine, CA. Mail resume to: ASR… https://t.co/zQBRf9f9FL https://t.co/g3pzXDAGEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Engineer Applications (Req#ALN2DS) Rspnsble fr dvlping &amp; deplying SW apps. Software Development Engineer (Req#AMV8AM) Responsible for dsgn, devpmnt, &amp; execution of… https://t.co/QSsCqXiynK https://t.co/n4VN0OwHMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer: MASTER SOFTWARE ENGINEER – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Mult pos avail: Lead overall tech design, dvlpmt, modification, &amp; implementation of comp apps using existing &amp; emerging tech platforms. Requires Master’s… https://t.co/2bhB0H62Zk https://t.co/1NFy8GpFe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Engineer: JOB SUMMARY Any journeyman license preferred. Electrical and mechanical aptitude strongly preferred. Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings, industrial systems, vehicles,… https://t.co/5nFxKPshDc https://t.co/TyjllrKGCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer- Cloud Expert: Date Posted: 21/Mar/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: Senior Software Engineer- Cloud Expert Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science,… https://t.co/jYXvMm6dFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer:   Job Description – Full Stack Developer (TEC01634) Job Description*  Full Stack Developer-TEC01634 Description  As a full stack developer you will work with the UX and DEVOPS teams to design web frameworks that will enable rapid… https://t.co/jjkMDhb1Sf https://t.co/fP8TqfCVSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SOFTWARE ENGINEER: POSITION PURPOSE The Sr. Software Engineer is responsible for joining a product team and contributing to the software design, software development, and overall product lifecycle for a product that our users love. The engineering… https://t.co/4pvpXuPYCB https://t.co/dqnf0AWOb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Analytic Software Engineer: How do cyber terrorists get past the industries best? They don’t. There are too many of us fighting virtual threats, protecting enterprises and entire countries from large-scale attacks. From creating a citywide… https://t.co/yRABpfdM9W https://t.co/ONOeeBvrAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Executive: Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Salary: Negotiable Sector: Work for Us Type: Permanent Reference #: SAL_CON_SR_4569321_1523540394 The Opportunity: RED is hiring a dynamic, driven, and self-motivated Business Development… https://t.co/xzoFE4lEtR https://t.co/wDovZ0StXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer, IdentityAI: At SailPoint, we do things differently. We understand that a fun-loving work environment can be highly motivating and productive. When smart people work on intriguing problems, and they enjoy coming to work each day, they… https://t.co/t39DRVb3XP https://t.co/m5afjJuWn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPC Specialist: Why should you join L2TMedia? Let’s start with the basics! L2TMedia is a premiere Digital Marketing Company focused on the automotive industry. We love car dealers and know how to help them succeed through our line of products that… https://t.co/x9HwfqjTz2 https://t.co/CEbVpa8XYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Who we are Hallmark Labs, LLC. (a subsidiary of Hallmark), based in Santa Monica, CA, currently operates two digital subscription services, Hallmark Movies Now and Hallmark eCards, as well as ongoing initiatives in personalized,… https://t.co/LGVDStdcNf https://t.co/naJ3pdQZLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sales Engineer: We are looking for a self-motivated senior software sales engineer with excellent customer facing, technical and organizational skills and previous experience in enterprise solutions sales. You get excited talking tech to all… https://t.co/Lcrt95pqYD https://t.co/K7MqG0gJ2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer Sr: Req ID : 405573BR Job Code/Title : E1152:Network Engineer Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest standards of business… https://t.co/v60zv0W20q https://t.co/d3NppWMZNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Systems Administrator – Linthicum, MD: AllStaff Technical Solutions, Inc is an established IT and Healthcare Services firm and we love what we do! We are seeking highly motivated, driven, energetic and personable individuals that enjoy being team… https://t.co/1x1tXoyOM2 https://t.co/819IGxoffP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared (Req# 00014): SENIOR JAVA API DEVELOPER (JAVA, REST API, JS) Title: Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified… https://t.co/L6LDB6Zahy https://t.co/8kAWd0ZqjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer IV Reston, VA: Job Description Reviews, evaluates, designs, implements and maintains company database[s]. Identifies data sources, constructs data decomposition diagrams, provides data flow diagrams and documents the process. Writes… https://t.co/HiwkQs9vxF https://t.co/WzksyDAeD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Business Operations: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/pD5hfFJqc0 https://t.co/41Hn7kb0PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Advisory Identity and Access Management Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/WIHuvdZ7tj https://t.co/18lpFDcnyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/zj87b5Hb1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Evaluation and Research Specialist – Exp. Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/q7x7xSFQjn https://t.co/QvX379tCS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – AcademicWorks – Higher Education  : About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people… https://t.co/l9HWwkhltY https://t.co/pOgR7lOYXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faculty Developer/Instructional Designer – SE1324: Valencia College is now hiring Faculty Developer/Instructional Designers. Change lives, starting with your own. There are plenty of places to find employment, but at Valencia College, you’ll find… https://t.co/UiHBLdZBh4 https://t.co/TTmjPrOycV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RA42: Software Engineer Intern: The main duties of the Intern are as follows: 1. 2 Data Analysts: Help us prepare the large data sets in Metrology and Guided Inspection area and help our data scientist polish the incoming data. 2. 2 Deep learning… https://t.co/n2YBJh3LrZ https://t.co/xuaf3CCPNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – UI Developer: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US Web UI Developer Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for… https://t.co/nUG2wHnRRD https://t.co/diE7UPORoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Primary Responsibilities Wright-Pierce, an award-winning, multi-discipline environmental engineering firm specializing in water, wastewater and civil infrastructure, is seeking aa licensedProject Manager-Wastewater, Water, Civil… https://t.co/BiqeNX1W7r https://t.co/eSvGOiPU3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Dell Products L.P. is seeking a Software Senior Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to be responsible for the design and development activities associated with software using a range of applicable technologies (e.g., programming… https://t.co/DeHNmhNwKs https://t.co/2fafKLkfVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN – Mableton: Description Lend direction as well as a caring attitude. Bring a smile and your vital knowledge to everyone, every day. Brighten prospects for patients and your career. Connect with your goals and change lives with Fresenius Medical Care… https://t.co/rsrNQqKFJ0 https://t.co/YtME9Mp6sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/qroRePNqxv https://t.co/r14zH2keTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VSAT / Electrical Engineer: 29885BR VSAT / Electrical Engineer Peterson AFB Colorado United States The Electrical/Software Engineer provides basic software support on all aspects of demonstrations or tasks; works directly on problems that are moderately… https://t.co/4JYjuBO889 https://t.co/vamQtI0KVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Principal Cyber Engineer: 111300BR Sr. Principal Cyber Engineer VA – Dulles The Cyber Engineering Department in the Systems Engineering Integration and Test Directorate is seeking a Cyber Engineering Section Manager, in Dulles, VA, committed and… https://t.co/xIe2TxbatJ https://t.co/xiFGOIxZx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EI Sales: Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Start apply with Xing Apply Now Please wait… Location: NYC Downtown EI, New York, US Requisition ID: 15393 Location: NYC Downtown EI, New York, United States  Requisition ID: 15393  Schindler… https://t.co/DcbnpH1qwO https://t.co/YYLQvz3Tbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Administrator: Immediate opening in a busy multi-company office. Responsible for providing support to end users on a variety of issues. Identify, research and resolve technical problems. Install and configure software, workstations and… https://t.co/0WNgVcbdQi https://t.co/cZW3NLDQEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Ariba, Inc. seeks a Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of specific product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd &amp;… https://t.co/aG5AMOeyqQ https://t.co/breojpVAZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/iBXftjSp5h https://t.co/BCe43EMZIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #442) &amp; Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #180): Dvlp &amp; execute sw test plans for ntwk security firewall… https://t.co/fROju3gmIG https://t.co/TxwkQj9OZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Technology Director: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/dOnGZlQRX9 https://t.co/1FKEpAa16U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Job Description Infosys DNA Technology Lead – US Business Analyst with SSRS Are you looking for a change? Do you want to collaborate with some of the best talent in the industry? Are you ready to join a company whose passion is to… https://t.co/FEf35VOMR3 https://t.co/pIEwIDFLSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver Robert Half Technology Salaried Professional Services Staffing Executive: JOB REQUISITION Denver Robert Half Technology Salaried Professional Services Staffing Executive LOCATION CO DENVER JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a… https://t.co/dyeAAkxlpT https://t.co/EgfR4O4k4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accessibility QA Engineer: * Test iOS and Android applications on phones and tablets against Accessibility WCAG 2.0 and W3C/WAI Guidelines * Write and execute manual test cases for Accessibility tests on all screens of the iOS and Android applications. *… https://t.co/u5MaYTRMUC https://t.co/1kidL3R67I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROJECT MANAGER: University of Washington Location Seattle, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category Administrative / Office,Bio-Tech / Sciences,Health Care,Law Enforcement / Security,Management / Executive Job status N/A… https://t.co/Fbm4wmsxJc https://t.co/5IpKKnkDB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director – Marketing: Spartanburg, South Carolina Updated a day ago Division:Sales &amp; Marketing Level: Manager/Supervisor Type: Direct Hire JobID: 28467 City/State: Spartanburg, South Carolina Job Description City/State: Spartanburg, SC Job Description: … https://t.co/SYzIsD1NwJ https://t.co/C7qEfTNiWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: Amplify SystemsAmplify Systems | Trend Setters in IT Consultancy – – About – Our History – Our Values – Services – Partners – Current Hotlist – Subscribe to Hotlist – Careers – Current Openings – Subscribe to Jobs – Contact – UI Developer –… https://t.co/eRMv5VksIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packaging Automation Engineer – Research and Development: Packaging Automation Engineer – Research and Development in Jacksonville, IL at Reynolds Consumer Products Back To: **************************** – – Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation –… https://t.co/C4BlzHwKfj https://t.co/c9MtNQMIth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator – Ops Center Lead – Austin, TX: Systems Administrator – Ops Center Lead – Austin, TX ==================================================== Req #: ******Location: Austin, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance:… https://t.co/Xihw6B8hlJ https://t.co/D9wOgD1oxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Global Enterprise Infrastructure: IT/Software DIRECTOR, GLOBAL ENTERPRISE INFRASTRUCTURE sought by Burleigh Point, Ltd. dba Billabong USA in Irvine, CA. Responsible for IT infrastructure operational results and KPI’s. Provide strategic… https://t.co/4I04lWyC8i https://t.co/YFupD96dh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princip Sftwre Engg: COMPUTER Princip Sftwre Engg (Santa Clara, CA) Prfm code mdfctn, tstng &amp; debggng &amp; analysis for APM solutn. Tst cmplte intgrtd APM prod &amp; bld apps. Dply &amp; srve vrtl comps. Implmnt tst scenarios simulating cust applics &amp; envrnmnt.… https://t.co/mJZDANHOtH https://t.co/yW5Nv7StSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Administrator: Immediate Supervisor: Assistant City Manager Grade Level: 12 Position &amp; FLSA Status: Full-Time Exempt Date of Latest Revision: March 2018 Position Summary: To assist administration with planning, recommending,… https://t.co/FtIhMmO1Kf https://t.co/ZExzj7jTsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing: CooperVision, Inc. seeks a Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing in Pleasanton, CA to support global pricing strategy and compliance through analysis of pricing data, tracking of competitive pricing/promotional… https://t.co/xUSEXRbQqp https://t.co/8BeS8DtBKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Community Enhancement: Director of Community Enhancement  Chesterfield County, Virginia (Richmond-Metro Area) is seeking an energetic, collaborative, strategic thinker who can articulate a clear vision for community enhancement and… https://t.co/VzvFQUGoG5 https://t.co/A1xqcCq4yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting Analyst: Senior Reporting Analyst Freedom Mortgage Corporation seeks a Senior Reporting Analyst to perform research and information gathering necessary to define, design, create, and document business requirements and specifications as… https://t.co/1rUOdkh83g https://t.co/5gPRLNCjzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Marketing Specialist: Social Media Marketing Specialist Overview: Are you an experienced Social Media Marketer with three or more years of practical experience? If so, keep reading!  We are a local media company with a growing Digital Agency… https://t.co/qYZwaEj8Vj https://t.co/3aPMbxGp7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/W Dvlprs: S/W Dvlprs HGST, Inc. has opptys in Irvine, CA for Prncpl Engrs. Mail resume to Attn: HR, 951 SanDisk Dr, MS:HRGM, Milpitas, CA 95035, Ref #IRVARA. Must be legally auth to work in the U.S. w/o spnsrshp. EOE recblid… https://t.co/QX0KpmtHVx https://t.co/RT7bjnuYo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai's Alibabacoin says Alibaba has no monopoly on 'magic' name: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The Dubai-based cryptocurrency firm Alibabacoin Foundation on Tuesday said Alibaba Group Holding Ltd cannot monopolize the "magical" Alibaba name, and asked a U.S.… https://t.co/WxzV7stmdL https://t.co/IIzIYafPtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Wakefield): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/4iitUBXShA https://t.co/mXbp92ULBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormwater Project Manager: Tetra Tech is a leading provider of consulting, engineering, and technical services worldwide. Our reputation rests on the technical expertise and dedication of our employees16,000 people working together across disciplines… https://t.co/lnd0Yr2q5s https://t.co/fsDbO0N5Pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – DLMP: City Rochester State Minnesota Telecommute No Department Laboratory Medicine &amp; Pathology Position description The Senior Project Manager works independently assuming primary responsibility for planning, directing,… https://t.co/XjIpf7ZV2q https://t.co/q6qPy2P2GP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Travel Data Analyst – Travel Industry: **Position is virtual, but qualified candidates must reside in one of the following states: AZ, AR, CO, FL, IA, IL, IN, MI, NE, OH, TN, TX, WI. As a pioneer and industry leader in on-demand contact center… https://t.co/zkozcvFsXT https://t.co/5OX4BoSCSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Asc: Req ID : 414286BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : The selected candidate will be supporting the Signals Reconnaissance Program in all phases of the software development life cycle. This individual… https://t.co/DJKopI5Kpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Tech Firefly is teaming up with an American international banking and financial services holding company, who is headquartered in San Francisco, California. Ideal candidate will be an individual who takes ownership of a process and… https://t.co/FxG2aVFrSA https://t.co/5PXrCs9oWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python: A well-known prominent automobile manufacturing company is looking to add a Software QA Engineer to their R&amp;D team. In this role, youll be responsible for extending and customizing their existing Python automation framework. You… https://t.co/hIsm1WYkMo https://t.co/f4GhVAQMcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: 37-year-old Restoration and Renovation Construction Service Company seeks an experienced Project Manager in Houston, TX and surrounding areas. This vital team member will be responsible for overseeing field operations for high-end… https://t.co/YUWdMvul6H https://t.co/277m4Xywer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEERS: Sr. Software Engineers, Fort Worth, Texas: Develop s/w reqs specs, functional specs, &amp; s/w design docs. Develop, design, test, implement &amp; support modular s/w components, memory mgmt techniques, standard calling conventions, low… https://t.co/yYmJRqjnDF https://t.co/vV68HfOzWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity, Application Developers, Help Desk Specialists: Job Fair Delta Resources has an impeccable reputation as a leader in the government services industry. Delta Resources is actively recruiting professionals with technical backgrounds and… https://t.co/u3HoGPlTVI https://t.co/h4AqT58Yah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Description We are currently seeking a PHP Developer to join our team of software engineers.  Candidate will work both collaboratively to help maintain and modernize our company’s multi-platform transactional databases and systems.  This… https://t.co/g502qN8Ftb https://t.co/WdBwzVtG88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate plans future hearing on Cambridge Analytica, other firms: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Senate Commerce Committee plans to hold a future hearing on Cambridge Analytica and other companies that may have improperly obtained Facebook Inc user data,… https://t.co/EChkNMqTCQ https://t.co/MthYNO20De]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer, Austin, TX, General Motors. Develop, deploy, &amp; test GM Cimplicity based solutions within manufacturing environment, such as Production Routing &amp;Tracking, Production Pull System, &amp; Electronic Pull… https://t.co/3GrTtzwtal https://t.co/syxZJTJftq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant #SS1970: UXC Eclipse USA, a DXC Technology company, in Bellevue, Washington seeks Technical Consultant. * 5 years experience with at least 1 year experience Structured Query Language, X++, C#, .Net, Json, Azure Cloud required. * Must… https://t.co/ymCieiXMXn https://t.co/pZnRs6rO0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/IrBKymjSND https://t.co/YeZDiqHWND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer Manager # 180032916: Applications Developer Manager Columbus, OH. Estimate project requirements; forecast resources &amp; project delivery commitments. Equal Opportunity Employer/Affirmative Action Minority/Female/Disability/Veteran… https://t.co/SdrYAsWQ04 https://t.co/zmXNw639od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member Technical Staff Consultant #VR1-N: Looking for Member Technical Staff Consultant at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Responsible for the deployment, operations and administration of the Hortonworks, Hadoop, Data Platform and Tableau infrastructure.… https://t.co/d4XiRIAJgK https://t.co/MqYoZLuPG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager: California locations: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc seeks candidates for the following positions: * Technical Program Manager II * Provide sophisticated technical… https://t.co/bxcK56s1SB https://t.co/JmyAR8xDoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Apps Support # 180031171: Associate, Apps Support Columbus, OH. Provide app support for ETL apps. Perform management &amp; problem resolution. Master’s or equivalent in CS, Engineering (any), or related field + 2 years relevant experience or… https://t.co/IPSJFM8fOr https://t.co/c7UkIvtoSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center infrastructure… https://t.co/TThIEhdYtH https://t.co/jV2USZNwfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Interface w/ business &amp; IT resources to understand &amp; analyze business, functional, &amp; technical requirements. EOE, AAE, M/F/D/V. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. All rights reserved. https://t.co/7CY8l6VjUw. recblid… https://t.co/4kGgTpZ4tW https://t.co/YJWPZHbP1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Softwr Dvlpr, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Provide scalable &amp; high performing cloud srvcs, incl IaaS, PaaS, &amp; SaaS. Review functional UI reqs, w/ focus on workflow &amp; usability. Implement UI functionality. Eval &amp; resolve defect tix. Utilize… https://t.co/25Rw6j104C https://t.co/9VvtmteOFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R44563: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer apps using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/w3OhQDNOyw https://t.co/EhYhsh44nd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP revises pricing for core business planning software: LONDON (Reuters) - Germany's SAP is revising how it prices its core business planning software after a legal crackdown against high-profile customers - beverage giants Diageo and AB InBev -… https://t.co/Zivog3tQ9B https://t.co/NB72KAknv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Woodville): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/pNglnvqdAR https://t.co/N4crRkzkSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Security Engineer I: Client Reference Code: 216241 JOB SCOPE: Responsible for engineering activities that monitor, detect and alert on potential security threats to the company’s telecommunications and signal processing hardware, software and… https://t.co/l0IFQBWxsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AGM RDO: Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Start apply with Xing Apply Now Please wait… Location: Morristown, NJ, New Jersey, US Requisition ID: 8082 Schindler stands for mobility. Mobility needs experts. Join our team in Morristown,… https://t.co/jqlfVNMcdG https://t.co/kHx3JxHKP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Safety Engineer 4:   Job Description – Software Safety Engineer 4 (17028642) Software Safety Engineer 4 Requisition ID : 17028642 Location : United States-California-Woodland Hills US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/HCubY7EuRD https://t.co/1H8XsQgID3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integration/Test Engineer Sr: Req ID : 422164BR Job Code/Title : E1783:Sys Integratn/Test Eng Sr Job Description : The selected candidate will be supporting the Signals Reconnaissance Program in designing and developing complex solutions for… https://t.co/a8nmibw7Zj https://t.co/3MO805LNlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Command &amp; Control SMA: Job Title / Level Command &amp; Control SMA Clearance Required? Top Secret/SCI Location: Nellis AFB, NV 89191 US (Primary) % Travel 0 – 10% Education Bachelor's Degree Job Descripti … https://t.co/waCjon3FYb https://t.co/ayNQihYUls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-Pricing Analyst – Rockville, MD or Irvine, CA: We all can agree that the quality of health care is marching forward and upward with great momentum. But it’s not just quality of care. The entire system is becoming more efficient and effective thanks to… https://t.co/giI8KdLor5 https://t.co/1G66Cixkyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: CooperVision, Inc. seeks a Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing in Pleasanton, CA to support global pricing strategy and compliance through analysis of pricing data, tracking of competitive pricing/promotional programs, and monitoring… https://t.co/vK52lo8u2r https://t.co/f0DDfLYhdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Service Delivery Manager – Storage: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/95ioepD6ga https://t.co/GqVNE5ERwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Process Analyst – Minneapolis, MN: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/Zn0jqvSWGm https://t.co/KT79Lx1aUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer-Code 15-1133 Software Engineer: sets directions of web frameworks, software methodologies and technology selection along with guiding the organization in building a robust, stable, and scalable solution to meet its… https://t.co/uVibp710Vb https://t.co/hkSK2HXs6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bioinformatics Analyst (NCI): Description: PROGRAM DESCRIPTION The Advanced Biomedical Computing Center (ABCS) is a part of the Biomedical Informatics and Data Science Directorate at Leidos Biomedical Research, Inc. The ABCS provides technology… https://t.co/LbwSbM2d5X https://t.co/fwMhfeaGcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple says all its facilities now powered by clean energy: (Reuters) - Apple Inc on Monday said it had achieved its goal of powering all of the company's facilities with renewable energy, a milestone that includes all of its data centers, offices and… https://t.co/WjrDiIgW1e https://t.co/ZcRTBAexD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Data Analytics Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/Kphnr31nNz https://t.co/pOQlPG9ojU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Architect: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/vfFzZbfir5 https://t.co/P23YKEV2dM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software QA Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #442) &amp; Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #180): Dvlp &amp; execute sw test plans for ntwk security firewall… https://t.co/vKFwJBi4VI https://t.co/XGb105gLcF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>