<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: C2S Software Developer – Kitware C2S Software Developer – Computer Vision – Arlington, Virginia, USA Job Description We are looking for a C2S – Commercial Cloud Services Software Developer to join our new office in Arlington, VA. The… https://t.co/5cqB1EV4rM https://t.co/JSyLuYY2fD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brilliant way to pay off $5,000 in credit card debt https://t.co/n8csLSNRYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley Takes on the Future of Fertility: New start-ups use wearable technology and mail-order blood tests to help women get pregnant and make sense of their future baby-making options. https://t.co/UOsAdk0p3a https://t.co/nEsDJHcvYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things you need to know today: If you have Amazon Prime, be prepared for that price hike people have been talking about -- it's happening soon with renewals. Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door. (You can also get "5… https://t.co/Yy8kswtk07 https://t.co/pYXzEB1bp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Who we are: Conversable is a funded software startup working on a SaaS platform for building enterprise-class chat and voice bots. Our founding team has started and sold several companies, have worked at companies like Zynga, Yahoo,… https://t.co/EP0P1wPMlc https://t.co/xfocCQ7Nio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Software Engineer: Cerner Skip to main content Skip to main navigation Skip to footer – Your Career Path – Client Services – Clinical – Corporate – Engineering &amp; Technology – Sales, Marketing &amp; Strategy – Students &amp; Graduates – How We Hire –… https://t.co/pTRZqEaSCX https://t.co/R4KE6Zcq1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Menlo Park, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a DevOps Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in Menlo Park, we’re a B2B services startup with Fortune 500 clients, high profile investors, and seasoned founders.… https://t.co/IayLcJ3JCv https://t.co/9Vyfif8im0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager – Education Assessment: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10752 Job Location United States Category Project Management Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is one of America’s leading K -12 educational assessment entities,… https://t.co/00iSJ3GmyM https://t.co/1ITqXC9aOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: ADT is seeking talented software developers to build scalable platforms and services to expand ADT’s product offerings and delight our customers. Experience across the full-stack and the capability of working both the frontend and… https://t.co/iQIWqnvO76 https://t.co/fEfwrLpkQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US admiral: China is Asia's biggest long-term threat: The US admiral expected to become the country's next ambassador to South Korea says North Korea remains the most imminent threat to peace in the Pacific but China's "dream of hegemony" is Washington's… https://t.co/DIevBoFhwF https://t.co/kdk6E8qyR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager: Assistant Project Manager – Port Arthur, TX in Port Arthur, TX at BO-MAC CONTRACTORS LTD. – Careers Home – Benefits – About Heico – Internships – Featured Careers – Professional Services – Engineering – Manufacturing – Sales… https://t.co/FEEsFWSeTZ https://t.co/VP9HjWJeqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Principal Job: Systems Engineer Principal Job Apply now Email Please wait… // Date: Feb 13, 2017 Location: Mclean, VA, US Company: SAIC Systems Engineer Principal (Job Number:417892) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Provide implementation,… https://t.co/HyKf3Njo4R https://t.co/Jr5mbihBfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don Lemon: This is much bigger than Roseanne's dumb tweet: CNN's Don Lemon discusses ABC canceling the "Roseanne" reboot after Roseanne Barr's racist twitter rant today, and explains that the issue stems from a normalization of racism in the United States. https://t.co/gg2e31vlMM https://t.co/vKqbo2j36m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Develop server-side code for robust high-volume production applications on cloud platform. Develop prototypes using SoftLayer API and NetApp ONTAP OS library APIs. Architect and implement… https://t.co/zc7ZyrOJJx https://t.co/kbmSnMI2V6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See bridge get wiped out by storm: A bridge is wiped out from heavy water flow in Cuba and two people narrowly escaped the wash out. https://t.co/esY78Bb9ts https://t.co/Je8HSbe56F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[52 women complain about USC gynecologist, police say: Fifty-two former patients of a gynecologist who treated thousands of women at the University of Southern California have reported they may have been victims of inappropriate and possibly criminal… https://t.co/BbP6kPIQYh https://t.co/bjdL2zrIYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript/ESRI API Developer: Riverside Technology, inc. (Riverside), recognized internationally for providing innovative engineering, science, and information technology solutions to Federal and state agencies, private companies and international… https://t.co/X5rGU7vu11 https://t.co/3gKAv0WuSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technician: Join our team headquartered in Chokio, Minnesota! Job functions will include, but not limited to; provision and maintain softswitch, Ethernet transport and circuit-switched networks; install and maintain all data network equipment and… https://t.co/X5jvPxKJ3V https://t.co/mMb94sE3RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow drops nearly 400 points https://t.co/eMNC61mLCO https://t.co/xuDoaZQ4Jc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Principal Engineer: Data Domain, LLC (a Dell Technologies Company) is seeking a Software Principal Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to be Responsible for the software design and development for external customer products. Utilize a range… https://t.co/zqcYHjUyKX https://t.co/nANW9KaEgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Take a Screenshot on a Mac: Because in 2018, you need the receipts. https://t.co/0OreNEUXye https://t.co/FPPwScPVku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Engineer: Our Team: Technology drives our business. Our team is made up of talented software engineers, infrastructure engineers, leaders and UX professionals. We care about technology as a craft and a differentiator. We bring our… https://t.co/eM4CHFCs0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair poisoned by same nerve agent used on ex-spy: British investigators have descended upon a small English town to find out how two seemingly random individuals were exposed to the same Soviet-era nerve agent that nearly killed a former Russian double… https://t.co/jG0z3OZ4W9 https://t.co/w3oLNBXfrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geospatial Support Staff / North Carolina /Denver: Req ID : 437838BR Job Code/Title : E1712:Applications Engineer Job Description : Lockheed Martin Missiles &amp; Fire Control (LMMFC) is seeking a highly motivated Applications Engineer to support advanced… https://t.co/EMBRlp2OvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer/Analyst: Java Programmer/Analyst at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High Tech –… https://t.co/4Ckd4pGIGs https://t.co/LHnp4E9XDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager, Merchandising Strategic Initiative: Job Title: Sr. Project Manager, Merchandising Strategic Initiative Job ID: ******* Location: FL-BocaRaton-6600NMilitary Regular/Temporary: Regular Responsibilities The Sr. Manager, Merch Strategic… https://t.co/Adgr5NasTh https://t.co/JEVaAMcXl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Intelligence Analyst: Closing On: 07/09/2018 Sr. Business Intelligence Analyst Location Americas, USA, Minnesota, Plymouth Job Reference SMNA00479 Schedule Type Full Time Job Description The Sr. Business Intelligence Analyst supports and… https://t.co/VYcOlrpUQM https://t.co/T8zYpBc1MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Chinese executive dies after falling from a wall https://t.co/3xQIESAQZm https://t.co/JDAvf0gK6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst: Quantum Secure Inc (San Jose, CA) F/T positions: Solution Engineer III: Resp for analyze &amp; cust security suite; req Mstr’s or equiv + 2 yr exp + skills. Software Engineer: Resp for dev &amp; &amp; cust security suite; req Bach or equiv… https://t.co/vinvTXXYgo https://t.co/mw92N8Q3Nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fourth of July Drone Show Helps Military Families With Special Needs: On Wednesday, Travis Air Force Base will host a light show by Intel's Shooting Star drones instead of traditional fireworks. https://t.co/EcWX99sb6v https://t.co/QMrCczvy6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Accountant – Corporate Accounting: Job Description Senior Accountant – Financial Services – Corporate Accounting •* Are you a Senior Accountant who is interested in the Exciting world of the Financial Services market and want exposure to a local… https://t.co/spsBfpK5Vd https://t.co/0r3fJY5mIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Data Scientist: 30751BR Experienced Data Scientist San Diego California United States Leverage technical and analytical expertise to explore and examine data from multiple disparate sources with the goal of discovering patterns and previously… https://t.co/4YywUsoqW8 https://t.co/UwMI0ttwZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Electrical: Milpitas, CA Full-time $95k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Electrical Project Manager with experience, please read on! Based in beautiful Milpitas, CA we are an exciting, fast-paced and respected construction… https://t.co/m5dcL5zScn https://t.co/dOCQmGcdbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Test Engineer: Req ID : 434496BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1784:Sys Integratn/Test Eng Stf Job Description : We are currently seeking a System Integration and Test Engineer to be a part of the team developing hypersonic technology that could forever… https://t.co/j0tTZmCC0M https://t.co/zV3SgQgWgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Subcontrct Spec 4:   Job Description – Supply Chain Subcontrct Spec 4 (18012439) Supply Chain Subcontrct Spec 4 Requisition ID : 18012439 Location : United States-Alabama-Huntsville US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/DwPws5LJOu https://t.co/125CSBiOKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Scott Pruitt may be getting a pass: President Trump continues to support EPA chief Scott Pruitt even though he's under several federal investigations. https://t.co/qeNBTlbg7o https://t.co/l5pIPNl3O1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4th of July Tech Sales (2018): Osprey, Nest, iPad, V-Moda: Don't want to wait for Amazon Prime Day? We have 22 deals on everything from drones to robot vacuums. https://t.co/u7HhHR81vy https://t.co/RiSKkPieFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: Senior Software Engineer UI Developer/Backend/Server Side RESPONSIBILITIES AND DUTIES – Responsible for the Design, Implementation and Test of software for controller and related products working closely with other Software/Firmware… https://t.co/uiUeARKOir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA tester: Java dveloper Ref No.: 18-26014 Location: long island city, New York 1. Good knowledge of SOA concepts, REST services. 2. Good knowledge of Java, J2EE and frameworks like Spring 3. Good to have knowledge of building micro-services on cloud… https://t.co/OdwCzIjP2m https://t.co/HdI8WERpuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II, Partner Solutions: Software Engineer II, Partner Solutions with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox… https://t.co/n5xYtbAcfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day Sale (2018): Tips and Sneak Peeks: Amazon's big Prime Day sale is almost here, and we'll help you get something out of the madness. https://t.co/fJr1bHASZa https://t.co/sOMT6fX5X5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Scrum Master: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Our IT team is constantly making it easier for our employees to get work done and for our customers to do business with us. As a Scrum Master, you’ll be using an Agile approach to… https://t.co/vC47bwnTA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Solutions Architect- Fraud and Risk (government and/or private healthcare): Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/tBfFVXoIv4 https://t.co/lxwIuSuXai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Manager • Medical Device • Relocation Assistance!: Washington, DC Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based in the greater Washington, DC area we are a successful and fast growing Medical Device company! Currently we are looking for a… https://t.co/iv3IQAsbFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Developer: RESPONSIBILITIES * ACTIVELY SOURCE EMPLOYERS USING VARIOUS TECHNIQUES INCLUDING COLD-CALLS AND ONSITE VISITS IN ORDER TO DISCUSS SERVICE OFFERINGS OF CWD * ESTABLISH RELATIONSHIPS WITH EMPLOYERS AND ASSESS THEIR NEEDS IN ORDER TO PROVIDE… https://t.co/RAlwziIz7k https://t.co/zjrXsjCeHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Developer: Front-end Developer – What We Do Featured The Evolution of RPA to Intelligent Automation White Paper – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work – Financial Services – Software &amp; Hi-Tech – Energy &amp;… https://t.co/9frEHyyQse https://t.co/dllUnziWSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real reason why LeBron chose the Lakers https://t.co/smVgAoKLiO https://t.co/Jl6nTfpWqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone bought $1 million in Toys 'R' Us toys right before stores went out of business: An anonymous shopper gave Toys 'R' Us a parting gift just before its stores around the country prepared to close their doors for the last time. https://t.co/KecySi9g1E https://t.co/vS6wSGdexk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance, Principal Engineer, R&amp;D – Advanced Technology: Medical Devices: Sr. Engineer, Quality Assurance (#PS-1005) in Santa Ana, CA, requires 40% domestic &amp; 10% international travel; expenses paid by employer. Principal Engineer,… https://t.co/bAEA7RlgGX https://t.co/R7xeBtc9kQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to work in core components for the Ariba cloud that includes application, persistence, meta-data, object model framework, common data server, customization and UI frameworks. Bach… https://t.co/ODF9u1U8sx https://t.co/77vkY4BSGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Android Phones of 2018 (New, Unlocked, and Cheap): Wonder what the absolute best Android phone is right now? Look no further. https://t.co/RAOE060zIx https://t.co/vupoM6pisu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What life's been like for Cohen since raid: CNN's Brynn Gingras sees what President Trump's personal lawyer Michael Cohen has been up to since the FBI raided his home, hotel room and office in April 2018. https://t.co/hV8t8dnNiG https://t.co/UFLE4b163I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER LEVEL 2 (RS): Careers Center | Senior Software Developer Level 2 (RS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability… https://t.co/NzNYOE4vBU https://t.co/B6hAehu23V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Identity Management: Oracle Identity Management(OIM) Ref No.: 18-22575 Location: Hoboken, New Jersey Hi, Hope you are doing great, Position: Oracle Identity Management(OIM) Location: Hoboken ,NJ Duration: 8+ Month Contact * Skills – The IAM… https://t.co/Mb6mI2G8LH https://t.co/r6T43ztHHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description If you are a technology driven individual who loves to create cutting edge software, this is the career opportunity for you. The FAST Labs business area is the innovative research and development engine within the… https://t.co/buGsDYDFe8 https://t.co/s00wfSaBgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer 3:   Job Description – Network Engineer 3 (18004400) Network Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18004400 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/eoxabQ3P5O https://t.co/kSSLPu6N2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: Title: QA Automation Engineer Location: Downers Grove, IL, US, 60555 Company: Univar Inc Requisition ID: 5043 It starts with great chemistry. Univar is more than a distribution company – we’re a leading, global partner dedicated… https://t.co/3vFvTawns5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ITS/Traffic Project Manager: Atkins seeks an energetic, highly motivated, detail-oriented, self-starter to join our Henderson, Nevada team as a Senior ITS / Traffic Project Manager. Job Details: Under direction, provides professional and project… https://t.co/qjsIMKnt6q https://t.co/PpRnfeVQNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor: Hit protesters with water cannons: Arnold, Pennsylvania Mayor Karen Peconi is facing backlash after suggesting that protesters should be sprayed with water cannons. https://t.co/tWdDExBqgD https://t.co/RBDTivMtOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadgets for Shooting Movies on Your iPhone: DJI, Rode, Joby, Moment: As directors like Steven Soderbergh and Sean Baker have shown, you can conjure movie magic with an iPhone. https://t.co/HIyjej8QWG https://t.co/ljfBt1LGjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECS Data Analyst: Job Description The Electronic Combat Solutions Business Area Procurement Data Analyst / Expeditor will have two main responsibilities within the ECS Procurement organization. First, this candidate will be responsible for Procurement… https://t.co/axG90jV3CH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Administrator / Infrastructure – Secret Clearance – Crane, IN: Requisition ID 2018-40533 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Sr. Systems Administrator… https://t.co/GboErU2AtE https://t.co/p2ZZPjLJkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/12/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/5C8VPJ9V5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I Transportation Engineering: Job Description – Project Manager I – Transportation Engineering Job LocationUS-TX-AustinJob ID0318-18035 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time… https://t.co/TlS0Q1H8iK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Project Manager: Job Details Req ID 14354 Title SAP Project Manager City Racine State Wisconsin Job Function Info Tech Salaried / Hourly Salaried Job Description Through its people and brands, CNH Industrial delivers power, technology and innovation… https://t.co/iYehZBb0k4 https://t.co/hsIJInbMoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Basis Analyst: IGT is the global leader in gaming. We enable players to experience their favorite games across all channels and regulated segments, from Gaming Machines to Lotteries to Interactive. We have a well-established local presence… https://t.co/uVMNHEa4ja https://t.co/RExCK5amxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems Operations Specialist – (C18-FI-PA04124): CAPE FOX FEDERAL INTEGRATORS IS SEEKING AN EXPERIENCED CYBER SYSTEMS OPERATIONS SPECIALISTS TO SUPPORT THE USAF/ANG. THIS POSITION REQUIRES AN ACTIVE TS CLEARANCE. The Cyber Systems Operations… https://t.co/7Vrzw1wlZi https://t.co/GY7nxjEkH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Estimator- Rathdrum, ID: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by… https://t.co/uvIv2UCUGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Network Intelligence Analyst – Senior TS/SCI w/Poly: DESCRIPTION: The Cyber and SIGINT Solutions Operation of Employer has a career opening for a Digital Network Intelligence Analyst, SR located in Columbia, MD. JOB SUMMARY: The Digital Network… https://t.co/aSL3E2Pnay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former pro wrestler dies at 38: Matt Cappotelli, once a promising WWE star, has died after a battle with brain cancer, his wife said in an Instagram post. He was 38. https://t.co/HIfml9qlji https://t.co/wQvyPybEPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application-Security-Engineer: Analyze application source code for vulnerabilities and research threats and attack vectors that impact web applications. Utilize static code analysis tools such as Checkmarx or Fortify to assist application teams to… https://t.co/Voz0eo84xv https://t.co/TsEGWph5Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Fire Systems – Saint Louis: **Project Manager- Fire Systems – Saint Louis** Locations:Saint Louis, Missouri Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building Technologies **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/VaZrLY9i1S https://t.co/dTvkESAnjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SteelSeries Arctis Gaming Headset Sale (and 10 Other Tech Deals): Pick up a SteelSeries Arctis headset for cheap, along with tents, 4K TVs, and more this weekend. https://t.co/RbRqrQX9Ef https://t.co/7FzSBM7FK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst Financial: Senior Business Analyst Financial Primary Skills Business Analyst Financials Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Senior Business Analyst Financial for location Braintree, MA for one… https://t.co/cM1l0XF5hv https://t.co/KdRiN5HYVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst: Operations Analyst ================== Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: NoneClearance Status: Not Applicable Job Description What You ll Get to Do: The CACI Operations Team… https://t.co/gemiuhRcQA https://t.co/KyHhU1zxMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Ref No.: 18-26040 Location: DEEFIELD, Illinois ETL- Teradata AbInitio, DataStage, Talend Complex SQL structures, Able to analyze an issue and come to conclusion. BI exposure Ability to work with middle management… https://t.co/68n26lOxbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science, Senior Team Lead: Job Title: Data Science, Senior Team Lead Location: Research Triangle Park, NC, South United States, USA Company: BASF – We Create Chemistry Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Chemical, Pesticide and Fertilizer… https://t.co/2m169BbaeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java AWS Consultant: Java AWS Consultant Ref No.: 18-26803 Location: Los Angeles, California Position: Java AWS Consultant Location: Los Angeles, CA Duration: Fulltime/Contract Job Description: Responsibilities – Building new pipeline, models and code… https://t.co/nVTXYj6XbX https://t.co/NdI22nHEHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. WPF Developer: Description: Strong C# with emphasis on multi-threaded real-time GUI development Strong WPF knowledge with MVVM Experience with Decexpress or PRISM Proficient in Object Oriented Design, software design patterns, unit testing, mocking… https://t.co/I2LvMjOh7r https://t.co/YeAEJwgZwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Research, design, plan, develop and/or evaluate new, advanced network technologies. Apply at https://t.co/5CW6XFiqmv, Req # 243924BR. Sprint is a background screening,… https://t.co/5kAACBw5FK https://t.co/8WBuLnOsfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medical examiner: Jose Baez was 'Trump-ian': Looking back ten years later, Dr. Jan Garavaglia, the medical examiner in the Casey Anthony case, says she sees a parallel between the trial's defense and today's political arena. https://t.co/6Xj01aHjRd https://t.co/3WGzAdQ1gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AN SAP Basis Administrator II: An SAP Basis Administrator II is needed to support the operation of Dura-Line’s SAP systems in Gainesville, TX. Requires a B.S. in computer science, computer applications or related field (foreign degree equivalent… https://t.co/6OQh82RCfh https://t.co/4P8UhkDmcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Automation Test Engineer, Software Engineer, Sr. UNIX Systems Engineer: Multiple Openings Centaurus Technology Partners, LLC Irving, TX Centaurus Technology Partners, LLC. has multiple openings for the following positions to work in Irving,… https://t.co/5eRQllsLIW https://t.co/Mk1hACRYFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R48474: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R48474 Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/OwWnGvKaaQ https://t.co/HQewRODsFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers: Senior Software Engineers, Saint Charles, IL: Analyze &amp; prepare workflows that describes the logical flow of the application. Integrate the application with interface systems like Oracle R12, AEM, Factory systems, Cybersource,… https://t.co/5Uo2GUMT3t https://t.co/LYNm1lGUSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama offers Democrats tough love: Former President Barack Obama, re-emerging into the political fray for a Democratic National Committee fundraiser here on Thursday, had a message for troubled Democrats: Do more than just mope. https://t.co/p6zP3mgFuN https://t.co/knus0Oj1Fl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer / Developer: Programmer / Developer needed for Aerospace company. Experienced with FoxSpace and FoxPro systems, Oracle SQL databases,C++ Programming and JavaScript. Pay range $39.65 per hour – $66.08 per hour depending on education and… https://t.co/0bzaXkQu6Y https://t.co/p0bg8WJKOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst #PK18, Software Developer #RP18: Computer Systems Analyst, Software Developer Newt Global Irving, TX Computer Systems Analyst – Senior Performance Tester professionals needed. Position Requires: BS degree in Electronic… https://t.co/0YtS2jiBU6 https://t.co/TN7py0LVT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Solutions Architect: Senior Digital Solutions Architect wanted by clothing retailer co. in Conshohocken, PA. Provide technical architectural guidance &amp; recommendations for designing, building, testing, deploying &amp; maintain’g… https://t.co/ZxJAO6MbHn https://t.co/rWT6YrnMC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Join our Information Technology team where you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our customers’ needs and make it easy for them to do business with us. You will work fairly… https://t.co/l1pZXRi9Si https://t.co/VhQ2tbsH2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part-time Intern Developer: Job/Internship Description – Part-time Intern – Developer(Transportation Planning) – Summer 2018 Job LocationUS-GA-AtlantaJob ID0218-17872 HNTB Job TitleIntern General College Position TypeIntern Part-Time… https://t.co/FEDK0q0w05 https://t.co/MkMX0FRfOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Bicycle's Light-Up Fork Will Never Leave You in the Dark: A new bike design has two LED strips built into the front fork, offering some guiding light on rides at night. https://t.co/R6kRVbkjce https://t.co/QA22AFM0Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer I: Employer Miami University Location Miami University, Oxford Campus, Ohio Salary 85,000.00-92,000.00 Posted Jun 08, 2018 Administrative Jobs Technology, Web, Mobile &amp; Application Development, Other Technology Jobs… https://t.co/WDasRyQ08N https://t.co/tFFBSg8nJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer (EDA): Job Title: Senior Staff Software Engineer (EDA) – ****** Primary Location United States-California-San Jose Job: Software Engineering Schedule: Full-time Description Xilinx is industry leader in providing FPGA… https://t.co/26p58PRK8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cyber Incident Response Analyst: General Dynamics IT has an opening for a DOC/NOAA Senior Cyber Incident Response Analyst with strong communication and technical skills that will provide cybersecurity monitoring and situational awareness across… https://t.co/RSTsOR22zo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer ================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a Software Engineer in Duluth, GA, with experience in the following areas: * Master’s Degree in Computer Science and 2 year exp in: .Net or C#; SQL Server;… https://t.co/sNn1VoJkGP https://t.co/dTadJAFbpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing marijuana could make these furry creatures an endangered species: They're furry, part of the weasel family, and may become endangered -- partly because of marijuana. https://t.co/NBXPdY5rtB https://t.co/UygVq8eMAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Growth Product Manager, Seller Network – Weebly: Senior Growth Product Manager, Seller Network – Weebly San Francisco, CA Full-time Company Description We believe everyone should be able to participate and thrive in the economy. So we’re building… https://t.co/PubH3Sfq4r https://t.co/7gDMqsfWm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior XML Modeler/ XSLT Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 days ago(6/18/2018 3:18 PM) Job ID 23720 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/0jO6EkuYh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Financial Operations Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The Financial and Operations Analyst will develop and provide management based reporting and analysis to support daily operations and projects for Prospect Physician Enterprise (PPE), a national… https://t.co/43EoQgZ3Zv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>