<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/bD0cosY3aN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/t8gTBGTFlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/aM1s4xYuj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/l85JSFuYST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/xwXn90555o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/3Yk29f9kSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/idSiap4fVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/f2s0rESFiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/yS2li6j80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/iDdmUgeGCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/zYr8rooYiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/me4WJLuRv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/irrNfHtish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/YrpVvX8ao8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/dY907HCHgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/v24X2TdU2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/DscQ8yQsu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/O4VMDCPqZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/gWybfDbroW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/RPhbMgR2hA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/t1jT6tlGNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/nTT9yzzkJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/RkGhbihirr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/ljBZfPD32Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/6F2foCyV7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/QgYvjzop2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/IV3f9czdFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/J335WBPPiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/cAyNLImYUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/AKFNjEjqNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/kvLUFFx2rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/em9wn01iPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/CboAjM840G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/FwNoxqeOyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/L96zi036cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/MNY654DVCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/WxVc58hnAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/7m5JctuXnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/3JkyTJlCYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/21pkqcOb3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/XKSTP13ykh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/6kXZ2uVF19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/E9XS0csj9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/8G7EUTcs40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/PrFuy131Gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/zjsgpoqnwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/nOnOtXlluJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>