<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not how you feel on a good day. It is how you feel when your entire body is telling you to quit & you find a way to keep going #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest temptation is to settle for far too little - Thomas Merton #life #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned that finishing a marathon isn't just an athletic achievement. It's a state of mind..that says anything is possible~Hanc via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["May you live every day of your #life." - Jonathan Swift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgive, run, love, run, laugh, run, impossible, run, imaginable, run, unimaginable, #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is short, surround yourself with #people who care” via @Lotay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to balance reason with passion; reason keeps you open, passion keeps your adrenaline going.” -Unknown (via @MizzSocial) #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great #dream begins with a dreamer. ~ Harriet Tubman via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There R those days when it's hard 2put 1foot in front of the other,but those R the days when champions R created" McNally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try again. Fail again. Fail better - Samuel Beckett via @CharityIdeas #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lack of dreaming, a lack of the possibilities, a lack of passion. And I didn't want to live without passion - H. Hefner #live #dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Nobody can go back & start a new beginning, but anyone can start today and make a new ending” Maria Robinson via @Run2SaveLives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemistry wakes your soul up so you can let passion in #feelit #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our passions are the winds that propel our vessel. – Proverbs #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion is the element in which we live; without it, we hardly vegetate. – Lord Bryron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with #passion is better than forty people merely interested. 
— E. M. Forster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In #dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities." Janos Arnay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragedy of #life is not that it ends so soon, but that we wait so long to begin it - Anon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything's #possible if you've got enough nerve. via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop appreciating the gifts you are given. Nothing, no friend ever taken for granted #thankful #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There lives in each of us a hero awaiting the call to action. - H. Jackson Brown Jr. #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life does not give us chances...life is our chance to give! ~Ziggy via @iheartquotes #live #run #friends #give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree, it will live its whole #life believing that it is stupid." Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After all these years, about every week to 12 days my body just craves a long #run." -- Gary Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you can #imagine is real.- Pablo Picaso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will do #today what you won't, so #tomorrow I can do what you can't" -Unknown via @timagee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want something, go get it. Period. ~ Pursuit of #Happyness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#You got a dream, you got to protect it. People can’t do something themselves, they want to tell you you can’t do it ~Pursuit of Happyness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever let someone tell #you you can't do something. Not even me. All right? ~ Pursuit of Happyness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This part of my #life... this little part.. is called "happiness" ~ Pursuit of Happyness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laziness may appear attractive, but work gives #satisfaction.- Anne Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not because things are difficult that we do not #dare, it is because we do not dare that they are difficult.~ Seneca #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A little part of one dies when not living and feeling your #passion. Live it. Feel it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be not afraid of going slowly; be afraid only of standing still." -Chinese proverb #start #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those days when it's hard 2 put 1 foot in front of the other, but those R the days when #champions R created~ McNally via @McMillanRunning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For my part I know nothing with any certainty, but the sight of the #stars makes me dream."-Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human #spirit is indomitable." -Sir Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2005 I thought that completing an ironman was impossible. I said 'you must be crazy' to do them. Now look at me ~ @chrissiesmiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go after your #dream, no matter how unattainable others think it is." -Linda Mastandrea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemistry can come in many forms #friends #love #passion #runningpartners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The day came when the #risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." ~ Anais Nin via @charityideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do something wonderful, people may imitate it." ~ Albert Schweitzer #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Motivation will almost always beat mere talent." - Norman R. Augustine via @cool_running #go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You've only got 3 choices in #life — give up, give in, or give it all you've got." via @LXLEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Running your first #marathon is like losing your virginity, once you get started you don't want to stop" unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not settle for less than an #extraordinary life.” via @nttr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Saying you don't have enough time is a bad reason to not #run. There's always time for a run." Sebelius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run the mile you are in." ~ via @ryanhall3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Live your #life, take chances, be crazy. Don't wait-now is oldest you've ever been & youngest you'll be ever again via @GregKnottLeMond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't rate myself as a fantastic, talented #athlete. I just have perseverance. I'm a cart horse. I work hard." -Colleen DeReuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People come into your life for a reason. Be #thankful for all of them."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we need little setbacks to propel us #forward ~ #run #keepgoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a dream that comes alive when we meet ~Unknown via @ZnaTrainer #love #life #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If people #believe in themselves, it's amazing what they can accomplish." - Sam Walton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take an opportunity to run in new locations. We can all be explorers #runningtip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all runs require a garmin and music. Sometimes it needs to be you and the ground #runningtip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest danger for most of us is not that we aim too high & miss it, but we aim too low & reach it. ~Michelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect the #distance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is 26.2 for a reason #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never give up on your #dreams. Remember that sometimes, you may need to put those dreams on hold, but never give up!” via @CrusePhoto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the first half of the race, don't be an idiot. In the second half, don't be a wimp." via @runnersworld #truth #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people care too much, I think it's called love." - Winnie the Pooh #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After climbing a great hill, one only finds that there are many more #hills to climb. ~ Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It always seems impossible until it's done" Nelson Mandela #marathon #run #ironman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only place where your dream becomes impossible is in your own thinking." ~ Robert H. Schuller #love #run via @nuggetsoflove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["U can either advance boldly in the direction of UR dreams, or retreat fearfully in2 the safety of the habitual" ~ Cortes via @nuggetsoflove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time isn't always on your side, #love now, love often; don't let love pass you by. via @DrAndyBaldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dead last finish is greater than did not finish which greatly trumps did not start" - Running shirt via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people sit back and let others act and do. It just gives us doers an opportunity to really #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running is a balance of physical exertion, enhanced mental awareness and spiritual peace via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe people are looking for the meaning of #life as much as they are looking for the experience of being alive. ~Joseph Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself. ~Joseph Campbell #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Passion is the genesis of genius." Tony Robbins #run #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#run #freedom #laughs #nature #awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Eventually you learn that the competition is against the little voice inside you that wants you to quit." Sheehan #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run with passion, live with passion, and feel with passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's very hard in the beginning to understand that the whole idea is not to beat the other #runners." Sheehan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Listen to your body. Do not be a blind and deaf tenant." - Dr. George Sheehan #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm always doing things I can't do. That's how I get to do them." ~Pablo Picasso #run #distance #challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. ~Roger Bannister #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people follow their #dreams, others hunt them down & beat them mercilessly into submission~ Kendall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running should be a relationship status. #RunNerds via @runaddicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life (and #running) is not all about time but about our experiences along the way."-Jen Rhines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hated every minute of training, but I said 'don’t quit, suffer now & live the rest of ur life as a champion.' Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To enhance your well being expand your network of #happy friends via @deepakchopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Friends don't let friends think negatively." via @AffirmationSpot #truth #friends #support #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I plan 2run that race so hard I won't want 2think about racing for at least 48 hours."-L. Thorvilson on 2012 Marathon Trials via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our truest life is when we are in dreams awake. ~Thoreau #dreams #life #chances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In #dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities."
- Janos Arany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The #heart has it's reasons that reason does not know."
- Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #positive thinker sees the invisible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible. - Unknown via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Toughness is in the soul and spirit, not in muscles.” ~Alex Karras via @neo_endurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will ever be attempted if all #possible objections must first be overcome. ~Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's meant to be will always find a way."- Trisha Yearwood #dream #don't #give #up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This 26.2 is for all the girls picked last in gym class" #Marathon Shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never settle for the #dream you think you can reach. Settle on the dream you want.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive thinking is a decision, it's a momentum, it's a vibration. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we do the #impossible we realize we are special people."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up, shoes on, dream big, and get out the door #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great love and great achievement involve great risk- Dalai Lama via @Running_Junkie]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>