<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new painting. One of my faves to date. A lush alleyway found where Chinatown and Strathcona meet http://t.co/EfUo6IB7B9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a newly completed painting of an alleyway in downtown Vancouver:

https://t.co/NHzvAb1Atf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished! This piece documents the arbutus trees on Lasqueti Island that I experienced earlier this year with some great friends :) With my upcoming exit from Vancouver, this is one of a handful pieces left... https://t.co/SWHGiTnOry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choo-choo! Laying down some base colour on a final smaller piece (24x24) to be ready for Friday’s opening of... https://t.co/rATkZ3WDTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend progress! 
.
.
.
#art #painter #painting #urban #urbanart #urbandecay #urbanlandscape #drawing #acrylic... https://t.co/08KaFOdp21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love every stage of the process, but adding those last final details, grafitti tags, random litterings, objects... https://t.co/vb25TENejk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studio organizing! Hanging work in the halls for the @parkerartsalon which opens tomorrow night!! Then Sat and... https://t.co/WL1u4WTk2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting will be done very soon. Because of the Tool concert announcement in Vancouver, I'm working extra... https://t.co/AuCQGl2RAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've thoroughly enjoyed making this painting in the past few weeks, should be able to finish tomorrow. Definitely... https://t.co/o567kcFddQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paintings, new studio, new year. Always begins with some basic lines and colour washes! The meditative... https://t.co/hPFmT2Dgv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up for the opening night of the @culturecrawl tomorrow! More to do but it's looking mighty fine in here... https://t.co/uwraBZpd0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time again! The 20th East Side Culture Crawl begins tomorrow!! This is my favourite show and event... https://t.co/CCHy4yPh9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #pokearthunt continues in Toronto this week.

This painting will be planted around 5:30pm tomorrow at... https://t.co/SHx1UH0UyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday everyone! I drew these frogs yesterday and am starting to paint them today...until it's time to... https://t.co/Bhb2IG2lpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current studio shot before weekend camping. Productive week! Alleyscapes and [incomplete] turquoise lilies! https://t.co/Qv9DndgLbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends! I am heavily contemplating the idea of teaching out of my studio and/or hosting event nights (i.e. paint... https://t.co/m6O34S47Bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studio wall snap shot, needs to de clutter a little bit but isn't too bad currently :) https://t.co/JLSSti22oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landscape 06 - Whistler/Garibaldi - 8x8

*Sold https://t.co/RHB3CPBR8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R2D2 all finished! Just chilling on the floor for now. Will find wall space soon ;) https://t.co/jsXeylIYUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Kauai for offering me this sweet flower to paint today, finished just in time for sunset swimming :) https://t.co/DuHIQqNAUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINISHED! First painting of the new year. Titled "Luigi Crush". Experimented with a couple of new stencil... https://t.co/M8UJpKNJiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling on the Seawall, putting the finishing touches on my latest painting on this beautiful day. https://t.co/hTFFsg8UT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrapping up my latest painting on the seawall this beautiful day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted a picture of Milhouse as a gift for a friend: http://t.co/Uh7uK2P4yw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's where you can find my artwork on the labels of @CollectiveBrew in the GTA: http://t.co/WQygeqfLAH This art: http://t.co/OhocVkAldJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new painting for an upcoming show in North Van http://t.co/eH8vNpHkOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a pic of yesterday's paper in Vancouver, talking about my recent paintings at the H'Arts fundraiser: http://t.co/K4VA8t795T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my mug in today's Sunday edition of The Province http://t.co/MplIn2pDMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Jay! http://t.co/bSjXZP49jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a painting of a blue jay I made: https://t.co/SJz5G79eCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have now listed my vancouver series greeting cards for sale. Holiday cards, anyone?? http://t.co/GJaAbsB7cC via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ya painted recycle bins, from vancouver back alleys! http://t.co/BZPhYXnMkh via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the Sun Tower in downtown Vancouver #art #vancouver #gastown http://t.co/lHIJlAQ2xg via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a card/print of a decaying phone booth that i painted from Main and Hastings: http://t.co/3EesDdAMj5 via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A greeting card of a parking meter painting. Order soon for the holidays!  http://t.co/aBjQiHzeQo via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodwards City of Vancouver Art Card &amp; by JonShawPaintings http://t.co/7Uzb53FUCO via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new painting of the woodwards underway http://t.co/m5TQTTyIXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadapostcares my parcel was lost and a refund is being issued. In what form of payment does that arrive? (e-transfer, letter, etc)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finishing up my piece at the H'Arts for the Homeless auction last night! It sold for a cool-Thousand too :) http://t.co/uyUC1kxV30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a brand new painting! This is in the Pender/Main/Hastings hood of Vancouver. http://t.co/eQepoGwdD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadapostcares Is there any issues shipping a parcel to a business address, not residential? (2535-3rd Avenue SE Calgary, Alberta T2A 7W5)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadapostcares ok thanks - if i have a receipt with the tracking number on it, that means its definitely in the system though yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadapostcares I sent a parcel today but the tracking number does not show up in the track system online. How do I know it has been sent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new print I just listed. It's a painting of an owl in flight! http://t.co/cEEjTceaj6 via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just done a brand new alleyway painting-You can come to this great event and bid on it for DTES shelter charity: https://t.co/7bf2PyPr0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Thursday I am participating in the H'Arts for the Homeless fundraiser again. This is my second year... http://t.co/1LN0lbXESJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spindlebox thanks mate! Taking that show down this week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I currently have one remaining print of the Woodwards Sign in my shop: https://t.co/cseT5hy491 Here's a pic of it: http://t.co/JyzV9Ms1tI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacLarenVan: Fist Bump Wed. Big @MacLarenVan to our very own @JonShawPainting. Attached is pict entitled "9-5." More like 8-7... http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out this new frog painting i made! http://t.co/wc3J5q80Cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool historical shot of the Sun Tower's construction, where @MacLarenVan is now based. http://t.co/rfxeAnuo5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holidays are starting to approach, you would certainly like to hand out some sweet art cards to your friends, no?? https://t.co/lgzyTZi8YT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new painting of an octopus that i just finished! #art #vancouver #octopus http://t.co/4BMlysM8jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver alleyway painting! #art #vancouver http://t.co/6v732fhAHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new painting I just finished. It was a commission work for my friend, who gave it as a gift to his... http://t.co/8uuaWslXJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaKwok @makeitshow thanks friend! i love love love making it! ill have those ready within a week too, btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaKwok @makeitshow wow thanks buddy! I'm so glad u enjoyed my work! just doing what i love doing, that's all!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weekend's @makeitshow saw 15,000 attendees!? Fantastic. I feel like I met at least half of you :) Thanks everyone for coming out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ajsharpe asked: I just stumbled upon your work while looking up illustrations and I love your pieces!!! How... http://t.co/SJOmgrWbYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A huge thanks to everyone that came by the Make It show to see my work. The response was literally overwhelming.... http://t.co/YmmM5dzp0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver  thanks - my current body of work focuses heavily around vancouver imagery: http://t.co/TlNyezx3Mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The holidays are coming up, wouldn't it be great to use greeting cards with cool art on them!? https://t.co/d1KanT6EFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0e3Rd26isN

Starting Thursday I will be exhibiting and selling work at the holiday... http://t.co/Au2ibZ1Trw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you go see Arvid's wonderful pieces at @KimotoGallery - Amazing work, great guy, fantastic gallery space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pseudoreplication - SOLD - to a very nice fellow. I'm glad it's going to his home. Thanks, Giulio! http://t.co/qSUXtHUsAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic! All three of my pieces in the Anonymous Art Show sold last night! Thanks to everyone who purchased!! :) :) http://t.co/KATxOQ4s2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, busy, super fun night at the @NVArtsCouncil last night! Lotsa happy folk out :) #AAS13 http://t.co/Kz9yH81JcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the folks at Waave+Dada for this neat blog post about me and my work:... http://t.co/SEijC8ZS1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a donation to the Canadian Red Cross. Show your support, donate now at https://t.co/Syedj9VWTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahNJBowman thanks man I built it myself! That's cool the crawl was great! Sold 4 originals and a ton of prints!!  Very pleased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gastown u got it friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gastown @CultureCrawl you guys ARE tweeting about Gastown, after all..haha. It is the most recent of my street post pieces :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece was sold at @CultureCrawl this past weekend and I couldn't be happier :) #art #vancouver #gastown http://t.co/UKJRHurREm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing crew! This is why I love our studio so much. Awesome people, great times! http://t.co/Ca7UYyQJAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece is now off to a great new home, sold at the @CultureCrawl this weekend! Thanks guys :) http://t.co/1CDh47KOwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone who came to the Culture Crawl this weekend, it was an amazing turn out and so much awesomeness... http://t.co/CZPffa0l8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HumphreyNicola: At @CultureCrawl don't miss @lisaochowycz @tcgcoop @dahlhausart @JonShawPainting @hoboguitars @GolemDesigns @Soigneatel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you friends for visiting us all at the studio tonight! Great start to the culture crawl :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight is the start of the @CultureCrawl, the studio is full of fresh work! I've also got prints and greeting cards for the holidays too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmandaGAdams yup its chilling there now, and ill have the animation projected onto the wall too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A BIG drawing of Darth Vader on wood panel! #art #starwarsisforever http://t.co/i7DgD8V1ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i made a 4 x 4 foot darth vader drawing, here is a stop motion video of it animating from start to finish: https://t.co/pJiFysZB03 #StarWars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my interview on Breakfast TV this morning talking about the @CultureCrawl - I'm at 3:37 - http://t.co/WXB05rPQoC  #art #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dawnchubai: coming up at 7:50 on @bt_vancouver we feature @Jonshawpainting  From @culturecrawl ! Cool techniques to his art! http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can watch me talk about my art tomorrow morning on @bt_vancouver at Octopus Studios, discussing the @CultureCrawl . I'll be on 7:49am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This new print is packed and for sale at the @CultureCrawl this weekend - come visit me at 393 Powell Street! http://t.co/WOVAxHJ18A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of prints to choose from at this weekend's East Side Culture Crawl. You can come visit my studio at 393... http://t.co/t9JnhqixOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my work in the latest issue of BCLiving magazine - a nice way to kick off the weekend! http://t.co/tOjLGaipyx #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[started animating a 4 x 4 foot darth vader drawing: http://t.co/3jG20teYbQ #vancouver #art #darthvader #StarWars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpusArtSupplies: Wow! Check out the cards and prints by #Vancouver artist Jon Shaw! Gorgeous! https://t.co/3QN3wp0Il8 @JonShawPainting …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gastown Check it out guys - just painted the Woodwards W-sign: https://t.co/E2l8Cx1HaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done! This is a new commission painting of the Woodward's sign I just finished. http://t.co/xIP1jklPHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a painting of a panther on three different canvases to create a full image: http://t.co/PNexcdszvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're interested in submitting art work for @CollectiveBrew , go here: http://t.co/FMWvhlbjFf These fellows put my work on their labels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a miscellaneous drawing I did recently. I haven't done figurative in a while, but I really enjoyed this... http://t.co/mMRlLVwCEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty awesome - I'm a fan of the awesome cross between urban and natural http://t.co/bX1btxSJUR via @Booooooom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art with gunpowder - I'm really enjoying listening to this description of Cai Guo-Qiang's work: http://t.co/968jOazuG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to see this...if I'm ever heading to Brisbane. Fantastic large-scale installation sculpture of 99 animals: http://t.co/l1d16HD0LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been painting the shipping cranes at the inlet lately. It's close to being done, this is a little snippet of it http://t.co/gvTcgEI1D3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is my co-worker's last day so as a going-away gift I painted him a Hank Scorpio http://t.co/PJLIV2nP1N]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>