<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer/Data Engineer –: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking a talented Systems Engineer/Data Engineer – Senior Level for our Plano, TX Facility. Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software development… https://t.co/Ib3jLGF60l https://t.co/Qlhdi2kVBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can a City *Really* Sue an Oil Company for Climate Change?: In a federal court in San Francisco, a judge heard a motion to dismiss from five fossil fuel companies, the defendants in the suit brought by San Francisco and Oakland. https://t.co/jQB2vy5DKy https://t.co/gLxHx4PdmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish SEO Specialist, Senior: Job Posting Title:Spanish SEO Specialist, SeniorJob Description: Our Senior SEO’s take ownership seriously. For them, establishing competitive goals, building forecasts and keeping a constant pulse on the performance of… https://t.co/mnK6F0Nj1t https://t.co/cnGT30zFVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingestible Sensors Electronically Monitor Your Guts: Researchers are cooking up pill-sized sensors to detect medical molecules and possibly diagnose other gastrointestinal ailments. https://t.co/iZtvotteFI https://t.co/mUFXrf9XDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Lead – Call Center Technical Solutions: Job Description Job Description We are seeking a talented IT Technical Lead – Advisor to join our product delivery team, focusing on delivering innovative health care solutions for CVS/Caremark. The… https://t.co/iOZK3pqPwZ https://t.co/LpoXKIdAiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Ruby on Rails: * Mid to Sr level Ruby on Rails Developer, youll be solving the many complicated requests and problems presented by our clients &amp; internal staff. We are expanding and with this new growth comes new challenges: *… https://t.co/HMqpTuk9il https://t.co/1WyfYca6TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Rules for Learning How to Talk To Each Other Again: Leading an evidence-based life just might help us have a less-polarized national conversation. https://t.co/nsMFy8WfZO https://t.co/f1im0Y4U4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emilia Clarke Wants a Chewbacca Tattoo—and a Dragon: The 'Solo: A Star Wars Story' actress loves her co-star. https://t.co/2fglzvDssW https://t.co/z2M0Gcl0Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students Turn Chevy's Camaro Into a Eco-Happy Future Machine: College teams from around the country competed by making hybrid and electric versions of the muscle car. https://t.co/EeVOZXserm https://t.co/fjzNjmPG9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porsche's Cayenne E-Hybrid Checks Your Route to Pick Your Power: The luxury SUV looks down the road to see where you need battery power, and where you need old-fashioned internal combustion. https://t.co/e36xgz01x3 https://t.co/zpXHDeYPa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg,… https://t.co/LZwHXl7Tf9 https://t.co/UZocUD8bSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inconvenient Minifauna and the Invasion of the Hammerhead Flatworms: Based on the amount of media attention they’re getting, the worms might work to bring attention to the upending of ecosystems by invasive species. https://t.co/xXUpvcgXtn https://t.co/0xvRVVHn9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP MDG/BODS/Info Steward/SDI/SDQ Consultant #00541960: SAP MDG/BODS/Info Steward/SDI/SDQ Consultant Job Location: CO – Denver, CT – Hartford, DC, DC – Washington, DE – Wilmington, FL – Tampa, GA – Atlanta, IL – Chicago, IN – Indianapolis, MA – Boston,… https://t.co/Zd1Lxsrnaa https://t.co/hUUymVGtrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Engineer: Rockwell Collins, Inc., manufacturer of avionics parts &amp; systems in Irvine, CA seeks Sr. Software Engineer for software development for high assurance Flight Control System applications; perform all phases of software… https://t.co/brVfACuFtF https://t.co/7YcabP2Md7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Binges and Benders, Postmates Knows the True You: A team of data scientists at the anything-goes delivery company revealed our collective whims, whether it’s scarfing brisket, stockpiling sex toys, or splurging on caviar. https://t.co/g01YeYZ9tB https://t.co/Qe6zuvFAAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Administrator – Govt Clearance: CRI is looking for an Oracle DBA possessing either an active DOD Secret or DOE L clearance to work with our federal client.This individual will be using the tool to create web interfaces for the Idaho… https://t.co/0LW4T2hiay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Senior Network Administrator: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-IL-Lincolnshire Posting Description This is a senior network administrator position with TRACC within Aon IT. This role will be in our Lincolnshire or Chicago, IL office locations.… https://t.co/SYsaSco2xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps (Docker) Engineer: Are you a Senior DevOps Engineer with strong Docker experience in prod? Do you want to work heavily with Kubernetes? If you answered yes, then check this out. WHAT IS THE JOB? As our most senior DevOps Engineer, you will… https://t.co/imiWcxoHga https://t.co/eqXjFpttgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Significant’ FBI Error Reignites Data Encryption Debate: FBI stats about inaccessible cellphones were inflated, undermining already controversial bureau claims about the threat of encryption. https://t.co/3vw7WEfPwK https://t.co/lcG2gh7lXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FI/CO Consultant: SAP FI/CO consultant required to assist client on multiple projects in Ohio. Candidate should have at least 5+ years SAP experience and excellent communication skills. Please apply via this Jobserve link in this advert. https://t.co/sjj0hqK7km https://t.co/tu2krZn150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java DevOps Trading Model Developer: McLean, VA We are developing exciting business applications using live streaming data in DevOps centric environment and are looking for a change agent and driven professional. We want to add a strong Java… https://t.co/XOmknAx8UE https://t.co/rcBptvJg6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the LAPD Uses Data to Predict Crime: The Los Angeles Police Department is using "predictive policing" to prevent crime, but this innovative approach has its problems. https://t.co/co8WY7DyVc https://t.co/5UDKhzXMEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Laser Battle Against Blood-Sucking Parasites of the Deep: What can salmon farmers do against the scourge of tiny fish-killing sea lice? Fry them. https://t.co/CYQ3i8tSTC https://t.co/bpxC0mPZFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Specialist: COMPUTER/IT Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) wrk in crss-fnctnl dvlpmnt or tstng team w/ focus on QA &amp; tst rltd tasks w/in prdct creatn prcss. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd &amp; 5 yrs exp req’d… https://t.co/OIZBLQoMof https://t.co/klnRWGsrsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Solo: A Star Wars Story’ Review: It May Be Inessential, But It’s Also Utterly Delightful: There are few, if any, revelations here, and some of the fleshed-out backstory is woefully dumb, but Han finally gets the solo adventure he deserves. https://t.co/3P03bCEdTs https://t.co/mwZVGcnXxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Math Says Urinals in Planes Could Make Lavatory Lines Shorter for Everyone: As long as you've got the exact right number of urinals. https://t.co/9I28dNMISI https://t.co/fBhwpQkDAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Materials Cost Analyst (2 openings): Materials Cost Analyst(2 openings)SMS InfoComm Corp.Grapevine, TX Control &amp; improve the procurement material cost processes &amp; procedures. Analyze cost &amp; prepare report for Purchasing Department. Conduct data &amp; cost… https://t.co/fnumtJUYFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Political Theater of Controlling Ebola With Border Checks: At best, thermometer-wielding guards waste resources; at worst they slow aid and supplies. So why do we still build checkpoints? https://t.co/1uwv9AYbdN https://t.co/VeETGAtQWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Photos of the Week: Mars Gets Pac-Man Fever: NASA just released an image of a crater-dune combination it is calling Bachan Pac-Man. https://t.co/bAuwNegQto https://t.co/yTFsKqNz53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Look Inside Theranos’ Dysfunctional Corporate Culture: When a chemist raised concerns about the blood testing machines' high error rates, she was ignored. So she resigned. https://t.co/b7piSz2A7q https://t.co/n3ugBMnzMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) wrk in crss-fnctnl dvlpmnt or tstng team w/ focus on QA &amp; tst rltd tasks w/in prdct creatn prcss. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd &amp; 5 yrs exp req’d or alt… https://t.co/Sd5RqyDVP0 https://t.co/cpt71JNiBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software/ Database Engineer: eClinicalWorks, LLC located in Pleasanton, CA has openings for: EMR Project Managers (#478709E), Sr. Software/ Database Engineers (#084441) and EMR Business Analysts (#997895C). See https://t.co/T97DnwAIrx for job duties… https://t.co/zkpRMKPJHi https://t.co/UfJtqigGmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ATM Software Specialist, Senior Software Developer: Diebold Nixdorf Inc. has multiple openings for Austin, Texas: ATM Software Specialist – Security (Job code: 5268 ) to develop, create, and modify ATM software applications with a focus on multi-vendor… https://t.co/I9IEoi7pBS https://t.co/9uPB9X0Wy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23andMe Goes Global In Its Data-Mining Efforts: The consumer genetics company is opening its data set to some researchers—and recruiting others to make that data set more robust in the first place. https://t.co/AQngMroX7t https://t.co/6zb35a0dVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is It Weird for Conservatives to Like 'Star Trek'?: On the latest 'Geek's Guide to the Galaxy' podcast, writer Ana Marie Cox discusses Ted Cruz's love of one of the most openly liberal TV shows. https://t.co/j7HSpKvVdD https://t.co/raEa3kpQQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Business Intelligence: Summary:Heartland is seeking a Business Intelligence Project Manager responsible for leading the delivery of internal and outsourced BI projects from project initiation to delivery. The BI Project Manager’s… https://t.co/l2NGWU2Cf7 https://t.co/5fY1990vO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signals Intelligence/Network Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/10/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/jqP2NzwSPi https://t.co/cpxPy721cD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kelly's Comments on Immigration Top This Week's Internet News: The White House chief of staff's comments about immigration had a lot of people online talking last week. https://t.co/ZbCSMMWk8b https://t.co/4MJMxfGJKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pega Developer – Mid Level: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Pega Developer Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. Pega Developers are engaged in all phases of the software development lifecycle which include; gathering and analyzing… https://t.co/8ydniV0fo2 https://t.co/MP57qeDjAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SAP Application Developer: Company Description: Crown Equipment Corporation is a leading innovator in world-class forklift and material handling equipment and technology. As one of the world’s largest lift truck manufacturers, we are committed to… https://t.co/RsGIh2QO2l https://t.co/yHXuqhmrl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ios engineer: Pinterest is a highly data-driven business and product and our engineers move fast to deliver the best experience and features for our pinners. We depend on having great instrumentation, developer tools, and build processes that will enable… https://t.co/uQx1GxDBUi https://t.co/OK3HUUd77F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Apple Systems Engineer: Why choose between doing meaningful work and having a fulfilling life? At MITRE, you can have both. That’s because MITRE people are committed to tackling our nation’s toughest challenges—and we’re committed to the long-term… https://t.co/tSjm61v5le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Volcanologists Predicted Kilauea’s Explosive Eruption: Scientists are now warning that the next phase of eruptions could send very large boulders as far as a mile from the crater. https://t.co/EFiBi10NkR https://t.co/ihme5TJ3d5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Developer: FCCI is seeking a Senior System Developer to join our team of talented developers focused on the delivery of secured, documented, high quality applications software in support of FCCI’s various insurance applications using… https://t.co/Z8USi9SKaz https://t.co/jeuE5hqRy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/SqQTlZvnje https://t.co/F6vCKkKuVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Physics of a Tesla Model X Towing a Boeing 787: This Dreamliner weighs 130,000 kg—but actually, even a human could pull a full-sized aircraft. https://t.co/VipuL949RI https://t.co/HvPSYm0BBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Architect: Gannett | USA TODAY NETWORK is one of the top 20 digital media companies in the country, sharing the list with Google, Facebook, and Amazon. We reach some 120 million unique visitors a month , more than Washington Post, New York… https://t.co/J1VvOH2EeK https://t.co/l2sDpUknef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appian Developer: Job Summary Role Description: The ideal candidate will be someone who has 5+ years of experience with programming and developing, preferably with 5+ years of Appian live project experience. The following experience is highly desirable:… https://t.co/4hDjGxdQAO https://t.co/RF79LFPoP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nanit Sleep System Review: Perfect for Sleep-Deprived New Parents: Nanit’s clever algorithm coaches you to help your infant get a better night’s sleep. https://t.co/uP6mAeQSAg https://t.co/XXWUM0ZQ2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, Applications (IT): This position develops and supports application systems used across a broad spectrum of business processes directly supporting Kidney Care activities in areas of Patient Care and/or Revenue Operations. Key Responsibilities –… https://t.co/in9nKZOQiH https://t.co/7SIGRocQlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud JAVA/AWS Developer – Active TS/SCI w/Full Scope Polygraph: Design, develop, document, integrate, test and deliver scripts, code and other services employing agile DevOps project life-cycle methodologies, processes procedures, in a cloud… https://t.co/RpigYNqAhc https://t.co/9HWjfk6Qms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA’s Jim Bridenstine Agrees Humans Are Responsible for Climate Change: “We are putting [carbon dioxide] into the atmosphere in volumes we haven’t seen before," said NASA's new administrator. "We are responsible for it.” https://t.co/6Vx91IC8Kf https://t.co/gDXo1wfSMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (Mid-Level): Job Description At CACI, we are thrilled to open our new Shared Services Center (SSC) in Oklahoma City, OK! Come join CACI, a company that provides information solutions and services in support of national security missions… https://t.co/HIXbDKoA2m https://t.co/Tpr0LT2ZEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/hlsTOkk7yR https://t.co/1549ghbA2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Deadpool 2' Is What All Sequels Should Be: Better Than Its Predecessor: The follow-up to the 2016 surprise hit packs even more punch (and punchlines) than the first. https://t.co/hDsetXoAxY https://t.co/3kEsmMo4sP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bioinformatics Programmer, Immune Response: Job ID 11428 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Biostatistics, Bioinformatics and Computational Biology More information about this job… https://t.co/W1A06qN8gY https://t.co/y4dogk0Alg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Manager: TECHNOLOGYDeloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Manager, Technology, AMS in Kansas City, MO and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to provide technology-enabled business… https://t.co/seogkYvs9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG G7 ThinQ Review: A Good Phone With Some Machine Learning to Do: LG’s G7 may confuse your houseplants for ham, but it’s still a top Android phone. https://t.co/Fmmz5bihC1 https://t.co/hG0OuoDzUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spermbots Offer a Promising New Way to Target Cancer: After discovering that sperm could be coaxed into carrying chemotherapy drugs, researchers shifted their focus from inducing life to slaying reproductive cancer. https://t.co/rRYcZgliH5 https://t.co/aNZdioX9c5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOF Information Operations Analyst/Trainer (SME IV): WWC is currently seeking an Analyst for a high visibility program providing training and exercise support to U.S. Special Operations Command (USSOCOM). SOF Information Operations Analyst/Trainer (SME… https://t.co/bRwsCLTD4A https://t.co/pM8CkXdKFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Key Takeaways From Mueller’s First Year—and What’s Next: One year in, Robert Mueller’s investigation into Trump and Russia appears poised to connect all the pieces of the puzzle. https://t.co/MEqfBN5U9Z https://t.co/dryYFTedOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist I: Job Description PSI Title: Data Scientist I Work Location: Various US Locations Description Planned Systems International is looking to staff numerous position within the United States and abroad in support of US Special Operations… https://t.co/7vEnXAPkmv https://t.co/1q1lcAMDmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Engineer Staff Member for Electro-Optical Payloads: Req ID : 400455BR Job Code/Title : E1384:Electronics Engineer Stf Job Description : An Electronics Engineer Developing Test Systems will work as part of a team of hardware and software… https://t.co/QMBnnUBl91 https://t.co/Nbg42VZYdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineering – CNC Machining Programmer: Job Description Provides technical support to manufacturing and related functions. Researches, develops, and improves manufacturing processes, methods, and systems for products, facilities, fixtures,… https://t.co/wpjnscCbvT https://t.co/2TVdzNGTqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UAV Sr. Software Engineer (Flight/Mission/Embedded): UAV Sr. Software Engineer (Flight/Mission/Embedded) Jobs in Manassas at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia –… https://t.co/WvflhMA01U https://t.co/xky8K5WtjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple Positions: American Airlines has multiple openings for the following positions in Ft. Worth, TX: Sr. Analyst, CASS Quality Assurance (Ref#18429) to devp analytical tools &amp; reports to capture data to measure &amp; report internal analysis &amp; trends of… https://t.co/HWynm4w3ZV https://t.co/XYFbnuFp0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst : Google LLC, San Francisco, CA 94126 job # below: Business Systems Analyst (Mountain View, CA) Define business intelligence technologies for Google. #1615.32770 Exp Incl: enterprise resource planning… https://t.co/cuFSrLV4K0 https://t.co/s1YWkh8zTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Insect-Sized Flying Robot Is Powered by Lasers: It’s the first robo-fly that doesn’t need to be tethered to a power supply. https://t.co/8IA0Bv4d67 https://t.co/qUzm7nOxHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: Logistics done differently. At XPO Logistics, we’re constantly looking for ways to improve, enhance, and adapt in an ever-changing marketplace. The Software Engineer III is responsible for the smart software that will make it easy… https://t.co/xSO4DJR7k7 https://t.co/Ch42pOwEQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Engineering 2- Fleet Mission Package Sustainment Manager:   Job Description – Mgr Engineering 2- Fleet Mission Package Sustainment Manager (18008141) Mgr Engineering 2- Fleet Mission Package Sustainment Manager Requisition ID : 18008141 Location :… https://t.co/9OJQ7Rq4lH https://t.co/KFLifksZYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autodesk Forge Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Antonio, TX Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/Rga2d0V1QM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ABAP Developer: Title: Senior ABAP Developer Location: RTP, NC 3 months but likely to extend Looking for a strong ABAP developer with sound knowledge of FI to work with Finance team to develop report. Candidate should have sound knowledge of SAP… https://t.co/rtO8roDaW3 https://t.co/xME0t7fM5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Sr. Systems Analyst P2P / MM: SAP Sr. Systems Analyst P2P / MM IMMEDIATE NEED for a SAP Sr. Systems Analyst with Procure 2 Pay / MM specifically to join our client in a Direct Hire / Permanent position in the Long Beach, CA area to work on the latest… https://t.co/5Dxy4qvmiX https://t.co/quj73U41Na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Untold Story of Robert Mueller's Time in the Vietnam War: Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s job is to make sense of how Russia hacked the 2016 election. But to make sense of Mueller, you have to revisit some of the bloodiest battles of Vietnam. https://t.co/CjjyYp457v https://t.co/7MiVqRf49u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Pega Architects #SPA20172: Senior Pega Architects Aim Big Inc dba Axiom Technology Group Inc seeks Senior Pega Architects in Westmont, IL. Transform/migrate systems to support multichannel process management applications using Pega products.… https://t.co/VDvmeGeyUr https://t.co/7WHjEZ7CxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Data Interchance (EDI) Manager #1000C: Littelfuse, Inc. seeks Electronic Data Interchance (EDI) Manager in Chicago, IL to design, develop &amp; support B2B Integrator app between LFUS &amp; trading partners. Requires BS in Electrical/Electronics… https://t.co/Zfb7K41gO5 https://t.co/GZ2cnDx9c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer 2 eBay Inc. seeks Software Engineer 2 in Austin, TX to work with Site Engineering Center to monitor eBay e-commerce site availability &amp; performance &amp; proactively detect any failures. Monitor code roll-outs (Live &amp;… https://t.co/QU1DCxscS9 https://t.co/jDXzfIOoP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Sex, Violence, and Hate Speech Is on Facebook?: Facebook issued its first report on objectionable content, showing the prevalence of graphic violence is rising, as is Facebook’s ability to detect it. https://t.co/oogIWxDXO5 https://t.co/HTlNrgtmdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELK Stack Developer (Elastic Kibana): Avenue Code is the leading software consultancy focused on delivering end-to-end development solutions for digital transformation across every vertical. Were privately held, profitable, and have been on a solid… https://t.co/XmG4G3EgiT https://t.co/lNulnRMUzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT – Unix/Linux System Admin: IT – Unix/Linux System Admin Primary Skills LINUX,UNIX,RHCE Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking IT – Unix/Linux System Admin for location Farmington Hills , MI for one of our Top client.… https://t.co/WFEVBd7YsE https://t.co/3vGrn8d6JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Analyst, Retail Applications: Under Armour is all about performance. Because what we make empowers athletes in every form to push themselves, to turn good into great, and to stay hungry for whatever comes next. And this is exactly what we… https://t.co/tDkKA1Ds2t https://t.co/t0cSZHz8Vu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Silicon Valley’ Finale Roundtable: Can the Show Go Anywhere From Here?: Previous seasons have left Pied Piper in various stages, but Unmitigated Success has never been one of them. What now? https://t.co/fz5fzbHVMk https://t.co/4o53a5gH5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Systems Analyst: HR Systems Analyst The HRIS Business Analyst will play an integral role in the successful implementation of the HR Technology roadmap. They will bridge process and technology solutions to enhance the overall delivery of HR programs… https://t.co/hbuONp3oAU https://t.co/EXi9sWYMGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Specialist: The primary purpose of this position is to assist Members Cooperative Credit Union in living out its mission to be the primary positive financial influence in the lives of our members/owners. To achieve this goal, the employee must… https://t.co/3HhDmdhiTr https://t.co/NUDms1IyQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons from California Mudslides: Science's Credibility Is At Stake: Opinion: Residents' failure to follow evacuation orders in Montecito signal a loss of faith in science. https://t.co/ZtdIJsTp6V https://t.co/ubI45S7ssB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Technician: Hardware Technician Department:Information Services Reports To:Network Administrator, Anthony Berry FLSA Status:Non Exempt TS Range:6/7 ($19.01) Opening Date:May 11, 2018 Closing Date:May 28, 2018          SUMMARY:The Hardware… https://t.co/tWbROv3Mgl https://t.co/zwWO7vR4DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Professionals: IT Professionals needed by CertainTeed Corporation to work in Malvern, PA. *Senior Application Analyst: to design, configure, enhance &amp; implement SAP PM &amp; EAM modules;  *IT System Analyst: to develop, configure &amp; implement SAP Materials… https://t.co/bVnn2nZws0 https://t.co/rW2nuqkfZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Photos of the Week: Mini-Moons Make Saturn’s Rings Extra Groovy: Pan, the “ravioli moon,” carves a path through the pretty debris ringing this most photogenic of planets. https://t.co/mNddcQpZWz https://t.co/G2mKBjClQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Samsung Semiconductor Inc. has the following jobs in San Jose, CA: Sr. SW Development Engineer [Req #8EJ1416] Code applications with Java and Android SDK- code and troubleshoot the “core” frameworks; Staff Engineer [Req #8EJ0101]… https://t.co/4pf5h1kPRm https://t.co/g6YPj2BmS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responsible, Consistent Babysitter: Seeking a babysitter near Seattle for 2 children. Hoping you can start within months! Pick-up or Drop-off: School, piano, and other activities. Errands / groceries: Grocery, etc. on occasion. Meal Preparation: Monitor… https://t.co/HuEegQeh27 https://t.co/Je182Gfwix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Enabling Javascript in Excel Has Security Pros Anxious: Enabling JavaScript should make Excel more powerful, but increasing access points makes it even more of a web security nightmare than it already is. https://t.co/Fggm0kQpai https://t.co/Ptc8jqErrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Engineering – Client Tax Tech – Java Developer: Recruiter Goldman Sachs Location Jersey City Jersey City United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 23 May 2018 Job role Tax Sector IT Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You… https://t.co/UlX6NrldEp https://t.co/B5rWvAIeQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Description DAY TO DAY: The work would be to take existing JavaScript application, and pipe it through Cordova (an open source mobile dev framework) to create an iOS application. This candidate needs to have iOS, if they have Cordova that’s a… https://t.co/fMX8hSrHBS https://t.co/1SlygJjgVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Do you enjoy making the complex simple? Are you motivated by delighting customers and representing a team? Can you track your work and keep your promises? Heuristic Solutions is looking for a Business Analyst to join our LearningBuilder… https://t.co/TxAun7fBB8 https://t.co/d7DAvH5rZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Overview Full Stack Developer Prolifics Digital Integration team is seeking a Senior Full Stack Web Developer with Java capabilities and proven JavaScript framework experience. The successful candidate will be part of an elite… https://t.co/ySa0t68B23 https://t.co/ncxAsDZrAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Salesforce Community / Software Development Manager: We believe in the power of people. We are a network strategy and technology company that is motivated by making a difference in people’s lives – their productivity, their creativity, their… https://t.co/XP8FeR6rNV https://t.co/V4KrJiWhSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer/Senior Application Developer: Post Date Date de publication 3/23/2018 Title Titre Application Developer/Senior Application Developer City Ville Winnipeg Province MB Description Application Developer/Senior Application Developer… https://t.co/wY7gEpPpEz https://t.co/xlltUojt9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 2 – TS/SCI with Polygraph Required: Northrop Grumman Mission Systems is seeking a talented self-motivated Software Engineer to join an exciting, complex, mission-focused software development project working with a team of qualified diverse… https://t.co/A0gTBdpDEj https://t.co/aR1cvotLUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying Goodbye to 'Halo Online,' the Fan Game That Recreated a Decade-Old Classic: Halo Online never officially came out outside of Russia, but thanks to a fan mod boasted a massive community for years. Now it's done. https://t.co/NQ11nWgVGZ https://t.co/noTKFcmtMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPT Advanced Development Engineer, Fuel System Specific Controls: Cummins is a place big enough to coach and develop a global workforce and create the world’s leading clean, engine and power technology. We’re also small enough for you to find your fit… https://t.co/NpuObq2E9l https://t.co/gVl4MccDMo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>