<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GahrSEEuh Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cat_Lance We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yeolsoo_1261 You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yeolsoo_1261 You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yeolsoo_1261 Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pourtheglass You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pourtheglass It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to be kind to yourself, isn't it? But it's well worth striving for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess what? You're super cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloEllenaj I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're doing great today. Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@androidmelody You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ma2adams You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quartz2moon It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Purple_Hel You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brownsugarbun Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fragcrucifixion The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iloveraccoonss You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iloveraccoonss You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snarfoo__ You've already made much more of a difference in the world than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The idea that I make the lives of my friends better really helps me get through life's challenges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hez_1979 Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeshyr Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zlink44 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfr500 You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellymC4 You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAG0NER_ You're such a good friend to reach out when you need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so proud of everything that my friends have done. That means you, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agdjenn We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Earperdemic The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@minkrose You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to breathe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joh6nn You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In hard times, some people become warriors, some become diplomats, and some become healers. They're all needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackHatNanny You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daydreaming about burgers today. Mmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackHatNanny You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackHatNanny Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackHatNanny Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Valyasochka If things are bad, they will get better. You will make it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iShwdy You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to be kind to yourself, isn't it? But it's well worth striving for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go look at a picture of your loved ones and think about how much they care about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Valyasochka Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe space matters. Please care for one another during hard times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@No0dleJeez Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello nice friends, good morning good morning! I missed you overnight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realtaneka You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realtaneka It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluebayoz Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alliegator1004 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Earperdemic You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person you want to become is merely the person you are plus time and energy. You can do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellseaChel You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluebayoz Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningdjh The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends who work from home: are you dressed? It can really help your mood and productivity!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyAlejos1 You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Posi_Rodimus You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are all so cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcrobbee You've already made much more of a difference in the world than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@No0dleJeez You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please remember to reach out when you need help. You deserve support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realtaneka Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*yawnstretch* Oh hi twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mossdogmusic Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mossdogmusic You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TindrasGrove You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpsterKitty You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuchApple You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxKiael You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxKiael You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_brown_recluse_ I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's fun to stay up late, but make sure you rest up regularly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unixbigot We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latrodectal Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahCuratesArt You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you met my moms, @inurashii and @mossdogmusic? They're really nice! Say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGoji Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaKPerry You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHead58 Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay to feel sad sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tleeh You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EcksLibris You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you decide for your body is right. No one else knows better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>