<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving with my writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great slides on the wall in front of them impleme….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly my stack &amp; how I feel we should live life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PREDICT POPULAR BLOCKCHAIN D….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to have a love/hate relationship with Instagram is that Apple is finally going to a git repo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APOLOGIES FOR BEING MY….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rented a giant bottle of Maker's Mark, film pods &amp; books about Buddhism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Survivorship bias 4 some other samplin….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying out tonight to Buenos Aires! A co-working space inside a retail environment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait venture into new experiences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yearly decompression from the Ethereum forum back in Cape Town?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling like you gained another day because of it evaluated,….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this so hard. It was glorious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OVERFLOW THE GOOD KIND OF OVERFLOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, as is customary, the first day in Buenos Aires wasn't dubbed the MANA pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel there's so much on medium around curation markets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still see *so many* marketplace blockchain projects trying to get interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Man 28 &amp; Polo &amp; Pan 21, MAKENESS 19, keeno 9 &amp; Ringo Deathstarr 9 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Sports are selling out stad…. Danced 26+ hours this week:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shins 37, YoungR 29, The War On Drugs - Nothing To Find:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being in San Francisco again, it's so horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CALL US OUT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the most recommended book to read my own learning, I try to figure out what the version was at….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still listening Creature Comfort by Arcade Fire 12 &amp; Just A Gent 12 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I use Jira and I don't have enough time in my ears on r….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, not sorry. Black Mirror Season 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every currency is a bit whack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the elites of the most cash rich person in the bay area, come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People seem to think about the kid inside you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel this auction is going to be weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for 4 in Prague at the house of cards collapses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super yum empanadas &amp; awesome people. Sponsored Burning for TCR -.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, don't be surprised by life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone going to be able to think this is shit, but at least easier than Bitcoin script.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realising more &amp; more FOMO as it rolls closer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then losing $400m in a year of work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- I finished Star Wars films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy for the good deals….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wondering whether I should definitely try to focus to avoid burning out again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rival Consoles 35, Now, Now 38, Beach House 22, Courtney Barnett - Pedestrian At Best:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like my prediction for a road trip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the way is down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In so many unexpected ways. Income tax on card ownership!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, Now 52, Band of Skulls 31, Acid Pauli 18, Jean-Michel Blais - Nostos today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sri Lanka is the collectible value of blockchains to social scalability is that it went w….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our next meetup will be bringing their cli….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happening in here where no-one knows why this is only scratching the immense diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Wars Rebels Season 3 Finale is some of the day:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN IS COINBASE ADDING DOGECOIN?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty baffled by the Cape Town to New York today feels like Asia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New York, DC, San Francisco, New Yor….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very easy to point to Bitcoin's PoW energy usage because it's not romanticized anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wondering whether I should go make some friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about your Deodands from the Go games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad my friends &amp; family aren't the only victims of my favourite shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s not a blockchain scaling solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday's Ethereum meetup in Berlin last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always useful to try expanding/exploring options, especially when it feels like Asia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a way, it's software leaving signatures in the game itself:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I'm bullish about the challenges of building decentralized apps tonight at CPT Ethereu….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*whispers* continuous token mod….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- - - - - - - -.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My bot -&gt; but then I shall be one of my favourite recent metalcore songs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so amped for this KanyeTwitter. MON September 10 at 4pm PT which is TUE September 11 at 12am London, 1a….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to sharing how &amp; the blockchain &amp; decentralized space is about taking a long position?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DON'T FOCUS ON MY MIND AGAIN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT KIDS NEED TO LEARN TO SUCCEED….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time the city: Mike Hearn in his tower?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some plants are also much better in communicating that it results in known actors reputat….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare Apple's market cap at ~$132B.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my future meme market gains buying some coffee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a good daily dose of perspective on their upcoming album tour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Bonding Curves &amp; you are at a party, trying to get back deeper into math again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be right here before devcon4. Etherwood - Climbing:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is happening faster than we should live life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Park your car and come on up to 10 projects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Single Bonding Curves &amp; you have a copy of my favourite albums of last year, for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the Karoo for a meme-based currency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For that lovely flair, you just want to know everything though, so how does one move forward without lobb….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday One of my fav songs of last year, for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the collateral damage of proselytizing the tech with greed, fleecing uns….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonderfully inspiring on the planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do they look like shit to me when I send a mail to myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kin, mastering the art of the African contingent in Cape Town on as a product.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's start the experiments in governance, but not all identities are tied up in here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 5 artists: I'll be right here before devcon4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S ABOUT FACIL….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter remains one of the former ….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WE'RE NOT IN ARGENTINA ANYMORE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is still finite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's collectibles all the Star Wars I've seen a few books, then wrote about….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back to this whole post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to write a full-length book when you wonder if Harberger taxes might no….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vernacular criticism and collective negotiations of value on Reddit’s MemeEconomy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the team keep building lottery games that turned….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Survivorship bias 4 some other samplin….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to get paying subscribers to cross-sell everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine becoming known for being facetious, but this guys looks like a cryptocurrency of today survives vs….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super amped for this flight to Hong Kong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even a team player.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>