<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Potts (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I really wanted was to prove that I could do things right, so that when I looked in the mirror, I'd see someone worthwhile. –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cats playing instruments? Only at The O Music Awards. Watch now &gt; http://t.co/GWXMghW4WY - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen is never late. Everyone else is simply earlier. –Queen (Princess Diaries 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How lucky I am to have something that makes saying goodbye so hard. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl wants to get a cute Disney tattoo like this: http://t.co/4DADHAjJZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re never alone, you know. Just think of your friends, the ones who care. –The Tigger Movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You seem so real. Sometimes I forget that this is all a dream. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your darkness belongs to you, just the same way your light does. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don’t go away. Please? No one’s ever stuck with me for so long before. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toy Story 4? Finding Dory? Monster Inc 2? Here's the list of next Disney movies until 2015: http://t.co/y4XxzHdkN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes bad things happen, and there's nothing you can do about it. So why worry? –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing it takes to accomplish something is courage. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the smallest things take up the most room in your heart. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky for me. My dad is the most amazing guy in the world. –Miley Stewart (Hannah Montana)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a world of my own, everything would be nonsense. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe you need a new lesson. Repeat after me: Hakuna Matata. –Timon (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't understand. There is so much that you don't see. Just think, if you can. –Aladdin (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never look back, darling. It distracts from the now. –Edna Mode (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things will look better in the morning. –Bagheera (The Jungle Book)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was just mad, that's all. I needed some time to think, but you shouldn't have left me out there. –Mike (Monster, Inc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said you'd always be there for me, but you're not. And it's because of me. It's my fault. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll know he's the one when he makes me laugh. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they’d look closer, they’d find out there’s so much more to me. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In life, you face challenges, but do not let those challenges destroy who you are. –Donald Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Disney fans know her: http://t.co/e258BiydNY  | But only the real Disney fans know her: http://t.co/VCH6Fbf3Hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say if you dream a thing more than once, it's sure to come true. –Aurora (Sleeping Beauty)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re you. I’m me. Together we can live in the harmony. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people keep watching Disney movies, again and again, and still never notice this: http://t.co/mwfa6vLYE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about me. Go and enjoy yourself. I'll stay here and be miserable. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Pott (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are like stars. You can't touch them, but if you follow them, they will lead you to your destiny. –Spudnick (Space Buddies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is the richest thing we will ever own. –Donald Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Disney Princess has zodiac sign too! Which Princess has same zodiac as you? Find out here: http://t.co/HGmFazuA2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are as real as you want them to be. Dreams are as real as the sky and the sea. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just stay loose, have fun, and you'll be fine. –Buttercup (Toy Story 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you’re grown up, you can’t come back. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to believe in forever, but forever's too good to be true. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true, and maybe something wonderful will happen. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Mickey without Minnie, what's Piglet without Pooh, what's Donald without Daisy, that's me without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toy Story 4? Finding Dory? Monster Inc 2? Here's the list of next Disney movies until 2015: http://t.co/3zK3iAgoOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wendy: “I should like to give you a kiss. Don't you know what a kiss is?” | Peter Pan: “I shall know when you give me one.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing is, even if we're apart, I'll always be with you. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Chuck Norris cried during this Disney scene: http://t.co/VgTGfJkWrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we work together, things are always better. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is more powerful than death. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any man who falls behind is left behind. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my family. I found it, all on my own. It’s little, and broken, but still good. Yeah, still good. –Stitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a journey to be experienced, not a problem to be solved. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney has been keeping this secret for years but finally it's out: http://t.co/LroRiRWzbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream’s not like math that you learn in school. It can’t be defined by some scientific rule. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is hope. It fuels our dreams. –Belle (Once Upon A Time)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like a mirror. Smile every moment. –Donald Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dream wouldn’t be complete without you in it. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And remember, bee yourself. –Genie the Bee (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not the person I once was. I’ve changed. I’ve turned myself around. –Yzma (Emperor’s New Groove 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I. MISS. THEM: http://t.co/U4lf8VacAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some friends come into your life for a reason, others only for a season. –Robby Ray (Hannah Montana)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play nice, unless one of the other kids wanna fight, then you have to kick the other kid’s butt. –Mushu (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goofy: “Maybe she's just not the one for you.” | Max: “That's what I'm afraid of.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life without worry? You seek hakuna matata. –Rafiki (The Lion King 1½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you say you can't or you can, you're right. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is more fun to talk with someone who doesn't use long, difficult words but rather short, easy words. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try and get some sleep, sweetheart. Things will seem better in the morning. –Mrs. Frankenstein (Frankenweenie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary things happen to extraordinary people. –Reepicheep (The Chronicles of Narnia)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just focused on the bad stuff when all you had to do was, let go of the past and keep moving forward. –Lewis (Meet the Robinsons)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the right path is not the easiest one. –Grandmother Willow (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT. WERE. THEY. THINKING?!: http://t.co/v4HWraADmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m so happy. I think I’ll give you a kiss. –Wendy (Peter Pan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beast: “I want to do something for her.” | Cogsworth: “Well, there's the usual: flowers, chocolates, promises you don't intend to keep.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just one of those days. Again. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are like stars. You can't touch them, but if you follow them, they will lead you to your destiny. –Spudnick (Space Buddies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the raindrops come tumbling, remember you're the one who can fill the world with sunshine. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't change anything. You can't change the past. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toy Story 4? Finding Dory? Monsters University? Here's the list of next Disney movies until 2015: http://t.co/G6qIDUJXh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is taking a few steps backward, maybe even more, to give way to the happiness of the person you love. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true if we have the courage to pursue them. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they’d look closer, they’d find out there’s so much more to me. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between pretty and beautiful is, pretty is temporal, whereas beautiful is eternal. –Miss Piggy (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream is a wish your heart makes when you're fast asleep. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving up is your choice, not your fate. –Plio (Dinosaur)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you choose to lock your heart away, you'll lose it for certain. –Jack Sparrow (Pirates of the Caribbean)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen with your heart, you will understand. –Grandmother Willow (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t look backwards for very long. Keep moving forward, opening up new doors and doing new things. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying is the important thing. It’s okay to fail as long as you keep trying. –Mr. Rzykruski (Frankenweenie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fate has a way of arranging what's right. –Mrs. Jenkins (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a woman says later, she really means not ever. –Charlotte (Princess and The Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To find hakuna matata, you must look beyond what you see. –Rafiki (The Lion King 1½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know yourself. Be yourself. –Ken (Toy Story Campaign)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's special moments are tomorrow's memories. –Genie (The Return of Jafar)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be with you forever. I want you right here beside me forever. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be imaginative, strong-hearted. You must try things that may not work. –Gusteau (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real treasures are your friends and family. –Woody (Toy Story 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your talent makes you who you are. You should be proud of it. –Tinker Bell (Disney Fairies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your heart is in your dream, no request is too extreme. –Jiminy Cricket (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could feel a love so strong and true. –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get it if you really want, but you must try try and try. You'll succeed at last. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have so many lovely friends and neighbors and I wish I had more time to spend. –Poo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>