<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Pushes Back In Court To Defend The Legality Of The New Travel Order https://t.co/KRAbuHsG5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DREAMer Should Not Be Released While Detention Challenge Proceeds, Judge Recommends https://t.co/uTXgJqe1DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breitbart Is A Player In This Paul Ryan-White House Drama https://t.co/tWOIt6vlYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Felony Charge Looming, Inauguration Day Arrestees Make Early Moves To Get Cases Dismissed https://t.co/8YOIaULlNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half Of All US Attorneys Were Asked To Resign Last Week. What About The Rest? https://t.co/ASPzOinScq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington State Pushes For Tuesday Hearing To Halt Enforcement Of Trump's New Travel Order https://t.co/NTbAYJRwE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challengers Will Try To Stop Trump's New Travel Order This Week Before It Even Takes Effect https://t.co/o94zjzUARb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["None Of It Made Sense": Martin O'Malley's Long Year After Running For President https://t.co/HktJlz0HPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists Prepare To Battle Trump Over Immigrants' Use Of Public Benefits https://t.co/TvPHx2DheK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions Orders The Resignations Of Nearly Half Of The US Attorneys Across The Country https://t.co/cZu43U9AXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAA Defends Its Decision Not To Limit How Small Seats Can Be On Airplanes https://t.co/F3caTFYJ43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omarosa Manigault Is Very Powerful — And A Lot Of Black Republicans Don't Like It https://t.co/4qWmwQ7riO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darrensands: New feature on the effect of Omarosa — who is quite powerful — on the black conservative movement, which is in flux. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU Lawyer Files Ethics Complaint Against Jeff Sessions Over Russia Testimony https://t.co/crbBAOVrRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington State Attorney General Will Continue Challenge To Trump's Travel Orders https://t.co/fjEymRse7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Restaurant Owners Sue Trump, Saying His Hotel Has An Unfair Advantage https://t.co/R18N2HGWnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Super PAC Launches Anti-"Trumpcare" Campaign In Key States https://t.co/EZHnvXtImZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Top HUD Aide Will Join CNN As Contributor https://t.co/ZHawOiRLKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Won't Stop Execution Of Man Convicted In Murder-For-Hire Scheme https://t.co/DtTf0e0hLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii Will Challenge Trump's New Travel Order https://t.co/GKYm2n5x1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top DOJ Nominee Won’t Commit To Having An Outside Counsel Look Into Russian Influence https://t.co/yZ5bdKupCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Republican Says Poor People May Have To Choose Between An iPhone And Healthcare https://t.co/f9VwXlzP6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions Adds To His Senate Testimony In A Letter Acknowledging His Russian Contacts https://t.co/rNJOnhOdSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Will Not Hear Transgender Student's Case This Term https://t.co/mX5t4Npoc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Will Sign A New Travel Ban Today — Here's How It's Different From The First One https://t.co/LQXTe1o92q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arkansas Faces Challenges On Second Day Of Attempting To Carry Out Two Executions https://t.co/9Y2e8BYPpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Moore's Suspension As Alabama's Chief Justice Is Upheld By Alabama Supreme Court https://t.co/AMFI8Ocvjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday Arkansas Executions Are On Hold — But Others Could Proceed In Coming Days https://t.co/uix1SGgumI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arkansas Scheduled Eight Executions Over The Next Two Weeks — But All Are On Hold For Now https://t.co/9KuMAi3vg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House Is Preparing To Make A Move On The DC Federal Trial Court https://t.co/YZpdwL83AB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Inauguration Day Arrestees Pledge To Reject Any Plea Deal Offers From Prosecutors https://t.co/aGv51fvcdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Democrats Are Trying To Figure Out How To Do Local Races In The #Resistance Age https://t.co/V9t4OlQzm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department Says No To Funding Vote On Puerto Rican Statehood https://t.co/IWf5ZVwooC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill O'Reilly Is Running Out Of Friends https://t.co/ISbYb5OmEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Are Waiting For Trump's Help (Or Wrath) As Key State Races Get Going https://t.co/dxTPdr1Suo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolling Stone Settles With University Administrator Featured In Retracted Campus Rape Story https://t.co/UmAnRHdF69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s How The Bill O’Reilly Ad Boycott Affects Fox News https://t.co/ZAkvRtUDD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Federal Appeals Court Will Hear Travel Ban Arguments In May https://t.co/IwwxuH7EYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Justice Gorsuch https://t.co/peLSEJtolF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass Arrests On Inauguration Day Swept Up Journalists And Legal Observers — And Their Phones https://t.co/o9MXEi5hDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Organization Settles Lawsuit With Celebrity Chef José Andrés https://t.co/U7eFutOZ7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch Up On Some Of The Week's Top Stories By Listening To Our Podcast, No One Knows Anything https://t.co/m7fafrFKer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Badly Wants Pundits' Approval. TV Loves His Syria Strike. So What Comes Next? https://t.co/nxpnE7Fy5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Senate Has Confirmed Neil Gorsuch To The Supreme Court https://t.co/5Ri6gimxZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Sues Feds Over Attempt To Reveal Identity Behind @ALT_USCIS Account https://t.co/bnGVDk301P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside The Original Fake News Story https://t.co/fHxaCSRa1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Republicans Really Don’t Want Trump To Fire The Director Of Wall Street Critic CFPB https://t.co/MaoA2P8gwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Short Section In Neil Gorsuch's 2006 Book Appears To Be Copied From A Law Review Article https://t.co/PGVe3VTads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Appeals Court Rules In Favor Of Job Protections For Gay Workers https://t.co/wWc50ULDDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How “Auntie Maxine” Became A Meme — And The Hero Of The Anti-Trump Internet https://t.co/LF9WxZODPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House Revealed The Finances Of Trump’s Top Staff. Here Are Some Of The Key Disclosures. https://t.co/BgNWLX3hNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US Government Can Keep Videos Of Forced Feeding At Guantánamo Bay Secret https://t.co/URAGIOIjZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump Will Have To Work With The Senate, Including Democrats, To Get His Judges Confirmed https://t.co/AEgDIEUnUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says CNN Is Fake News — But That’s Where He Wants Surrogates https://t.co/rg8ze7ApOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Democrats Are Starting Their Own Groups To Work Outside Of The DNC https://t.co/VxGkASl33m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Won't Comment On Report That Trump Officials Helped Give Nunes Intel Reports https://t.co/b2CzATz2NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justices Consider Decades-Old DC Murder Case — With Possible Effect On Prosecutors Everywhere https://t.co/FcolUGXIWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House Thinks Black Lawmakers Could Be The Democrats Willing To Deal With President Trump https://t.co/EoLviZ9W06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DREAMer Detained For The Past Six Weeks Granted Release On Bond https://t.co/UxNLVxYt0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Rejects Texas' Standards For Deciding Intellectual Disability In Death Cases https://t.co/5OScWv3I47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump And America’s National Nervous Breakdown https://t.co/RAfFtM2Ff6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Extends A Hand To Hispanic Businesses — But Some Are Worried About What Happens Next https://t.co/MLgPmWnbhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department Defends Trump's Travel Ban As Being Within Trump's Authority https://t.co/Udjf5aVvTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Obamacare Will "Explode" After Replacement Fails In Congress https://t.co/wWRCDy3z4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NAACP Won't Renew Contract Of Its President And CEO https://t.co/U64eRgIfJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Problem At The Center Of The FBI Director Hiring Process https://t.co/Zn3LisRoUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators Want US Job Protections Before Expanding Foreign Workforce https://t.co/gJpXsBFcR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Safety Board Nominee: Employees "Just Can't Resist" Sharing Workplace Secrets https://t.co/RXtoRygQmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Flynn Not Complying With A Congressional Subpoena Doesn’t Mean He’ll Be Going To Jail https://t.co/DfxsvCfPWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Poll: Almost Half Of Young White Voters Disapprove Of President Trump https://t.co/h1lEaAzbmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Is Donald Trump Standing By Mike Flynn? https://t.co/mFF35cxDb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 Important Things About The Trump Admin You May Have Missed Amid All This Insanity https://t.co/u1H02oJ6IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trump Supreme Court Short-Lister Backs Up Sessions’ Latest Criminal Justice Move https://t.co/gpxq2jgYv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Few Likely Reasons Why People Aren’t Quitting At The White House https://t.co/8zD4l3zQ7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey America, Here's How To Impeach a President (If You Want to) https://t.co/3pPX371fz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When It Comes To James Comey, It’s Fox News Opinion Vs. Fox News News https://t.co/Pp5ZaPBTAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Inmate In Georgia Wants To Be Executed By A Firing Squad https://t.co/LHnjDhxVa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News Host Kimberly Guilfoyle In Talks To Possibly Replace Sean Spicer https://t.co/CCeP7JOH9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Launches New Political Group https://t.co/eBIjF0xLuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For The Second Time In Two Weeks, Judges Question Trump’s Travel Ban https://t.co/sENV6qYHHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Being A Woman Is Not A Preexisting Condition In The Republican Health Care Bill https://t.co/2K7wIoYAw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Chair Hires New CEO As Reorganization Begins https://t.co/YCSYp2vHm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds Of Angry Residents Take On Republican Congressman Over Health Care https://t.co/rswM5IJPnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Justice Department Won’t Say Whether Jeff Sessions Will Recuse From Any Part Of Hiring The Next FBI Director https://t.co/pao509QT3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Ruins Paul Ryan’s Big Tax Policy Day https://t.co/JOz3yEZCWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Things To Watch Now That President Trump Has Fired James Comey https://t.co/cF9Qb6J3MP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Black Democrats Want A Lot More From Tom Perez https://t.co/ddXL8plPVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Passion Of Ivanka Trump https://t.co/kAjXqmA03c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan Starts Tax Overhaul Push With Roundtables — And A Fundraiser https://t.co/F3QKxfhw8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU Sues Over Alleged Racial Discrimination By A Mississippi County Sheriff's Office https://t.co/5vCtPo2J1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House To Announce 10 Trump Nominees For The Federal Courts On Monday https://t.co/aSmtcsPrRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Scott Won't Comment On The Justice Department's Not Bringing Federal Charges In Louisiana https://t.co/CMKaw8I89P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People On Twitter Are Using #ThingsJesusNeverSaid After House Republicans Passed Their Health Care Plan https://t.co/5a9RIYk2zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Trump's Top Donor Try To Remake One Of The Biggest Conservative Groups? https://t.co/BwVreXCDVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Orders Georgia To Extend Voter Registration Deadlines In Special Election Runoff https://t.co/id4xem2Y0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Returns To Politics With A New Focus On The Grassroots https://t.co/CiCMXwJrEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Orleans Mayor: The Confederate Monuments Weren’t An Accurate Representation Of History https://t.co/dTdd3IjJX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Intellectually Disabled? Supreme Court Orders Alabama To Reconsider Death-Row Case https://t.co/YH4DzgmG28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ESPN Became A Conservative Cause https://t.co/zgNmRfWh2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Does Milk Play Into Our New Trade War With Canada? https://t.co/MIH0A6vU9i]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>