<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't make time; so those who waste the least, achieve the most. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausting is okay. It means you're in the game. You're on the way up and you're not on the way down. - Lee Rosen #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will work for a living but they'll die for recognition. - Lee Odden #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you make someone smile today? You've still got time. - Melissa Stewart #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes those who need it the most are inclined the least"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we have no identity apart from our jobs, we are truly vulnerable. - Dan Miller #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing more expensive than education is ignorance."
- Benjamin Franklin #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until you cross the bridge of your insecurities, you can't begin to explore your possibilities. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can go back and start a new beginning, but anyone can start today and make a new ending. - Maria Robinson #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we don't start, it's certain we can't arrive"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your friends will believe in your potential, your enemies will make you live up to it. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not all those who wander are lost" a line from the poem written by J. R. R. Tolkien for The Lord of the Rings. #johnbdeleo https://t.co/8HiWnwkXEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a choice. Optimism is a choice. Kindness is a choice. Giving is a choice. Respect is a choice. Choose wisely.- Vala Afshar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay committed to your decisions, but stay flexible in your approach. - Tony Robbins #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you aren't having fun creating content, you're doing it wrong.- Ann Handley #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to be big. You have to be remarkable. - Joe Pulizzi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating the mind without educating the heart is no education at all.- Aristotle #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best is the enemy of good. - Voltaire #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens. - Jimi Hendrix #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God heals, and the Doctor takes the Fees."
- Benjamin Franklin #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I quit now, I will be back to where I started, &amp; when I started I was desperately wishing to be where I am now. - Unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who passively accepts evil is as much involved in it as he
who helps to perpetrate it."
- Martin Luther King #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch your mouth: The language we use creates the reality we experience.-Michael Hyatt #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life will never improve unless you start making daily improvements. - Lewis Howes #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The few who do are the envy of the many who only watch"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life is short. You have no clue when this ride will end. Stay present and live fearlessly. - Brenden Dilley #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first and the best victory is to conquer self.”
- Plato #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the one who teaches other people how to treat you. What do you teach? - Chalene Johnson #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can a dollar buy these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can often change your circumstances by changing your attitude. - Eleanor Roosevelt #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey world! I just supported Acts 17 Apologetics on @Patreon, and you can too! Internet high-five? https://t.co/rrYvXJStZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The true sign of intelligence is not knowledge but
imagination.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To live a creative life, we must lose our fear of being wrong. - Joseph C. Pearce #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is not a destination, it's a journey"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't make time; so those who waste the least, achieve the most. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took Debbie to the hospital with chest pains. I couldn't contain my happiness that everything… https://t.co/BWJhOcVRgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you treat yourself sets the standard for how others will treat you. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Try not to become a man of success but a man of value.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing in communication is to hear what isn't being said. - Peter Drucker #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the works of C.S. Lewis! This is one of my favorites! Do you think this is all there is to life?  #johnbdeleo https://t.co/51XzVEvriT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all born ignorant, but one must work hard to remain stupid. - Benjamin Franklin #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no shortcuts to any place worth going. - Beverly Sills #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Unless you change how you are, you will always have what
you've got.”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no cosmetic for beauty like happiness. - Maria Mitchell #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I couldn't wait for success... so I went ahead without it."
- Jonathan Winters #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your talent deserves a voice! - @Meddleit #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life does not get better by chance, it gets better by change. - Jim Rohn #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not all those who wander are lost" a line from the poem written by J. R. R. Tolkien for The Lord of the Rings. #johnbdeleo https://t.co/qKS2Kv5xlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life is short. You have no clue when this ride will end. Stay present and live fearlessly. - Brenden Dilley #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G.K. Chesterton is one of my favorite authors, really love his book called Orthodoxy.  #johnbdeleo https://t.co/WEvU6DeEzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look for ideas to confirm your thinking, rather look for trends that will disrupt your thinking. - Rich Simmonds #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooper Lake! https://t.co/HAIg9L9Jux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little scenery from Cooper Lake today!

#nature #lake #amazing @ Salmon La Sac https://t.co/nLzMyfBFxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stint fishing with Matt and Zan at Cooper Lake today! Matt caught a 3.5 pounder!

#fish #fishon… https://t.co/pFwTYRUEkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went fishing with Matt and Zan at Cooper Lake!

#fish #fishon #lake #brothers #friends @ Salmon… https://t.co/Hqtfwz7CxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let today's opportunities become tomorrow's what ifs. - Pat Flynn #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating the mind without educating the heart is no education at all.- Aristotle #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others you give up your power to change. Take responsibility for your future! - Chris Voss #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather live with a good question than a bad answer.- Aryeh Frimer #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The forecast for Ellensburg! Winter is coming!

#snow #cold #icy #notready @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/hFHZFrl40w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are the only one who can use your ability. It is an
awesome responsibility"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to be big. You have to be remarkable. - Joe Pulizzi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is easy to get to the top after you get through the crowd at
the bottom"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your creative juices flow and don't be afraid to take chances! - Joel Comm  #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrylRealistic @betrendsetters @CPI_Results]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotter done again today. 

#exercise #walkabout #walk #freshair #autumn @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/mCZ1djvbrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiration doesn't respond to meeting requests. You can’t schedule greatness - Jay Baer #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausting is okay. It means you're in the game. You're on the way up and you're not on the way down. - Lee Rosen #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to risk going too far to discover just how far you can really go. -Jim Rohn #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Positive thinking won't let you do anything, but it will let you
do everything better than negative thinking will"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live simply. Dream big. Be grateful. Give love. Laugh lots. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Jesus, gotter done again today!

#10000steps #freshair #walkabout #exercise @ Historic… https://t.co/itCNqPlWCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indifference is expensive. Hostility is unaffordable. Trust is priceless. It's all about Relationships. - Ted Rubin #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If winning isn't everything, why do they keep score?"
- Vince Lombardi #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so busy I don't know whether I found a rope or lost my horse. - Mark Schaefer #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability is a poor man's wealth."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody who ever gave their best regretted it. - George Halas #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotter done again today!

#10000steps #walk #exercise @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/tsY7OatSN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many pictures! Out for a walk down by theYakima river!

#walkabout #warmth #autumn #beauty @… https://t.co/DqOBvfDojq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening, not imitation, may be the sincerest form of flattery. - Dr. Joyce Brothers #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Determine never to be idle... It is wonderful how much may
be done if we are always doing.”
- Thomas Jefferson #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't pass your values on to your kids, someone else will. - Frank Sonnenberg #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have courage. It clears the way for things that need to be. - Laura Fitton #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom begins with owning your flaws and disowning your fears. - Umair Hague #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotter done, 10,000 steps today! It helps that it's a beautiful day in the 'Burg!

#10000steps… https://t.co/D4W06d0Ghg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My walk around the 'Burg today. What a glorious day!

#warm #walkabout #nature #beauty @ Iron… https://t.co/qPGundhGfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nodding the head does not row the boat. - Irish Proverb #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The soil says, "Don’t bring me your need. Bring me your
seed."
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious. - Albert Einstein #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you would create something, you must first become
something.”
- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything from your past does not belong in your present. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistently investigate what gives other people energy. Be the fan that fuels it. - Darren Rowse #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every exit is an entry somewhere else. -Tom Stoppard #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't exercise your freedom of speech until you have exercised your freedom of thought. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who passively accepts evil is as much involved in it as he
who helps to perpetrate it."
- Martin Luther King #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell more people that you love them. You never know how much they might need it. - Chris Brogan #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have courage. It clears the way for things that need to be. - Laura Fitton #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is the end result of all true learning.- Leo Buscaglia #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you choose today will determine who you are tomorrow. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>