<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My glasses frame broke. Im blind.. like seriously, I cant see anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone out there who knows how to put together a pre' decent music video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai We are totally having this party! Not sure when but it WILL happen!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai is so awesome!! #Pocky #AllDayEveryday http://t.co/qXys5eTZeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one wants to watch a movie with me :( #SadLifeSoSad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my first Christmas remix!! ---&gt; https://t.co/U0cN9iafFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai bout time. It's been like a month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we were on the radio today =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @passion268 coming to Vancouver in 2014?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never trust Shauna when skateboarding....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopped by Starbucks after meeting Best's Prayer Group. Thaaanks Karina!! http://t.co/fdhcWyPImC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai it's otaaaays. When's the next time your free? Apparently Jeff only comes if you come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only @TheManlySamurai would say "hab pun sinigang" instead of "Have fun singing" #LifeOfCamille #filipinoproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Im headed somewhere after practice which might take til 4. So we can party after 4 if you still has time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had a jam session with the broo. Im probs going to record a session and post it on YouTube soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai What time you getting picked up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I wish but Ms Baker wants the choir to stay after school to practice for our performance on friday. so cant =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to get on skype more often....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I failed my physics test... Well as long im getting at least 73% in the class, I should be fine... I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One side of my hair is curly and the other side is straight....  Not sure how I manage to style my hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my remix is done. Exporting right now and will submit it to the contest soon. Will be on soundcloud maybe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craving sushi... Can someone bring meeh some?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a job already. I need to save up for them DJ equipment.. Why you companies no hire me?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Im planning on what equipment to get next and Im thinking of getting a DJ. Now should I go for Vinyl or CDJ? #DJ #Vinyl #CDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my cousin's house got totally destroyed. Thank God they're safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elyonworship I waaaant!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 1 of 4, of my creation of the "Hark The Herald Remix". 3 more days 'til I have to submit it to the contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hair's starting to grow longer, Im thinking of getting a new hairstyle....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to do these challenges with the group one day...  http://t.co/6hmvJ9qisD @TheManlySamurai @VincentAraujo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I spend too much time changing shoelaces..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its actually really nice to relax for one night. Listening to some music and playing games on my iPod. #ReallyNice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeannePineda of course! Its your best feature!! Haha. Plus I've always talked bout your height, I ain't stopping!!! MWAHAHAHA #BestBroEvaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good talk with @JeannePineda. Missed my (Short) lil' sister. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to be working an a Christmas remix for the next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pink blanket #LifeOfBen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DJTRIUNE: It's crazy how a lot of Christians are too scared to be a light in a dark place, instead, they'd rather be a light in a lit p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plans for the month of November: Work on the Capital Kings remix and do a bunch of covers if I have the time. #NoProcrastinating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai @VincentAraujo you should send me the video ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is how I spent my evening..... Working on music.... Well at least I have the whole month of… http://t.co/wEELm62Zm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Did you actually take a video of the dance battle between meeh and @VincentAraujo ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: Its been awhile since I uploaded a song so here is a new one before I get busy again with remix... http://t.co/6ElXDnFT5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that I uploaded a song, its time to work on the Capital Kings remix!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its been awhile since my last upload but here is a new song! https://t.co/QEnby459Gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Living Water http://t.co/reyKzTfApV on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uploading a new song right now. 43% at the moment... =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna do a cover of Oceans from @hillsongunited soo baad!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Ill think about it ;) Its okaay, you aint the only one in daat situation. #CakeForEverone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hate french class right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai This kid....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that my @therealtobymac mix is getting a bunch of plays on SC is amzing! Almost 1k plays! Thanks guys!! &lt;3 https://t.co/X6zb9tNrpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tothekidswho: here's to the kids who love sleeping because its the only time they don't feel stress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's between you and God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got my Arizona, now its time to do some work. http://t.co/VFCtwQgJk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Just had some good beef steak... No big deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MatthewParker2: Reason is more logical than Logic. AHHHH C WUT I DID THERE???? #woah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 hours of french homework... 
Im.. Finally.. Done.. 
HA NOOPE!! I STILL NEED TO DO THAT FRENCH BAKING PROJECT!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent the whole day so far doing my french projects. Good thing there was no school today or else I'd be very busy for the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VincentAraujo what are we supposed to do for the 3 question video project? When is it due?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 french projects... Lets do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ms. Baker gave me a solo for choir today. Well that my second solo for choir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai #TheTruth #LifeOfTheParty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai We'll see about the smoothie... But I owe you for sure. :) We shall discuss in tutorial tomorrooow!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Seriously?! Weeeeell the project is: I need to describe a person and explain how we met, etc. I also need photos. You in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai This kid... Since you want to help me on this project, you should help me on my other french project too! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to do NLS soon.. Gotta be a lifeguard by summertime so I can earn some money...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai are you serious!!! He's making us make cookies with french recipes for Halloween as a project...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked God for strength, and God gave me difficulties to make me strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressful week... Hope its over soon #Tired #EndOfTerm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Is Sellam making you bake cookies for a project in french?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying a cup of hot chocolate from Ellie. =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai DEAL!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Can i call you rudolph?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 concerts done, 1 more this week and 4 more next week.. Leeeego dooo this!!! #SuperSaiyanMode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my photography work... ---&gt; https://t.co/bB4i04wFaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai We need to do this!!! I agree that we all push Jepp down the hill..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still thinking about taking a friend's advice of DJin' for school dances next year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai WE BETTER!! We need to bring Yuxin and JEPP!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai PLEASE POLLOW ME! *SLAP* I MEAN POLLOW ME NOT PALO ME!!  Join a sport or something already -______- #YourUmbrellaIsLonely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Duuude! Ive been watching filipino vines for about an hour now... heeeelp meee!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Deem Filipino parents.
https://t.co/C9i0vobxk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should go on skype more often...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My desk setup is finally done!! http://t.co/F11lJ4n7Iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DJRavine: This is how my day went. Wake up 10am psyched to be productive. Open Ableton. Start project. Reddit. *BLANK*. Time is now 4pm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @SwedRevolution for winning the @CapitalKingsUSA remix contest! GG!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duck faces and lip bites w/ Asumi and John. Typical physics class.. #NoBigDeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stand in the rain
stand your ground
stand up when it's all crashing down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish Revolution commented on my Capital Kings remix! #HappyDance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I re-uploaded my remix due to some weird key changes with the track and the vocals.. Anyways... https://t.co/mv1kqHRPCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Capital Kings - Be There (12th Son Of Jacob Remix) http://t.co/qcq6Dk6SgC on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#KuyaAteMoment @lqianoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I was gathering all my stuff from my old room to move to my new room and... yeaah that's the mess. http://t.co/QOXz18Jm77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got home from biblestudy. Learned a lot today =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Capital Kings - Be There (12th Son Of Jacob Remix) http://t.co/3KmtWjIFl5 on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally finished the music for Shauna. Next up is to finish the @CapitalKingsUSA remix!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for another Christmas remix contest! Will be working on it soon so stay tuned in about 2-3 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally started working on the music for Shauna's animation project. Good progress, should be done tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once im done with tomorrow, my week will be pre' chill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still working on homework... I can do this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Filipino_probs: Even if you don't think Pacquiao is the best boxer to ever live, you gotta admit he's the most humble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Too far brooo, too far...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>