<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevematthews: Harrison Pensa’s Website Among Lawyerist Award Finalists http://t.co/xohqeOXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_bilinsky: Twitter joins "Do Not Track" http://t.co/QsUZgQCd Where is facebook??? #BCLegal #lpm #privacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done, Tony! doRT @BoughtonLaw: Tony Wilson discusses language to be wary of in franchise deals:... http://t.co/gvq4CtXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Disrder in Amer Crts": A: Do u no if yer daughter has been inv in voodoo? W: We both do. A: Voodoo? W: We do. A: You do? W: Yes, voodoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another from Disorder in Amer. Courts: ATTORNEY: Were u present when your picture was taken? WITNESS: Are you shi**ing me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual testimony frm book Disorder in American Courts: ATTORNEY: What gear were you in at moment of impact? WITNESS: Gucci sweats + Reeboks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAD! RT @WoodfordCKNW980: Retird #Kitsilano #coastguard Commander F.Moxey tells @billgood980 lives will be lost if station closed #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should the media publish the home address of a women on house arrest? Esp when it's reported she'll be there alone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoughtonLaw: Fred Lee reviews the Guys &amp; Dolls performance for The Lawyer Show, a fundraiser for... http://t.co/8fWZIk9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buried in Van LMA HELM submissions of best legal marketing in BC. Privileged to be judging. Tough competition! #bclegal #solosmall #lma #in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McQuarrieHunter: Wade now on stage at Hyack Festival! http://t.co/chiyLUSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McQuarrieHunter: They even hung our banner straight at the New West Hyack Festival! http://t.co/nFbRWCaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read Obama's LinkedIn page. Two things surprised me: we're only two connections apart! Ha! And secondly, he has no recommendations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold- star day at Cypress mtn today! http://t.co/32cNOLGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool!!!!"@PattyMC22: Really enjoyed meeting the Honourable @pmharper - an honour indeed! http://t.co/1JoFSRFX"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Counsel_Network: Newest Opportunity: Legal Director - Category : In-House CounselLocation/City :  SK - Prince Albert LEGAL DIRECTOR( ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MayansOfficial: Well...this is awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant MT "@blockersave93: Perfect rebuttal 2 NRA's preposterous stance. RT @robdelaney .@NRA Look @ what @davidfrum tweeting right now."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilRiddell: Vernon lawyer who represented Greeks is the first in Canada to plead guilty to working for a criminal organization http ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@MonishaMartins: MT @goldsbie: Superior Crt (Ont) says "media or journalists" may tweet frm crtrm: http://t.co/UcU4djTG (@SunReporterYuen)"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: The RCH Foundation is seeking a Stewardship Officer. If you're interested in this position check our site for more i ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @atlblog: What's more entertaining than a law firm rejection letter riddled with typos? One that's from a Biglaw firm! http://t.co/HC ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MT @MonishaMartins: #portmann = #epicfail" = #PRdisaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawsonLundell: Designating common-law spouses as #pension beneficiaries crucial after landmark Ontario court ruling http://t.co/HC1F ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another partial tree down + thru a fence. Pac press photog taking own pic (out of frame) nearby. http://t.co/4niQnHxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great day to be a dog! http://t.co/J2UcyVfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear! No injuries or broken windows, but city crews very busy near 19th + Manitoba at 2 diff corners. http://t.co/V4vP675O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bea-U-tiful! ;) MT @CindyZheng: Just got my picture @McQuarrieHunter ...What do you think? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @terrybecker: Tx to @citypittmeadows public wrks 4 clearing our rds north of Lougheed tonite-much appreciated! Snow + ice = treacherous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx for the RT Gayle. RT @ghkcole: RT @lawyerPR: Is it possible to hug a town? Together let's try. #Connecticut #HugNewtown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo - tx, buddy RT @CainesArcade: Sending a hug to Newtown from all of us. #HugNewtown http://t.co/FdPeINGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx for the RT, Jack. RT @stansburyj: RT @lawyerPR: Is it possible to hug a town? Together let's try. #Connecticut #HugNewtown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd forgotten the beauty of that song. Tx! RT @GLEN_MICH: Bridge Over Troubled Waters https://t.co/agVlfuTJ #HugNewtown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE IT! RT @NicoleDevos: RT @imagination: Sending a hug to Newtown from Caine's Arcade #HugNewtown http://t.co/WNIiHUqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to all who are helping #HugNewtown.  Keep the RTs going until we've surrounded them. #Connecticut #newtown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbeese: The Legal Marketing Association has an outstanding line up of speakers and forums for next year's annual... http://t.co/oZLxAcas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Our Bundle of Joy contest ends next week! If you know someone who gave birth at RCH encourage them to get involved!  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible to hug a town? Together let's try. #Connecticut #HugNewtown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise advice, Heather RT @heather_morse: For those with set auto posts, I'd check to see what is in your queue for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! Congrats, Simon! MT @BullHousser: Bull Housser's Managing Partner, Simon Margolis, appointed Queen’s Counsel http://t.co/wmeQNHRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dougmollenhauer Thanks, Doug!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddleink Boy, will we miss your Last Word, indeed. Sigh. Just keep on writing, my friend. Anything. Really. We'll keep reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beckerlawyers: North Fraser Estate &amp; Succession Planning Group #bclegal http://t.co/9IMDV8dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktweedy long overdue! Just finally caught up on twitter admin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accountability + honesty matters RT @lubelluledotcom: @lawyerPR Quebec, run ovr yr politicians please!  Please sign: http://t.co/xKHTFGNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure ARE! Tx 4 noticing! RT @Dani7220: @lawyerPR - Thanks for the productive meeting today! Things are heading in an exciting direction:-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to wear!? MT @staciriordan: OMG!  I was invited to speak at #Brazil's 2nd annual #FashionLaw symp. today! #grateful Who's been to #Rio?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your lawyers are on social media - greater chance of attracting a reporter 4 comment (yes, this is gd).  Do u have a media policy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinaschenbren You had the perfect mix, Kev. Not too dry ... just 'melt in your mouth' perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better yet, what they *feel*  RT @unmarketing: Your logo isn't your brand. What someone thinks when they see your logo, that's your brand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bclawwatch: Upcoming Event: South Asian Bar Association of BC Conference: Via Dye &amp; Durham’s Industry News service,... http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinaschenbren You bet! You may be doing more of the same this weekend too, no? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matwilcox: I travel...a lot. The Fairmont Pacific Rim hotel in Vancouver is by far one of the best hotels for service in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just "whipped up" by a master MT @kevinaschenbren: New blog post: Lessons from the KitchenAid Twitter mishap. http://t.co/3MDP7ySe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinokeefe: How to get social media buy in from lawyers - RLHB http://t.co/x0QGptv9 h/t @amyjomartin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holdencalgary No kidding? What a talent. Cheering her on from Vancouver!! Go Lyndsey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holdencalgary Beautiful voice. She's an Adele look-alike!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @holdencalgary: "I want to put a ding in the universe" - Steve Jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zellers' marketing swan song took risks + won. Brand revealed too late? Death bed irony.  @globeandmail http://t.co/1shq9qDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a heart-warming moment (or a good laugh) at TG dinner ask your kids to share  what they are grateful for. Could be insightful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT the ..?"@theprovince: Oops: New Orleans lawyer arrested after joint falls from pocket in court http://t.co/2kUfHHp0"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinaschenbren: New blog post: Lessons from the KitchenAid Twitter mishap. http://t.co/9zjbK2xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CLEBC: If you didn't receive our Fall Calendar in your email inbox this morning, view it online here: 
http://t.co/VT97Xxp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lesson! RT @seanmcginnis: KitchenAid Handles Offensive Tweet Crisis Extraordinarily Well http://t.co/LtHNLW51 via @ginidietrich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erindermer Must find legit reason to write "boondoggle" or "kanoodling" in a media release ..unlikely in law-related release! One can hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoughtonLaw: Boughton is currently hiring for a Business Development Coordinator. Apply before September 28th:... http://t.co/SB56Zf05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoughtonLaw: Got a burning legal question? Ask one of our lawyers @SmallBusinessBC's next Ask The Expert: Lawyer session on Oct 16:  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @erindermer One of my favs: "Kanoodling" as uttered by a brit lawyer. Go on, someone find a use for that one on @cbcradio or @cknw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone tired of talking about the magnificent Vancouver weather yet? Note to self: water the garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh! RT @FaskenMartineau: http://t.co/weuavZ7A is now back on line, thanks for your patience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mcquarriehunter must b thrilled! DT @BellePuri: #RCHsupporter on CKNW #DonationDay at hospital raises quarter million dollars! Thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!! RT @BellePuri: #RCHsupporter on CKNW #DonationDay at hospital raises quarter million dollars! Thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @Elliottmarkc via RT @sallyschmidt via @ShumatePR - offering exclusives to media is risky. I'd say proceed cautiously, if at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelDC  Perhaps it is just in the tone, but I often wonder about purpose for screening. Clients don't often want the annce self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCKNW980: #Breaking Golden Ears bridge now shut down to traffic in both directions due to #PortKells fire &amp; explosion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me? When calling a law firm, it's unfriendly when asked to identify yourself to recptn/asst. Do u mind call-screening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL! RT @sallyschmidt: Just saw one of my LinkedIn connections added a new skill: Misconduct. Thinking it means employment law but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Our time on @CKNW is now over, but the phone lines will stay open until 5PM today. Call 310-4000 to donate - no area ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @CanLawMag announces top 10 BC/Alta firms. Congrats to all 10!  Long live regional firms! http://t.co/wZ1tMgMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RJOHNSONCorp: Now hiring! Senior Family LAA – West Coast Specialty Firm http://t.co/OROTqcz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RJOHNSONCorp: Apply today! Intermediate Litigation LAA: Downtown #Vancouver Specialty Boutique Firm http://t.co/mpj8erTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many ways 2 handle crisis MT @WoodfordCKNW980: John #Furlong refusing media interviews ... yet on his website to "set the record straight."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royal Columbian Hosp needs you! Call 310-4000 to donate to the @royalcolumbian! #RCHsupporter #donationday #cknw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shout out 2 our client services mgr Danielle, who is lurking under a pseudonym on twitter (Sorry, couldn't resist!). Pls welcome her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks smashing! "@ThreePinkDots: Love my dad's getup for the Downton Abbey finale. bethbteel… http://t.co/Tld5tMwj"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL "@benjy: For god's sake people, it׳s DownTON Abbey. "Downtown Abbey" sounds like the name of a big-city prostitute."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasmineDecarie: Tips 1-4 in this article http://t.co/HDLRu4dJ underscore why lawyers can be twitter challenged via @AnnTran_ #LMAMKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not ideal conditions at #whistler today, but hey, it's still a day on the slopes! http://t.co/f87nU73p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lawheadhunter: Lawyers earn $66.6 million fee in one of largest class action cases in Canada. #lawnews  http://t.co/OEKyDGNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasmineDecarie: Always remember there is no "Do-Over" button on the internet: Search Engines Never Forget http://t.co/rpvhaTFV by @h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoughtonLaw: Boughton Law is hiring a full-time Network Administrator. If you think you've got what it takes to join our IT... http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox  Sheesh.. that hasn't stopped some others :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! MT @SabineEckardt: Imp reminder frm @lawyerPR today that markters are more thn brochure bunnies #lma #providingvalue #marketing #BCLegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gd live tweeting, DB! RT @david_bilinsky: Susan Van Dyke: Great client service translates to loyalty and referrals. #CLEBC #LPM #BCLegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! RT @david_bilinsky: S.Van Dyke: Ideas/experiences that are remarkable will spread + make gd convrstn + delight us.  #BCLegal #CLEBC #LPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_bilinsky: Susan Van Dyke: Quality in a service is not what you put into it. It is what the client gets out of it.  Peter Druck ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats! "@NKEllison: Oh yes! Client just increased their marketing budget by 50% due to increase business from our social ads campaign."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @news1130traffic: 7:00pm - PATTULLO BRIDGE - CLOSED in both directions due to a police incident. Use the Queensborough or Port Mann a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jkcallas: B2B Marketers: LinkedIn Launching Sponsored Posts http://t.co/aLFMWv4z via @ShellyKramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RachelLaing: She was just trying to make it classy! RT @lawyerist: Woman fined for bedazzling her court-ordered ankle monitor http:/ ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>