<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["If death meant just leaving the stage long enough to change costume and come back as a new character, would you slow down? Or speed up?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we call chaos is just patterns we haven't recognized. What we call random is just patterns we can't decipher."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lower you fall, the higher you'll fly."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7FwHZpP7YR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not like you anymore. I don't need to brag about my pain."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: I see what you did there, @chuckpalahniuk. 
#BeautifulYou http://t.co/gYlEucRDlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need to rebel against myself. It's the opposite of following your bliss. I need to do what I most fear."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/2gSBKgua1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't know what you want, you end up with a lot you don't."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your past is just a story. And once you realize this it has no power over you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WelshIrvine: @PalahniukQuote @chuckpalahniuk You'd have to find it first and there wouldn't be enough to nourish a house fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant. http://t.co/d0sSUXdIo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot be the person they know and the great, glorious person you want to become. Not at the same time."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is partly suspicious with chances of betrayal."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club http://t.co/Kxwr4fPNyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe you don't go to hell for the things you do. Maybe you go to hell for the things you don't do. The things you don't finish."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The girl's lover was gone, but his shadow was still there."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is the world we live in. Conditions change and we mutate."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I suppose it’s comfort, perhaps a sense of self-control, doing worse things to yourself than the world will ever dare inflict."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can spend your whole life building a wall of facts between you and anything real."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Don’t ask. #tbt http://t.co/vyVqAtWKxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More and more everything in my life was a fix for an earlier fix for an earlier fix until I forget what the original problem was."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes. Working jobs we hate, so we can buy shit we dont need."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As far as regret, I think that's the sign of a well lived life. If I grew old without having regrets, I'd regret my caution."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without pain, without sacrifice we would have nothing. Like the first monkey shot into space."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This isn't about guilt or innocence. The dinosaurs weren't morally good or bad, but they're all dead."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At this rate, we'll never get to the future."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's the best revenge of all: happiness. Nothing drives people crazier than seeing someone having a good fucking life."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TylerD81: http://t.co/i3OgaK2QRw Chuck Palaniuck in Brighton: Q&amp;A, Reading, 35mm #fightclub, THANKS @chuckpalahniuk!!! @PalahniukQuote …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone smiles with that invisible gun to their head."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Palahniuk &amp; Chelsea Cain on the Doomed Tour. http://t.co/iPCOa9akNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Hell, you'd be foolish to count on people displaying high standards of honesty. The same goes for earth."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hysteria is impossible without an audience. Panicking by yourself is the same as laughing alone in an empty room. You feel really silly."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I really wanted to put a bullet between the eyes of every endangered panda that wouldn't screw to save it's species." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haunted Fan Art.  #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/NY29X8hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's not wearing makeup so her face just looks like skin." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Isn't a kid alive who doesn't dream about rewarding her folks, or punishing them." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doesn't reincarnation strike you as just another form of procrastination?" - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Patrick Bateman is 18, a claw-hammer, a hatchet, various syringes, a 14 year-old girl, a bathtub, muffled screams,  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote from Choke. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/DTW66nGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will always have some excuse not to live your life." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world will always punish the few people with special talents the rest of us don't recognize as real." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think that I shall never see a poem as lovely as a hot-gushing, butt-cramping, gut-hosing orgasm." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Adventure without risk is Disneyland." - Douglas Coupland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ballad for our revolution turned into background music for a television commercial." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyler &amp; Marla #FightClub Art http://t.co/P9q9ZvhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where we're standing right now, in the ruins in the dark, what we build could be anything." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These stories are ghosts, bringing people back from the dead. Just for a moment. Just for a visit. Every story is a ghost." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Someone just asked me if it bothers me that my work is disparaged as sexist among critics. It doesn't. Because all  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote from Choke #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/GdeyN5yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I spent my life attacking everything because I was too afraid to risk creating anything." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What people forget is a journey to nowhere starts with a single step too." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Getting fired is the best thing that could happen to any of us. That way, we'd quit treading water and do something with our lives." - F.C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: "I just can't follow Bret Easton Ellis anymore. He's so pretentious that I hate myself for following him." Hey GENE ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change me. I can be thin with big breasts and big hair. Take me apart. Make me into anything, but just love me." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shannon from Invisible Monsters #ChuckPalahniuk Art http://t.co/N3x99p0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's funny how the beauty of art has so much more to do with the frame than the artwork itself." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I might be a touch of a sadist and a little bit jejune... but at least I'm not a victim, not any longer." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your heart is my pinata" #InvisibleMonsters http://t.co/fnnmPeN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a shallow bitch. But a physically superior, near-perfect-looking shallow bitch. And that can override anything. -Bret Easton Ellis, AP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Wow.  RT @31_julz: #marla 1st session w/ @MFShadowink #iamjacksbrokenheart #tattoo  #ink  @HelenaBC_  @chuckpalahniu ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to give up! You have to realize that someday you will die. Until you know that, you are useless!" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How can you possibly believe he really loves you?... You have no choice... If you need to be loved." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's pretty much how we get through our own lives, watching television. Smoking crap. Self-medicating. Redirecting our attention." -Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I need is a new story about who I am. What I need to do is fuck up so bad I can't save myself." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Palahniuk Quote... http://t.co/husJdlve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jlturpen: And often paid for RT @methadrone13 
"A book is as private and consensual as sex." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A book is as private and consensual as sex." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: In the cold LA night Bateman keeps whispering: "You thought you got rid of me, Bret?...But you didn't...I'm still h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harold_smith: @methadrone13 I accept that and raise you http://t.co/TiGsdzFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damned By: Chuck Palahniuk Art http://t.co/eM4WeK5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can watch much television, then being dead will be a cinch." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're only supporting characters in the lives of each other." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Long-term, we're all going to die. Then our bodies will rot. No surprise there. Short-term, we're going to live happily ever after."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters Art http://t.co/b6jOmNFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Picture anybody growing up so stupid that he didn't know hope was just another phase you'll grow out of." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ask yourself: What did I eat for breakfast today? What did I eat for dinner last night? You see how fast reality fades away?" - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marla Singer. The big tourist... #FightClub http://t.co/5J8W39co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is evil something you are? Or is it something you do?" - Bret Easton Ellis, American Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters Quote http://t.co/pl5sD27G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The truth is, immigrants tend to be more American than people born here." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FightClub http://t.co/Axd5LmA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes, working jobs we hate, so we can buy shit we don't need." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody looks a little crazy if you're looking close enough. And if you can't look that close, then you don't really love them." -Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only when we eat up this planet will God give us another. We will be remembered more for what we destroy than what we create." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot be the person they know and the great, glorious person you want to become. Not at the same time." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dreams don't come true. Dreams die. Dreams end up dealing meth in a booth at the back of the Olive Garden. Dreams get spleen cancer." -D.C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted to destroy everything beautiful I'd never have." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel my heart ache, but I've forgotten what that feeling means." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lucky ones are just born dead." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was simply imitating reality, a rough resemblance of a human being, with only a dim corner of my mind functioning." - Bret Easton Ellis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are these things really better than the things I already have? Or am I just trained to be dissatisfied with what I have now?" - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only person we'll hate more than each other is ourselves." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Everyone please go out and VOTE today. Make your voice heard. If you don't know where your polling place is, go here ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is static. Everything is evolving. Everything is falling apart." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: "Why don't you have anything positive to say?" whines a member of Generation Wuss while petting her cat and listeni ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without access to true chaos, we'll never have true peace. Unless everything can get worse, it won't get any better." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe we have to break everything to make something better out of ourselves." - Fight Club]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>