<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s the teaser trailer for Niantic’s Pokémon GO-style Harry Potter game: The good news: Niantic/WB Games/Portkey has released a trailer for “Wizards Unite,” the Harry Potter game built in the same spirit as Pokémon GO. The bad news: It… doesn’t show… https://t.co/6zu9RkfeKC https://t.co/db9Hhl8JTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Full Stack: Role: Full Stack Developer Location: Norwich Type: Permanent Salary: Competitive salary with great benefits including wind down Fridays! Full Stack Developer required to join the AI delivery team for this cutting edge… https://t.co/So36Asq8OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penetration Tester – Central Belt Travel Only: A UK consultancy with an office in Edinburgh is looking for a penetration tester to join them. The core geographic area of work that you’ll be assigned to will be the central belt of Scotland, so you should… https://t.co/3MunGH13O1 https://t.co/OjrZZ4BwlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon did exactly what it should have with its HQ2 process: I love my colleague Jon Shieber, he’s a great guy. But his arguments against Amazon’s HQ2 process are just wrong, and are part of an increasingly poisonous atmosphere around employment growth… https://t.co/s5HRLXaneV https://t.co/syKbSpHsYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full stack Developer – South Yorkshire: Full Stack Developer – South Yorkshire My client is a growing engineering firm looking for a mid-level Full Stack Developer who enjoys working autonomously and is not afraid of a challenge. You will be joining… https://t.co/uiYeDV2LRI https://t.co/wWnUPBKwWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Specialist / Developer: 2 Week Short Term Contract Sickness cover with possibility of rolling and becoming perm SQLSpecialist / Database Developer Large manufacturing company Fylde Coast circa £16 per hour Angus James Recruitment Ltd is currently… https://t.co/FJYJd1A3u7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynd announces a new air purifier and desktop monitor: As far as goals for hardware startups go, you could do worse than ridding the air of allergens, pollutants and the like. Launched in 2016 as a Kickstarter project, Wynd is going back to the… https://t.co/jVnua2LsI3 https://t.co/6PT1l3tJdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Deployment Engineer: Optical Deployment Engineer My client, a global powerhouse within the Social Media industry, is looking for an Optical Deployment Engineer to join their team in London on a 11 month contract. Duties: * Deploy, configure, and… https://t.co/cynfol7PA8 https://t.co/C9xdPtAa5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan GDP: Natural disasters hit economic growth https://t.co/MC8ufX546P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Ugly' mistake sends Google data to China https://t.co/oC1YlCrKsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Tooling Lead: Service Tooling Lead Location: Farnborough Rate: £450 – £550 per Day Duration: 6 Months SC Clearance required due to client site Job Description: The client seeks a tooling specialist to work under the direction of the Solution… https://t.co/CvCZUCxsaD https://t.co/IFNJh3EJbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: I am currently looking a Security cleared/Security clearable DevOps Engineer to join a fantastic team based in Basingstoke. You will be responsible for ensuring all of the cogs continue to turn, fix any bugs &amp; take ownership of the suite… https://t.co/vDfcNSiXpJ https://t.co/xT0iLhDQJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Withings launches a fitness tracker for some reason: Withings is back with, of all things, a fitness tracker. It’s a bit of an odd addition, two months after the company re-launched, post-Nokia. The company’s first product, the Steel HR Sport, picked up… https://t.co/HkyuMCqEeS https://t.co/FR3LTWPsvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .Net Technical Lead – Waterford: C# .Net Technical Lead – Waterford How would you like to take ownership of a new and exciting C# .Net FinTech application that is highly anticipated on a global scale? I’m working with a forward-thinking Technology… https://t.co/H4of8VdZXH https://t.co/nUolxtoVPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Co-ordinator/Administrator: Experienced Project Co-ordinator/Administrator required for a large technology deployment project. Experience in Windows 10 and/or o365 is an advantage but not essential: Key skills: * Experience in assisting Project… https://t.co/lfSOscXAba https://t.co/Og86TWD0iA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer: Net Developer Location – Deeside Salary £30,000pa Currently looking for a .Net Developer with a couple of years experience and is looking for their next step in their career. My client is a well-known UK brand with a development team of… https://t.co/BCpVlgFdU1 https://t.co/WNbUCzf78b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators urge FTC to look into shady ad practices in apps for kids: For us jaded adults, the long-running trend toward making apps and games free to download but stuffing them with paid options is just an annoyance or perhaps a logical progression of the… https://t.co/XaDWNubie7 https://t.co/eHgk08rHXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: DBA- Cambridge- Finance- Permanent- £40k-£50k I am working with one of our longest standing financial clients based in Cambridge to help them build their data management and database teams. They are currently looking for a DBA to… https://t.co/prTr0eDIKX https://t.co/xDRYPmktNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Support Officer: Umbrella rate: £13.00 Per Hour Working on behalf of a Local Authority, Aatom Recruitment has an excellent opportunity for an experienced ICT Support Officer on a 3 months contract with a possibility of an extension. Purpose of the… https://t.co/OyCDlPOPQj https://t.co/8RbDdlQN9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lime is debuting its line of shareable vehicles in Seattle this week: Lime will introduce "LimePods" in California in 2019. https://t.co/slvPNkrdoi https://t.co/OrW5iLqjH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Licensing Operations Specialist: Licensing Operations Specialist Thames Valley Park, Reading Contract is 18 months Brook Street is currently working on behalf of our Global IT Client to recruit a Licensing Operations Specialist. This is a contract role… https://t.co/bTlGs8YdYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Chorley: Java Developer – Chorley Agile, JSP, MVC, HTML, JQUERY, Tomcat, TDD This well-established software solutions provider are looking to add a Java developer to join their talented development team based in Lancashire. This diverse… https://t.co/6RwhOJVOCI https://t.co/Ggz8Qc807l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Consultant – VMware/Citrix – Flexible Working: The perfect role is here! We are currently seeking a Senior Technical Consultant/Engineer with strong VMware Citrix and Hyper-Converged Infrastructure experience to join an MSP that really… https://t.co/oIoBFyix72 https://t.co/052u55DUrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This $199 PS4 and ‘Spider-Man’ Black Friday bundle has my bargain-sense tingling: I'm calling it — this is the best deal of this year's Black Friday season. It's bonkers. Sony is selling a PlayStation 4 Slim with the new "Spider-Man" game for $199.… https://t.co/na775LoL61 https://t.co/ijlSHl7UzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil price drops amid fears over demand https://t.co/pW4F80QRmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game Services Programmer: Game Services Programmer Edmonton Gaming and Production – Gaming and Production Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and… https://t.co/54q2nz1H9K https://t.co/64KGTAHEW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: My Antwerp based client are looking for an experienced .NET Developer to join their Software Development Team for an initial 6 month contract. The .NET Developer for this role will have at least 3 years experience in the following:… https://t.co/cdUc8wDSXu https://t.co/e3YogcQIXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Apron lays off 4 percent of employees as it seeks profitability next year: Meal kit company Blue Apron announced small layoffs today as part of its Q3 2018 financial results. The layoffs, which affected four percent of Blue Apron’s workforce, are… https://t.co/KQ7sb7CRmA https://t.co/K1eInzWStM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Sales Desk Executive (German speaking): International Sales Desk Executive – Relocation to Woking – £25,000 (up to £30,000 in OTE) Our client is redefining specialist IT distribution, creating a platform to deliver a proposition that is… https://t.co/zVpqlr2mG5 https://t.co/Dqm5vA8Bg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Analyst – SpecFlow, C#, Agile – £48K: Software Test Analyst Automation Testing, SpecFlow, C#, BDD, Agile £38,000 – £48,000 based on experience Hampshire; Winchester, Southampton area A great opportunity for an experienced Test Analyst with… https://t.co/uTiDo5IiXY https://t.co/F96oMg3jrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital ad spending grew to $49.5B in the first half of 2018, according to IAB: The online advertising business continues to grow at double-digit rates, according to the latest report from the Interactive Advertising Bureau (a trade group for online… https://t.co/PP4iJxxvqX https://t.co/0FvMLvBuaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integration Project Manager: Experience delivering systems integration projects? Extensive experience of forming customer-facing project teams? Knowledge of EDI systems? Apply now! I mean, feel free to keep reading for more information, but this really… https://t.co/Nm4fbuHDvu https://t.co/iYopsrotTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Analyst: IT Service Desk Analyst – Retail We are looking for a IT graduate with a proven background in IT support in the retail sector. The IT Service Desk Analyst will provide 1st and 2nd line support for all Head Office staff and Retail… https://t.co/sV7yz9nrfH https://t.co/XW8hcrPcGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zendesk shifts to platform play with Zendesk Sunshine launch: Zendesk has always been strongly focused on customer service in the cloud. They began to look at this more broadly in September when they purchased Base to move into sales automation and CRM.… https://t.co/vh8kQLCevU https://t.co/eyvv0sPmsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Install Engineer: Urgent requirement for IT Installation Engineers for a project starting on Wednesday (14th November) in Guildford You will be providing engineering support with the installation of new PC's/ Laptops. Please find full project… https://t.co/8HXoR56pty https://t.co/YDNUI4ktl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Marketing Cloud Specialist – London: Salesforce Marketing Cloud Specialist – London As a Salesforce Marketing Cloud Specialist you will be supporting the marketing team in the London office of this global organisation and working as part of a… https://t.co/052wnyh2IP https://t.co/tXcvYtRnpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How machine learning systems sometimes surprise us: This simple spreadsheet of machine learning foibles may not look like much but it’s a fascinating exploration of how machines “think.” The list, compiled by researcher Victoria Krakovna, describes… https://t.co/tJLm5G0UzO https://t.co/Ga3NUIbHnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer | London | circa £48,000 ++ Ideally we are looking for someone who is quite strong in Networking, Citrix NetScaler, HP 3PAR SAN and VMware ++ Jonothan Bosworth Recruitment Specialists are currently looking… https://t.co/1fFvovsdIq https://t.co/Vc2sy2KDTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iceland Christmas ad: Petition to show it on TV hits 670k https://t.co/GNYTPlr5Je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poldark makers buy rights to Sir Philip Green story https://t.co/WUj2yEKTUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Assistant / Software Engineer: Do you have a computer programming background and an interest in surveying and photography? Are you someone that can manipulate high volumes of data and use software to find solutions? Are you a Graduate, Software… https://t.co/RK3uDob9Vu https://t.co/bPvNEHNcS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Digital (Contract): Senior Project Manager – Digital Transformation (Daily Rate Contract) Duration: 12 Months Initially Daily Rates: €400 – €500 P/D DOE My client, a global organisation located in Dublin, is seeking an experienced… https://t.co/qhZBzOi2nQ https://t.co/hw22xdrinW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb ends forced arbitration days after Google, Facebook did the same: Uber and Lyft put an end to forced arbitration earlier this year. https://t.co/hO2zVlIHHV https://t.co/4KhxRsM3Gd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer Infrastructure Engineer Infrastructure Engineer General Description: Working with the Head of Information Systems you will be integral to ensuring that the IT infrastrucure is robust and flexible to meet… https://t.co/oLY6mMFX4r https://t.co/rxGIeYwZll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCCM Administrator: VIQU are working exclusively with a Global Professional Services Firm who are seeking an experienced SCCM Infrastructure Engineer/Administrator to work on a company wide greenfield SCCM solution. Technical responsibilities include:… https://t.co/KLjv3IdnMR https://t.co/bahPnb4PUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefox’s newest Test Pilot experiments help you track prices and email links: Test Pilot is Mozilla’s program for experimenting with some of its more outlandish ideas for Firefox and beyond. Some of those experiments make it into the browser itself,… https://t.co/74KJCBPfwz https://t.co/q0DmdAEKZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Administrator: IT Administrator – Service Desk (1st Line Support) – Full Time – Wimbledon – South West London Our Head Office IT Service Desk provides our national business with technical and functional support and incident management across core… https://t.co/4PS6VuN1Yf https://t.co/BZTUQb7fZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Applications Architect: Our client is looking for a talented Technical Applications Architect to manage the infrastructure of integrations and ETL systems and processes, which deliver technical capabilities that support business processes and… https://t.co/5bfg938muQ https://t.co/RWQngvNWoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comics legend Stan Lee has died: Stan Lee, likely the best-known and most beloved comics writer of all time, has died at the age of 95. “Stan Lee was as extraordinary as the characters he created,” said Disney CEO Bob Iger in a statement. “A super hero… https://t.co/zfvOQvPpaq https://t.co/X41k9OopFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – £35k – £55k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex: Java Developer – £35k – £55k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex A Java Developer is required by a leading company based in Burgess Hill, West Sussex. They are currently going through a large expansion… https://t.co/wSOl4wPlHy https://t.co/hLeSn56XOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: UX / UI Designer Blindley Heath, Surrey Permanent. Salary £45,000 + benefits Working with multidisciplinary teams helping to define the user model and user interface for an existing bespoke software product, new features and products. You… https://t.co/mYPyzD8khW https://t.co/wxGW2f2g4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Engineer: Lead Java Software Engineer Wanted in Taunton The Lead Engineer works as part of an Agile software engineering team, leading the technical aspects of the team’s work. They will be hands-on coding in Java, while ensuring that designs… https://t.co/GK4xtGN5fO https://t.co/vQbWukSEPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder to roll out expanded set of gender options in India: Tinder is preparing to roll out more gender options in its app in India. The company will announce shortly that users will be able to edit their profiles in order to choose a different option… https://t.co/FuxkIONKX9 https://t.co/ONg5ImG1f3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xiaomi criticised for UK smartphone £1 flash sale https://t.co/BXs7PLatNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Counsel: General Counsel London Legal – Legal Permanent/Full-time Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the creation of new realities. In gaming and… https://t.co/HcG4ZO5M90 https://t.co/2lipXjiWIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audioburst turns the best part of podcasts into personalized news briefs: Tel Aviv-based Audioburst has been developing a search engine for audio news, which allows users to locate audio content within podcasts and other talk radio programs. Today, the… https://t.co/aore4EHfLe https://t.co/nxLDNfoujg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter, those ‘verified’ bitcoin-pushing pillocks are pissing everyone off: Elon Musk’s tweets piss me off for two reasons. When he’s not accusing actual heroes of sex crimes or trolling the federal government, it’s what comes after that drives me… https://t.co/1PmplWFx0Y https://t.co/3HX7yWW0Tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator – Dublin CC: Systems Administrator – Dublin CC I have a really exciting opportunity for a Senior Linux Engineer to join one of Ireland's Technical success stories. They have grown so rapidly and become a multinational organisation… https://t.co/tlJmUTJ5jK https://t.co/OylbyZrWth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager, Healthcare IT: Healthcare IT Project Manager PACS &amp; RIS Healthcare IT Systems £45K – £55K + Bonus + Car or Car Allowance + Pension + Healthcare + Phone + Laptop + Full and Comprehensive Product Training **An excellent opportunity for… https://t.co/DOFJhQZtAq https://t.co/Jbrwjn2Z0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft is launching a rider loyalty program in December: Ride-sharing service Lyft is today announcing its new plan to encourage repeat use: the launch of a loyalty program for riders, Lyft Rewards. The program, which will begin rolling out next month to… https://t.co/sxRj71beBX https://t.co/ByRvV4moNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German Speaking Customer Representative, Uxbridge: German Speaking Customer Representative, Uxbridge Working for an IT solutions provider with a presence across Europe, our client are market leaders in their field. They're looking for conscientious… https://t.co/82qBjxJEBh https://t.co/PMO2MLaosy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelin action group meets for first time https://t.co/gd00HotbF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diageo sells Seagram's and sambuca brands https://t.co/pqE19eXSvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Embedded Software Engineer, C, C++, Cambridge: Graduate Software Engineer (embedded C/C++) you will have recently graduated from a leading University with a Software/Electronics relevant degree and be striving to begin your working career within… https://t.co/vRmDIL6CMF https://t.co/x1fSftjr6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In venture capital, it’s still the age of the unicorn: Howie Xu Contributor Share on Twitter Howie Xu is the vice president of artificial intelligence and machine learning at Zscaler. He previously co-founded TrustPath and served as an entrepreneur in… https://t.co/2jGH9EJtAi https://t.co/JPRm8pjbZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer – Android SDK, Studio, iOS – Bath – DOE: Android Developer | Android SDK, Studio, iOS| Bath | Competitive Salary Do you have experience of building bespoke Android Apps? Do you have experience with Android SDK and Android Studio? Are… https://t.co/491d19IpZG https://t.co/n07HycCyeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudflare rolls out its 1.1.1.1 privacy service to iOS, Android: Months after announcing its privacy-focused DNS service, Cloudflare is bringing 1.1.1.1 to mobile users. Granted, nothing ever stopped anyone from using 1.1.1.1 on their phones or tablets… https://t.co/e8Bf0CNQhz https://t.co/9Q35eA6d4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Our client is an expanding Scottish organization who are looking to recruit a permanent Developer to their Systems team in Edinburgh. Due to their continued growth, they need a junior Developer who will be working on the development and… https://t.co/oRToYr2MdE https://t.co/HwpNyQOHuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware Engineer / Software Engineer / C / C: Job Title: Firmware Engineer Location: Peterlee, County Durham Salary: £30,000 per annum Job Type: Full Time, Permanent Established over 30 years ago, the company, based in Co. Durham, England is a market… https://t.co/EmjabbelGP https://t.co/Op1w9Qu0Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How issues of microtransit, congestion and parking are closing in on cities: Earlier this week in a new experimental newsletter I’ve been helping Danny Crichton on, we briefly discussed transit pundit Jarrett Walker’s article in The Atlantic arguing… https://t.co/vt52A50ZZo https://t.co/GDLoOuvgyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer, Preston: IT Support Engineer – Preston – £29k – £34K Clemence Rogers is working in partnership to recruit an IT Support Engineer based in Preston. Key Tasks: • Install, configure, troubleshoot, support and maintain ICT equipment,… https://t.co/roxCfiBwgJ https://t.co/dQYfJSXJMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Data Analyst is required to join a leading IT &amp; Software Solutions Provider. The Data Analyst will be responsible for analysing demographic data from customers during the implementation of a Master Data Management solution. Job Title: Data… https://t.co/ai7oo1w0Vo https://t.co/x3RR8MWows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: We are looking for a Software Engineer to specify, design, develop and test embedded software for complex medical systems for diagnostics, surgical, and drug delivery applications. Working for a Cambridge based company,… https://t.co/ov3Wv8Yn3Y https://t.co/V0YnQ4IWy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firms 'struggling to recruit as overseas staff stay away' https://t.co/qiGsk7XffQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook simulates itself up a better, more gradual product launch: When you're launching a new social media product, like an image-sharing app or niche network, common wisdom is to make it available to everyone as soon as it's ready. But simulations… https://t.co/Yxmw6FAwUZ https://t.co/35WgTWfRBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Support Engineer – Poole – £25-28K: Customer Support Engineer required by a well-established business based in Poole to join their Technical Support team. Outstanding customer service and a professional confident manner is essential for this… https://t.co/MMTxlYUlor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Portal needs more. At least it just added YouTube: To offset the creepiness of having Facebook’s camera and microphone in your house, its new Portal video chat gadget needs best-in-class software.  Its hardware is remarkably well done, plus… https://t.co/SOMQznqCsU https://t.co/rMh6UhomKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Drupal Developer: Title: Contract Drupal Developer Location: Woking, Surrey Rate: Dependent on experience Role: A Contract Drupal Developer is required to work alongside an existing team on a fantastic new project for a huge global client.… https://t.co/DhkblY1wjH https://t.co/1ytZujGeLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE TESTER: QA Automation Tester – Software Tester – Newcastle – £40-45,000 + Benefits Overview A leading Financial Services Company are looking for a new Automation Software Tester to join their team. Due to a number of new projects coming live,… https://t.co/TEJu2DJ4Qm https://t.co/OLJwl36aPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Placing bets beyond the venture hubs of New York and Silicon Valley: Roy Bahat Contributor Share on Twitter Roy Bahat is the head of Bloomberg Beta. More posts by this contributor For founders and investors, it’s time for some ‘real talk’ about money Who… https://t.co/VJRT32bmhK https://t.co/LcfNnREIvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Engineering Manager: We specialise in the recruitment of high quality candidates in the IT, Development &amp; Engineering sector. We have an excellent opportunity for an Engineering Manager to be a key member of the Engineering Team, who will report… https://t.co/6KWcbs2QK9 https://t.co/Utpkz8X3q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer – All Levels: Position: Developer – All Levels Location: West Midlands Salary: 28-40k Ref: (Apply online only) Our client based in Tamworth are a collective of companies, expertise, and talent assembled specifically to help brands own every… https://t.co/7jx0inkpSL https://t.co/09LJlEVr5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xbox One will work with keyboard and mouse as of November 14th, starting with Fortnite: We knew the Xbox One was set to get keyboard and mouse support eventually, but now we know exactly when. https://t.co/qFwQ66Exz7 https://t.co/XSTFNvEUJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: SQL Database Administrator Bradford £40,000 + benefits Our client, a leading international E-Commerce business based in West Yorkshire have an exciting opportunity for an SQL DBA with at least 5 years commercial and… https://t.co/mGqgt8GUUY https://t.co/p1BM4j7Nl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer https://t.co/nzWEdvqDSY MVC C#, Stonehouse, up to £50K: Developer https://t.co/nzWEdvqDSY MVC C#, Stonehouse, up to £50K  Our client has been supplying bespoke software solutions to the logistics, automotive and healthcare sectors for over 18… https://t.co/q1AlADI2a4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pure Bit, a South Korean exchange, pulls a $2.8 million exit scam: Another day, another exit scam. This time it comes to us from South Korea, where an exchange, Pure Bit, has completely shut down after raising $2.8 million in Ethereum from investors. The… https://t.co/d4gY1zxh32 https://t.co/jjd4hp6T6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Mail-owner DMGT 'looking to buy i newspaper' https://t.co/ukJUYfJSDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cost of renting in the UK in seven charts https://t.co/HiKwrodznZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Software Developer: X2 ANDROID SOFTWARE DEVELOPER JOBS AVAILABLE IN LEEDS, NORTH YORKSHIRE We currently have 80 employees, across 3 UK based sites. With new exciting projects coming in we are seeking talented software developers to join our… https://t.co/m97Y9yPQ2C https://t.co/zONk8GUAiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Consultant – GRC – Financial Services: Our client, the global leaders in the electronic payment industry are growing their Cybersecurity Consultancy team here in London. The Role: * You’ll be working as a member of the European Cybersecurity… https://t.co/VRSuEao13o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rakuten has SoftBank in its sights: This week, I’ve tried to do something new at TechCrunch with this experimental column — getting obsessed about a topic broadly in tech and writing a continuous stream of thoughts and analysis about it. With my research… https://t.co/2DAAeBsAYi https://t.co/0hw6Nq1yub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application and Database Administrator: Job Title: Application and Database Administrator Location: Guildford Salary: Competitive, depending on experience Job Type: Full Time, Permanent The company is a leading Software and Data Services provider working… https://t.co/jKaT0P8dix https://t.co/h7ATELHB2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Support Consultant: Senior Software Support Consultant required by a well established and rapidly growing forensic accountancy firm based in London city centre who need an experienced Software Support Consultant to provide high level… https://t.co/LGkjD9oJBr https://t.co/b3TU5YMkHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Manager – Dublin CC: Cyber Security Manager – Dublin CC €95,000 DOE Our Global client is currently seeking an experienced Cyber Security Manager to join their Dublin office. Based in Dublin city centre you will be managing and monitoring… https://t.co/GdtZs1P6Nm https://t.co/PFbDihzHw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Division Manager in Electronics: Our client, an established and successful design and manufacturing business for over 30 years, is offering an exciting opportunity for an Electronics Division Manager to join their team. This is a varied, unique and… https://t.co/eeYR6F3vox https://t.co/KVfBAVDlli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers stole income, immigration and tax data in https://t.co/ggbw0PNPqb breach, government confirms: Hackers siphoned off thousands of https://t.co/ggbw0PNPqb applications by breaking into the accounts of brokers and agents tasked with helping… https://t.co/Uo4oRoeaxC https://t.co/QznSkTYwww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: Are you an experienced IT Support Technician looking to grow and develop your career with real progression opportunities? If you answer yes, we’d love to hear from you! CV Screen is recruiting for a growing and expanding IT… https://t.co/OpwvIM9oIV https://t.co/Kki9Spysq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Line Engineer – Vmware, Windows Server: 2nd Line Engineer – Vmware, Windows Server Would you be interested in working for a rapidly growing MSP? I have a fantastic opportunity for a technology focused MSP based in central Crawley. You will be… https://t.co/3nmXYjES8x https://t.co/Rf98VuoqQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst-Business Analyst-Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst-Business Analyst-Systems Analyst Job Description Business Systems Analyst-Business Analyst-Systems Analyst Business Systems Analyst required for a well established… https://t.co/WEmxwI4CcH https://t.co/xnL355BpBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do tampons and WWI have in common? https://t.co/xma3t9wllW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>