<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Supplier Quality Management: Head of Supplier Quality Management is responsible for developing and delivering world class Supplier Quality Management programs that employs risk management and keeps pace… https://t.co/8qa2ZSo57P ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porsche, Audi to develop joint electric car platform to save costs: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Porsche and Audi, Volkswagen's main luxury car divisions, plan to develop a joint platform for electric vehicles that will enable them… https://t.co/caVSQQxdrw #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/EQtRrx9MyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO Architect: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications, hosting, cloud, IT /SAP services company enabling millions of customers to transform their businesses through innovative technology… https://t.co/FqyJWyEMPa ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 Summer Corporate Intern – Product Engineering: Client Reference Code: 212550The 2018 Summer Corporate Intern Program is open for dedicated and hardworking students. The goal of the Spectrum Corporate… https://t.co/WUvaIXm2eP ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Identity Management Engineer: Company Summary First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) operates through its family of companies to help people achieve and protect their dream of homeownership.… https://t.co/wsbUe8sUjb ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Solutions Consultant: Do you enjoy educating customers?  Do you have a strong desire to connect people with technology and entertainment? If you answered yes, then open the door to your future!  In… https://t.co/iuTxolN7ze ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Sales Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems… https://t.co/6YGjWPt4RS ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Solutions Consultant: Do you enjoy educating customers?  Do you have a strong desire to connect people with technology and entertainment? If you answered yes, then open the door to your future!  In… https://t.co/ZXivVIuHaT ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer, Core Metadata Group Our Team Informatica Core Metadata Group delivers authoritative and trustworthy data quality to all stakeholders, all projects, and… https://t.co/K82NRw5DC7 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Engineer, Informatica Cloud Service: Senior Software Engineer, Informatica Cloud Service   Our Team The Informatica Cloud team is responsible for building the leading… https://t.co/JBl2AvQIjA ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITI Cloud Architect Senior Associate – Consumer Markets: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our… https://t.co/C9hW6Ab2rd ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electrical Engineer: Overview Nashville, Tenn.-based Bridgestone Americas, Inc. is the U.S. subsidiary of Bridgestone Corporation, the world’s largest tire and rubber company. Bridgestone Americas and… https://t.co/x0hlErvNWW ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Business Systems Analyst: Company Summary First American Title’s Mortgage Solutions division is a member of the First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) family of companies. First American traces… https://t.co/aEn6LnHEz7 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer – Machine Learning: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams… https://t.co/7EY9LJjgO8 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analytics Senior: Position Overview The Single Family Operations division is seeking a Data Analytics Senior to join the Condo Operations team. The Condo Operations team is responsible for the processes… https://t.co/qsXtg7vaVR ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO Architect: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications, hosting, cloud, IT /SAP services company enabling millions of customers to transform their businesses through innovative technology… https://t.co/l6VPovu4AD ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager of EPIC Information System Reporting: One of the most prestigious Hospital in the beautiful, warm and coastal San Francisco Bay Area is actively looking for a Manager of EPIC Information System… https://t.co/ovrQBPFZim ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Solutions Consultant: Do you enjoy educating customers?  Do you have a strong desire to connect people with technology and entertainment? If you answered yes, then open the door to your future!  In… https://t.co/ACjWHkB6me ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Product Manager:  About the Opportunity As a Product Manager for Data at Pitney Bowes, you thrive on working with high-profile clients and suppliers to develop new innovative data solutions. It will give… https://t.co/OMjyuLQ0tX ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Solutions Consultant: Do you enjoy educating customers?  Do you have a strong desire to connect people with technology and entertainment? If you answered yes, then open the door to your future!  In… https://t.co/NuSS90ShG8 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile DC Pipeline: Description: THE COMPANY   Fannie Mae provides reliable, large-scale access to affordable mortgage credit in communities across our nation. We are a leading source of funding for housing in… https://t.co/D83HjEXjWe ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCL Programmer: When you join Huntington Hospital in Pasadena, CA, you are aligning yourself with an organization whose values drive our philosophy of care. Our focus on delivering quality, service, and cutting… https://t.co/MBQajphwoe ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin may not be worth all the hoopla: N.Y. Fed blog post: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Bitcoin and other digital currencies have, so far, not been formidable competition for cash, checks or credit cards as a payment method in the… https://t.co/9fWs23v1qI #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Glr6Y1FrjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: Company Summary First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) operates through its family of companies to help people achieve and protect their dream of homeownership. First American was… https://t.co/kFAUaM1G2c ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Lending Specialist VP – Technology/Media/Telecommunications: Primary Location: United States,California,San Francisco Education: Bachelor’s Degree Job Function: Credit Schedule: Full-time Shift: Day Job… https://t.co/pwTzYi0azq ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Solutions Consultant: Do you enjoy educating customers?  Do you have a strong desire to connect people with technology and entertainment? If you answered yes, then open the door to your future!  In… https://t.co/S3n7noPORa ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Application Support: Company Summary First American Title Insurance Company, the largest subsidiary of First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF), traces its history to 1889. One of the largest… https://t.co/gfZQ82etx1 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Lease Administrator: Responsibilities: The Senior Lease Administratoris responsible for ensuring Company rights, obligations, and opportunities for non-real estate leases are accurately reflected and… https://t.co/fBoKcUtRtx ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-Sales Engineer – Los Angeles: Why Silver Peak?: Silver Peak is currently at the forefront one of the most exciting and disruptive trends in the history of the networking industry – the software-defined wide… https://t.co/RqOtsekbXo ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metric &amp; Data Analyst Stf: Req ID : 417962BR Job Code/Title : E9494:Metric &amp; Data Analyst Stf Job Description : The Quality Enterprise Metrics and Analytics Team is looking for enthusiastic individuals with a… https://t.co/edgXjIBTTF ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager CRM: POSITION: CRM PROJECT MANAGER TYPE: PERMANENT REPORTING TO: PM DIRECTOR IN THE PMO LOCATION: SAN FERNANDO VALLEY, CA INDUSTRY: ENTERTAINMENT THE ROLE: Our client is looking to consolidate… https://t.co/wZkvJKJ1Eq ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Ariba iXp Intern – Direct Spend Business Development Job: SAP Ariba iXp Intern – Direct Spend Business Development Job, Palo Alto Client: SAP Location: Palo Alto, United States Job Category: Information… https://t.co/BKCjAFIxkQ ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FI/FM Sr. Consultant (State / Local Public Sector) – US Based Job: Date: Feb 6, 2018 Location: Washington D.C., DC, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Customer Service and Support Expected… https://t.co/GvkkRHLRm3 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Applications Engineer – Job Code IRC14003: Computer/ Information Technology Lead Applications Engineer: Develop, analyze, customize, integrate, test, &amp; administer enterprise computer applications for… https://t.co/iRgy3km2hW ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultants #8226: Navigant Consulting, Inc. (HQ Chicago, IL) seeks Senior Consultants for various &amp; unanticipated worksites throughout the US to consult w/clients on projects for pharmaceutical &amp;… https://t.co/J40kgAj2Vc ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Server/Security Analyst: CITY OF GREENVILLEinvites applications for the position of:  Server/Security AnalystUnder limited supervision, plans, designs, installs, manages and optimizes enterprise servers and… https://t.co/tHP4BsvQ30 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Strategic Analytics, Bus Banking #180001204: Associate, Strategic Analytics, Business Banking Columbus, OH. Conduct moderate to complex risk analysis &amp; generate thoughtful analytics &amp; recommendations… https://t.co/iSx2xNbGvZ ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer needed in Wake Forest, NC.  recblid tdbdtwecvt6za30pn7xjm7ry3ocsl6 https://t.co/X20pyOUF7Q ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Principal Architect – Data Protection: Description The Information Security (IS) Principle Architect – Data Protection is a key leader in the Security Architecture team within the Security… https://t.co/Pb2cMhLELe ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Analyst II: The International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) is North America’s strongest and most diverse labor union. Teamsters organize workers in virtually every occupation imaginable, both… https://t.co/SGPhmnkWFL ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: Arista Networks (Santa Clara, CA) has multiple openings: Hardware Engineer (job#HWE0717) responsible for all stages of HW design process; Mechanical Engr (job#MCE0717) responsible for… https://t.co/2kywSXicRn ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Analyst: Information Technology: IT Corp., Aliso Viejo (Orange County), CA. has multiple openings at various levels: Systems Analysts General (Job#009-16): Collect, review, analyze &amp; recommend… https://t.co/Ou6BTB8Hf6 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 4: Software Engineer 4 Lynchburg, VA. Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent in Electrical and Computer Engineering plus 5 years experience as a Software Engineer or related occupation for… https://t.co/s46KlScEUC ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer (Mountain View, CA) Design &amp; develop self-driving technology to improve transportation for people around the world. #1615.31808 Experience Includes: robotics research;… https://t.co/N3NxR78QpL ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. transportation agency calls March 1 'summit' on autonomous cars: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Auto manufacturers, technology companies, road safety advocates and policy makers will attend a March 1 conference over potential… https://t.co/p7wAFyK9GA #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Rec8cxvuRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Senior Engineer – #000784: Requisition: 000784 EMC Corporation (a Dell Technologies Company) is seeking a Software Senior Engineer at our Louisville, CO facility to develop software solutions for… https://t.co/gSyAYzs93j ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer (Payspot, Inc. dba epay North America, Leawood, KS): Responsible for maintaining, building, &amp; supporting office/customer service phone system, email system, end… https://t.co/8gyonJyUIF ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Duties: Provide technical and architectural guidance for design and implementation of software system enhancements. Mentor, guide, and train onshore junior… https://t.co/6qUftNR0Hp ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: Information Technology: IT Corp., Aliso Viejo (Orange County), CA. has multiple openings at various levels: Systems Analysts General (Job#001-16): Collect, review, analyze &amp; recommend… https://t.co/ffw2b8R3hc ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security… https://t.co/y5J0MU4LNM ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transactional Real Estate Attorney: Long Beach, CA Full-time $85k – $200k Posted 02/07/2018 If you are a Transactional Real Estate Attorney with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing (THIS POSITION… https://t.co/v0u9ZjNJJu ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 28548BR Domain Hi -Tech IT Service Management Skillset Functional Testing , Manual testing , Performance Testing Tools , Country USA State /… https://t.co/G1ZdubCTvu ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: SOLUTE, Inc is a dynamic group of professionals that focus on solving the nations hardest technical challenges in software engineering, data analytics, and cyber security. The Advanced… https://t.co/h4kOkBeGVC ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst – IT: Responsible for interacting with business partners to understand business need for Information Services. Participates in planning, design, and development of backlog, stories or… https://t.co/GTGnM6xt0k ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer Sr.: Job Description QA Engineer Sr. (WD***********) Products designs, manufactures and markets intrusion and access video security products for a global security market for both commercial and… https://t.co/9brv51t2q4 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Application Specialist: Job Description Aimco is looking for a Business Applications Specialist at our Corporate Headquarters in Denver, CO! This Team Member is responsible for providing Procurement… https://t.co/sOTWMavNvU ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst IV: Business Intelligence Analyst IV for American Multi-Cinema, Inc. (Leawood, KS) Ensure users easy access to data that is useful to them &amp; translate user information requests… https://t.co/PGTLUAH3kg ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager II: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and… https://t.co/yUx77AzBdv ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer, IBM Corporation, Durham, NC: Act as lead software developer for consensus and ordering algorithms for the Blockchain platform. Design and architect ordering service for… https://t.co/DIv0Xc3Nt6 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Requisition #: 180007281: Requisition #: 180007281 Software Engineer Columbus, OH.   Duties: Provide technical and architectural guidance for design and implementation of software system… https://t.co/A9hBO1QH05 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst – Requisition #: 180003169: Application Support Analyst Requisition #: 180003169 Location: Columbus, OH, US Job Category: Technology Duties: Analyze user requirements, procedures,… https://t.co/BnVxUq3Mf4 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector BI Report Developer Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our… https://t.co/9FxHXsVzjY ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst IV: Business Intelligence Analyst IV for American Multi-Cinema, Inc. (Leawood, KS) – Ensure users easy access to data that is useful to them &amp; translate user information requests… https://t.co/HconEDKpVw ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Development Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: • Software Engineer Applications (Req#ACYPX4) Review hardware, software infrastructure &amp; app factuality for… https://t.co/LG1KYeAoy4 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 4: Software Engineer 4 Lynchburg, VA. Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent in Electrical and Computer Engineering plus 5 years experience as a Software Engineer or related occupation for… https://t.co/7M1UuWqbAH ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung chairman named as suspect in $7.5 million tax evasion case: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics' ailing chairman, Lee Kun-hee, was named by South Korean police on Thursday as a suspect in an 8.2 billion won ($7.5… https://t.co/0zecwJ0MfM #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/JoCrAtnqtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager II: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and… https://t.co/zpWNQdgDbJ ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer – Access: Programmer – Access VDOT86527102*Richmond, VA*The Transportation Mobility Planning Division (TMPD) seeks an experienced MS Access Programmer to debug and troubleshoot the Statewide Planning… https://t.co/xluCCEOznh ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Information Security Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network… https://t.co/YPYSR2LyrY ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultants – Information Technology: TransUnion, LLC seeks Consultants – Information Technology, Batch Credit Services for Chicago, IL location to analyze, develop &amp; implement business requirements. Master’s… https://t.co/ezcd2Gs5dE ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer, Senior: Req ID : 408148BR Job Code/Title : E1463:Systems Engineer Sr Job Description : Job Description – Engineering Proposal Analyst in the Engineering Estimating Group located in the… https://t.co/VXtc7ISdD7 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager (PM): 101810BR Senior Program Manager (PM) CO – Aurora This Senior Program Manager (PM) will be accountable for execution of a Special Access Program in the Advanced Mission Solutions… https://t.co/9ZaVig0kDg ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Product Designer: Crowdskout is looking for an UX focused Product Designer to work on our data-oriented software. The primary purpose of this role is design oriented research, collecting and distilling the… https://t.co/obQqPd3FFP ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Full Stack Software Engineer ) – Platform Development (All Levels): Description Software Engineer – Platform Development (All Levels) ServiceNow is changing the way people work. With a… https://t.co/zNbJJHEAOS ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Network Engineer: Working at Hewlett Packard Enterprise Company Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program – Students &amp; Graduates –… https://t.co/FaW7KoJlGJ ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems… https://t.co/XdwH3l9mZH ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer AnalystSCC85527000*Richmond, VA*This position works on advanced system development assignments involving https://t.co/kqgqWqhUcJ client server systems that work with SQL Server… https://t.co/DgUe46c0hu ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Full Stack Java Programmer: Sr. Full Stack Java ProgrammerVSP87527415*Richmond, VA*VSP is looking for a Senior Full Stack Java consultant to assist with refinement of requirements, design and development… https://t.co/utRWtO5mG5 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer – Access: Programmer – Access VDOT86527102*Richmond, VA*The Transportation Mobility Planning Division (TMPD) seeks an experienced MS Access Programmer to debug and troubleshoot the Statewide Planning… https://t.co/3ElAf1VyXw ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electrical Engineer: Overview Nashville, Tenn.-based Bridgestone Americas, Inc. is the U.S. subsidiary of Bridgestone Corporation, the world’s largest tire and rubber company. Bridgestone Americas and… https://t.co/YwUj5NXyTm ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer AnalystVDH73525679*Richmond, VA*Strong background and work experience in developing true web applications. Five or more years of work experience in Oracle 12c Database, SQL,… https://t.co/VoNF3ai7XU ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO Architect: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications, hosting, cloud, IT /SAP services company enabling millions of customers to transform their businesses through innovative technology… https://t.co/Y7c68dIVMJ ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent Development Consultant (Technical Trainer/Instructor): CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world.… https://t.co/5o9iES4RTy ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Information Security Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers… https://t.co/1HpOjUlJej ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Tech Lab Dev (Associate): PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/HAJpWKKLkW ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems… https://t.co/vmle8mML29 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems… https://t.co/7HpqS8Bnbl ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kalanick returns to court in Waymo-Uber autonomous car secrets trial: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Former Uber Chief Executive Travis Kalanick's famously competitive nature was the focus of questioning on Wednesday in a… https://t.co/pYwmEC82pH #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/wlo1dOhkJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[z/OS DB2 DBA (DBA3 SC3): z/OS DB2 DBA (DBA3 SC3)DIS65526634*Little Rock, AR*The Z/OS DB2 DBA will be primarily responsible for the maintenance, enhancement and performance tuning of z/OS DB2 databases as well… https://t.co/GNUtt0m2gB ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Sales Engineer – Walnut Creek: CenturyLink (NYSE:CTL) is a premier network solutions provider and trusted partner to our customers. As part of our recent acquisition of Level 3 Communications, our… https://t.co/pmemF2Kz4B ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent Development Consultant (Technical Trainer/Instructor): CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world.… https://t.co/mJTZeqv6v5 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Threat Research Team: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers… https://t.co/xHwmxTZgf9 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems… https://t.co/Wd1GjMmpGo ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers II: 98213BR Software Engineers II MA – Cambridge Raytheon BBN Technologies is one of Raytheon’s premier research and development centers. Our diverse research portfolio combines the best… https://t.co/LU1s2scRxs ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electro-Optical Mechanism Engineer: Req ID : 398714BR Job Code/Title : E1882:Electro-Optical Engineer Job Description : Sunnyvale, California: Designs and tests optical mechanisms (e.g. gimbals, fast steering… https://t.co/ZIxpvtDe3d ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response: Job Purpose: Respond to urgent or crisis situations within client networks to effectively mitigate threats through preparedness, response and recovery approaches, as needed, to maximize… https://t.co/nn6g4EHhxp ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer: Job TitleServiceNow Developer – ID:30751 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsServiceNow implementation experience in ITSM modules (Incident, Problem, Change, CMDB &amp; Asset) –… https://t.co/nBynuBhs9m ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android UX Engineer: Android UX Engineer Santa Clara, CA Full Time Position Job Description: Should have 6+ years of programming experience with C/C++/Java At least 5 years software development working… https://t.co/nYq7sHOEq2 ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP EPPM Architect Job: Date: Feb 2, 2018 Location: Boston, MA, US, 02101 Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Consulting and Professional Services Expected Travel: 0 – 100% Career Status:… https://t.co/FY9TqbGISe ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Strategy &amp; Insights Analyst: Fannie Mae provides reliable, large-scale access to affordable mortgage credit in communities The Senior Strategy and Insight Analyst’s core responsibility is to create… https://t.co/imngXFiqBE ⬅️#tech #job #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>