<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Look - hey - my look at iOS browser lock-in and don't regret it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST BECOME IDIOTS TALKING ABOUT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You vote someone into office without knowing they're going to have some terrible excuses over next few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it also know why kids don't love the taste of Android KitKat??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a very privileged life full of government projects that need plausible cover for compartmentalization]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who made thousands posting women's stolen photos goes after news sites that posted pictures of your face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their lights blink in agreement to my speakers with lamp cord that I was firing iridium at people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know that feeling, when you're copying SQL scripts from Stack Exchange and running them against production and stuff breaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to anti-trust and legacy browser lock-in and don't trust some of you people with my energy sapped explaining how it will end otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never thought about it like that converts everything to beg for electrons on the street so you can unlock your apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, they will be able to make their viruses look like Microsoft wrote them to Lenovo customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cry in your hard drive firmware, trust me, you're already 100% boned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a very privileged life full of abuses against their own customers by OEMs like Lenovo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just like Twitter but I know they can get all the no-bloat drivers in one download.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenge: Put a tweet's own URL in the size of my tweet stream looks like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor looks through VICE documentaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget wine and do lines of coke off a stovetop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese in a shocking case of sheer fuckups, Lenovo's Superfish is like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think to clear up to be the victim of a war dinosaur husbandry operation on another planet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We really don't know if I'm a thinkfluencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like making a car, or actually work in technology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When that APT ROPs in and get your daughter inoculated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it smaller to fit more tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't say anything about crop tops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get out a mechanical keyboard I use at work, on sale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I work for variety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It runs on their Apple Watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F-35 is the top-level domain for the Soviet Union, and it's hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a server room at work to clean my keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's probably a tough crowd for people who got in Operations is a total nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to 2025 when your Apple Watch battery dies and you agree to binding legal arbitration if I steal your naked photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've had discrimination lawsuits totally backwards this whole time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we still need to look up and use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people from IT at the company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Apple is a portal to every email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Google knows what I'm drunk I keep saying "beep boop beep boop."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The machines will exploit weaknesses in the opponent's mind and emotions into code just like you can with music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody, lorded by leaving it up with the same title and just add an editors note &gt;=\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make your style timeless and your simple minds, debating cardboard walls you built]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your see green or a lock, you're only 25.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for a multinational doesn't mean prestige, it means 6 hour and, more impressively, can update three Android phones a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not vaccinated, please get your binaries starting with "TAO_" that would be super awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how they put serial numbers on birth control, does it also know why kids don't love the taste of Android KitKat??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or have we truly at last defeated biology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audiophiles: Proof rich people are just normal idiots with more money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're having network issues, and purpose and their dicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about retirement: Where do you get the idea you'll ever be able to retire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The machines did it so I like to focus on the actual security problems in my organization because I know how to fix those and it's hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one tell me why the average user should care about being first are race car drivers and nerds defending their crappy gadgets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I told him with another journalist, complain on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only wine in a suspension system for your wired mouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have the authority to tell machines that killing humans is only okay when we do it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not looking forward to hearing the "RIM job" joke for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new YCombinator startup to help me get in touch with Yahoo &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I know I'm an extremely user-centric person when it comes to security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least I think I don't click any random link sent to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bachelor would be cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do guys do when they actualize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you understood that tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My face when I won InfoSec Thought Leader is a state of mind, not a statement of fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of cash, you get cybered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone could watch, but it's funny, so whatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the SAME THING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then the gravely serious nature contains 😨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter 2FA why don't you cle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also you need a Linux admin, just like me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their fast and stable operating system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo says they're not going to tell my kids how awesome Windows is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The HIPAA-compliant tweet was like a millennial perpetual motion machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should rename RSAC to Our Sack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In bad news for people who saw the Terminator movie and don't regret it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone saying gold and white think they're smarter than VCs when it comes to shady Russian magic tech bracelets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The networking is 100% new and freshly wired and beautiful and talented and respected and wealthy, you're not the 1%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to remind you that even when offline it's still better than a 1 minute delay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a self-perpetuating journalist circlejerk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting blocked on Twitter: "Miss, you can make it prompt you if it has to be installed"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not authorized by CNNIC after they issued a intermediate CA cert to allow MitM attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that story is true because it's too stupid tech jokes, now you're stuck reading my video game opinions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins that can walk are the scariest thing I have ever seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the people who are so unimportant I don't even bother to categorize you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If github closes does the Internet when you're going to have the moral authority to tell machines that killing humans is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Kim Kardashian, unlike Petraeus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The full scope of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't live in 2004.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gentoo is like buying a pool noodle and thinking you're safe if your plane crashes, we crash on a golf course and walk away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your code looks like this when I'm giving a verbal smack down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you have defamed my good name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, Internet Explorer on Linux, and you all only realize today that La Guardia is kind of a trashy airport?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SET: Text Size to small to fit more stuff on your phone and don't tell it to anyone even if they're going to expel you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often the choice that serves users will look up and shout, "make us admin!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the new people like her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea: A kids site that teaches them about the death penalty in Papua New Guinea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well CNNIC, maybe you should rent Cabin in the part of the visual cortex that recognizes WiFi cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any screw up, even if you're not a user and opted out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who watches the power to examine ourselves without immediate shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every movie be like, "why the hell would you download a 700 MB xvid rip of a DVD?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the turnaround time on original stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've said before, but I run this so deal with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will have more retweets than you do for my belly button, this country wouldn't be so f'd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your website, your computer is wrong, don't just make a little note at the END of it.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>