<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/TAYFIsxVOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/YQkGXNQ6h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/nXMIjbiQBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/5epKU0uRNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/IaQGyWcq83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/1MQdl3jhQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/6G7roIk4QV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/rQyyRzbJKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/YQkGXNQ6h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/ZaXcczkT9G  http://t.co/wfshnB5ebq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/Fnz3w1lvgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/KrRYC6b4FE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/o0VV4XDHqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ThinkGeek Building Brick Slippers - AWESOME - theband4: http://t.co/Sqwyu3L6gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the History of Sausalito, California - theband4: The city of Sausalito, California offers an... http://t.co/LiiZugXLPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Films of the 1940s - theband4: http://t.co/snZMshbsos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/wu3155j9RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/x2HySsygCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/7ot1FDMtmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/h6nJA5PtcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/foIWjk4GQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/LA5wh5LIut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/cVeFkDcDgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/ER8KVLVJEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/9gKY0XKhLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/spn7T5AVkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/Gjz4yThjZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/OBLCTEFH9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/96snKL68IW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/3VMTmnubs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/Bj9S9BMCih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/4nE2KL3zrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/h6SZLMcGCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/vbiJKPDrry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/ei3NHtEiWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/9rwnqcFBKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/dc1WuWdgYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the Future 80s SyFy with DeLorean!!! - theband4: http://t.co/IwGSaUqXuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Sci-Fi Monsters, Heroes and Villains - theband4: Heroes, monsters &amp; villains basically define... http://t.co/HlCYgU6AJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Movies of the 1930s - theband4: The decade experienced a political and economic turmoil. Aside from the... http://t.co/sEY51Fjduh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/xFgbBwl7Gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/M8Xe2m3eee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/iDMXLSyc03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/pRON86Bxci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/h7j7j8mipF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/XOrHDBCL2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/tsn3iAyMBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/ITHywsmimE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TtEZ9YgOVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/ONiQxsEUI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/klErX13tic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/4u7bVtaSxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>