<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I.R.S. Will No Longer Force Kochs and Other Groups to Disclose Donors https://t.co/ktTOKs6iJ7 https://t.co/iQTT8lwZte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen, Missouri, Trump: Your Friday Evening Briefing https://t.co/H8UTuOcY2l https://t.co/AwRNY6iCfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiat Chrysler’s C.E.O. to Step Down Early https://t.co/jWvBFNjgUl https://t.co/J43YiqWKCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Dept. Gives Federal Investigators Ultimatum in Eric Garner Case https://t.co/w6qXHRfhv0 https://t.co/IoYQcyM35a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live From Beijing: A Disappearing ‘Saturday Night Live’ https://t.co/NOeUCA1YdB https://t.co/3JU8x5AZ59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confronted With Evidence of Russian Hacking, Trump Reverts to Conspiracy https://t.co/3yvT8zots3 https://t.co/H4LKLUIkc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Doubles Down on Russia. The Spies Shake Their Heads in Disbelief. https://t.co/FMva4x4w3u https://t.co/WEvLjFtCHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri Duck Boat Accident Kills 17, Including 9 From Same Family https://t.co/6VQrNnYEbo https://t.co/zZ2CphrTcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Blasts Fed, China and Europe for Putting U.S. Economy at a Disadvantage https://t.co/04EWPOXFBx https://t.co/L4Rbn4r1Ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[76ers Foiled in Their Pursuit of Houston’s Daryl Morey https://t.co/Kig8pmk4gF https://t.co/RAJsjoaJUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney Fires ‘Guardians of the Galaxy’ Director Over Offensive Tweets https://t.co/LoVCcpaQlZ https://t.co/jOO0mmVR3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber Is Target of Federal Sex Discrimination Inquiry https://t.co/NFsPBdGvBG https://t.co/pVQqLoWIfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, She Is in Kansas: Ocasio-Cortez Makes Her National Campaign Debut https://t.co/Ke08HyaE9G https://t.co/XLHBy4Nm2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider Attack in Afghanistan Exposes Risks for Advisers at Center of Trump Strategy https://t.co/MCLYNvxZ5f https://t.co/IVSqMTNV75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Minister Feting a Lynch Mob? India Recoils in Disgust https://t.co/wOfRk0HOKr https://t.co/4vcdPWdT80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Endorsement in Georgia Race Surprised, and Frustrated, Some Republicans https://t.co/izzpE0DL4S https://t.co/3C76jkQac6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Poisoning Inquiry Turns to Russian Agency in Mueller Indictments https://t.co/YkXcGZeGUJ https://t.co/Zmav6oR0HC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Missouri, ‘Mamma Mia’: Your Friday Briefing https://t.co/iJCY4KbVsH https://t.co/CaQhp9fvWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Secretly Taped Trump Discussing Payment to Playboy Model https://t.co/TqVQIhpHs0 https://t.co/J11XQOVRv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shine, Trump’s Top Communicator, Was Questioned by Federal Prosecutors https://t.co/R5WEHS4JRP https://t.co/wVBqeNErm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He Preyed on Men Who Wanted to Be Priests. Then He Became a Cardinal. https://t.co/mXXu57vYC6 https://t.co/hsGmIrwHfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Migrant Families Reunite, Texas Border Cities Scramble to Help https://t.co/q0ge4gpjp5 https://t.co/oI41UWdrf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Expected to Name David Solomon as Successor to C.E.O. Lloyd Blankfein https://t.co/2VEWrYKoBP https://t.co/PNj3FO6RiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins Policy Says Players Could Be Suspended for Anthem Protests https://t.co/MOldjABdOX https://t.co/mW2TIv3psc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Orders Direct Taliban Talks to Jump-Start Afghan Negotiations https://t.co/9j3HnPnjn9 https://t.co/D53aHERE2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid Worker Shortage, Trump Signs Job Training Order https://t.co/hwfB1W1yOw https://t.co/RcH0CCerpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Accused of Being ISIS Fighter in Syria Faces Prosecution in U.S. https://t.co/is9goIB8uc https://t.co/40yvn9KEd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Withdraws Appeals Court Nominee Who Deplored Multiculturalism https://t.co/4xMuudU5VL https://t.co/tPeTUKfWrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Man Convicted in Slaying of Cuomo Aide in 2015 https://t.co/L7fe5z0VEz https://t.co/J3smQ5veO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Move to Discipline Officer Involved in Eric Garner’s Death https://t.co/OKG1MXKPRA https://t.co/rCyciK1Ll6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 2 Media Moguls’ Once-Warm Friendship Turned Frigid https://t.co/EhKx7ktzjV https://t.co/9X5R3zzDGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast Pulls Offer for Fox Assets, Ending Bidding War With Disney https://t.co/y1rSz64gpP https://t.co/eIAe8nCnE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Start, Trump Has Muddied a Clear Message: Putin Interfered https://t.co/USCs5cLjsj https://t.co/ih7b7ZJGtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Is Said to Open Tax Inquiry Into Trump Foundation https://t.co/RbPEDfC1fR https://t.co/OriAEDZZ2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maria Butina, Suspected Secret Agent, Used Sex in Covert Plan, Prosecutors Say https://t.co/Dleva8dOLf https://t.co/y0Y38xtMxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Men Indicted in Machete Killing of Bronx Teenager https://t.co/aLF7guQLzt https://t.co/HhQNMFLmVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Man Convicted of Plotting Attack on Theresa May https://t.co/bPDqajocJb https://t.co/ojo9T8aaQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect Charged After String of Murders and Robberies in the Houston Area https://t.co/yyKmXgrira https://t.co/akynCDn9rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Opens His Arms to Russia. His Administration Closes Its Fist. https://t.co/4ofaOOGIni https://t.co/ubidMBln8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As ISIS Fighters Fill Prisons in Syria, Their Home Nations Look Away https://t.co/WhuurUofSl https://t.co/WLjiQlpOMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annabelle Neilson, Muse of Alexander McQueen, Dies at 49 https://t.co/q8Eri4Zpgn https://t.co/8zFNDeAbiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Fined $5.1 Billion by E.U. in Android Antitrust Ruling https://t.co/iAeHiMsdN8 https://t.co/jYp7Mh0bLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Crisis Management Guru Bungles a Crisis https://t.co/ImKjhLNGh9 https://t.co/A4XX5MZHrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How WhatsApp Pushes Mobs to Murder in India https://t.co/qVyyQa3Nxg https://t.co/DG8ltosvFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closed for Business: Trump Administration Moves to Shrink Grounds for Asylum https://t.co/1Y3C625auX https://t.co/nIKB7Rv60v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Trinitarios: How a Bloodthirsty Gang, and a $5 Loan, Led to the Death of a Teen https://t.co/E5RovUgTyX https://t.co/FQtuapMNTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Uber, New Questions Arise About Executive Behavior https://t.co/jPhUSxp8gQ https://t.co/gZsiZpr4CA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Tried to Burn Down Condo to ‘Kill All Jews,’ Police Say https://t.co/YXDBbHmarH https://t.co/WmtnXoBsQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Now Says He Accepts U.S. Intelligence Reports on Russian Election Meddling https://t.co/ihnpFkV5AG https://t.co/aBgfjP4pbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Plead Guilty to Manslaughter in Gas Explosion That Killed a Fire Chief https://t.co/A1NUjV4Yxs https://t.co/1MR4gf7eHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Health Secretary Tom Price Wasted $341,000 on Improper Travel, Inquiry Finds https://t.co/2zrcpYOcNT https://t.co/uIz4HNLn1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.R.S. Will No Longer Force Kochs and Other Groups to Disclose Donors https://t.co/ktTOKs6iJ7 https://t.co/DIVehcFWXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea Will Transfer American Remains in Coming Weeks, Official Says https://t.co/jiVgXLlj4e https://t.co/1uUTEQHdtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Army Recommends Silver Star for Captain Criticized in Deadly Niger Ambush https://t.co/QZxnm7jaCZ https://t.co/U3VAehv9UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman Sues Mario Batali, Saying He Groped Her in Boston Bar https://t.co/d0bMeBjJLr https://t.co/IFZsE6Co7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Pecker, American Media Chief, Is Said to Have Immunity in Trump Inquiry https://t.co/nTfjPXQhWb https://t.co/lUsrXOZ2JO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos Eyes Federal Education Grants to Put Guns in Schools https://t.co/cFFbr9uDer https://t.co/1sDRAJctQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How FireEye Helped Facebook Spot a Disinformation Campaign https://t.co/FAhrTXe87r https://t.co/lzBCAFsJuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos Is Said to Weigh Letting School Districts Use Federal Funds to Buy Guns https://t.co/nJAzYLUJeq https://t.co/s48DGoLpQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘How Did We End Up Here?’ Trump Wonders as the White House Soldiers On https://t.co/eXS3Rz2B3O https://t.co/G0rJ3zOPlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing Paperwork Got Him Out of Jail. Then, Police Say, He Raped and Killed. https://t.co/EicrK75rLi https://t.co/6yrmxannAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Meyer Suspended by Ohio State for 3 Games https://t.co/oHf1zEBltI https://t.co/RAH2HlS1Cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohen Wasn’t Alone: Records Suggest Others in Trump Circle Had Role in Hush Money Arrangements https://t.co/MqCdHNXFiV https://t.co/tqX9LeM5uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Investigators Subpoena Michael Cohen for Documents Linked to Trump Foundation https://t.co/OobrtKYJUI https://t.co/RkUldCKLmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Aramco Is Said to Postpone Its Potentially Record-Breaking I.P.O. https://t.co/fHGnasitTn https://t.co/LY626W7hKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in Iowa Student’s Killing Used Stolen ID to Obtain Work, Official Says https://t.co/ezzudIXJN3 https://t.co/uD8KAPE1Dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Party Says It Has Thwarted Attempted Hack of Voter Database https://t.co/7CiaOjl9Is https://t.co/R5GaPdsEf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Counsel, Don McGahn, Has Cooperated Extensively in Mueller Inquiry https://t.co/jrkAgbpE88 https://t.co/A5P8gaARJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gymnasts Describe Emotional and Physical Abuse by a Prominent Coach https://t.co/sid0cX15JL https://t.co/5kE2qG05el]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Sergeant Who Shot Unarmed Man Is Fired Amid Investigation https://t.co/xFF9xzvaoK https://t.co/eO2yd2HSiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Winning the War in Afghanistan? Depends on Which One https://t.co/E0YMHCpH0O https://t.co/AisqvBpToI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This E.R. Treats Opioid Addiction on Demand. That’s Very Rare. https://t.co/Y6Ut5meQaB https://t.co/dy9Dw1BIAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Trump Administration Is Remaking the Courts https://t.co/PVNCyvqXwq https://t.co/P5nAU1DEGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murder Mystery in Ancient Monastery Reverberates in Coptic Church https://t.co/id0a40JpuT https://t.co/KEodiOTohu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A One-Two Punch Puts Trump Back on His Heels https://t.co/iWrsTZHB7N https://t.co/KozELCixPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stationed Overseas, but Solving Crimes in New York City https://t.co/cR1BxGw6Kk https://t.co/Q99WT2CokZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video of Man Berating Officer Opens Debate Over Recording in Police Stations https://t.co/2EWxUgs93v https://t.co/gWOBahKnD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Says He Arranged Payments to Women at Trump’s Direction https://t.co/TH9kt5EW1N https://t.co/5xmvNFN0tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embracing Conspiracy Theory, Trump Escalates Attack on Bruce Ohr https://t.co/VHerXLILIN https://t.co/qQFbM45Sle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citing Costs, Trump Retreats From Massive Military Parade in Capital https://t.co/v65ajLWvFJ https://t.co/4M8b1ZH4Q8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pope, Germany, Prague 1968: Your Tuesday Briefing https://t.co/3dKyr0DIos https://t.co/8UjsEa5rwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Nazi Guard in U.S., Now 95, Is Deported to Germany https://t.co/MQvgNddPas https://t.co/xJRJQRoGuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon’s Ripple Effect on Grocery Industry: Rivals Stock Up on Start-Ups https://t.co/onnDBqCrlC https://t.co/p4nm5YRE0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gay Afghan Teenager Denied Asylum in Austria Because He Didn’t Fit Stereotype, Rights Group Says https://t.co/TBQo6tuvtD https://t.co/3EGzOlsJVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Takeaways From Elon Musk’s Interview With The Times About Tesla https://t.co/nv3Ni6557s https://t.co/nw8DBaq8DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DealBook Briefing: Tesla Supplier? Your Check May Be in the Mail https://t.co/C677EVEaaW https://t.co/VeTYB3ammx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump, a Mysterious First Lady, Weathers a Chaotic White House https://t.co/wNkFxw7VpV https://t.co/wp5UZfPd39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Wife, a Secret Past and a Trail of Loss and Blood https://t.co/1aS5ITlvGW https://t.co/R9MzdECKTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Austerity Helps Bankrupt an English County, Even Conservatives Mutiny https://t.co/iseWT4OxSE https://t.co/1TUwoMN8lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk Details ‘Excruciating’ Personal Toll of Tesla Turmoil https://t.co/JMMZomOOTu https://t.co/cHSkNTQZ64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He Begged on TV for His Family’s Return. Then He Was Accused of Killing Them. https://t.co/03BXOVE5Zh https://t.co/Itkuvs3Esq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charged With Killing His Family, Colorado Man Turns Blame on Wife https://t.co/cvR2Ri8JAG https://t.co/VUu7OK1H2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Doctor Arrested at Orlando Airport Complains of Being Treated Like a ‘Black Person’ https://t.co/ydOeNOTVVF https://t.co/g22i4xpVRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Question Kavanaugh’s Testimony About Bush Nominee https://t.co/5V9eQdjctG https://t.co/tIaE1xHN5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Special Counsel Team: So Careful They Won’t Even Disclose Their Shake Shack Orders https://t.co/lkdFksCkL3 https://t.co/hLIviqXQlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuomo vs. Nixon? He’d Rather Campaign Against Trump https://t.co/cMZ9ttPvw6 https://t.co/Wo2hWccobI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bunch of Men Got Tinder-Pranked in Union Square https://t.co/AGfe85CSqK https://t.co/Rzax0JvgDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Employees Protest Secret Work on Censored Search Engine for China https://t.co/T2r3auE7Qv https://t.co/NV06N2dxGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State Investigates Sexual Harassment at the Spotted Pig https://t.co/SAUTaOtGW6 https://t.co/9fPTCSNBBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Haven Overdoses Tied to Laced K2 https://t.co/JV36ObRovv https://t.co/ifwFNlQMym]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>