<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[New solo show announced London 2013 at Little Black Gallery http://t.co/7R8735vP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAR_updates too kind!!! thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtfulBadgerUK you are very welcome! Lovely to meet you all. Fingers crossed on vote today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayneford thank you! Not sure what it means but its nice....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionaalcampbell thank you!!! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won!! Best in show at Creative Review awards.My first trophy since winning the disco comp at primary school.. http://t.co/csSKOL9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am having a group show of my work during photomonth organised by the wonderful @AlexGracePhoto. Details here https://t.co/W3i6DjvE …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some fun reportage dog photography on my new blog 'year to help'. Rescue dogs in Greece... http://t.co/rWmh3qPJ #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexGracePhoto sorry for slow reply, will Facebook the link. Let's meet soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph recovering well in hospital after his recent fall. Here he is reading about James Bond http://t.co/n3kY044a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexGracePhoto: @ArtRabbit #Exhibition Listing! @MartinUsborne @DanielKukla   http://t.co/uQKIu1H8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kehrer_Verlag: The Silence of Dogs in Cars: Die Sehnsucht der Hunde - Fotografie | STERN.DE http://t.co/yHITC7P1 @MartinUsborne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very proud to see photos of my book being launched at Frankfurt bookfair, thanks @Kehrer_Verlag! http://t.co/ooVh2HAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_geomatics #yourewelcome!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper thanks for the continuing support! Appreciated. Hope you're well in new post, m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozkizilphotog hi there, please email me at studio@martinusborne.com, happy to chat. Thanks for being in touch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe in hospital. Concussed but still smiling. He said accident 'was at least better than choking on a grape' http://t.co/X1oGY1SB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just googled Joseph's whitechapel hospital address and it said "If you are on the verge of death, pray they take you to Hackney instead" God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet  I'm writing a book about dog welfare and working with AllDogsMatter, is it possible to contact you re puppy farm issues/advice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urghhh. Joseph just fell over in library and back in hospital. He's seriously weak after heart attack. Off to see him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Sussex to photograph an unwanted rescue dog. Am told a good photo makes adoption twice as likely. Say..'liver treats!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBrukbacher thanks for the appreciation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eyewitnessimage oops!! Sorry. Thanks for support though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually not much of a puppy, almost fully grown staff with no hair who stinks and licks my neck whilst driving http://t.co/2dhPvbwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving up M1 to pick up very sick puppy staffy to take to vets... Positive thoughts all!! #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs in Cars hot off press. Order exclusive signed copies with postcards here £45 + pp http://t.co/yqo03VJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayjessop yes!! Order exclusive signed copy with postcards here http://t.co/yqo03VJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eyewitnessimage yes! Have changed business! No, I'm afraid that I got infected, am trying to change, sorry! Google are sorting it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First few bound copies of Dogs in Cars just arrived! Amazing!!! Full batch due in a few weeks http://t.co/D8w2fohp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HankChianski thank you for mentioning! much appreciated  Glad you liked. Joseph is recovering somewhat, seeing him tomor #hoxtonminipress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper 1 for dogs 19 for me!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got filmed for The Apprentice at a street stall in east London. Tried to buy 20 buffalo burgers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sylwiassta so sorry! other people had problems too. please call the studio on monday after 10am and speak to Jake +44 20 3602 4278. thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lukey_Latham_ #cutestaffy !! have you considered entering him in search for britain's cutest staffy? http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaffiesRus have you heard about the search for Britain's Cutest Staffy? http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatfingers thanks for tweeing about the #cutestaffy campaign. money raised goes to rehoming dogs. Please keep spreading the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please check out current photos from Britain's Cutest staffy on my blog here !! http://t.co/yg5OeVpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonderful photos coming in to Britain's Cutest Staffy. Spread the word, money raised to abandoned dogs http://t.co/F5NfuN9D #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katkatters @lokihorton I hope you will enter and remember you can submit 3 photos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katkatters Hi Kat. Thanks for tweeting about the #cutestaffy campaign. money raised goes to rehoming dogs. Please keep spreading the word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kickstarter as if they helped out at all!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rebecca_Leisk so glad !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three days working at a dog sanctuary in India and I'm already exhausted by the suffering #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaydewyn Cute!!! Enter them in the serach for britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 proceeds go to rehoming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mattysmith14 Milo is adorable!! Enter him in comp to find britain's cutest staffy to help rehome staffs #cutestaffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanycraven23 #cutestaffy ! he's smiling. have a look at our search to find britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadevickibarber What a #cutestaffy!! Have you heard about search for britain's cutest staffy? raising money for staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficiallyHeath Thats great. Many thanks Heather!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MushkaTheStaffy Yes. Staff crosses can enter too. Thanks for sharing. It is going to be a tough competition to judge for sure!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaffyRescue Hi. I've started an online comp to find britain's cutest staffy to raise awareness. pls share http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rescuebobby Hi Bobby. So glad you found a home. I'm trying to help staffys like you. please  look &amp; share this - http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveStaffy Hi Bailey. Tell your mum to enter you into the search for britain's cutest staffy! http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 raising money 4 staffys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamStaffie looks like you do some great work! I have an online comp to find britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 pls check it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Staffy_Club Hi. I've started an online comp to find britain's cutest staffy all to help with rehoming. please share http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaffieSupport Hi. I've started an online comp to find britain's cutest staffy. raising money to rehome. Please share. http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamtheStaffie Hi Smily Sam!! You should enter the search for britain's cutest staffy. raising money to rehome staffys http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaffiesRus Check out the search 2 find Britain's Cutest Staffy. All to help with rehoming: http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyStaffy_Moo Hi Moo!! Tell your mum to enter you in this http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3. ALL money raised goes to rehoming staffys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HappyStaffyShop I have an online comp to find britain's #cutestaffy. money raised goes to rehoming http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 please look &amp; share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MushkaTheStaffy ps. all money raised goes to rehoming staffys and you could win a professional dog photoshoot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MushkaTheStaffy Hi Mushka. Tell your foster parents to enter you into search for britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficiallyHeath I agree! Am running comp to find britain #cutestaffy to raise money to rehome staffys. Please share http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GarethIJones yeh I know ,been on at google for ages to change it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kickstarter: No word if @MartinUsborne's furry friends lent a paw with shipping his 400 packages or just hung out looking cute. http ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbiejaynex  Hi Abbie-Jayne did you have a chance to enter this into our comp? http://t.co/F5NfuN9D - are you in UK?? #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PricklyEmu @MartinUsborne Hi Corinne, do you mind if I post this image to my blog http://t.co/dwbHFhqo??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[first day back in India and stomach is already speaking a strange dialect of hindi. Dog sanctuary is amazing #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staffybtuk awww #cutestaffy ! am running an online comp to find britain's cutest staffy. money raised goes to rehoming http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KHelpAllAnimals such a terrible sad story. too often staffys end up in the hands of bad owners. check out #cutestaffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AllDogsMatter: Frasier is a 3 year old neutered male Staffordshire Bull Terrier cross who was abandoned and found as a stray.... htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cutestaffy competition entries are looking GREAT! keep em coming! ENTER HERE: http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 please RT and share with staffy owners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezRose thanks for sharing the staffy project and glad to hear your book arrived!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dublyoo: 1 new project and 2 inspiration blog shares from photographers @MartinUsborne and @NadavKander at http://t.co/F0NwDlHZ #des ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlyenever09 thank you thank you!! #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyelizgray absolutely. Lets do what we can #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Broadbentius yay!!! So glad you like #dogsincars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Broadbentius: @MartinUsborne Just got the book, really fantastic!! Somebody is going to have a very happy birthday. Cheers, Tom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esmedisgrace glad you like!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezRose  have launched a site to find Britain's Cutest Staffy. All to help with rehoming, please pass on http://t.co/fqQJH5oR #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezRose glad you like!! (And glad the post worked, phew!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 430am this morn I saw a TINY puppy abandoned on main road. Was on way back from kerala airport. Took it to rescue centre. Will report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi spinach flans are undercooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewlester88 thank you!!! #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easipetcare what a great thing to do! Have RT. Am running comp to find Britain's Cutest Staffy &amp; raise awareness. http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @easipetcare: Not long left now to claim this fantastic staffie offer! 

Remember you can pay this month and use at any time... http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyelizgray Hi Amy. Staffies are sooo sweet! we're looking for Britain's Cutest Staffy to raise awareness. Please RT! http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staffybtuk Looking for britain's cutest staffy. Comp to raise funds to help these lovely dogs - follow link RT http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Waltonx that is a very #cutestaffy! beautiful markings. please consider entering her &amp; raise money for staffy's here: http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonWicks25 what a #cutestaffy !! please consider entering your puppy into our comp to find britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LLR87 Hi Lauren. beautiful dogs! We are raising money to help staffy dogs with an online comp. please check it out. http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Banumuzik @AllDogsMatter she is adorable!! please spread the word about the comp and encourage people to donate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightowl400 go to http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 to enter search for britain's cutest staffy. great prizes. ALL money raised goes to rehoming staffys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlyenever09 Glad to hear you have entered!! Please spread word about the competition &amp; encourage people to donate to help rehome staffys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewlester88 Hi Andrew. Thanks for tweeting about #cutestaffy ! All money raised goes to rehoming these lovely dogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At last!! Have Indian visa...back to airport tomorrow to retry my flight http://t.co/JSmrzKMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Banumuzik @alldogsmatter love it!!! #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightowl400 he looks lovely!!! Have you entered him?? #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amy_lauren_xx try me!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper no they don't know who I am!! Nor do the immigration services!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlyenever09 thank you woof woof #cutestaffy  !!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>