<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/B5qlYFhiTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/awsP657IzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/wzRxsmFwHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/cjbj0t8dLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/iVuUwO1J36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/MYfzwWO54Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/233gqbEl8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/Y8DyJw0tM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/HBIdk0CpCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/lxRSplQbZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/615EAJjepf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/iljil6nIor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/jIGTfjEqYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/zGpMxg48Ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/Y8DyJw0tM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/Ixy1WrcQGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/LFZx16xKq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/FFco1aJPWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/ewwporhhxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/BikTTNsd7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/DXI6vpFF7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/PTXTFPQ9v6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/JO3pjBzWV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/xjhF051voN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/elYHBQRZ9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/R4T3T1Vour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/eo2QTWf92y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/LvBy4fh2Pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/qQeP0C6Qhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/0LMWOencIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/kTXgypXuod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/TDPXeDAORM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/UsFPJ2lnc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/kSaCk9QBUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/i6doHPlNht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/IKSQS9knpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/yRJFrDSXu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/JK5y1WdxSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have heard of Bitcoin?  Read these 10 important things you should know... http://t.co/sNNsBYbxa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/4K9ALSQk5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/jIGTfjEqYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/ldXxOqfKFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/kgl3FbQ2p4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/Mjl4eTUyMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/Aj5TS2yMre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/QW51HsnnU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/MOWDEaTB4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/hOV7ghYjzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/JND0rZIhex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/LEiHadDMOI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>