<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamParsons1: Brilliant stat: “@JanAageFjortoft: (Fun) fact: Since Torres scored his last club goal October 19 last year, Messi has  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 yours sounds glorious mate. Will bring stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonpegg: I feel a bit sorry for Nick Fury, he'll never get to see his own film in 3D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Stevo_football: The Chuckle Brothers is trending. So are Jordan Henderson and Jay Spearing. #justsaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: RIP MCA Thanks so much for introducing me to this sentiment
http://t.co/2fhcRi3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Beastie Boys star Adam Yauch dies aged 48 http://t.co/8hC5sdiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Adam Yauch #MCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae I'm sure you'll survive! Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when #hibs didn't sign Ricardo vaz te because they didn't think he was good enough?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 will be out for tea tomorrow night but having some drinks in town after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 sorry pal, have arsed my shoulder somehow, so out of action. Do you fancy a beer later instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is the cisse goal. Oh my god.... http://t.co/pwzA4BiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new #biffy b-sides record is unreal. Takes me back to 15 again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 nah it's cool I can come and get you. Will you be home?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woops that was for @aspy87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just going to go straight from Uni. Have you no got the motor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 on at 2.10. That time ok for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah I have the time and date saved on my calendar with a reminder set for five minutes before #gayfortheshard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 eh. Aspinall. Be more like #cambiasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 nice one. Nah it's at fountain park unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 pretty tough going, morale is through the floor. Thursday can't come soon enough. When's yours? Want to do IMAX avengers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 yeah definitely. Keen for a Thursday afternoon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah ah right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah good man. What was it for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah you could always just join them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Abu Dhabi's property price slump http://t.co/l39s2GaJ papa Robertson lending his expertise and whistling his 's's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GusTheFox: Just been very out of order to a tortoise. Very out of order indeed. I ate his heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the first ever review of The Office http://t.co/66sa4rWj”. --- awkward for that journo....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BritSnowboard: Very sad news of a fire at Sheffield Ski Village in the night. The "birthplace" of many British skiers and boarders.
 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This next time I'll be on the plane to Dubai. Keen. Just the issue of two brutal exams in my way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn looks great, kind of thing I would buy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinbridges86: Know how Pep feels, been there myself in Champ Man 01/02. Give it a month, your bosmans arrive, arranging friendlies ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevenfletch10: Hibs fans asking me if I'm goin to the cup final..of course I'm goin to watch the super hibees lift the cup #onceahi ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae yep, looks like I'm getting shafted, again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employers are complete bastards. Not
fair to mess around with peoples careers. #fuckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinbridges86: Ronaldo's free kicks are shocking man, a masterclass in blasting the ball over the bar. He's playing Pro Evo with th ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huuuuge gym choons on the playlist today #lightsout #guerillaradio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Andy_Campbell: I just went through airport security behind Summer Glau and no-one else knew who she was. #nerdgasm” --- babe alert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: I'm glad John Terry's missing the final, he's a thin-lipped honky bastard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 brutal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifically cringe moment from Geoff shreeves interviewing ivanovic there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate Chelsea, but theyve won my support for the final for that. Although it will be the dregs of their squad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StevieMoffat: I hope everybody remembers how much they celebrated this as they lament Chelsea Reserves ruining the final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World class pro ev defending from Chelsea. Making fouls but not bringing anyone down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mikel playing a total blinder for #chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 he was always a wee prick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Chelsea get through they will have no cb's. Banter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah dont think you could ever do that. Not even in rugby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought he has crap last season. But #Ramires has been absolutely class for #chelsea. What a finish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ian_Crombie Starbucks is my regular haunt, but it was raining... #firstworldproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #costa in Stockbridge is absolutely horrific. Children be damned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god I am so #bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously went for cantonas celebration. And Schmeichels save vs Newcastle #premierleague20seasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for bergkamps flick and shot for best goal #premierleague20seasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of hand-ringing over right back. Went for Neville but so few genuinely great premiership right backs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schmeichel, g.neville, Adams, vidic, ash cole, c.ronaldo, scholes, viera, giggs, t.henry and shearer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revision going brilliantly, just picked my #premierleague '20' seasons team and voted. I've gone for...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn @alicrawley fraid not! Im in revision lockdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrMarkBeaumont: David Peat, a great friend & my mentor in documentary making, has passed away. Words can't describe how he'll be mis ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday's cheese fondue. #glorious http://t.co/LHw5L7H6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Andy_Campbell: Vacancy for expedition team member, 3 months across europe, all costs covered, adventure awaits! http://t.co/ohcZ5nJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for your favourite outstanding moments from 20 Seasons of the Premier League http://t.co/XagTOkDw #20Seasons &gt;&gt;&gt; Some gems in there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HansOlssons: Another ACL injury at testing of the new skis, Yannick Bertrand! That makes injury nr 4 during this years testing!! Not ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinbridges86: Just watched Warrior for the first time. Emotional! Gonny text my brother see if he fancies a square go when I'm home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RodPetrie1875: Think there is something wrong with my twitter account as your messages of thanks/congratulations haven't been gettin ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ref decisions 'personal' - Lennon http://t.co/OZ352SvK? --- poor wee Celtic! Never get anything their way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisisMannah: An Edinburgh Derby Scottish Cup Final. THIS IS OUR YEAR. Mon the Cabbage #bravado]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HibernianFCClub: Green v Maroon, Leith v Gorgie, Big Gaz v Rudi. Forget about 1902 it is now all about 19.05.2012 - 'mon the Hibees  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HibernianFCClub: Games won't get much bigger; Hibs v Hearts at Hampden on Saturday 19 May 2012 for the Scottish Cup #upforthecup #gg ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisisMannah: Sunshine on Leith yesterday and I'm hoping its Raining in Gorgie today. Glory Glory to the Hibees #GGTTH @HibernianFCClub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got weird al each way for #grandnational today. He's done the business for me before!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scotlandteam: Scotland win 9-6!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballAid: It turns out @bbcapprentice runner up @Thomas_Gearing is a #FootballAider !! He played for #WestHam in '09 &amp; won 12 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballAid: Here's @bbcapprentice runner up @Thomas_Gearing bombing down the wing in our 2009 #WestHam match, he looks a handful!!  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @Normally_Human. Cycled round the world in 91 days unsupported. Ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WorldCycleRace: Provisional time for Mike Hall @normally_human is 91 days 18 hours 23 mins.for 18,175 miles. See him on Sky Sports later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Boyz II Men on #Spotify a new fav!!@rory_g_macrae @JojoRobertson1 @brober87 @OfficialMannah  http://t.co/Nib0C9E9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBRE: CBRE Group, Inc. expands its EMEA business with acquisition of affiliate in Turkey http://t.co/T4k6Kyqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard lots about how #prometheus is a bit shit. Still going to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wossy: Just saw Prometheus. Two words. Oh dear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha, Hundred Reasons are trending, remember them? First band I ever saw live...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mr_seanhughes: @Joey7Barton I know. Violence in football is unacceptable. #panorama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrMarkBeaumont: Everyone follow @Normally_Human - he is about to make history #cycling #circumnavigation #worldrecord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#finished #knackered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @rory_g_macrae @aspy87 always keen for a bit of cuppy. shotgun not in goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akselsvindal: Just met a girl that works at the hospital here in Innsbruck. Not a big fan of downhill racing. Albrecht and Grugger w ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamSpiers: I’m a football child of the 70s. Refined Hibs were pure football inspired by Pat Stanton. Hearts back then were just s ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn tianamen square John terry is my favourite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philmcnulty: Big fan of Torres but not sure he has been that badly treated by Chelsea - might have been treated better had he scored ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DjokerNole: I was waking up for this guy at 4am to wach him ski!Tomba la Bomba-my childhood idol. Next stop - Roma finals :) http:// ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bayern players all seem to completely hate each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah home. cannae handle it. give me a text if you have a drink around here after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah difficult after worst result in history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best £85 I've spent this year. Cheers @HibernianFCClub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 might want to kill myself at this rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant sleep #saltnsaucefinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamSpiers: There must be a deep romantic streak in Scottish football. Just about every neutral I meet wants Hibs to beat Hearts t ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>