<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford, Fiat and Nissan ads banned for dangerous driving https://t.co/2r4I1Qkeev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firms urged to use other routes if no-deal Brexit threatens vital drugs https://t.co/A8scsZ9hFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Apex Developer: Our client is an award winning financial services provider who are based in Cumbria but operate nationally. We are currently looking for an Oracle APEX Developer to fill a permanent position in the IT team, based between the office… https://t.co/FrIv3mc0ZF https://t.co/1rRjlQkeeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Title: Project Manager Suitable For: Project Manager, IT Project Manager, Senior Project Manager Salary: £50,000 to £55,000pa DoE + Bonus Location: Northamptonshire, Field Based, Regional Travel c1hr Work Pattern: Full Time Monday to… https://t.co/vvbfv1Vdn9 https://t.co/tFRMxI9spl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firms 'must be clearer' about Brexit risks, watchdog says https://t.co/xWuNOUhXun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HM Revenue &amp; Customs investigates players, clubs &amp; agents over tax https://t.co/h5U5GMBDOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PenTester- Große Projekte und gigantisches Potenzial- Home-Off: PenTester- Große Projekte und gigantisches Potenzial- Home-Office Hervorragende Möglichkeit in der Home-Office ausführliche Penetration Tests durchzuführen, sich international zu entwickeln… https://t.co/HswPvCM56p https://t.co/xIwoDX2JOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Kushner’s Thrive Capital brings in $1B: Thrive Capital has announced the close of its largest fund to date. https://t.co/zqIMT79usC https://t.co/lQMlJcorw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Mid Level: JAVA DEVELOPER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER MAIDENHEAD, BERKSHIRE – TO £60,000 BASE DEPENDENT ON SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE REF: ETA0205A KEYWORDS: Java, Spring, Web, Applications, Developer, Software Engineer, ElasticSearch, Solr, Scrum,… https://t.co/pZFnmenhcZ https://t.co/bKJvy4LRjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eRates Application Support Analyst – Investment Bank – London: Front Office – eRates Application Support Analyst The team is responsible for supporting globally the ION platform, in-house pricing application, algorithmic trading components, STP, for… https://t.co/JgohHtvtkv https://t.co/A5Ie20rwlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TC Sessions: AR/VR surveys an industry in transition: Industry vets and students alike crammed into UCLA's historic Royce Hall last week for TC Sessions AR/VR, our one day event on the fast-moving (and hype-plagued) industry and the people in it. Disney,… https://t.co/zsia589vcz https://t.co/iyXEl6GW8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure Admin – 001 – London: Azure Administrator (Alteryx Designer / R Server &amp; R scripts / ) 19763-2 London 2-3 Month initial Contract (Apply online only)/day (DOE) ASAP Start Leading client is looking for Azure Administrator start asap on excellent… https://t.co/fDUxMpQGXW https://t.co/fvCXbcXjSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyper-V Infrastructure Engineer: Hyper-V Infrastructure Engineer – Microsoft, Infrastructure, Windows – Salary up to £60,000 + Benefits – Central London The company: An award-winning provider of cloud-based solutions with offices across the globe. Due to… https://t.co/AQYZCjXGE5 https://t.co/Ce9lwDQQ4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parity founder demos Substrate, live launches a blockchain in minutes instead of days or weeks: While the blockchain world has seemingly blazed along in the last 18 months, much of the action has been in the currency world. The underlying technologies… https://t.co/lbJND8kdjo https://t.co/harfawq0UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Working Hours: 8AM – 5PM Mon – Fri, on call every other weekend from home for emergencies Description: Growing electronics organisation are growing their Technical Support Department and are looking for a Technical Support… https://t.co/Q7KyVm7Cjn https://t.co/q0Uj3pQnQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: ECS Group are currently looking for a Solutions Architect to join a global provider of IT Solutions based in Leeds. As the Solutions Architect you will be responsible for working with key business stakeholders to specify, design and… https://t.co/KVkYNdOcwv https://t.co/bb0aitPOlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Solution Architect: BI Solution Architect – UK Wide – Permanent – Microsoft We are currently looking for a BI Solution Architect for a very reputable IT Consultancy in the UK. The role will require someone who is mobile as they will be working in a… https://t.co/f5IRuIGrJ0 https://t.co/nXxZKz4asx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Do you have excellent PHP development skills? Do you have experience with Laravel 5 and PHP 7? Do you have experience in a customer facing role? If so, please read on as this could be the perfect role for you… I am looking, on behalf… https://t.co/KxbyejBuMO https://t.co/3scQdoFz9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools and home care disrupted by Glasgow equal pay strike https://t.co/RXzOxkSQzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Lewis pulls the plug on DVD players https://t.co/Ys77hzWDwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Design Architect: Our Worldwide leading Solutions provider is looking for an experienced Infrastructure Design Architect who will have responsibility for providing leading edge innovative infrastructure solutions across various sectors and… https://t.co/mxka9ARrX2 https://t.co/v4IbEEL34e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lime will open brick-and-mortar scooter ‘lifestyle stores’: How can Lime differentiate its scooters and bikes from the piles of Birds and Spins filling Los Angeles sidewalks? Apparently with a physical storefront where it can convince customers of the… https://t.co/r51yxMwN7w https://t.co/o8Bj1aWIJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gilberto Benetton: Co-founder of fashion chain dies https://t.co/dkFGgoUmKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Network Deployment Engineer: Lead Network Deployment Engineer – £40,000-£50,000 – Chelmsford, Essex Our national client are looking to recruit a Lead Deployment Engineer to work on large networking related projects alongside TDAs and Programme… https://t.co/ePpYsIX6Wx https://t.co/IcJftyPirl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer – £40k – £45k – Ascot: Senior Front End Developer – £40k – £45k – Ascot HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript £40k – £45k Ascot, Berkshire Senior Front End Developer required by a growing software company located in Ascot. The company are a… https://t.co/vByLKBosEV https://t.co/hVROXgvRjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Line Engineer: 3rd Line Engineer Would you be interested in working for a Microsoft Gold Partner based in West London? My client is rapidly growing and need a 3rd line engineer with a strong Microsoft background particularly around Exchange. You will… https://t.co/TyBqK1XCpW https://t.co/D5lxcWAaeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VMWare Consultant: An opportunity to join a dynamic, market-leading cloud business who can offer genuine career progression and development." VMware Consultant Basic Salary: Up to £65k Additional Package Info: Pension, Healthcare, Life Cover, Bonus Our… https://t.co/f3Xkqi6ld3 https://t.co/lrtovRgCkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liam Fox says Trump 'very keen' on trade deal https://t.co/70ZQ5fU9D9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboy, the Belgian e-bike startup, raises €10M Series A: Cowboy, the Belgian startup that designed and sells a smarter electronic bicycle, has raised €10 million in Series A funding. Leading the round is Tiger Global Management, with participation… https://t.co/XaRydB9Lki https://t.co/scjHjj3iAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Games Sales Engineer: Games Sales Engineer London Business Development – Business Development Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the… https://t.co/FArv4hQaJG https://t.co/PZ9JhG4qX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Engineer / Systems Engineer: IT Infrastructure Engineer / Systems Engineer – Microsoft / Cloud Technologies Bradford, BD3 Competitive Salary + Company Benefits Package Ready to further your career architecting &amp; supporting Enterprise… https://t.co/uF0ehGLArg https://t.co/WcXFjfFAWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Country: The new virtual country with no borders https://t.co/LSCUcVqXJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is blockchain living up to the hype? https://t.co/cbr1WHnLHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I hate meetings - and how to make them better https://t.co/vkk4n8ol7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix to raise $2 billion in debt to fund more original content: Netflix’s commitment to growing its original content collection will see the company again returning to debt markets to raise more financing, the company announced today. According a… https://t.co/3Y0dUkLdvL https://t.co/JAi5lyKZ6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2018: How does the government collect and spend our money? https://t.co/mVUx9JMEgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Davos in the Desert’ begins in Riyadh https://t.co/FQmeYaOu2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Design Engineer- Jersey: Reporting to our Infrastructure Manager, this role will contribute towards the overall strategic and technical ownership of Linux, physical and virtual estate, this includes systems supporting International business,… https://t.co/i0ecV7M6Vo https://t.co/9JVEaiVdN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: Are you a talented .NET Developer looking to work on systems hosted in the cloud? How would you like to work for one of the fastest-growing e-commerce sites, HQ'd in Portsmouth? Sounds like the dream, right? Well dream no more come and… https://t.co/HfCVfGHrdl https://t.co/tXEHTaDzjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morrisons loses data leak challenge https://t.co/Fzdka90UfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay launches Instant Selling, a new trade-in service for smartphones: eBay today launched a new service to help users unload their old smartphones on its online marketplace. With eBay Instant Selling, as the service is called, consumers can list their… https://t.co/Iedz6Dj5ML https://t.co/FyarCw0Hil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interim Data Analyst: We are seeking an Interim Data Analyst or Interim Technical Business Analyst for an urgent short term contract. Based in Bath you will be working on a cutting edge project pushing the latest technologies within Data Analysis and… https://t.co/RuuyDIlA56 https://t.co/p1drGI1bYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Test Analyst: Graduate Test Analyst Looking for a Graduate Test Analyst to join one of Europe’s largest Cloud SaaS companies. They specialise in the hospitality industry and used by some of your favourites including; Costa, Pizza Express and… https://t.co/33uQcJSEWx https://t.co/yuVTnNVAL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt and Thailand: When the military turns against free speech: You wouldn’t normally mention Egypt and Thailand in the same breath. But both countries underwent military coups within the last five years, and even among the many oppressive regimes in… https://t.co/gGS7vYJ4NN https://t.co/OkrSbuuYvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: Are you a talented .NET Developer looking to work on systems hosted in the cloud? How would you like to work for one of the fastest-growing e-commerce sites, HQ'd in Portsmouth? Sounds like the dream, right? Well dream no more come and… https://t.co/zY9dqdENvk https://t.co/DPG7X74XH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Our client is a highly successful software company with a very strong market position and reputation. We are now looking for a full stack Developer who will play a key role in the organisation and who has the energy and desire for… https://t.co/AUUvRySAJS https://t.co/V53EIkdtHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Trainer: One of our city centre based clients is currently looking for an ICT Trainer to join their company in a busy role supporting both one to one and classroom style learning. This is an exciting opportunity to join a well established business.… https://t.co/Sk0jvVgcrS https://t.co/jEbnKjbfB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full stack C# Software Engineer: Full stack C# Software Engineer – Norwich – £35,000 – £40,000 (potential flexibility) Tec Partners are recruiting for an experienced Microsoft developer, ideally with full-stack experience working with C#, JavaScript and… https://t.co/hmXxLUS04a https://t.co/p989IUvxEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Infrastructure Engineer: Senior Infrastructure Engineer required by a successful technology company based in Southampton. Due to continued success and growth they are looking for a Senior Infrastructure Engineer to join their team. The successful… https://t.co/WFyalEAySZ https://t.co/u2z4plzSuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Systems Developer (SQL / C): Junior Systems Developer (C / SQL) Salary DOE + 34 days Holiday + Pension + Healthcare + Life Assurance Lichfield, Staffordshire, West Midlands Are you looking for excellent training, a wide ranging role a close knit… https://t.co/PIDWjHJO10 https://t.co/jkrtVYq4z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Martens' profits march forward https://t.co/Fkn1gqQnv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer Python Developer – CONTRACT: We are currently looking for a brilliant CONTRACT Data Developer to work on a large Technology Transformation Programme of work (OUTSIDE IR35) This is a really interesting piece of work, 6 months+ – Based in the… https://t.co/jW3YGNLYIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Cloud Engineer: Working on a major digital transformation programme for a high street bank through a consultancy client of mine we are looking for an experienced Google Cloud Engineer with specific knowledge of Google Data and Google network… https://t.co/WFgSCWTtK9 https://t.co/m0qKj8rqnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps contract – Kubernetes, GCP: New DevOps Engineer contract (that has a big focus on building and optimising Kubernetes infrastructure) with a 'smart cities' tech company. * Well funded (backed by a blue-chip) tech scale up focused on harnessing big… https://t.co/u5hSvXAYEl https://t.co/9iVYTqcYvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanghai Composite: Stocks surge on hopes of market support https://t.co/aJEyxzHeEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikes send Ryanair profits sliding https://t.co/EfQjCrzC53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Exciting Brand – Energy Sector: Java Developer – Exciting Brand in the Energy Sector Java Developer – Energy – SQL Server – 2:1 – Java Software Engineer A Java Developer / Java Software Engineer is sought by one of the energy sector’s… https://t.co/lgUYpncAuV https://t.co/F3xGX0bPks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citrix Engineer: Citrix Engineer ROLE: Reporting to the Head of Infrastructure, you will assist in the ongoing delivery of Network and Infrastructure services to the company, including day to day infrastructure support and maintenance of the Citrix… https://t.co/oGA8I201yi https://t.co/1xoQPuv5Qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addison Lee plans self-driving taxis by 2021 https://t.co/9kzKad6zs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addison Lee and Oxbotica ink self-driving deal, will offer autonomous car services in London by 2021: After undertaking a year-long investigation with Ford and four other mobility specialists on how to build self-driving systems that integrate with… https://t.co/y1ccsmW9kM https://t.co/Fa78ngiU75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The market dictates the product we sell' https://t.co/Fe56f3LXQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The £1.3bn finance firm that was conceived in a pub https://t.co/JtgYj7uHrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2018: Why is it so hard to spend money on roads and rail? https://t.co/zTvKMzVvTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2018: Everything you need to know https://t.co/1Ok9nRcu2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philip Morris accused of hypocrisy over anti-smoking ad https://t.co/sehCA6goYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryanair flight: 'Racial abuse passenger' referred to police https://t.co/CzVyWs04Af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch BepiColombo’s twin spacecraft launch tonight on a mission to Mercury: Humanity is about to return to the hottest planet in the solar system. BepiColombo is a mission to Mercury conducted jointly by the European and Japanese space agencies, due to… https://t.co/yOiB1jPvXo https://t.co/d5WffNTH4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Delivery Manager, Maidenhead: Security Delivery Manager, Global Salary &amp; Benefits: £65,000 to £75,000, 15% Bonus, 8% Pension, 26 Days Annual Leave, 10X Life Cover, Private Health Cover Security Delivery Manager required by a market leading… https://t.co/qRPadwRId9 https://t.co/hdYPjaNLfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure Architect – Insurance Industry: Azure Architect/Developer Salary: Up to £80,000 per annum Hours: Full Time/Permanent Monday to Friday 9am-5pm Location: Can be based in either London/Tunbridge Wells/Whitstable/Chesterfield/Chelmsford There’s a… https://t.co/E4JRlRJDcy https://t.co/rqMyMcqoUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – C#, AWS/Azure – Plymouth – £20,000 to £40,000: NET Developer | C#, AWS / Azure, NoSQL | Plymouth| £20,000 to £40,000 An interesting opportunity to join a growing company that develops streaming services solutions. This company is seeking… https://t.co/2t3pPKCbOw https://t.co/AbfODJW0Nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Our client is the world’s first and only fullstream provider of integrated oilfield products, services and digital solutions. They deploy minds and machines to enhance customer productivity, safety and environmental… https://t.co/TOH8kZk34V https://t.co/pNiXgQ3OoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apply for free tickets to Startup Battlefield Latin America 2018: We’re just a few short weeks away from the inaugural Startup Battlefield Latin America 2018 that takes place November 8 at the Tomie Ohtake Institute in São Paulo, Brazil. That’s when up… https://t.co/gbyMEyomgL https://t.co/ZKY1jlFBP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overlay Leading Communications Services Provider German Speaking: Overlay Leading Communications Services Provider German Speaking Are you looking for a new role with an industry leader within their field? If you have a want and need to be part of… https://t.co/vxjZD8vwQv https://t.co/cxL0DyeWUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Developer: Junior Developer Opportunity – Leading UK Company Croydon This is a fantastic opportunity for a recent computer science graduate, A-Level student or those with an avid interest in coding. In this role you will be part of an exciting… https://t.co/Q8wdMTm7Xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early-stage SaaS VC slip snaps recovery as public software stocks soar: Jason Rowley Contributor Jason Rowley is a venture capital and technology reporter for Crunchbase News. More posts by this contributor International growth, primarily in China, fuels… https://t.co/lxX6w4rLaw https://t.co/nbtO6nx9rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Developer: Are you an experienced Developer looking to join a growing team in a fact-based public sector environment? If so, this may be the job for you. The team: The Digital Delivery Team will work with the users to continually develop best… https://t.co/mvXSyWKnih https://t.co/fRw5PWiYoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PlayStation Vue is first US pay TV provider to integrate with Apple’s TV app: Sony’s live TV streaming service, PlayStation Vue, announced this week it has become the first U.S. pay TV provider to integrate with Apple’s TV app in order to display… https://t.co/Yla2R5USF5 https://t.co/XZPnDvLXGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer: My client, part of one of the largest advertising companies in the world, are looking to add a Big Data Engineer/Architect who will work on collecting, storing, processing and analysing of huge sets of data. Your main focus will be on… https://t.co/BJuBJIIAhV https://t.co/AXyWCPvY7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K-beauty: The rise of Korean make-up in the West https://t.co/WyWBizYynu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal / Web Developer x2 – £25k-£60k (DOE) – London: Drupal / Web Developer x2 – £25k-£60k (DOE) Publishing London, City A growing publishing company situated in the heart of London, are looking to recruit two Drupal Developers (junior/senior level) to… https://t.co/9QfSLbOcDV https://t.co/FAsY2sDw63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Analyst: A leading business in Cheshire are searching for a BI Analyst to join a newly formed Analytics department. If you enjoy a varied role whereby you really engage and make a difference to a business then this could be of interest. You will… https://t.co/OvQggW88OQ https://t.co/2UI9jdEa2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Line Desktop Support Engineer – Banking/Investment Banking: Our client, a dynamic, growing telecoms client, are looking for a 3rd Line Desktop Support Engineer to join their team based on their customers site in Canary Wharf. You will be based with a… https://t.co/H5iAxbzK3W https://t.co/qEzYm7AOCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Sales and Quotes Engineer:   Job Description – Technical Sales and Quotes Engineer (053512) Job Description  Technical Sales and Quotes Engineer – (053512)  Description   Main duties will involve evaluating and preparing quotations and tenders,… https://t.co/Wh2hsts3kp https://t.co/07Muhx2sSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free societies face emerging, existential threats from technology: Bilal Zuberi Contributor Share on Twitter Bilal Zuberi is a partner at Lux Capital, and is on the boards of Evolv Technology, CyPhy Technologies, and Nozomi Networks, among others.… https://t.co/HbG0nyV9xu https://t.co/petvPgOye3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The billionaires fuelling a space race https://t.co/AnjQ01xgBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: We are currently looking for an IT Support Engineer to join a leading pharmaceutical company based in the Reading area. As the IT Support Engineer you will be supporting the IT Manager in the day to day running of an IT support… https://t.co/ofias9IwHD https://t.co/5tZIDJqgCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Crowder Consulting is a consultant engineering and software development company that specialises in the fields of water supply, water distribution and sewer networks. Established in 1985, the business designs and provides… https://t.co/l19i1jJX9a https://t.co/OG3qRpwujn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community Manager – Fan Engagement: My client, a global giant within the technology industry, is looking for a Community Manager – Fan Engagement to join there team in London, on a 12 months contract initially. Core hours are 10.00am – 4.00pm. The… https://t.co/1nfD1kHHFv https://t.co/30dLxvB1f1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Are you a Network Engineer with experience of Cisco tech? Do you have a working knowledge of firewall technologies and the ability to provision next gen firewalls and SIEM tools? Are you looking to progress your career, working on large… https://t.co/nXQvfTPiLH https://t.co/4GH65KCMf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China is funding the future of American biotech: Silicon Valley is in the midst of a health craze, and it is being driven by “Eastern” medicine. It’s been a record year for US medical investing, but investors in Beijing and Shanghai are now increasingly… https://t.co/PkIKIhqzqc https://t.co/sVZU0Z2U2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Digital Forensic Investigator: RSR Police is a market leading recruitment business dedicated to supplying experienced practitioners on a temporary, contractual or permanent basis to the Law Enforcement market. RSR Police is currently recruiting… https://t.co/UUESxmDl5Q https://t.co/Cp7GLufmqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AV Engineer: Currently recruiting an AV Installation Engineer to be based in the Midlands to attend customer sites within the region. Role and Responsibilities: * To have a good understanding of Audio Visual, be able to translate from technical drawings… https://t.co/DJLjMBmZdO https://t.co/xpY2B2zW1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULLSTACK .NET DEVELOPER – BELGIUM (BRUSSELS) – 12 MONTHS: FULLSTACK .NET DEVELOPER – BRUSSELS – 12 MONTHS + For my client in Brussels I am looking for 2 .NET developers to join them for a long term commitment. The role: Forming a brand new team, working… https://t.co/3vPQ7qgaeY https://t.co/mdbqawY3XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buggy software in popular connected storage drives can let hackers read private data: Security researchers have found flaws in four popular connected storage drives that they say could let hackers access a user’s private and sensitive data. The… https://t.co/4UmUzksg5U https://t.co/vqw5Ys44AB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Technician: ICT Technician Dates: To start ASAP Salary: Bucks Pay Range 2-3 £18,703 – £23,108 Location: High Wycombe, Buckinghamshire Contract Type: Permanent Contract Term: Full-time (37 hours per week) – 21 days holiday + bank holidays We have a… https://t.co/R8Tb0WBbYi https://t.co/TBCYbpYX40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gearing up to step into virtual reality: For the past two years, we’ve been closely following the advances of new VR experiences. Much of this gear is still in development, but if you’re eager to dive in and get a sense of what’s available right now,… https://t.co/Gfhug73fyb https://t.co/GHg63NFNdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Role description You will provide technical support to internal &amp; external customers via telephone and using remote support technology as well as face to face and travelling to our various sites when required. You will have… https://t.co/hk7tpApUtV https://t.co/QVVqxCcW9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: This contract with the Home Office is INSIDE IR35 paying £425.00 per day for 6 months based at their Hendon Data Centre. Any candidates with SC clearance hold are preferred but also considering suitable candidates who are willing… https://t.co/FyCYLF5wVB https://t.co/8zdFfaouuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: SQL DBA, SQL Database administrator, SQL Server DBA This is a great opportunity for an experienced DBA – Database Administrator to join an award winning organisation based in Denbighshire, taking ownership of the performance,… https://t.co/qvrIIAZhtC https://t.co/NppJbHPsaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla is rolling out a cheaper, mid-range Model 3: Tesla is now offering a new, cheaper mid-range battery version of the Model 3 that starts at $45,000 before federal tax incentives. CEO Elon Musk announced the new variant, which has an estimated battery… https://t.co/aFd4K7MwRb https://t.co/6Cigu45X5f]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>