<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jackanory05 @LADFLEG @JimAllister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel @MMA_Jim @DaireBoyle94 Sir. Bigger than McGregor Diaz. I have pishy on points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMA_Jim Chuck Liddell v Purple Aki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duffy_MMA How's the shoulder ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ If he ever shites on the floor stand there and angrily call him by his full name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ Charlie Andrew Wahees Robertson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ *andrew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Bin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ Putin would get the north back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gillett92 I remember myself and swimmer matty LFC telling you this about 8 years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBoydBarrett Mike Pence had a fry I'm Shannon on a stopover recently. We ain't neutral bud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ Andrew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LADFLEG: Here's a fun game. Amend newspaper stories to replace the minority group the DUP has attacked with the word "Jews" and then si…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Ireland 2022]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballCliches: I will be using the Welsh spelling of "Uruguay" from now on, thank you very much https://t.co/2m8TYcwnsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bogvvitch: I'm fucking screaming https://t.co/hV8VtgxO97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC Aye it's quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC Watch the shield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRedmenTV: 😂 https://t.co/OTcdwk74WB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LADFLEG @Deank06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LADFLEG @BrixTuohy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LADFLEG: RUC commander at Garvaghy Road orders Orangmen to turn back to Drumcree (1995, colorised) https://t.co/OjfEEs0DV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ehbenj Shaun Goater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @josefoshea: Viewed from Ireland - #Brexit is a bit like seeing your neighbour standing naked in front of his house, screaming at the bi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bostonladftp @KAHJoeTAL @Pauldalylfc96 @Joerrfc55 @scousemeow @MajorBlue613 @billyshaker @alfieriley @bluesapper1 @Scouse_ma @WBCFredJr @WBCShirl2 @AbiWBC @WBCsigns You do know King Billy was gay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[104 billion of those were me https://t.co/Hsq7Fy6QNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ehbenj Mite be enough to bring Paul back to life tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieHolme Jesus I actually was thinking this morning mid pod " I wonder could Jamie get tommo on this" haha class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieHolme Good man! I'll have it downloaded for Monday morning. Same lads on it again? Didn't realise Danny was a scouser! He played up near me when he was at Derry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonnyHewitt1: Don't think I'll ever get tired of  this 😂😂😂 https://t.co/HkbgFHCepM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC 100% the reason I'm bald lad. If I was a Manc I'd have a Barnet like Bon jovi if I was a Manc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC The clubs already mental. 100 minutes to go in the tie and were 5-0 up. Finished 7-6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC Imagine we had have signed him to play with Suarez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JOEdotie: This was a fantastic gesture by Aldo https://t.co/oKOSTAm7aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KONNYKON_: Pablo Escobar was eventually snitched on by local children. 

Mortally wounded by police gunfire his last words to them were…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @themaxburns: ARE YOU THE GUY I TELL ABOUT THE CRIMES https://t.co/F0S9CCB7dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnnyMilburn: Woah Black Betty.... https://t.co/Z0coe9zVb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalLongo Planet derp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donegaldarren @DavidD_73 @danielhowdon No idea. He's married anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donegaldarren @DavidD_73 @danielhowdon Hahahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CalvLyfeson: Into work. https://t.co/niYlEq9Zup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalvLyfeson Here's to you Mrs Robertson, we all love you more than you will know.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaireBoyle94 @AiddyFriel When's he back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaireBoyle94 @AiddyFriel Salty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel @DaireBoyle94 CL final to look forward too. I'll take  that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992  https://t.co/R2dGlQ5MtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaireBoyle94 @AiddyFriel  https://t.co/vKA51XbmPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Fucking love the Reds man! Fucking love you too! Allez Allez Allez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aarbeloa17: I would love nothing more than a final between the two best clubs in the world: Real Madrid and Liverpool.
Come on @LFC! Le…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel You pumba and nook doing shots of ronseal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillEdgarTimes: Liverpool past 4 games: 
First 75mins: 9-2 up. 
Last 15 minutes: 6-0 down.   

@TimesSport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel Get the Dulux in ya cunt! Yeeeeoooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CalvLyfeson: To all the lads that'll over analyse this. Fuck off. We're in a European Cup final!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS What's that tube saying. I'm on bt watching stevie having a tug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel ARE YA FEEEEEEEWWWWWWWMING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesPearceEcho: Players re-emerge from the dressing room to celebrate in front of the away end. They are holding the banner dedicated…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_ChrisBascombe: Liverpool v Real Madrid in the European Cup Final. Alan Kennedy's phone has not stopped ringing for a month. He will ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC Lunatics seany!! Pure fuckin loons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YEEEEEEEWWRRRRRRRRRRRRRRSSSSSSEEEEEEEEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KopBlock205: I picked the wrong week to stop sniffing glue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up thon fucking Reds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Wouldn't change it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ehbenj Boiled gammon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Glass of red for the Reds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Quivering with fear and we're 3-0 up. Imagine if we were only 1 up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Hahaha yes mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 About to have one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jhiggins3: Beautiful banner for Sean Cox here in Murrays Bar https://t.co/9WKYNhdJgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS He wasn't good next to Sakho. He's probably the stupidest player I've seen play for us in years. Literally minutes ago I read him referred I him as birdbrain. Sums him up well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Had 3 years of being shite before that. Fair enough if you rate him each to their own. But he is shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Good for him. He's an awful defender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Is launch both into the channel come June]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS He's better than Moreno but nowhere near good enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Half a season of being not shite out of 4 seasons? Bin him off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS No he's not. He's sub par. Will always let you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys drink this in. This does t happen often #ALLEZALLEZALLEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@porktrousers Haha that's going back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrjamesob @DaireBoyle94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tears 😂😂😂 like that Ronaldo bust. https://t.co/w58T9pXfgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalLongo Great word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrjamesob Give us what we want or we'll drink paint https://t.co/e85fpms1Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WildAtlanticTV: Stunning shot by Martina Gardiner who captured this #fullmoon over #angriananfort Co Donegal #WildAtlanticWay https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theliverpoolway Is it true Dave? Haven't seen anyone reliable saying it. Would be disastrous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveisonfire Did the same. Feel I need counselling 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ @IsMiseShane 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsMiseShane @UpTheReds_ Amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 He had to go back into hospital on Friday for an infection but he didn't have to stay in. He's getting better everyday but it's going to be a long road. Cheers for asking! How's ur wee man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsMiseShane @CalvLyfeson Mad transfer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Virg is in the Ra! https://t.co/rpLrEPTcPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ The islamic republican army 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Most horrid club on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Crazzyintheusa: How to deal with road rage. https://t.co/S8YlPZfcw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way fans have rallied for this man and his family is unreal https://t.co/fsXetnzr9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminOgden It's a disaster in its current format]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalLongo Aye kinda. I like to see Celtic do well but I detest sevco. Hope they go bust again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalLongo I'm from Donegal though. Massive Celtic county.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalLongo I hate rangers more than Everton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenorNewman: Where Pete Price is from https://t.co/EA6ONypWHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sweirz: " ... and it finished #Celtic 5 #Rangers 0"

Steven Gerrard at Gretna ... https://t.co/elYrKoe4aD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>