<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you like 'Yayo' by Lana Del Rey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find someone who has a life that you want and figure out how they got it." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a #DelReyDisease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want my cake and I want to eat it too. I want to have fun and be in love with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My intention was never transform into a different person. What other people think about me is none of my business." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you say 'Lana Del Rey' everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just saw the beauty queen Lana Del Rey sing and she was a dream." —Katy Perry (via: @NadineManson)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ELLEUK: @LanaDelRey is going to be answering YOUR questions. Click here to see when and how: http://t.co/nFG65Unh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #TeamLana ! Check this out: Ask Lana Del Rey anything. http://t.co/wmHJxvAW — @ELLEUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey will be opening a new Mulberry store at the Mandarin Gallery on October 24, 6-8 PM, in Singapore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Si Lana Del Rey' Trending Worldwide!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LanaForGrammy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause baby we were born to live fast and die young. Born to be bad, have fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I only know how to do me, so that's just what I'm going to do." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was trying to document my life in sound form." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy, you're sweet like sugar cane. Make me feel alive again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamLanaMissLanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause I have nothing else to do, it's summer but committed to you. Have a big degree in philosophy, but I don't know what I wanna be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you're proud to be a #TeamLana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your soul is haunting me and telling me that everything is fine but I wish I was dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roses are red, Violets are blue. Haters of Lana? Are they human too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success has many Fathers, and I am the Mother of them all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey I loved you yesterday, I love you today, I always have and always will. Cause loving you forever can't be wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KEEP VOTING! http://t.co/3vLt6QYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mariagarciatub: @LanaQuote @LanaDelRey everyday i vote for her (':]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you vote Lana Del Rey today? Vote for @LanaDelRey at the 2012 MTV EMA's. VOTE HERE: http://t.co/3vLt6QYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At first, you think you have a dark side it's exciting &amp; then you realise the dark side wins every time if you decide to indulge in it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now my life is sweet like cinnamon. Like a fuckin' dream I'm living in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose your last words, this is the last time. Cause you and I, we were born to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I mainly let my imagination be my reality. Fantasy is my reality." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey presents: Born To Die Tour dates! http://t.co/RKHogc6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey aka L I F E.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've been doing what I do for a long time. I've had a life. I don't need to create a persona to live through." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Putting your faith in the people is like building a house in the sand." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You laugh at me 'cause I'm a Team Lana, I laugh at you 'cause you'll never have an amazing idol as mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I didn't sign up to be famous, I just wanted to sing." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Top10GreatestVoices Lana Del Rey. http://t.co/4qcC301B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Of course I wanted to look good, but 'smart' was the primary focus." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have success because I'm at peace and I'm a good person in my everyday life and that's important." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So, although there's a dark side to love, there's also something really hopeful." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you've been lonely for a while, and then you find someone who understands you, you become really attached to them." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe nothing happens by mistake. You know, the universe has a divine plan." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All the things you start off with are given to you by somebody else. You have to be brave and try to start again." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When Lana Del Rey's happiness is my happiness, that is life." —Team Lana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go away to somewhere warm and where you're loved." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I like this roller coaster, maybe it keeps me high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes, love feels like a life - or death situation." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wish I could escape into some alter-ego, just so I could feel more comfortable on stage." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of feeling like I'm fucking crazy. I'm tired of driving till I see stars in my eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a totally different life experience when you have to learn to love the things that don't love you back." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for Lana Del Rey at the NRj Music Awards 2013 for 'International Revelation of the Year' — VOTE HERE: http://t.co/YZ5Q2ADA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey Please go online and talk to your fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cola by Lana Del Rey is nothing if you don't have a pussy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rays: I love you so much LANA DEL RAY!! — Lana: … http://t.co/QfxtGL3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My goal in life is to be a good person who lives with dignity and grace." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I got my red dress on tonight." — http://t.co/ewcs6cTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is genius in choosing the title of her album. http://t.co/gGW89ybY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SongsThatMakeMeCry Oh Say Can You See — Lizzy Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summertime Sadness. http://t.co/AdCImEOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I still can see Blue Velvet through my tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMA is shit without Lana Del Rey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana: I heard that you like the bad girls, honey... http://t.co/0tvZBOEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaven is my baby, suicide's my father, opulence is the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for Gods &amp; Monsters and Fav for Cola. http://t.co/YhLQ8yPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: Alana Del Rey. Album coming soon! http://t.co/ogRlFrOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don’t think I call myself a diva, maybe an icon." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey #MTVStars — http://t.co/Ji9UuijD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Springsteen is the king, don't you think? I was like, "Hell yeah, that guy can sing."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel in line with the vision I have." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana's voice✔ Lana's hair✔ Lana's eyes✔ Lana's lips✔ Lana's smile✔ Lana's body✔ — Lana Del Rey = Perfection ✔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drive fast, wind in my hair. I push it to the limits cause I just don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Kzp4ZquF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride. http://t.co/ogVCKP9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've been really blessed to have a lot of romance in my life. It's like my last luxury." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey in Paris today. http://t.co/XM8sajOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you gonna be my lover? Are we gonna be true loves suicide? It's either live or die boy? It's either live or die?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm scared that you won't be waiting on the other side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bond Girl. http://t.co/S4YZE6bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey with a fan. http://t.co/7tzJuUNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pussy tastes like pepsi cola and looking to get fucked hard. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyFan: "Cola" is already doing well making TOP 100 in more than 13 countries in iTunes charts. Maybe we will have another hit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put me onto your black motorcycle. Fifty baby doll dress for my 'I do'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I really love the Paradise Edition, to me it feels even more natural than the original Born To Die." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana: "If you don't buy The Paradise Edition..." http://t.co/g6bFNAjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay in your room, get in your bed. Maybe you can get me inside your head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q: "What's the most romantic place for you?" — Lana: "I don't know. I'm very romantic, so I can find it in so many place."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My own imagination, and my own vision for the way my future could look is inspiring to me." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paradise has two sides. http://t.co/X4Ush73W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like men who have experienced life." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be young. Be dope. Be proud. Like an American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey and her pussy. RT If you think she is cute! — http://t.co/aekADHoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is ugly and horrible — said people who can't afford a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a burning desire for you, baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCR1: The beautiful @LanaDelRey is on with @FearneCotton right now! http://t.co/ZEbJ6zB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you should invite @LanaDelRey to your show. @TheEllenShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paradise. http://t.co/WtmVOeAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Distance sometimes lets you know who’s worth keeping and who’s worth letting go.” —Lizzy Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Slay RT @DelReyLane: The Paradise Edition is currently #3 on the UK iTunes Albums Chart! http://t.co/GEsupDYG http://t.co/2Q8EoCCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mona Del Rey. http://t.co/dHm75uwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you think that music is something that you want to make a life at, well, you just do it. Just don't stop." —Lizzy Grant]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>