<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TGGB8Olvea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/7dRMskVOsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/ASQi8FwPpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/VqAnKRjtZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/BfhaRKZJP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/iQqkRIw2u0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/ZQWdjFOpTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/fxCInXQjRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/jZRX7qJ2Ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/DJszasvFrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/bDODzDQlh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/ixXxj3QaHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/06lrQni4W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/x6VdOqInfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/slB1AHgtD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/WqvZawqn2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/2hNLeNkvXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/TmFWEe3hYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/xuX1y8rPji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/erE68zwumV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/d76wbnh6EY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/MFiuhxDJbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/FtGFqzznQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/5NWdEy9JNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/qR3nQE3nEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/gbspd99Xm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/B50DosqOpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/DYiCKTRS1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VUJCbW5RFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/BkAdx3FBOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/nxJaAFMF6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/D5mdukObVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/yDk2t3sraG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/OM5uHIKPfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/NonYeRwe1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/eFWEzb0cY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/SdqSCf1GWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/ZKEdjlr0UI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/TW7sdFKSUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/OUKvCrLjG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/38TYMDP8du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/jOWRAROFUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/nbwqc4dORE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/toQ8UkT2Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Dog Breeds - theband4: http://t.co/SA4ctdMgOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 20 Cat Breeds - theband4: http://t.co/WJNqGP1JCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/EJPA4IcuTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VUJCbW5RFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/bPpb4P9MBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/5jzSVjFEY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/fCyyvs0rLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/yDOhPu7Xd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/V5OZsbGrG4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>