<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kZlNFfnSTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveValerieee You've spoiled me for anyone else,Valerie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AppSapp you got the secret. Coolness attracts cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessCollins_y0 u have all high cards in your hand, win &amp; be generous, you'll go far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1993 the American military was defeated and  thrown out of Mogadishu, whence it became a staging area, a safe... https://t.co/Yu6Y9R2URc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamoppose E.O. You're not selling me anything.You sound like the kind of gal I would want to see a movie with and share popcorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sleepy part of town, people getting out the door on a beautiful sunny day. The town was not a violent place... https://t.co/5YhXuVoxcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shout out to New Zealand player Sonny Bill Williams of the World Champion All Blacks for making this... https://t.co/Gk3CzijiLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful. Always. https://t.co/l7Nv1syt6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6FtGRFGQnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At last a western with a cast not seen since Sam Pekinpah's The Wild Bunch. Tarantino is bringing back the western. https://t.co/fr8Ue28kgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DtASBjXr1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Vwhni4Ip2q https://t.co/rj5FmBvfs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A high-profile white man can't be bludgeoned or choked or shot. His appearance provides contrasting optics. More... https://t.co/ps3PdckNXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jWaWa4uGRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vsTfXtUVB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. You offer a fresh face to new thought. You'll never get stale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give the nervous system a break with lovely music. https://t.co/Rd53RVL5zZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JpdvFxHALe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Christians terrorists get a free pass. https://t.co/USmeDO9sIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pjH2dkZBa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great comedy about "thoughts &amp; prayers" https://t.co/BJWEZ308Ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally somebody's noticed https://t.co/39IvAhBFKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Reported mass shooting in San Bernardino, California https://t.co/5aKM3pTBaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XbkkqQIr6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask the neo-cons how that worked in Iraq..that's how we ended up with ISIS. Shut the fuck up, Donny. https://t.co/3Tf8wKvC0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the conversation no  pro-lifer wants to have. https://t.co/ax5KfgAfoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/onPlM57lKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2e4ot0kLRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew you were special when we met. You do cast a spell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is because I know you will profit and learn from it. Thank you for your presence and gratitude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did we survive? https://t.co/tvNgb8zkB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blacks in the burbs, caroling. Gotta love the homies https://t.co/PxeOwXfgRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Rio today it safer for young people to live under protection of traffikers than police pacification. https://t.co/RJTJkocn6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johah Lomu passed at age 40. For his time in the early 90s he was the world's most imposing rugby player and... https://t.co/dxqTWKFIzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Brazil"- 2012, acyclic https://t.co/RaAbCX0rO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/I6ko6SHimV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6LUHtxbEM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/EjDSs1SINC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant, Beautiful &amp; Brave in Paris! https://t.co/V8nMKEbpjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't want to forget tribal elders who went to jail to protest this ill conceived pipeline through First Nation... https://t.co/I7T8wRMupc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius! It's time to expose gun lobby racists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wendell Pierce Tweet Exposes Hypocrisy of American Gun Control Laws | Urban Intellectuals https://t.co/zJaefYqyLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NsWcCgUX8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong, wrong,wrong. Connect the dots. In the past three weeks in C. Springs there have been two Christian... https://t.co/4OssoT3cap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0pAEFVYeNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, please.  I always prefer small steps. Lots to catch up on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8gVoFSawYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plain and simple Christian terrorist attacks - home grown. https://t.co/gqwmaBgYec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not parse these acts of terror. Let's call it what it is, home grown Christian extremists killing six... https://t.co/3O07UbbT70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this relaxing and special. https://t.co/DyYZxsZ7Q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the second attack by Christian terrorists in my home town in three weeks. https://t.co/O9oEo6V81L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunman wounds two cops and several others outside Planned Parenthood clinic in Colorado Springs https://t.co/xo69ID9b7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JbuI2Ffc9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yBA1j6Cmsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Z0ENL5WqJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these people from other countries play one song together. Imagine the possibilities. https://t.co/Nafcfkg42A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK...now I feel safe! https://t.co/YBaypRoatz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/spwdwZrojf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DM@shanakassa yes, where to meet? I am @ 1st &amp; Arbutus in kits or can come to your apt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rThXXR7Cjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KrE5PaTc4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(uncensored) Your naked body is not a crime. Is nude art obscene? https://t.co/7J3I2W6lzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rLdNkA7ney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PD8djk0dko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of 90s folk with a hint of John Mayer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds pretty whiney to me. In fact moot. Maybe the person has not heard that the new Prime Minister of... https://t.co/g4UXvClLaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National emergency? Belgians respond to terror raids with cats https://t.co/veUbhaN8Vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ojHBeu9jRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anonymous are now ‘rickrolling’ Isis https://t.co/GXVK0yiqUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what ISIS sees on its social networks. Anonymous now wears white hats? https://t.co/soFSEXNnWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anonymous are now ‘rickrolling’ Isis https://t.co/XakajJgHhk via @Dazed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was cross-fit, now there's this... https://t.co/BP9Jpcj0q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love in Action: Occupy Spoken Word Piece with Drew Dellinger https://t.co/luFK8eDHma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to dust off Occupy. Spoken word. https://t.co/sksvcbeC4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this interview from my choice as best in the business over the past few years. She's seen it all in... https://t.co/x7yMLq7R8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LsiUgIm1ZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people whose lives were lost on November 13. https://t.co/MntQrvjaNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gp3VyQmavd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institute Special Update: The Crisis in Syria - International Institute of Minnesota https://t.co/5fDfmfi2QE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely a slam dunk for the President. https://t.co/jeBGHE8XCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A genius. https://t.co/PHH2NN5weL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each day hundreds of boats find a safe harbor in the Greek islands. Many never reach land. Somehow the survivors... https://t.co/MUY51VIkut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim Marine masterfully bashes Trump by posting his military ID badge: ‘Where’s yours?” https://t.co/G8x9E4MoCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nfSBCltRMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you prove you are a Christian....? https://t.co/uokgRjDPJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Republican test to make sure toddler refugees are not terrorists. https://t.co/7x0tXKwLWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/beqJETBuQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GhqetUGc05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The father is out of work and on the run from enemies and his wife is pregnant. https://t.co/UJz6lKfMMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS is not what you think. https://t.co/roCxc5SxNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa each year I look back. I am glad I climbed as a young man. I am blessed to have this adventure. Nice to hear from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sober reality check in the aftermath of Paris https://t.co/wPKDx5IhBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Weakening Islamic State Still Poses a Threat | Stratfor https://t.co/Y92BrXdjug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys outed some 50-plus KKK members, many of them Christian governors, now take on ISIS. https://t.co/4HgWDKhFoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30,000 Americans will die this year in the U.S. from domestic terror. Many of the terrorists will be Christians.... https://t.co/mW6e01nqwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intimate look post-tragedy. https://t.co/V8Rmzej1GH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this day, November 17, 1979, we climbed Ramdung Go, a 20k peak in the Rowaling Himalaya. I am here with Ang... https://t.co/CVtF7bl4Gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Syrian refugees have endured a hellish existence at the hands of tyrants, much as my forefathers did just a... https://t.co/QaDHAp7jI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XCrZZCzwEc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>