<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior White House official to resign following allegations of abuse - Washington Post https://t.co/i7i23tnwP7 https://t.co/hypkR9C2KI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House staff secretary Rob Porter has resigned https://t.co/AD4P2V4cki https://t.co/36OSvlb1hV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer: Deal is sprout of bipartisanship https://t.co/gMyjPGOSWp https://t.co/2V91Tnk1Ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy, 11, dies saving friend who fell through icy pond: 'God made him, and he made an angel' - https://t.co/2FGTO5skiU https://t.co/tse7etiEVt https://t.co/XCnzt4n99w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate leaders unveiled a two-year deal, a victory for both parties that could prevent a government shutdown https://t.co/Zfrl2mtB28 https://t.co/K3x4Nq3hDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for US military parade now underway https://t.co/M9d7f1lEgf https://t.co/FECqk9QO4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northbound I-95 closed 'indefinitely' in Palm Beach County after multi-vehicle crash, deputy-involved shooting - WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale https://t.co/OG93GYTAxM https://t.co/Ne9yiwG35X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northeast braces for up to a foot of snow as ice threatens commuters from Appalachia to New England - Daily Mail https://t.co/pUJqSitWOf https://t.co/ZNky9se9vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools, offices close as storm moves into Maine - Press Herald https://t.co/uhWYVGxWAW https://t.co/8VNzRi03dX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former CIA analysts: We can't trust Devin Nunes https://t.co/volKb5a5c3 https://t.co/grNTcvg7Gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polish President signs controversial Holocaust bill into law https://t.co/KPFX2YCwPJ https://t.co/BVc14Q0jzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eiffel Tower closed as heavy snowfall blankets Paris https://t.co/MSmiV0ZdUy https://t.co/ouiyLY3jiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly says he expects memo recommendations by Thursday https://t.co/zb0aEu9aNl https://t.co/WzbhKuTd9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman found holding her own eyeball outside South Carolina church - Fox News https://t.co/5hK18lOzBE https://t.co/IiEarGdBah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Threatens Shutdown as Negotiators Close In on Budget Deal - New York Times https://t.co/0bnjZ0oJ1c https://t.co/z8ZJs5CVTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un is sending his sister to South Korea for the Winter Games, the first time any member of the Kim dynasty has visited the country https://t.co/C7hFBcLUt2 https://t.co/pifH7lS6vP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After months of deadlock, Germany's main parties agree to form a coalition - Washington Post https://t.co/JaqwWZb3WX https://t.co/8tDe6BCD03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ana Navarro: Sick of Trump demonizing immigrants https://t.co/O7d1jod5Y2 https://t.co/NxCEZmHqrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbreak as heroic New York boy, 11, dies after successfully saving his pal, 12, who fell into frozen pond - Daily Mail https://t.co/pKJAxiXlWN https://t.co/6uRK290Uil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden: Dreamers not bargaining chips for wall https://t.co/cdVbIa7ejc https://t.co/xeejSnfFFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['He's a Hero': Boy Dies After Falling Through Ice, Pushing Friend to Safety: NYPD - NBC New York https://t.co/lLimUgIIOF https://t.co/IWlsFwkWcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gowdy Reflects on Past Investigations: I Always Get Asked 'Why Don't These People Go to Jail?' - Mediaite https://t.co/s2svriIRF7 https://t.co/oxqrwmF51X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst: Who's the 'rocket man' now? https://t.co/i5HXKw0mKF https://t.co/fSRf5kgKrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diplomats: N. Korea plans military parade on eve of Olympics https://t.co/J6YY2mQUIx https://t.co/ComVsaWmGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MRI reveals torn ligament in left knee of Knicks' Kristaps Porzingis - ESPN https://t.co/zss7C5nsW7 https://t.co/4TChQ9I7BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden: Trying like hell to do everything Beau would want me to do https://t.co/GEUXwjG3uv https://t.co/6VEQH2XCUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casino tycoon Steve Wynn resigns, citing 'avalanche' of bad publicity amid sex misconduct claims - USA TODAY https://t.co/1GS9vqP5hD https://t.co/TrRsYKvSHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Collins: GOP should return some Wynn money https://t.co/RvDtlHb66m https://t.co/oqv0bOHqTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House passes another spending patch as top party leaders finalize two-year budget deal - Washington Post https://t.co/SWPMycp4xF https://t.co/nKkGvTsyl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Josh McDaniels changes mind, will stay with Patriots and not take Colts job - ESPN https://t.co/uv7qyPlzbY https://t.co/7sZvyGr67s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions calls for 'fresh start' at FBI https://t.co/K4GSuUAnXS https://t.co/Tq1EBoMe4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wants a military parade 'like the one in France' https://t.co/KSRTZYIQsR https://t.co/LD6Wr5oJ65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump tells Pentagon to plan a military parade - CNN https://t.co/7Xx3wmLbRO https://t.co/c1p95JJQgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bharara: Trump has said only mobsters plead the 5th https://t.co/XDoq7ZWm9A https://t.co/hcST8KhwF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles Times owner will sell paper, ending a long-troubled relationship - Washington Post https://t.co/vUj5wtR7K7 https://t.co/7bEnxby8Ph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller biographer: Investigation is bigger than you think https://t.co/G0WxTsHqOP https://t.co/YgEqXayR9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans prepare to muscle through short-term spending bill https://t.co/uEGGdV2nGa https://t.co/VMHyAoWJbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polish leader signs controversial law on Holocaust speech - CBS News https://t.co/lBNMbHDeXK https://t.co/aOBS0wIEiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Did Kylie Jenner Name Her Baby Stormi? It's Definitely A Unique Moniker - Bustle https://t.co/K4pqmynufb https://t.co/Tl7L4eAcbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Shutdown worth it for our country https://t.co/4KE89XmKFQ https://t.co/jrt80e39tB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump spokeswoman fires back at Flake: 'His numbers are in the tank' - The Hill https://t.co/9VjaRC28nf https://t.co/q1Jh9tYsco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the moment Falcon Heavy lifts off https://t.co/IO2d82C8u0 https://t.co/2UBhbYGUA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Democrats 'don't want safety,' then shut it down, President says at roundtable on MS-13 gang https://t.co/SjzXokU0uu https://t.co/nes1tTGl9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contractor promised 30 million meals to Puerto Rico. Only 50000 were delivered. Lawmakers ask why. - CNN https://t.co/zzvn70YepL https://t.co/JGkYBEkFzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amtrak Acela train separates en route to Boston - New York Daily News https://t.co/PA5tgZ3D7B https://t.co/E5q9mCNr3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durbin: I don't see a shutdown coming https://t.co/XIVubuPwjR https://t.co/C6laPMUNxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan Rocked by 6.4 Magnitude Earthquake; Building Collapses Reported - The Weather Channel https://t.co/uJjqjxZwdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House says Trump's 'treason' remark was a joke https://t.co/hegiEpjvPp https://t.co/IWgHWPY101]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shutdown watch: Key House vote Tuesday https://t.co/t2X805ogir https://t.co/hDnEjBA8U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Tammy Duckworth: I swore an oath to the Constitution, not to clap when Trump demands - Washington Post https://t.co/CVwIk6eezO https://t.co/AjKbbqBf4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator fires back at 'Cadet Bone Spurs' after Trump called Democrats 'treasonous' - https://t.co/DnyL6nUbom https://t.co/0XlPKEBpkG https://t.co/V33dqZ1BaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow opens down 500 points. The index entered what's known as a correction — 10% off from its recent peak. https://t.co/NRbfcUGBVH https://t.co/MQfUiV0QJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No East Coast tsunami warning, National Weather Service says - CBS News https://t.co/NLfKviJykE https://t.co/FcrsDvGnTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened on the Dow's worst single-day point fall https://t.co/pwiGtKafsC https://t.co/Q6CGc0ub0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polish president to sign Holocaust bill despite international concerns - Washington Post https://t.co/MTC6P7e7bt https://t.co/fa3J1Nb2od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markets Right Now: Mideast markets suffer modest drop - SFGate https://t.co/uBC8rpkL4r https://t.co/LKB1VJh3Sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump is changing the GOP, not the other way around https://t.co/YezCx78LCo https://t.co/YcZYBDSaqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the GOP react to Obama's SOTU speeches https://t.co/gaHWHZeoIA https://t.co/KZaYVDPJpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian, European Markets Follow Wall Street, With Stocks Suffering Sharp Losses - NPR https://t.co/MVhqOd1yS3 https://t.co/Jmco0hLljX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House intelligence committee unanimously votes to release Democratic memo - CNN https://t.co/mhMyV326yO https://t.co/AiLuyhS85X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maldives' ex-president Nasheed urges India to intervene to resolve crisis - Reuters https://t.co/pafjTZCRVR https://t.co/dRZEHPSZXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain's absence hurts chances of Dreamers deal - Politico https://t.co/Sg6FDxmmFV https://t.co/ov3GGLMOS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires starting gun on 2018 elections https://t.co/WZ9O0HCYuX https://t.co/EtrLAaAleX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audit finds Pentagon agency mishandled hundreds of millions of dollars - CNN https://t.co/kwiSQFmPAW https://t.co/4a9xsIb3T6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's EPA chief called him an 'empty vessel' https://t.co/n2hIjx9DRG https://t.co/epf2TtvT0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weather Conditions Result in Crashes, Multiple Fatalities on Iowa Roads - https://t.co/D7tAsoB9LM https://t.co/boWOOltX3P https://t.co/pDKuccFSFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump accuser runs for office https://t.co/fM1v5U9IN9 https://t.co/2iGPTRtRcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China carries out anti-missile test amid tension over North Korea's nuclear programme - South China Morning Post https://t.co/T5YrTqQWdw https://t.co/tAACrABze0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times: Trump lawyers worried he could get caught lying to Mueller https://t.co/yOo1jWfJO9 https://t.co/vMSr4dm17X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Committee Votes to Release Democratic Rebuttal to GOP Russia Memo - New York Times https://t.co/Whfz76MXNZ https://t.co/Vx7C7usEa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Live by the Dow, die by the Dow. https://t.co/xcZNCWHuBG https://t.co/jCTqRuVthL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell holds the key to next week's immigration debate, and he's not talking https://t.co/RRSfCczPcX https://t.co/3rZkQtQ6Xe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress should censure Nunes. Just like McCarthy. - Washington Post https://t.co/y3uDYuW8xg https://t.co/s09zN5GDH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adds Schiff to his 'little' club https://t.co/rzr8VKPDtR https://t.co/2kcgSCOyr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: A stock market lesson for Trump - the hard way https://t.co/wjNmTgv7lt https://t.co/D3DrRhcmhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 deputy killed, others wounded in Colorado Springs shooting - Fox News https://t.co/2ROAUXg3nP https://t.co/AYMfnUtDpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Schiff: It's time Trump got a time out https://t.co/9IDP9mSeAD https://t.co/dZy4fwS1QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOD mishandled $465 million, audit finds https://t.co/v5TBXYo9RR https://t.co/QPx604Qyi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Frasier' Star John Mahoney Dies at 77 - Variety https://t.co/BcjV7vFNTe https://t.co/xmgmUChn1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: President thinks not clapping for him is 'treasonous' https://t.co/CZaXqcm0YL https://t.co/ox94cWZEMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump touts economy as market tanks - CNN https://t.co/Uuxud10FbB https://t.co/49KWlLiFEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House intelligence committee unanimously votes to release Democratic memo - CNN https://t.co/4LidQx4MBU https://t.co/V6bfKd0ndU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wants credit for no planes crashing. Should he get blamed for train crashes? https://t.co/fAeG7PE1Wo https://t.co/RZT5w9xHYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hostage situation under way at Miami restaurant, police say - Fox News https://t.co/zerIJkWV7t https://t.co/ug6dQ9CD4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schiff: Kelly should give Trump a time out https://t.co/BnwhX1V5Yz https://t.co/klNnb9eFbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpaceX's Falcon Heavy, ready for takeoff, faces a changing market for heavy-lift rockets - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/IQ6y39KweA https://t.co/tYSaS8LK35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's shifting views on stock market highs https://t.co/BQaTiUl0wg https://t.co/kiKT7euZx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump calls some Democrats 'treasonous' https://t.co/6w7lWkpXJs https://t.co/xvXslJ1gO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis received sex abuse victim's letter, contradicting denial - National Catholic Reporter https://t.co/SB9MaMbq9d https://t.co/uyEZfZY12y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wood's death remains mysterious https://t.co/WjLBJij9B2 https://t.co/vN3ZWMkK0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a blow to GOP, Supreme Court declines request to block a PA redistricting ruling https://t.co/8LNSuZ8UrB https://t.co/6VdoHAjDbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump uses Britain's protests to jump back into health-care fray at home - Washington Post https://t.co/t3wLqHIlDM https://t.co/4xxI1IkWWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two years ago, Scott Pruitt called Trump an 'empty vessel' on 'the Constitution https://t.co/dyBxraETeK https://t.co/BbY7i7MzLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Justice Allows New Pennsylvania Congressional Voting Map - Bloomberg https://t.co/N7ktvo09A6 https://t.co/dcTQ7ummha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP expected to agree to send Democratic memo to Trump https://t.co/uwU4ORAK06 https://t.co/hoNNXCuFAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says Nunes may become a 'Great American Hero' https://t.co/OgRH52rntj https://t.co/C5E4TBYxk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 tortured arguments Republicans are making about the Nunes memo - Washington Post https://t.co/MQmPhl0fvs https://t.co/Wu5ZMvOuzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former CIA director: Nunes abused his office https://t.co/RC0r6oh2jj https://t.co/ZY8Q7XcojO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US forces begin reducing numbers in Iraq after authorities declare victory over ISIS - AOL https://t.co/GK0ZkCFEwC https://t.co/kDQ0UPsPzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump slams 'little Adam Schiff' as Democrats push to release their memo https://t.co/30Pccnxohl https://t.co/Q8qAwkp5LE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>