<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jordan_law21: New blog post at Stem Legal: How to make your Twitter biography count: http://bit.ly/a10V56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for new followers -- I'll do my best to remain worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad: just returned from Chicago from last in-person board mtg of Int'l Legal Mktg Assoc . Great city; terrific board. Proud of our wrk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats, Josh! RT @joshchandler: Have been added to the @Mama_To_4/cool-tweeps Twitter list (OK, this is just too nice, thanks Heather!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, Colin! RT @colincameron: Client Relations: Creating Loyalty in Your Best Clients http://bit.ly/auQrKY by @lawyerPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab the Oct Lexpert, flip to the back page and read Marzena's latest column. LOL thru the whole column!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For your bucket list: Maui's Four Seasons Hotel. Simply divine... particularly if you're ready to part with a lot of cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matwilcox: Until I was 13, I thought my name was SHUT UP.  - Joe Namath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Riskin: Tonight I love Alaska Airlines and unlove Delta #Fail very much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing the LMA board and incoming board in Chicago soon! Such a fine group!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw @erinmconnell last night... looking so fine, optimistic & spreading good words for Wilcox staff.  Interested employers better move fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Brit Petro! For the next junk shot: Plug the oil leak with Wall Street derivatives, Greek bonds... and BP shares. - P. Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sting concert still echoing in my head and my ears are still smiling.  "Desert Rain" w/orchestral arrangement was quite simply  magical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for my pal Val who just became a partner in her Vanc design studio. Woo-hoo!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouverites: must attend LMA "Leverage competitive intell" how-to seminar, May 27 -- http://bit.ly/aSZLdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beloved followers, please note: @susanvandyke now @lawyerPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Did you cheer and holler en francais?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites I'm still a card-carryng member of the page-turnng media consumer.  I even &lt; GASP &gt;  clip out articles  & draw mustaches on faces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For parents desperate to keep up.... XYZ = EX-amine Your Zipper, according to my 8-yr old boy. He musta heard this a few times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc  Enjoying @cbcnewsbc tweets. Hardly need to read/watch news anymore!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawTimes: CL editor GCohen moderating LMA panel  May 27 "Everything U need to know about the ACC Value Challenge" http://bit.ly/8ZEEd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unmarketing WOW. Shocking :) That's a different person!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevematthews Brilliant.  Thanks, Steve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of getting spam comments on my blog via WordPress.  Takes time to weed them out. Any suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Sporting a great new image! How DO you get your teeth so white?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatSlavin Hoping for a full recovery for your sister, Nat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy with my web team -- creative, fast, professional, fair fees and oh so easy to work with.  Can't wait to share latest launch w/U!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OttawaLawyers COFFEE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougJasinski: facebook privacy policy is now longer than US constitution.  Check out the graphic: RT @wired: http://nyti.ms/ay3Uuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful & easy site RT @LexisNexisCan: Need a lawyer? Find a lawyer and Canadian legal information on Canadian-Lawyers.ca http://ow.ly/1K2rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuku Very cool. Good luck with that. I've also been integrating SM into my clients' plans -- so nice to be playing with new tools, huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites ROFL ... while counting down the minutes until you responded. So not kidding!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougJasinski (AKA Papa Skunk) Continues to be my twitter hero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotsa new followers! Thanks for joining me, gang. I'll strive to be worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. Will that be fun? RT @DougJasinski: RT @bcbusiness: Dave Cobb named new president and CEO of BC Hydro: http://is.gd/c4SwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx, Mr. Cape Twn! RT @siphojanuary: Kul RT @wileyccoyote TYVM, gang :) @palmerreuther @siphojanuary @susanvandyke @billybadbird  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx, girl! RT @wileyccoyote: TYVM, gang! :) @palmerreuther @siphojanuary @susanvandyke @billybadbird @BethFrysztak @NewlineCreative...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this one RT @david_bilinsky: "Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new." A. Einstein.  #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm.. where did everybody go? Houston, we have a problem. #FAIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TX! RT @gaillamarche: @wileyccoyote @susanvandyke @lalaland999 @m_margette @FTFortMyers @creative_girl @StateInsurance1 tx 4 RT's & fdback!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is the ability to go from one failure to another with no loss of enthusiasm. " -- Sir Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't have everything. Where would you put it? " -- Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian dollar crashing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gaillamarche: #LMA friends, if U know a legal secretary job in San Diego, let me know; former colleague now in So Cal looking for work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougJasinski: @jordan_law21 is now addressing LinkedIn for law firms over on Stem's LFWS blog (via @stevematthews): http://bit.ly/aXH5pT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisdom from a dentist: floss only the teeth you want to KEEP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling giddy ... Vancouver forecast is SUN for next 4 days. You'll hardly see a prettier city or happier people than on a sunny Van w'end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People might forget what you said or did, but they won’t forget how you made them feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always row together. You’re in this together, only to differing degrees. Some r partners, some not, but all working 4 clients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With evry invoice u send a client, summarize your achievements & value. Dates, phone calls, e-mails, reports do not nec = value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Media Skills: lawyer as spokesperson (LexisNexis) video. After 18 yrs in corp comunications, kinda glad I'm not learning much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. Who's got the fire hose at Harper Grey? RT @cbcnewsbc: Kash Heed resigns again following revelations that ... http://bit.ly/cAKMXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My former firm Harper Grey making front page news today re Kash Heed investigation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palin... the gift that keeps on giving RT @matwilcox: Sarah Palin is so....well....watch for yourself.  http://bit.ly/bG6i4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx for the RT @NatSlavin: RT @susanvandyke: Client fdbck programs' value : ignore them and they will go away http://tinyurl.com/23n8c7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Good one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client feedback programs' value summed up: ignore them and they will go away http://tinyurl.com/23n8c7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @TaraCain!: RT @susanvandyke: Do you know any great lawyers who want to work for a *fabulous firm* in Maple Ridge/Pitt Meadows area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know any great lawyers who want to work for a *fabulous firm* in Maple Ridge/Pitt Meadows area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinaschenbren Happy belated birthday, Kev!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Hey, there's an echo on your twitter page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Go on, what's your elevator pitch, Mat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox What's yours, Mat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current rant: who's the wise guy who started packaging spices in quantities that won't fit in a standard spice jar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevwrites: Thanks to all who read my Klout piece on @natlawreview. It's a top 3 story for January! http://bit.ly/gjbXz9 #fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I see light at the end of a very busy spell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Hunger Games by Suzanne Collins was riveting. Forgot I was reading and was running for my life. Exhausted now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites GRRRRRrrrrr!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Spirit bears are OK only if toothless, de-clawed & recently fed. But you have to hold trademark - now owned by bc gov't. No joke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Heather & I were asked to redraft their mktg rules & I only remember their concern about grizzly bears in mktg material ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heather & I were asked to redraft their mktg rules and I only remember discussing their concern about grizzly bears in mktg material ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miss604 But then that would be like saying "pennies from heaven" and just doesn't sound right when referring to govt ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't law firm tweets ever state "we hammered the other side"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law Society of BC just informed me some of my published material will be used at PLTC (bar admission course). Feeling honoured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law Society of BC just informed me some of my published material will be at used at PLTC (bar admission course). Feeling honoured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aceismyname Tx, JR.  Adore my LMA pals . Should I worry,tho? No Canadians on the 2011 inter'l board now.  Who's gonna correct spelling ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finishd my last inter'l legal mktg assoc board mtg.  I'll chair my last committee call tmrw, then I'm done. I'll miss these colleagues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun night last night with my LMA Van pals at winter social. My last official appearance as a board member...sad, happy, proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6th or 7th contact into 800flowers  (aka @bloomex) for cust service.  Brutal. Finally promised new flowers coming Monday.  Will they arrive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trucks rolling now! RT @lawheadhunter: McQuarrie Hunter merges all offices to Surrey, now largest firm in Surrey.  http://ow.ly/3nn2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoughtonLaw OMG, Boughton: you've never looked better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccawcheung Thanks! I wrote that article in 2008. There are probably 2 more dozen of mine on the CBA site. Love to hear from readers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraCain MEC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now on live chat with operator from @bloomex - 4th method... this is getting interesting. .. great ex of how NOT to treat your customers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 days and counting ... still no response from @bloomex. I've e-mailed, phoned and tweeted. What else to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraCain Craig's List!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated pic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, umm, does City Hall need a building permit to do renovations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG RT @cbcnewsbc: unconfirmed reports 2 construction workers killed on  job sites in downtown Vancouver  http://bit.ly/eC6deM #yvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc Hey, here's an idea... what would happen if Carole James and Gordon Campbell ventured off together? Discuss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox Love that. Big shout out to Sam for his words of wisdom #taxiadvice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client response to my comment? "Huh.  And here I thought mktg was advtg and sponsorships." Evidently, there's still a lot of work to do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's comment 2 a client: mktg isn't only dazzling visuals + words, it's also closing gaps btw ur service, client needs + expectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of new followers over the past coupla weeks. Thanks for joining me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox I chat with cabbies all the time, too. Do you ever get the same driver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leonard Cohen concert from the box suite tonight... yeah , baby! Anyone else going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good 1 RT @david_bilinsky: "The best angle from which 2 approach any problem is the try-angle. " ~Unknown #quotes #humor #solosmall #bclaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start a legal blog! RT @CherylBame: Considering whether 2 blog?  Check out Legal PR Advice on how to get started. http://bit.ly/eJ9TIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo! RT @BoughtonLaw: Boughton repeats tradition of sponsoring low-income families thru the YWCA’s Presents of... http://bit.ly/fYxgT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelawyercoach and I presented a jam-packed TagLaw webinar for associates on critical steps for success. So fun to tag-team with Allison!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>