<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very engaging interview with the splendid James Wood by @emmabrockes https://t.co/WTV4P2Eo9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Macron's contemporaries recalls: "Il était assez bon en name dropping culturel."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Henri-IV, the young Macron affected a long black overcoat and would declaim the poetry of René Char in a "theatrical voice".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would have happened if Macron had not failed the entrance exam for Normal Sup? https://t.co/UdbkqI5FRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful journey through the career of Art Blakey by Geoffrey Smith https://t.co/kSG9zIvhlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allsorts100 All Blues and Flamenco Sketches recorded at the end of the following month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Side one of Kind of Blue was recorded 59 years ago today. Imperishable. https://t.co/Vk78yCS5S6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jazzonthisday: Miles Davis recorded Kind of Blue, the bestselling jazz record of all time, #onthisday in 1959. The iconic album was rec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have @tconnellyRTE writing for @ftcomment on Brexit, the border and souring Anglo-Irish relations https://t.co/6rqmkGsSY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SebastianEPayne: Theresa May’s road to Brexit: @FinancialTimes commentators on the speech - thoughts from @EuroBriefing @sarahgor @gide…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this week's @FinancialTimes comment and opinion on Xi Jinping's empire in one place https://t.co/FgP72oYkqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPittBrooke @mrianleslie Terrific piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rbrtrmstrng: Londoners stink at snow https://t.co/0K4eKT1TIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gilliantett: Excellent pithy take by @EdwardGLuce on the White House mess(es) https://t.co/V0xdKIpDNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two experts go head to head on whether it's time to roll back US bank regulation https://t.co/ApLOxCDJrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Silva for organising fascinating dinner with Richard Sennett. Rich discussion of urbanism, planning &amp; London's future after Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spitalfields https://t.co/ztGlPn68rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[East Dulwich https://t.co/PhJhiUGZhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GavinJKelly1: 1. In January 2017 Zac Cox, my brother-in-law, died working in the World Cup Stadium in Qatar. The Coroner’s Inquest conc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's suddenly gone all 1950s on Southwark Bridge https://t.co/ECS23uBSlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TonyBarber8 on the slow motion collapse of Europe's centre left https://t.co/Gcsk0w0Un0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autocracy vs democracy - @martinwolf_ on Xi's gambit https://t.co/fFQew5hEys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent from @MESandbu on Labour's constructive embrace of a customs union https://t.co/lmu9bYRyk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KuperSimon: UK business prefers even Corbyn’s fantasies to May’s Brexit https://t.co/CO3Rg6EsaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign up to the @FinancialTimes' morning opinion email here https://t.co/1hoJmqAmiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not so much a blood match as a friendly get-together of fellow members of the newly enlarged European community."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Three vs The Six - the "Common Market match", Wembley, 1973 https://t.co/17zv5GA5tO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChassNews @FT The precedents for taking on the cheminots are not especially auspicious are they? #1995andallthat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sathnam: This graduate scheme changed my life
https://t.co/kK4wEasybJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SlaughterAM channels Carlyle and Thoreau in this @FinancialTimes op-ed on the backlash against Big Tech https://t.co/vhqZzh4ym7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GavinJKelly1: Britain's long experiment with mediocre management. My piece for @ft. https://t.co/v7yVcDzhYR https://t.co/yXfWSxVqSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/b15u4FXeOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Clegg on the government's misguided venture in economic basketry https://t.co/hdSMw30uIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This confrontation between Macron and a farmer yesterday is quite something https://t.co/vOkM3CpnxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FinancialTimes: FT View: Why Theresa May’s fragile Brexit truce is unlikely to last for long https://t.co/r0O9nh6ZFR https://t.co/ZW8CI…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CER_Grant: EU rejection will be much quicker than that, as I explain in @FT: https://t.co/kjNozqcAoN https://t.co/rzAD8HsXRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCWild Friday night post-bop https://t.co/MGPk7gllGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all the @FinancialTimes' commentary on Brexit this week in one place https://t.co/S5xAxJsq60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, in which @TomHale_ patiently explains the difference between savings and gifts, is very good https://t.co/RhPrzvv8lI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwinheathcote Apparently, the inspiration was the Wittgenstein Haus in Vienna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very pleased to see @JessGreengrass's philosophical novel getting such good reviews. I remember, in a previous life, marking her excellent essays on Heidegger! https://t.co/kpQAZJip1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swooning over Habermas's house in Bavaria https://t.co/JLoF5sECco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JeanBirnbaum: Une longue et belle rencontre avec le philosophe Jürgen Habermas, chez lui, près de Munich, c’est la une (et un dossier d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great: Ann Olivarius on the overdue opening up of the Rhodes Scholarship https://t.co/CNPBlEZNZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philipstephens on the yawning geopolitical gap where American leadership used to be https://t.co/PLOyh1nuKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head still full of @nilsfrahm after last night's show at the Barbican. Bach meets Bill Evans meets Kraftwerk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating @RanaForoohar column on the lessons to learn from the success of Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/jnNkpN0bU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful profile of Andy 'Extended Mind' Clark by @LarissaMacFarqu https://t.co/7MMK7BlsrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilosophyMttrs: You Can't Unsee This :  Happy Birthday Rocky Descartes ! https://t.co/USgOOeh7i9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Their racism is a warped deformation of their leftism" - a powerful column by @Freedland on the socialism of fools https://t.co/BB9RLWXGBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Sennett for @ftcomment on how London can reinvent itself after Brexit  https://t.co/2dnPex7epy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joedgoldberg: This is a must watch. It shows how Jewish members feel it is tbeir duty to complain on what are bang to rightals cases an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a great Easter read: ten dispatches from the @FinancialTimes' correspondents around the world https://t.co/Kt1wXeNpwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andrewtghill: "This should be played on a loop before every important board meeting." My Instant Insight on the tearful Australian skip…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats off to @boroughwines_mk for stocking the wines of the former Habsburg Empire #mitteleuropa https://t.co/X2hcZoFQQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalcolmMoore: Evidence of the value of the information in our Brexit coverage. https://t.co/nXbpFUC0nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mireille Knoll a vécu le Shoah dans son appartement" - moving (and chilling) interview with Auschwitz survivor Marceline Loridan-Ivens https://t.co/bH8Jg9khuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L'affaire Kristeva takes another turn: she denies she is "Sabina", the agent recruited by the Bulgarians in 1971 https://t.co/8G6YisjUsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As did, for the record, Jean-Luc Mélenchon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine Le Pen got short shrift when she turned up at the Marche pour Mireille Knoll  https://t.co/c7D0nUDPIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenmiranda: Pleasantly melancholic Suffolk thread https://t.co/sQyRktNOqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenmiranda: Story of the day https://t.co/M78KncLXnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today France buries Arnaud Beltrame and marches in memory of Mireille Knoll, survivor of the rafle du Vél' d'Hiv, who was murdered in an appalling anti-Semitic attack on Friday https://t.co/WMtMCiMGR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harikunzru: Seems like Laurent Binet’s tongue in cheek casting of Kristeva and Sollers as villains in The 7th Function of Language is b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good shortlist https://t.co/aCPw4dcO5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahchurchwell @philosophybites It is indeed a great gig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FinancialTimes: Brooke Masters: Westfield has become the Death Star of malls — pulling shoppers from all over London into its orbit and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @leafarbuthnot: Brilliant evening hosted by @AllenLaneBooks with the French writer Didier Eribon. His timely memoir Returning to Reims d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rglucks1: Échapper à la rafle du Vel d'hiv pour finir poignardée, brûlée, chez soi, dans le 11e arrondissement, 76 ans plus tard, par u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@simon_schama on the socialism of fools from February 2016 https://t.co/ExDSWzSMZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gendarmerie: #DGGN C'est avec une très vive émotion que je souhaite rendre solennellement hommage à l'héroïsme de notre camarade A.Belt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH @spacemagick Unfortunately not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gursky https://t.co/QFazE1VCyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StewartWood: The German Social Democrats had an expression in the 1890s: "Anti-semitism is the socialism of fools". Sadly, Labour's lea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the @FinancialTimes's commentary on a bad week for Big Tech in one place https://t.co/RnCI8Y5iHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great collection of pieces by @MESandbu on the future of macroeconomics https://t.co/Rb7PrDd2VX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @tmitchpk on Liu He, China's real second in command and the man who will have to fight the trade war with the US https://t.co/TjI1p7Er5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fadgadget "Ne'er cast a clout ..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are entering the phase of Trump unbound" - @EdwardGLuce on the appointment of John Bolton https://t.co/nKRUgh9p5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary show at the Barbican this evening by the king of Ethiopian jazz, Mulatu Astatke https://t.co/Z1HeRlbDWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 March, 1968 and 2018 https://t.co/dRK4xYIPXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johngapper reminds me that Michal Kosinski wrote for the @FinancialTimes about the Cambridge pyschometric research into Facebook likes back in 2013 https://t.co/GgoSyU4DUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good: @lemondefr on six key moments in the student movement of May '68 https://t.co/ro8HjXEkPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Wolf makes the case for radical reform of Council Tax https://t.co/jmkrkmR9P3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FinancialTimes: Just published: front page of the Financial Times UK edition, Thursday March 22 https://t.co/rtRAKMvpzE https://t.co/nn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouf! Sarko https://t.co/O67qWLrzso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sublime date was recorded 54 years ago today  https://t.co/3oo8hpuJr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimHarford: Economics failed us before the global crisis, says @martinwolf_ - https://t.co/zvotOBBEUs via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_tooze @martinwolf_ Thought this chart showing Germany's recovery under Hitler was pretty extraordinary too https://t.co/QGmMaSNgxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RanaForoohar on five bad things that have happened to Big Tech this week https://t.co/Dy9NfGtr7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philipstephens: Three cheers for the European Commission’s tax on tech https://t.co/TWcOC0Bu6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix someone else's research with quantities of Old Etonian chutzpah, and bingo! @johngapper on CA's  business model https://t.co/zGDbLxw9QN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wire, 1979 https://t.co/GCxJl7wwyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If cities only work for the highly paid, they just don’t work - great column by @sarahoconnor_  https://t.co/XXxm9WeeE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidallengreen: A Withdrawal Agreement for a Brexit in name only.

By me, at @FT: https://t.co/AnmDXN4Pvw https://t.co/Fcs1XZ6bMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rebeccamead_NYC: fascinating @MJSchulman profile of Marianne Elliott, Brit director of staggering new Bway production of the always sta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adam_tooze: “A German finance minister is a German finance minister, the party affiliation plays no role there,” Should this line from…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BlakeBaileyOn: Happy 85th birthday, Philip Roth! https://t.co/od1efQd66h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful column by @johnthornhillft on the Cambridge Analytica affair: we've allowed an informational resource to turn into a cesspit https://t.co/RhZgRZek8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By the end of the tour, Coltrane seems somewhat transfigured ..." @tnyfrontrow on Miles and Trane's last tour https://t.co/CwkzgWLMqo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>