<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is no struggle, there is no progress. (Frederick Douglass)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HumanityNeeds: More revolutionary strength, less capitalist fetishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a human being first and foremost, and as such I am for whoever and whatever benefits humanity as a whole.(Malcolm X)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm for truth, no matter who tells it. I'm for justice, no matter who it's for or against. (Malcolm X)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: The Revolution: a true revolution does not create a new class of elites, it simply wipes out hints of elitism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to deal with an unfree world is to become so absolutely free that your very existence is an act of rebellion.(Camus)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imperialism leaves behind germs of rot which we must clinically detect and remove from our land but from our minds as well.(Fanon)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Mass Culture: a culture tailored and crafted by the elite ideology then fed to the hungry masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are decades where nothing happens; And there are weeks where decades happen. (V.I. Lenin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AIbertCamus: Language must be used to inspire the audience never to indulge the author's literary desires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How beautiful! It's the revolution!" Ernest Mandel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By surrendering my life to the revolution, I found eternal life. (Huey P. Newton)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YgamblingSucks: Gambling is an institution that solicits feelings of money-worship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By rejecting the love of one, I received the love of all. (Huey P. Newton)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By having no possessions, I have possessed all. (Huey P. Newton)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HowAdsBrainwash: by making you long for stuff instead of deep social relations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By having no family, I inherited the family of humanity. (Huey P. Newton)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today it is a case of the grasshopper pitted against the elephant. But tomorrow the elephant will have its guts ripped out. ~Ho Chi Minh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Weapons Scientists: well paid professional who use exotic vacations to cover up their guilty conscience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A populace never rebels from passion for attack, but from impatience of suffering . Edmund Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a rebel? A man who says no. ~Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: 84 percent of prison inmates throughout the world were abused as children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The serious revolutionary, like the serious artist, can't afford to lead a sentimental or self-deceiving life. ~Adrienne Rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revolution has always been in the hands of the young. The young always inherit the revolution. ~Huey Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InjusticeFacts: John Kellogg (the cereal tycoon) founded the Race Betterment Foundation, an organization which planned to sterilize min…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolutions are not made by men in spectacles. ~ Oliver Wendell Holmes Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolutions are not made with rosewater. ~ E.G. Bulwer-Lytton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShitUDontNeed: Vacations, the locals hate the tourists, the tourists are usually middle class people trying to pretend they're upper cl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When all other rights are taken away, the right of rebellion is made perfect. ~Thomas Paine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are inclined to compromise can never make a revolution. ~Ataturk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HowAdsBrainwash: by weakening your love for other human beings and strengthening you love for stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An oppressed people are authorized whenever they can to rise and break their fetters. ~Henry Clay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who would be free must strike the first blow. ~Frederick Douglass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The freedom of all is essential to my freedom. ~Mikhail Bakunin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rosa__Luxemburg: Salvation through revolutionization!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In general, the vitality and relative dignity of an animal can be measured by the intensity of its instinct to revolt. ~Mikhail Bakunin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To revolt is a natural tendency of life. Even a worm turns against the foot that crushes it. ~Bakunin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: Google supported the Egyptian revolution with web applications; Yahoo censored all emails dealing with the Wall Street…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love without role, without power plays, is revolution.- RITA MAE BROWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The job of the writer is to make revolution irresistible.- TONI CADE BAMBARA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2GetFired: Send your boss an accidental text that says 'I can't wait for the revolution!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolution begins with the self, in the self. - TONI CADE BAMBARA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our homeland is the whole world. Our law is liberty. We have but one thought, revolution in our hearts. - DARIO FO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Malcom___X: Capitalist corporations are racist organizations which continue to ensure the oppression of the African American community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a revolution, damnit! We're going to have to offend somebody! - PETER STONE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can jail a Revolutionary, but you can't jail the Revolution. - HUEY NEWTON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DearConservtive: The psychology of conservatism is a psychology of fascistic attachment to property.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spirit of revolution will not die while the hearts of these workers continue to beat. - ERNST TOLLER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When dictatorship is a fact, revolution becomes a right. - VICTOR HUGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Ivy League Colleges: ironically working class students would die to attend these institutions where brutality and indi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revolution is like a vessel filled with the pulsating heartbeat of millions of working people. - ERNST TOLLER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destroy everything. Don't build on the past. There is no past. - JOHN CORIGLIANO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the people behind me and the people are my strength. - HUEY NEWTON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The history of the human race always has been, and most likely always will be, that of revolution. - LEWIS F. KORNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: The Corporation: a machine which says to the individual, either become a consumer or be doomed to a life of suicidal i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to conquer, what we need is to dare, still to dare, and always to dare. - Georges Jacques Danton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest revolution of our generation is the discovery that human beings can change their lives." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2SpotTraitor: Traitors to the left tend to be extremely volatile, emotional, absurdly sentimental.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['So early in my life, I had learned that if you want something, you had better make some noise.' - Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live your beliefs and you can turn the world around. - Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disobedience is the true foundation of liberty. The obedient must be slaves. - Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aim above morality. Be not simply good, be good for something. - Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RevPosters: Can someone create a poster with the words 'More Freedom, Less Submission' share using #RevolutionaryPosters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While there is a lower class, I am in it, while there is a criminal element, I am of it, while there is a soul in prison I am not free. Debs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no country to fight for; my country is the earth, and I am a citizen of the world - Eugene V. Debs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are certain that we are invincible, if humanity will not emerge from this imperialistic massacre broken in spirit it will triumph. -Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is no revolutionist who would have the revolution of the proletariat only under the "condition" that it proceed smoothly. -Tchernychewski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikhaiIBakunin: Anarchy is not about mindless pleasure-seeking, it is a political movement that exists within a revolutionary context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The millions of people armed in the holy cause of liberty...are invincible by any force which our enemy can send against us. - Patrick Henry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No real social change has ever been brought about without a revolution... revolution is but thought carried into action. - Emma Goldman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InjusticeFacts: After five years in a relationship the average couple make more eye contact with television show characters than each o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The political arena leaves one no alternative, one must either be a dunce or a rogue. - Emma Goldman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The revolutionary's real generosity toward the future lies in giving all to the present." Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dear__Teenagers: Material wealth will not broaden your intellectual scope. It will make you more ignorant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Political power grows out of the barrel of a gun." ~Mao Tse-Tung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world." ~Howard Zinn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WealthyFacts: According to Forbes, wealthy people do not like to live close to the community of citizens that they regularly exploit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Historically, the most terrible things - war, genocide, and slavery - have resulted not from disobedience, but from obedience." Howard Zinn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real technological revolution happened when people started using the internet to fight corruption and oppression. ~Mark Zuckerberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThomasJeffersin: Name one religion that has called on the people to revolt against their exploiters, systematically and politically? Of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is no measure of health to be well adjusted to a profoundly sick society." ~Krishnamurti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The revolution is not a moment or a day, the revolution is a way of life." ~Tupac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_RevoIution: I am the revolution and those who fear me are cowards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Poverty is the mother of all revolutions." ~Steve Jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Revolution is the festival of the oppressed' ~Germaine Greer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Capitalist Democracy: if 400 billionaires hoarded all the wealth of a nation would you consider this democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Revolution is not an action, it is a process." Huey Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Violence is man re-creating himself. ~Frantz Fanon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate victims who respect their executioners. ~Jean-Paul Sartre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay. ~Simone de Beauvoir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Howard__Zinn: Corporations are seizing control of the healthcare system ensuring that underprivileged citizens die of basic diseases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reform is for people who have government connections, revolution is for the people! ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A desire to resist oppression is implanted in the nature of man. ~Tacitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShitUDontNeed: Fast food, it's physical poison, mental poison, it weighs you down, it anchors you to the corporate production machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The king must die so that the country can live. ~Maximilien Robespierre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the forces in the world are not so powerful as an idea whose time has come: the revolution. ~Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Embezzlement: the bankers tapping the treasury in 2008 like it's their personal piggy bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell the children the truth. ~Bob Marley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you're living? ~Bob Marley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JFKennedys: Vote with your political actions instead of voting for the handpicked puppets of your enemy class.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>