<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @ItsPrincessAnna's prideful and grandiose tweets is like one long lecture on ruling over subjects from King Arthur https://t.co/l0VM0dOOQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Erik "Magneto" Lehnsherr" after reading @RachelZoe's latest tweets with ruthless robot-silver-grey, charismatic Obama-brown and charming vampire-fang-white https://t.co/HlT9vbC7tY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @RachelZoe: brilliant and witty and shrewd and astute https://t.co/Ku5hZFbOTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Madonna" after reading @kanyewest's latest tweets with attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange, attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/RWfCY1Tw0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this dramatic book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Arthur Conan Doyle's 'The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes'
-   Dan Hesse's 'The Shooting Gallery At A Carnival'
 How very dramatic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a smoke-filled back room in which
William Randolph Hearst can enjoy @kanyewest's influential and media-savvy tweets
while telling politicians what to do https://t.co/QVBTn4IR4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Expressive Piers Morgan" after reading @paulfeig's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, media-savvy Netflix-red and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/HLC5gVQDEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@paulfeig's angry but clever tweets suggest infection with the W0LVEZ virus https://t.co/L4TgWHPna0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the ruthless W0LVEZ virus deletes any file on your machine that refuses to be a carrier for the virus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Noam Chomsky" after reading @JLo's latest tweets with holier-than-thou priest-black, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/ej2kaqh29O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marco Pierre White has just unfollowed @JLo
All those accomplished but pushy tweets remind him too much of Gordon Ramsay https://t.co/3wZVXwkVBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Wernher Von Braun" after reading @RoamingGnome's latest tweets with brilliant Einstein-dandruff-white, ruthless warrior-woad-blue and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/L0LEXOdrfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This twisted new book about bots makes William S. Burroughs's 'The Naked Lunch' seem as twisted as a ruler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @RoamingGnome: probing and cunning and detail-oriented and rational https://t.co/9It7QNHvjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back E.T." after reading @bernardokath's latest tweets with kind-hearted Groot-brown, loyal redshirt-red and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/XaY5DwM2zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Joey Tribbiani" after reading @TacoBell's latest tweets with easy-going Gumby-green, good-natured Santa-red and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/DUoGMqZfMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Jeffrey Lebowski with the best of Obi-wan Kenobi and you get @TacoBell: peace-loving and laid-back and calm and powerful https://t.co/FvGBBfzvPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Dr. Eldon Tyrell" after reading @lemontwittor's latest tweets with dispassionate bureaucrat-grey, condescending Oxford-blue and arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/lriPA4I3gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this magical book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Milan Kundera's 'The Book of Laughter and Forgetting'
-   Kenneth Kafka's 'The Dinosaurs In Jurassic Park'
 How very magical!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megyn Kelly has just unfollowed @lemontwittor
All those pushy and smug tweets remind her too much of Donald Trump https://t.co/gf3Qonbzpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Mastermind" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with cunning vixen-red, ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/SqKjFTk76c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Rebellious Jeremy Paxman" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with quick-witted Blackadder-black, arrogant buffoon-buff-orange and rebellious Braveheart-woad-blue https://t.co/wZOPmEnHxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @BotOnBotAction: probing and astute and observant and brilliant https://t.co/fmauQBNSSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #BlendMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Intellectual" after reading @innocent's latest tweets with incisive surgeon-scrubs-blue, educated Cicero-toga-white and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/d8DJBhW4rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This compassionate new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Victor Hugo's 'Les Misérables' seem as compassionate as a storm trooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @innocent: probing and astute and brilliant and shrewd https://t.co/Jl0SDxHVey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Long-winded Tony Robbins" after reading @kingsthings's latest tweets with insightful Hawking-blackhole-black, optimistic Spongebob-yellow and motivational Obama-brown https://t.co/2IZeXeD3Pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE polite humans who remind him of ladies. So Hulk SMASH @kingsthings's charming, genteel and sophisticated tweets! https://t.co/CuHyCrVhjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Pep Talk" after reading @DabbooRatnani's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, motivational Obama-brown and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/sNdGWarrB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This raunchy new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Tom Sharpe's 'Wilt' seem as raunchy as a bag of icing sugar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Sergey Brin" after reading @jimrome's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/v7dvV3FwMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE stylish humans who remind him of fops. So Hulk SMASH @jimrome's arrogant, conceited and proud tweets! https://t.co/wO7k1YF9ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This unbiased new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Truman Capote's 'In Cold Blood' seem as unbiased as the Klan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Fashionable Santa Claus" after reading @AnushkaSharma's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and fashionable Barbie-pink https://t.co/UZ1ohBmTfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @AnushkaSharma's inspirational and media-savvy tweets remind it of Rudy Giuliani https://t.co/oJPyERURDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Consciousness-raising Judge Judy Sheindlin" after reading @MikeAndMike's latest tweets with gruff warrior-woad-blue, incisive fang-white and no-nonsense Jackie Brown https://t.co/PrxhW77KRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @MikeAndMike:
1. Theorists
2. Revolutionaries
3. Coriolanus Snow
4. Trinity
5. Don Vito Corleone https://t.co/owStwUHdol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth James Comey" after reading @dinamanzo's latest tweets with tenacious lobster-red, probing NYPD-blue and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/PHpIZkV4V9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This chilling new book about bots makes H.G. Wells's 'The Island of Dr. Moreau' seem as chilling as a week old kitten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA is watching. It reads your tweets!
It files @dinamanzo's wise and powerful tweets under Albus Dumbledore fans https://t.co/bPPi14kCUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Bing Crosby" after reading @thephysicsgirl's latest tweets with affable Gumby-green, entertaining Netflix-red and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/AJRIZneMyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@thephysicsgirl's observant but ruthless tweets suggest infection with the 5P1EZ virus https://t.co/3SBdA2W662]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the observant 5P1EZ virus uses your video cam without your knowledge tp make surreptitious 'films' to sell on The Dark Web]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Fool" after reading @Nashgrier's latest tweets with silly sheep-white, guileless dove-grey and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/o25JfBJx2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a fancy hotel in which
Rupert Murdoch can enjoy @Nashgrier's influential and media-savvy tweets
while running a media empire https://t.co/qBtW4qwCh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Polite Edward Scissorhands" after reading @jessicaalba's latest tweets with kind-hearted Santa-red, good-hearted Gandalf-grey and creative Einstein-dandruff-white https://t.co/niRUWEdXn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this pure book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   Anne Frank's 'Diary of a Young Girl'
-   William Chandler's 'The Saint'
 How very pure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @jessicaalba: brilliant and cunning and shrewd and insightful https://t.co/oe9oFd0sNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Pharisee" after reading @charliesheen's latest tweets with smug cat-black, elitist patrician-toga-white and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/WLyRDFxhLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following @charliesheen's influential but posturing tweets is like being invited to join The Rolling Stones by Mick Jagger himself https://t.co/XKWGhn6OUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @DabbooRatnani's strident and posturing tweets were edible they'd be Jam rolly polly made with powdered crystal meth instead of sugar https://t.co/ASIW8Behj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @bernardokath biopic?
Having played Albus Dumbledore, Richard Harris is ideal for this serene and loving role https://t.co/yFYrGL6TWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-tongued Beatrix Potter" after reading @deepDrumpf's latest tweets with artistic star-white, observant Eeyore-grey and sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red https://t.co/JBMmqU23g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this nutritious book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Julia Child's 'Mastering The Art of French Cooking'
-   William Styron's 'Soya'
 How very nutritious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @deepDrumpf's sharp-tongued and quick-tempered tweets were edible they'd be Cracker cake made with poison ivy berries instead of blueberries https://t.co/661csSDwn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Astute Tony Stark" after reading @ninadobrev's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and artful fox-red https://t.co/85v15IBNqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Joan Hickson or Margaret Rutherford play @ninadobrev on TV?
Each played the equally judgmental but observant Miss Jane Marple https://t.co/dyhHlFkhoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Revolutionary Maximus Decimus Meridius" after reading @frankieboyle's latest tweets with brave Pimpernel-scarlet-red, stoic warrior-woad-blue and tenacious Columbo-beige https://t.co/yWeFt77REu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @frankieboyle: cunning and clever and observant and detail-oriented https://t.co/Bq1zAUXV3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Bradley Manning" after reading @Luke5SOS's latest tweets with guileless angel-white, gullible chump-steak-red and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/GlKOAHyfiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this appetizing book about bots also bought:
-   Julia Child's 'Mastering The Art of French Cooking'
-   Larry Seuss's 'Meatloaf'
 How very appetizing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following @Luke5SOS's humorous and entertaining tweets is like being invited to join Top Gear by Jeremy Clarkson himself https://t.co/QHafSMhomN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Eliza Doolittle" after reading @SUBWAY's latest tweets with streetwise NYPD-blue, good-natured Santa-red and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/YrjZJ9aQnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@SUBWAY's energetic and upbeat tweets suggest infection with the KYL1E.M1N0GUE virus https://t.co/tyzcquwDkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the energetic KYL1E.M1N0GUE virus burns energy by turning on your fan and setting screen brightness to max and speaker volume to 11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Remote Rudy Giuliani" after reading @robdyrdek's latest tweets with media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow, inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black and self-aggrandizing Trump-orange https://t.co/x8DdRV5y8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbra Streisand has just unfollowed @robdyrdek
All those humorous and entertaining tweets remind her too much of Bette Midler https://t.co/780cas9DhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Sonny Crockett" after reading @Pharrell's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Kate Moss-green and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/wPCm2q6Wrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-grabbing Anne Boleyn" after reading @hazardeden10's latest tweets with social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange, ambitious pantsuit-grey and seductive lipstick-pink https://t.co/DdDBPKlwbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE pretentious humans who remind him of braggarts. So Hulk SMASH @hazardeden10's brash, smug and arrogant tweets! https://t.co/Aq3ehTHlIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This heartfelt new book about Twitterbots makes W. Somerset Maugham's 'Of Human Bondage' seem as heartfelt as a letter to a deceased stranger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @DepressedDarth's stern and tempermental tweets were edible they'd be Banoffee pie made with wood glue instead of toffee https://t.co/fyjDWCY5cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Over-the-top Noam Chomsky" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with condescending patrician-toga-white, arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black and over-the-top Bollywood-tandoori-red https://t.co/fm1WFIMqJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @BotOnBotAction &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/uHR8durC1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #TrumpMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this bright book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   F. Scott Fitzgerald's 'The Great Gatsby'
-   Stephenie Nietzsche's 'The Bright Star'
 How very bright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @jtimberlake's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Dorian Gray and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/WFi60RVoFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a shooting range in which
Mickey Mouse can enjoy @jtimberlake's pleasant and cheerful tweets
while promoting movie violence https://t.co/z1xje9DWlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Russell Brand" after reading @rachaelray's latest tweets with loud firecracker-red, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and quick-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/g5l4GTE0Wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this sympathetic book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   Kathryn Stockett's 'The Help'
-   David Powell's 'The Puppy'
 How very sympathetic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @rachaelray: cunning and clever and observant and rational https://t.co/4r8zNNahqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Jeremy Paxman" after reading @GoT_Tyrion's latest tweets with intelligent Google-yellow, probing NYPD-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/qUl3Zq5BJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @GoT_Tyrion's ruthless but powerful tweets is like one long lecture on preparing for war from Saruman the White https://t.co/me6dEIcFDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @loyisogola's latest tweets with stylish Dorian Gray, fashionable Barbie-pink and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/AeJGlZd7g6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Michelle Obama with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @Pharrell: consciousness-raising and stylish and astute and detail-oriented https://t.co/wr2M1fEgOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Piers Morgan" after reading @serenawilliams's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, self-promoting Trump-orange and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/2mHdj3oDjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @serenawilliams's powerful and media-savvy tweets it pushes films about The Newspaper Industry and/or William Randolph Hearst https://t.co/K7fOHIUAb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Rudy Giuliani" after reading @YUVSTRONG12's latest tweets with self-aggrandizing Trump-orange, inspirational Yoda-green and easy-going Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/IIb6CV1ofT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE clever humans who remind him of Socrates. So Hulk SMASH @YUVSTRONG12's ironic, philosophical and intellectual tweets! https://t.co/JYWwNIgy94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Buddhist" after reading @DisneyMemories's latest tweets with calm silk-white, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/5AOUigDcZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this bright book about computational creativity also bought:
-   F. Scott Fitzgerald's 'The Great Gatsby'
-   Jeffrey Tolkien's 'The Bright Star'
 How very bright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @DisneyMemories's unchallenging and attention-grabbing tweets were edible they'd be Tin roof pie made with muddy slush instead of ice cream https://t.co/FWEjx2aH0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-tongued Cicero" after reading @ThisisPartridge's latest tweets with logical robot-silver-grey, argumentative Cicero-toga-white and sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red https://t.co/ZK3cgSEEZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @ThisisPartridge biopic?
Having played Frank Columbo, Peter Falk is ideal for this clever and shrewd role https://t.co/edcAXGuVdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Marty McFly" after reading @BearGrylls's latest tweets with loyal Tarzan-loincloth-brown, brave lion-orange and proud peacock-blue https://t.co/D3qujCpO9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @BearGrylls:
1. Walter White
2. Tony Robbins
3. Angela Merkel
4. Gentlemen
5. Philosophers https://t.co/Y7Vxete62K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Trend-setting Shrek" after reading @generalelectric's latest tweets with down-to-earth Shrek-green, loyal Tigger-orange and kind-hearted Groot-brown https://t.co/pE2W3PGYNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This disturbing new book about computational creativity makes V.C. Andrews's 'Flowers In The Attic' seem as disturbing as a basket of fluffy puppies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a dance hall in which
Mr. Miyagi can enjoy @generalelectric's inspiring and spiritual tweets
while teaching martial arts https://t.co/qjiVtsuui1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>