<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["To love oneself is the beginning of a lifelong romance." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep in mind that neither success nor failure is ever final." - Roger W. Babson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Attitudes are more important than facts." - Dr. Karl Menninger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you'll not settle for anything less than your best, you will be amazed at what you can accomplish in your lives." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People rarely succeed unless they have fun in what they are doing." - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's always too soon to quit." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hide not your talents, they for use were made. What's a sun-dial in the shade." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door." - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed." - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am the greatest, I said that even before I knew I was." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ambition has one heel nailed in well, though she stretch her fingers to touch the heavens." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Light tomorrow with today." - Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're off to Great Places! Today is your day! Your mountain is waiting, So... get on your way!" - Dr Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you learn from defeat, you haven't really lost." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not length of life, but depth of life." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a window of opportunity appears, don't pull down the shade." - Tom Peters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is through cooperation, rather than conflict, that your greatest successes will be derived." - Ralph Charell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never ignore a gut feeling, but never believe that it's enough." - Robert Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ability to honestly and quietly reflect on one's life is one of the most powerful tools for personal growth." - Richard Carlson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your assumptions are your windows on the world.  Scrub them off every once in a while, or the light won't come in." - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Plans are only good intentions unless they immediately degenerate into hard work." - Peter Drucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nature gave us one tongue and two ears so we could hear twice as much as we speak." - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Persistent questioning and healthy inquisitiveness are the first requisite for acquiring learning of any kind." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man of ability and the desire to accomplish something can do anything." - Donald Kircher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know where I'm going and I know the truth, and I don't have to be what you want me to be. I'm free to be what I want." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Making good decisions is a crucial skill at every level." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we do not plant knowledge when young, it will give us no shade when we are old." - Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We make our own fortunes and call them fate." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the midst of movement and chaos, keep stillness inside of you." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All great achievements have one thing in common - people with a passion to succeed." - Pat Cash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your life does not get better by chance, it gets better by change." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be a Columbus to whole new continents and worlds within you, opening new channels, not of trade, but of thought." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one person who could ever make you happy, and that person is you." - David Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The words that enlighten the soul are more precious than jewels." - Hazrat Inayat Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness depends upon ourselves." - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The doors we open and close each day decide the lives we live." - Flora Whittemore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust your gut." - Barbara Walters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The path to success is to take massive, determined action." - Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Men easily believe what they want to." - Latin Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." - Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cadbury Countlines -Boost 10 https://t.co/Azzz72bHf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can change our lives. We can do, have, and be exactly what we wish." - Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your attitude is either the lock on, or the key to the door of success." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!" - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A problem is a chance for you to do your best." - Duke Ellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hell, there are no rules here - we're trying to accomplish something." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world has the habit of making room for the man whose words and actions show that he knows where he is going." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you really want to do something, you'll find a way. If you don't, you'll find an excuse." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The direction in which education starts a man will determine his future." - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The people who matter will recognise who you are." - Alan Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing builds self-esteem and self-confidence like accomplishment." - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are no seven wonders of the world in the eyes of a child. There are seven million." - Walt Streightiff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Once you choose hope, anything's possible." - Christopher Reeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The dictionary is the only place where success comes before work." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never wanted to be the next Bruce Lee. I just wanted to be the first Jackie Chan." - Jackie Chan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't dream at night, I dream all day; I dream for a living." - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honest disagreement is often a good sign of progress." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great minds talk about ideas, average minds talk about events, and small minds talk about people." -  Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The successful man will profit from his mistakes and try again in a different way." - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All achievements, all earned riches, have their beginning in an idea." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The tragedy of life doesn't lie in not reaching your goal. The tragedy lies in having no goal to reach." - Benjamin Mays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A wise man will make more opportunities than he finds." - Francis Bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Confidence comes not from always being right but from not fearing to be wrong." -  Peter T. McIntyre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Action is the antidote to despair." - Joan Baez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability is of little account without opportunity." - Napoleon Bonaparte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me." - Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel that the greatest reward for doing is the opportunity to do more." - Jonas Salk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only the wisest and stupidest of men never change." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Playing it safe is the riskiest choice we can ever make." - Sarah Ban Breathnach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["While you are upon the earth, enjoy the good things that are here." - John Selden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Many people take no care of their money till they come nearly to the end of it, and others do just the same with their time." - Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honesty is the first chapter in the book of wisdom." - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Imagination is more important than knowledge." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is literally true that you can succeed best and quickest by helping others to succeed." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Promise yourself to be so strong that nothing can disturb your peace of mind." - Christian Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is a mirror and will reflect back to the thinker what he thinks into it." - Ernest Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Small opportunities are often the beginnings of great enterprises." - Demosthenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream lofty dreams, and as you dream, so shall you become." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is often the result of taking a misstep in the right direction." - Al Bernstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself." - Leo Tolstoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world." - Anne Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage." - Ana?s Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember that not getting what you want is sometimes a wonderful stroke of luck." - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Learning without thought is labor lost; thought without learning is perilous." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be a friend to thyself, and others will be so too." - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I have the belief that I can do it, I shall surely acquire the capacity to do it even if I may not have it at the beginning." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Believe deep down in your heart that you're destined to do great things." - Joe Paterno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is the weight, not numbers of experiments that is to be regarded." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Strength is a matter of a made up mind." - John Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Once you make a decision, the universe conspires to make it happen." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe one of the most important priorities is to do whatever we do as well as we can." - Victor Kermit Kiam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human spirit needs to accomplish, to achieve, to triumph to be happy." - Ben Stein]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>