<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: Job Description Tracking Code 5145-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the world that… https://t.co/EnGdDtFNHG https://t.co/NcpGnEFfjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivors of deadly tour boat explosion airlifted to the US - CNN: CNN Survivors of deadly tour boat explosion airlifted to the US CNN (CNN) At least one American tourist is dead and ten people were injured after a tour boat exploded in the Bahamas,… https://t.co/VJNz6cTT6W https://t.co/UDvpHjT1Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolton: US Has Plan to Dismantle NK Nuclear Program in Year - U.S. News &amp; World Report: U.S. News &amp; World Report Bolton: US Has Plan to Dismantle NK Nuclear Program in Year U.S. News &amp; World Report President Donald Trump's national security adviser says… https://t.co/sycTAlYZQC https://t.co/SKcb5Oet3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack developer: For Siemens Full-stack developer job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers Job Full-stack developer… https://t.co/VkGPFFhKLY https://t.co/WwQRFZzV2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 dead, 9 injured as tour boat explodes in Bahamas - Yahoo News: Yahoo News 1 dead, 9 injured as tour boat explodes in Bahamas Yahoo News 1 dead, 9 injured as tour boat explodes in Bahamas originally appeared on https://t.co/jSEwVmH6TA. A fiery explosion… https://t.co/XtOxtbv8rz https://t.co/HWDgt1QzX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 People Dead in Shooting at Maryland's Capital Gazette Newsroom - New York Times: New York Times 5 People Dead in Shooting at Maryland's Capital Gazette Newsroom New York Times ANNAPOLIS, Md. — A man armed with a shotgun and smoke grenades stormed into… https://t.co/YeUbd1q1tX https://t.co/sbDFkgVBcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: FULL STACK DEVELOPER LOCATION: WESTERVILLE, OH Full Time and Contractor Only visa independent candidate need to apply JOB DESCRIPTION: Education: Bachelors Degree Skills: Core Java, Spring, Web-Services/ RESTful, Oracle With JS… https://t.co/jPZ2eBrTFq https://t.co/CwKS1uMvAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 NBA Free Agency Takeaways: Paul George bets on Thunder; Kevin Durant to re-sign with Warriors as expected - https://t.co/Rn3xGR5UC6: https://t.co/Rn3xGR5UC6 2018 NBA Free Agency Takeaways: Paul George bets on Thunder; Kevin Durant to re-sign with… https://t.co/rxtjKxvBqU https://t.co/N2uVOSRhFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy End To June - CBS Denver: CBS Denver Stormy End To June CBS Denver Moose Relocated After Showing Up In Metro Area YardColorado Parks and Wildlife say a 400 lb. moose was found in someone's yard in Westminster. 'Opportunity To Heal': Jefferson… https://t.co/DetuTwEuzH https://t.co/ubMJCZ898k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's Oldest Man Richard Overton's Bank Account Drained After Identity Theft - Newsweek: Newsweek America's Oldest Man Richard Overton's Bank Account Drained After Identity Theft Newsweek The oldest living man in America has reportedly had his bank… https://t.co/bD1OiqnIp7 https://t.co/8lcJ6BN8Js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Software Engineer: C# Software Engineer Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is… https://t.co/x7keVDqz62 https://t.co/ygssAsQ0pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US envoy to Estonia says he has resigned, citing Trump's treatment of European allies - USA TODAY: USA TODAY US envoy to Estonia says he has resigned, citing Trump's treatment of European allies USA TODAY As President Donald Trump prepares for a visit to… https://t.co/j5Vr8XMCNm https://t.co/JQ607ZDVzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn Jun 5, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #4945: Information Technology Job Code: #4945 Title: BI Developer Job Type: Contract Job Location: Columbus OH Job Description: Manifest Solutions is currently seeking a BI… https://t.co/F38OR72Sy2 https://t.co/VxeR5My5i3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Job Title Business Systems Analyst Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type Location TIMET – Toronto – Toronto, OH 43964 US (Primary) Job Description Summary Develop interactive tools that convert enterprise… https://t.co/4TbRBxCy6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Modeler: Data Modeler Ref No.: 18-23636 Location: OH, Ohio Requirement / Project Manager – Infrastructure / Wilmington, DE At least 5 years of experience as a Project Manager of a large project environment in the software industry working with a… https://t.co/bHbvuRp09Z https://t.co/UJcB8WWzi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increased threat of a trade war is ramping up fears of a 'full-blown recession' - CNBC: CNBC Increased threat of a trade war is ramping up fears of a 'full-blown recession' CNBC Even as growth ramps up to what could be the fastest rate since before the… https://t.co/O09QhIOfOI https://t.co/OJtTZVPFb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration may seek to detain migrant families longer than previously allowed - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump administration may seek to detain migrant families longer than previously allowed Washington Post The Trump administration… https://t.co/kFRazuIQvT https://t.co/TUNwkl3cmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US assessing cost of keeping troops in Germany as Trump battles with Europe - Chicago Tribune: Chicago Tribune US assessing cost of keeping troops in Germany as Trump battles with Europe Chicago Tribune The Pentagon is analyzing the cost and impact of a… https://t.co/X5sFGSMLC0 https://t.co/6yXVSGbhyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Bill de Blasio Joins Call to Abolish ICE - Daily Beast: Daily Beast NYC Mayor Bill de Blasio Joins Call to Abolish ICE Daily Beast New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio took to Twitter Friday to join the growing call to abolish ICE, labeling the… https://t.co/96cYwr0Ck6 https://t.co/30WAWzBOfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Job Title Network Administrator Requisition # ******.3 Job Type Full-time Shift Type First Shift (Day) Location PCC Airfoils – Mentor, OH – Mentor, OH 44060 US (Primary) Job Description Job Description Job Title: Network… https://t.co/IOi6us3PK7 https://t.co/oGjgjbySa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez name-dropped her lipstick brand and it sold out - CBS News: CBS News Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez name-dropped her lipstick brand and it sold out CBS News Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, the 28-year-old who defeated powerful Democratic… https://t.co/6gpHAzJXl4 https://t.co/D2vOMHH1pL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Senior Project Manager: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 23 hours ago(6/4/2018 10:45 AM) Job ID 23610 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance… https://t.co/YkyXda2P4R https://t.co/EALMaCmDWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Tells Democratic Donors To 'Get Organized' And Register Voters Before Midterms - NPR: NPR Obama Tells Democratic Donors To 'Get Organized' And Register Voters Before Midterms NPR Former President Barack Obama has kept a low profile since he left… https://t.co/fAG6O0VKA5 https://t.co/amkiZMPc3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN migration agency rejects Trump nominee Ken Isaacs as leader - CBS News: CBS News UN migration agency rejects Trump nominee Ken Isaacs as leader CBS News Last Updated Jun 29, 2018 9:19 AM EDT. GENEVA -- The U.N.'s migration agency snubbed the Trump… https://t.co/pAOKPA1S2U https://t.co/ZbHPHuayUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration could be holding 30000 border kids by August, officials say - Washington Examiner: Washington Examiner Trump administration could be holding 30000 border kids by August, officials say Washington Examiner The Trump administration… https://t.co/83laOqTJfr https://t.co/kCF35GrxeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workday Integration Developer: Workday Integration Developer Columbus, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 05/24/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary Skillsworkday integrationTax TermsC2COverview Hello Please go through the JD below and let me know if… https://t.co/3ibqbkuO4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late-Night Hosts React to Sarah Sanders Being Kicked Out of a Restaurant - Hollywood Reporter: Hollywood Reporter Late-Night Hosts React to Sarah Sanders Being Kicked Out of a Restaurant Hollywood Reporter "My heart really goes out to her. She was… https://t.co/pG77GkIIZ0 https://t.co/nDKYgR11Pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Application Analyst and Developer: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 3 months ago(3/30/2018 4:49 PM) Job ID 23412 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance… https://t.co/rshQGZ1xRe https://t.co/jnzqqlgtPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five dead in Capital Gazette shooting; suspect Jarrod Ramos is in custody, police say - Washington Post: Washington Post Five dead in Capital Gazette shooting; suspect Jarrod Ramos is in custody, police say Washington Post A man with a vendetta against a… https://t.co/ANoOeciXuB https://t.co/MUis23DqAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Webmethod Developer: Webmethod Developer Primary Skills EDI,XSLT,Restful API,WebMethods,MWS,Messaging Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Webmethod Developer for location Columbus , OH for one of our Top client. Job… https://t.co/ildrMl7rMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Rosenstein's and Wray's testimony undermined GOP efforts to undermine the Russia investigation - Washington Post: Washington Post How Rosenstein's and Wray's testimony undermined GOP efforts to undermine the Russia investigation Washington Post The… https://t.co/qXcevBJKgJ https://t.co/ScJRxo9WuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Don't get cute': Trump is really sore about Harley-Davidson's perceived lack of loyalty to him - Washington Post: Washington Post 'Don't get cute': Trump is really sore about Harley-Davidson's perceived lack of loyalty to him Washington Post By now it's… https://t.co/z0dAyKH8Y2 https://t.co/pEW3G2ZdXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump meets with immigration officials in Arizona on 'behalf of children and the families' - Washington Post: Washington Post Melania Trump meets with immigration officials in Arizona on 'behalf of children and the families' Washington Post… https://t.co/hpMBtb2kky https://t.co/SD8Pguxu4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Hen protester allegedly threw chicken feces at eatery, police say - Fox News: Fox News Red Hen protester allegedly threw chicken feces at eatery, police say Fox News Reginald Scott See, 51, of Martinsburg, W. Va., was charged with littering and… https://t.co/3B47ArGFG4 https://t.co/E4eqOdzNUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Columbus, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 06/05/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: Java Developer Location: Columbus, OH Contract: 6 months Apex Systems is currently seeking a Java… https://t.co/yZdMT2mBJH https://t.co/1XynPrysQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon buys PillPack, an online pharmacy, for just under $1B - TechCrunch: TechCrunch Amazon buys PillPack, an online pharmacy, for just under $1B TechCrunch A week after appointing a CEO for its healthcare joint venture with Berkshire Hathaway and… https://t.co/eakt7zuKqM https://t.co/2viAztRNu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Company Name: MarkWest Energy Partners, L.P. Location Name: Denver, CO Location Address: 1515 Araphaoe St Twr1 Ste 1600, Denver, CO, United States (US), 80202 Education Level: Bachelor’s Required Relevant Experience Level: Mid Career… https://t.co/ypjccL1VUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: What the Enterprise Digital Marketing UX Design team contributes to Cardinal Health The UX team is responsible for supporting website design needs, user experience development and front-end code creation for the business units… https://t.co/TE3YXmRAhK https://t.co/O9OeRmtUkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack developer: For Siemens Full-stack developer job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers Job Full-stack developer… https://t.co/oDpQMg6lBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 dead and 22 injured after gunfire at New Jersey art festival - USA TODAY: USA TODAY 1 dead and 22 injured after gunfire at New Jersey art festival USA TODAY TRENTON, N.J. — A dispute between rival gang members was the probable cause behind a shooting… https://t.co/Rpr3G8p6yX https://t.co/McSCTPt9MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Applications Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/O2JrfT86PD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search warrants give details about Paul Manafort's financial entanglement with a Russian oligarch - Washington Post: Washington Post Search warrants give details about Paul Manafort's financial entanglement with a Russian oligarch Washington Post Two… https://t.co/9oDKPAKKBT https://t.co/IWQsJ5hE1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant, Business Intelligence Loyalty Marketing: What does Business Intelligence contribute to Cardinal Health? – Pivotal high-profile role to take data to insight to reporting on Medical Segment loyalty programs to show holistic performance business… https://t.co/tiDIVspYqH https://t.co/AWrY4yEZyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Cloud Software Developer Advanced: For Siemens Full-Stack Cloud Software Developer Advanced – Milford, OH job – Research &amp; Development – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/YoW1rjf4bx https://t.co/TaygySiwVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police officer in Antwon Rose shooting admits he did not see a gun, charged with criminal homicide - New York Daily News: New York Daily News Police officer in Antwon Rose shooting admits he did not see a gun, charged with criminal homicide New York… https://t.co/55DEAlmfHv https://t.co/opCQnwzVit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Janus Decision Means for Teacher Unions - New York Times: New York Times What the Janus Decision Means for Teacher Unions New York Times Arizona teachers protested in April in a statewide walkout, one of several this year. The walkout movement… https://t.co/jEcgWa52TM https://t.co/gLpf3KxQsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany Crashes Out of World Cup with Loss to South Korea - New York Times: New York Times Germany Crashes Out of World Cup with Loss to South Korea New York Times Germany humiliatingly crashed out of the World Cup with a 2-0 loss to South Korea in Kazan… https://t.co/6By2nGRuVo https://t.co/3B86WygVd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/T3RMfw7msi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embattled FBI agent meets with Congress behind closed doors - CNN: CNN Embattled FBI agent meets with Congress behind closed doors CNN (CNN) Congress will get its first chance Wednesday to grill the FBI agent who has been at the center of the controversy… https://t.co/Trt2qY8Cxm https://t.co/26nynhr5q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1-year-old died after stove fell on him in northeast Las Vegas - Las Vegas Review-Journal: Las Vegas Review-Journal 1-year-old died after stove fell on him in northeast Las Vegas Las Vegas Review-Journal A 1-year-old boy died last month after a stove… https://t.co/CFQbEVJ4g4 https://t.co/XZlgofXIBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform Engineer (SAP): The SAP Basis Engineers role is to support the administration, planning, for all the systems in the SAP landscape. The SAP Basis Administrator will perform all SAP Basis related activities and collaborate closely with SAP… https://t.co/RwJSkccf8J https://t.co/k1QErToC6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY The purpose of this position is to lead individual, multi-disciplined real estate project solutions for clients, with direct accountability for project delivery. Characteristics of… https://t.co/oyWsK8MfMF https://t.co/WnWpip1xS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Spotfire Data Analyst: SENIOR LEAD SPOTFIRE DATA ANALYST Global Consulting Company _**Green Card holders or US Citizens ONLY**_ _**DO NOT APPLY UNLESS YOU ARE A GREEN CARD HOLDER OR A US CITIZEN**_ LOCATION: Cincinnati, OH _**CANDIDATE MUST… https://t.co/yhLpM019Hn https://t.co/vFCYTkjOOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez? A Democratic Giant Slayer - New York Times: New York Times Who Is Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez? A Democratic Giant Slayer New York Times She has never held elected office. She is still paying off her student loans. She is 28… https://t.co/0Y0E9guZCF https://t.co/niRiWK3vhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician – Mid/Sr – TS/SCI – Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio: Come join General Dynamics Information Technology Team! – Follow all approved customer policies, processes and procedures. – Follow the written and verbal instructions provided by… https://t.co/Qr1LAesP1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Engineer: .Net Software Engineer ====================== Tyler Technologies is growing and is looking for software engineer to design, develop and maintain enterprise level software applications used by the public sector nationwide. As a… https://t.co/axCQBjvrZV https://t.co/3zxU3yfnHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trone wins Democratic primary for Delaney's House seat in Maryland - Washington Post: Washington Post Trone wins Democratic primary for Delaney's House seat in Maryland Washington Post David Trone, the Potomac tycoon, won the Democratic primary for the… https://t.co/JZfbN2K5er https://t.co/9Az4jaIM92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court upholds Trump travel ban - Washington Post: Washington Post Supreme Court upholds Trump travel ban Washington Post The Supreme Court ruled Tuesday that President Trump has the authority to ban travelers from certain majority-Muslim… https://t.co/AlHMXS06PC https://t.co/J5R5o8Ve0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel of Elon Musk, according to his flock - The Verge: The Verge The gospel of Elon Musk, according to his flock The Verge Last year, hospitalized and bedridden for several months following a suicide attempt, Salina Marie Gomez turned on individual… https://t.co/FDcum6xdso https://t.co/kpDOhaJwp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality Winner, NSA Contractor Accused in Leak, Pleads Guilty - New York Times: New York Times Reality Winner, NSA Contractor Accused in Leak, Pleads Guilty New York Times WASHINGTON — Reality L. Winner, a former Air Force linguist who was the first… https://t.co/ytjfQwpIkn https://t.co/lguj0OgM6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Dayton: Dynetics Careers – Software Engineer – Dayton Go to homepage Menu – Jobs – About Us Log in Login Log in Register now Forgot Your Password? Software Engineer – Dayton Dayton, OH |Full Time In order to apply for this or any other… https://t.co/NfkaRPjxj9 https://t.co/rixlaaCDsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court says crisis pregnancy centers do not have to provide women abortion information - Washington Post: Washington Post Supreme Court says crisis pregnancy centers do not have to provide women abortion information Washington Post The Supreme… https://t.co/HDdMWr0vZK https://t.co/0OF6D77y6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Legislature And Politics - NPR: Immigration Legislature And Politics NPR Legislative plans to tackle immigration are up in the air, as President Trump tells Congress to wait until after the midterms, and tweets about doing away with… https://t.co/RKMOIBhJU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Engineering Lead: Job ID: ********-11804-SH Company Name: Verisk 3E Description: Do you have an entrepreneurial spirit and know how to get things done? Are you looking to join a company where creativity and innovation is encouraged? If… https://t.co/4spXaMNlo6 https://t.co/FPgU1pIL34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[77-year-old retirement home resident charged with fatally shooting fire captain responding to explosion - Washington Post: Washington Post 77-year-old retirement home resident charged with fatally shooting fire captain responding to explosion Washington… https://t.co/dVSxHmz1kU https://t.co/xRnxS7ulod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi Rebukes Maxine Waters for Endorsing Harassment of Trump Officials - New York Magazine: New York Magazine Nancy Pelosi Rebukes Maxine Waters for Endorsing Harassment of Trump Officials New York Magazine After a restaurant in Virginia refused… https://t.co/CK6iu26MW4 https://t.co/1uyB1AdDWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Operations Manager: IT Operations Manager / Cincinnati , OH Overview: At TQL, our rapid growth and success has been dependent on our ability to deliver cutting-edge technology with an emphasis on performance and reliability. As the IT Operations… https://t.co/k3TrWc9YCe https://t.co/OKApZpd35t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a MAINFRAME APPLICATION DEVELOPER… https://t.co/e6YqWG9M14 https://t.co/fjpf0Wu8HZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Java Developer: Jr. Java Developer Ref No.:18-11065 Location: Milford, Ohio Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 06/21/2018 Jr. Java Developer/Entry Level Software Engineer Must have a Bachelors Degree Diverse Lynx LLC is an Equal Employment… https://t.co/KgngvNbcox https://t.co/brUggqoMMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Border detention facilities are nicer now than under Obama - CNN: CNN Trump: Border detention facilities are nicer now than under Obama CNN West Columbia, South Carolina (CNN) President Donald Trump said the one thing he's taken away from the… https://t.co/Miupy5BdOK https://t.co/2eLxcE55aM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigators look at earlier shootings at Malibu Park where father was killed inside tent while camping - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Investigators look at earlier shootings at Malibu Park where father was killed inside tent while camping Los… https://t.co/v6Bb3JZLfk https://t.co/8EnJqv8gmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Project Manager, Toledo, OH: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by… https://t.co/phGNjql77t https://t.co/LXQyC8tlCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After family separation crisis, Trump returns to his tried-and-true tactic: ratchet up the rhetoric - CNN: CNN After family separation crisis, Trump returns to his tried-and-true tactic: ratchet up the rhetoric CNN (CNN) President Donald Trump has hit on… https://t.co/ZjWlU9w4gw https://t.co/SOTMHKqC9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (JAVA Developer): Cardinal Health at Home is a best-in-class provider of medical supplies to patients in the home. It is comprised of two separate operating segments: Edgepark, a leading direct-to-consumer (DTC) medical… https://t.co/AvL1aHIXC8 https://t.co/DVOzrOKyTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis: DHS wants two temporary camps on US bases to house immigrants - CNN: CNN Mattis: DHS wants two temporary camps on US bases to house immigrants CNN Eielson Air Force Base, Alaska (CNN) Defense Secretary James Mattis said the Pentagon is in "close… https://t.co/rkhYkjkOXP https://t.co/8jLWoWx7SV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst – SAP Supply chain management: Do you thrive in environments where you have a great deal of autonomy? Are you an IT systems specialist with great analytical skills? Are you passionate about providing the best service possible? If… https://t.co/jcptoYRdBE https://t.co/HIbwOFw7Ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Disgusted' by Video of Boy's Killing, Callers Flood Police Tip Line - New York Times: New York Times 'Disgusted' by Video of Boy's Killing, Callers Flood Police Tip Line New York Times Sunday marked two days since the police first asked for help finding… https://t.co/syp9VzIKnL https://t.co/HLCYWRi09t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI developer: UI developer Ref No.: 18-27226 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio ROLE:UI DEVELOPER LOCATION: Cincinnati – Ohio JOB DISCRIOTION: Key skills required for the job are: Usability-L3 (Mandatory) Angular JS-L3As a Lead, you are responsible for managing… https://t.co/xXlricqL50 https://t.co/STfuTxUYkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Huckabee Sanders' Restaurant Tweet Was Illegal, Says Ex-Ethics Chief - HuffPost: HuffPost Sarah Huckabee Sanders' Restaurant Tweet Was Illegal, Says Ex-Ethics Chief HuffPost She can't use her official White House account to attack a private… https://t.co/bIkolB8Nfp https://t.co/gw3kCau1EC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erdogan declares victory in presidential election in Turkey - Washington Post: Washington Post Erdogan declares victory in presidential election in Turkey Washington Post ISTANBUL — Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan declared victory in a pivotal… https://t.co/JgkEJbtAEX https://t.co/naut3ZmrYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Illegal Immigrants Should Be Deported With 'No Judges or Court Cases' - U.S. News &amp; World Report: U.S. News &amp; World Report Trump Says Illegal Immigrants Should Be Deported With 'No Judges or Court Cases' U.S. News &amp; World Report WASHINGTON… https://t.co/IukbrYaeXB https://t.co/Z3K2DTOKuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You're out of your cotton-picking mind': A Fox News guest explains hate speech to a black man - Washington Post: Washington Post 'You're out of your cotton-picking mind': A Fox News guest explains hate speech to a black man Washington Post “Fox and… https://t.co/5fSeGrJjPR https://t.co/comMFxzIF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java / Cobol Applications Programmer: Card Services Job Talent Network Form Join our Talent Network! Thank you for your interest in Alliance Data! Please fill out the information below to receive updates on available opportunities. *First Name *Last… https://t.co/zPU9nbUgvQ https://t.co/nid2RMVdYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two San Diego police officers shot while responding to call - CNN: CNN Two San Diego police officers shot while responding to call CNN (CNN) Two San Diego Police officers were shot after they breached an apartment that smelled of smoke on Saturday night,… https://t.co/5QAoSj8Pfp https://t.co/xiMX3lQ2qX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince William arrives in Jordan as he starts historic Middle East tour - CNN: CNN Prince William arrives in Jordan as he starts historic Middle East tour CNN (CNN) Prince William arrived in Jordan on Sunday on the first stop of a five-day Middle East… https://t.co/YBMAfPSUhJ https://t.co/i39hSHzccQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince William's Middle East tour will be his most challenging royal trip to date - CNN: CNN Prince William's Middle East tour will be his most challenging royal trip to date CNN Jerusalem (CNN) The Duke of Cambridge faces perhaps his biggest… https://t.co/yhb2jzM7w4 https://t.co/oLoA88xppt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care… https://t.co/QUw2HgT4PJ https://t.co/A6LdFLxQXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Level Software Developer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Senior Level Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability… https://t.co/gJ5mf2oKlL https://t.co/3QPnt6bA6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's New Plan for Immigrants: Jail Them on Military Bases - Daily Beast: Daily Beast Trump's New Plan for Immigrants: Jail Them on Military Bases Daily Beast Family separation may be over, but mass detention will continue with the help of the… https://t.co/rmLigyIkqv https://t.co/ziNQDWVstv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: US Citizens and GC Candidates only Description Client is looking for a C# developer responsible for building a C# application, including anything from back-end services to their client-end counterparts. Your primary responsibilities will… https://t.co/RxBdPmWYEF https://t.co/J1AVqW0VUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie Arrington, South Carolina Candidate Who Beat Mark Sanford, Is Seriously Hurt in Crash - New York Times: New York Times Katie Arrington, South Carolina Candidate Who Beat Mark Sanford, Is Seriously Hurt in Crash New York Times Katie Arrington, a… https://t.co/o9MWrrqBAC https://t.co/ScypdGkVp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI hands House GOP thousands of documents on Russia probe - Politico: Politico FBI hands House GOP thousands of documents on Russia probe Politico The FBI turned over thousands of documents to Congress this week, including details about its use of… https://t.co/Pcvuk8Upqq https://t.co/QDnVpuJvjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Functional Manager, IT Business Services: SAP Functional Manager, IT Business Services – Home – About Us – Careers – Contact Us – Sign in – Products &amp; Services – Bearings – Power Transmission – Engineered Surfaces – Lubrication – Chain &amp; Auger –… https://t.co/6u6NAXhceX https://t.co/xUTFUNOFun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why a small-town restaurant owner asked Sarah Huckabee Sanders to leave — and would do it again - Washington Post: Washington Post Why a small-town restaurant owner asked Sarah Huckabee Sanders to leave — and would do it again Washington Post Stephanie… https://t.co/6EfLoQc9m7 https://t.co/KhuEPguYgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blast rocks stadium as Zimbabwe President Emmerson Mnangagwa campaigns - CBS News: CBS News Blast rocks stadium as Zimbabwe President Emmerson Mnangagwa campaigns CBS News HARARE, Zimbabwe -- An explosion rocked a stadium where Zimbabwe's president was… https://t.co/AAw0lzCZmM https://t.co/QPVj99ScVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior ETL/Java Developer: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn May 29, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #4918: Information Technology Job Code: #4918 Title: Junior ETL/Java Developer Job Type: Contract Job Location: Columbus OH Job Description: Manifest… https://t.co/ngiLMTuJCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jogger detained for 2 weeks after accidentally crossing US border from Canada - CNN: CNN Jogger detained for 2 weeks after accidentally crossing US border from Canada CNN (CNN) A woman jogging along a beach accidentally crossed the US border from Canada,… https://t.co/exPyg2qS6x https://t.co/tbGcmy6Trh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Frontend Developer: Senior Frontend Developer in Columbus, OH at ScottsMiracle-Gro – – – – Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation – Home – Our Culture – Benefits &amp; Wellness – Inclusion &amp; Engagement – Military &amp; Veterans – Featured Careers –… https://t.co/Rz2bTnxsKc https://t.co/rSWpli8BQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Lead: Job Title: .NET Lead Location: Findlay, OH Job Number: JO-1806-27512 Description ProKarma is currently seeking a .NET Lead to join our team in Findlay, OH! Qualified candidates must possess a minimum of 8 years’ experience with at least… https://t.co/unFdbNUK3m https://t.co/Zhv14UwUul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Asian News 9:49 am GMT - Yahoo News: Top Asian News 9:49 am GMT Yahoo News SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — The U.S. military said Saturday that it was moving "assets" to a U.S. air base near South Korea's capital and to the inter-Korean border to prepare… https://t.co/UYJGncdRVb https://t.co/P2UXBrtGQ0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>