<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying won’t help anyone. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't run away from your troubles. There ain't no place that far. –Uncle Remus (Song of the South)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles are real but they need someone to believe, so they can happen. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do words go when they are not spoken? Are they hiding, shy or frightened, crying or smiling? –Book of Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My father said, "Differences can make you stronger." –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have a secret crush on your favorite Disney Prince? We do too!! Mine is #2! Check them out--&gt; http://t.co/MNkmD62a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth sounds insane sometimes.  –Linguini (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re only a fool if you give up. –Jafar (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's impossible if you believe you can do it. –Phineas (Phineas and Ferb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My one true love. I'll find him someday. He's out there. I just know it. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is gone. I must move on. –Pocahontas (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you smile, it's pure perfection. It shines through everything you do. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. -Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you walk the footsteps of a stranger, you'll learn things you never knew. -Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish a little wish. Hope a simple hope. Dream a happy dream. –Pinocchio (Disney Hallmark)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith in your dreams and someday your rainbow will come smiling through. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is never wrong and so it never dies. –Kovu (The Lion King II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People make mistakes. That's what life's about. The key is to learn from them. –Josie (Sky High)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a patient listener, but opinionated to the point of stubbornness when my mind is made up. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls talk too much. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dory: “Trust me on this.” | Marlin: “Trust you?” | Dory: “Yes, trust. It’s what friends do.” –Finding Nemo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All good things come to an end. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be imaginative, strong-hearted. You must try things that may not work. –Gusteau (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t know what I can do, still I know I’ve got to try. –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like food, I love it. –Anton Ego (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can. That doesn't mean that anyone should. –Remy (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, the journey of a thousand miles begins with the first step. –Rafiki (The Lion King 1½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to your mother. It's a scary world out there. Mother knows best. –Mother Gothel (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the years go by, our friendship will never die. You're gonna see it's our destiny. You've got a friend in me. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just a part of growing up. A little adventure, a little rebellion, that's good. Healthy, even. –Flynn Rider (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody knows the trouble ive seen, nobody knows my sorrow. - Zazu (Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your heart is in your dream, no request is to extreme. - Jiminy Cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’ll wait and see, a few days more, there may be something there that wasn’t there before. –Mrs. Potts (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curl up with your pillows and your blankie. Close your eyes and dream so soft and hazy. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to live my own life, follow my own path. I wish for things to change, and that's the problem. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be true to yourself and you'll be magic. Be kind, believe in others, help, and you'll make magic. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella: “A wonderful dream comes true.” | Fairy Godmother: “Like all dreams, I'm afraid this can't last forever.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a lover, not a fighter, ‘cause way down deep inside I've got a dream. –Big Nose Thug (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, teamwork isn't about ego. It's about "we go". –Mushu (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get it if you really want, but you must try, and try, and try until you succeed -Sebastian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when I'm upset, I still love you more than anything in the whole world. –Mrs. Potts (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/zGIkUNQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s time to let go. Everything’s gonna be all right. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your heart be filled with sorrow. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A laugh can be a very powerful thing. Sometimes in life, it’s the only weapon we've got. –Roger (Who Framed Roger Rabbit)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was hiding under your porch because I love you. –Dug (Up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the car Obama got for his daughter.... #NotFair http://t.co/nX2MmomX - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is perfectly blue. The clouds are perfect too. And here I am with you, what could be more right? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends are more important than anything else. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the right path is not the easiest one. –Grandmother Willow (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where one thing falls, another grows. Maybe not what was there before, but something new and wonderful all the same. –Bambi’s Mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t feel like myself. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to leave, you can. I'll remember you, though. I remember everyone who leaves. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might find something that we weren't looking for, which might be just what we were looking for, really. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't you ever had a dream, something you wanted so bad you'd do anything? –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No man is worth the aggravation. That's ancient history. Been there, done that. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want and what we need are entirely different things. –Pleakey (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes when you lose your way, it’s really just as well ‘cause you find yourself. –Cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not hurt. I'm all right. I'm a lot tougher than some people think. –Mowgli (Jungle Book)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People change everyday till they find their own way, so can you. –Mrs. Jenkins (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just do your best and take a rest and sing yourself a song. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm with you, I don't feel so alone. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do a good job. You don't have to worry about the money. It will take care of itself. Just do your best work. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be brave or strong or smart, but somewhere in my secret heart, I know love will find a way. –Kiara (Lion King II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s better to be alone. Nobody can hurt you. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what happens to me, I'll always be with you forever. –John Smith (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. –Charles (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing can go wrong if everything is right, and everything is right somehow. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you keep on believing, the dreams that you wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the voice in your heart. Always know that's how to find who you are. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm out here in the dark, all alone and wide awake. Come and find me. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Pott (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be a princess, you have to believe that you are a princess. –Mia (The Princess Diaries 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're weird, but I like you. –Dot (A Bug’s Life)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you choose to lock your heart away, you'll lose it for certain. –Jack Sparrow (Pirates of the Caribbean)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flower that blooms in adversity is the most rare and beautiful of all. –The Emperor (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realized that I miss you and I need you. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you give is what you get. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let them tell you it's simply not done. When you follow your heart, you'll shine bright as the sun. –Cinderella II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most everyone’s mad here. You may have noticed that I’m not all there myself. –Cheshire Cat (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a new attitude, everything can change. Make it how you want it to be. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goofy: “Maybe she's just not the one for you.” | Max: “That's what I'm afraid of.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mulan: “They're disgusting.” | Mushu: “No, they're men.” –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t help but feel like they’re meant for me. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like food, I love it. –Anton Ego (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet you didn't know this about Anne Hathaway &gt;&gt; http://t.co/f3xpYg35AV sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't run from love. It has a way of tracking you down. –Tug (Brother Bear 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand you. You understand me. That's the place where we can start. –Belle (Belle’s Magical World)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In bad times and good, I have never lost my sense of zest for life. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest part is what to leave behind. It's time to let go. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every smile that you show leaves a magic filling in the air. –Cinderella (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power of a big heart. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things will fade away as season come and go, but the treasure of true friendship will never lose its glow. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a chance ‘cause you can and you will see all the possibilities. If you try, you will find. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't leave me. I love you. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we do fantasy, we must not lose sight of reality. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A day without a friend is like a pot without a single drop of honey left inside. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never hurts to keep looking for sunshine. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be with you forever. I want you right here beside me forever. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go and chase your dreams, you won't regret it. Anything can happen if you let it. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>