<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["The more connections you and your lover make, not just between your bodies, but between your minds, your hearts,... http://lngtwt.com/HcHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is union w somebody, outside oneself, under the condition of retaining the separateness & integrity of one's own self." - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...that which you have thought about will be drawn into your life - be it answers, friendships, health, abundance, or love." - Mike Dooley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love... It surrounds every being and extends slowly to embrace all that shall be." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks for your #followfriday and RTs, much gratitude to you all! have a wonderful weekend and keep spreading love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is trembling happiness. " - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "Life is pain and the enjoyment of love is an anesthetic." - Cesare Pavese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Understanding is the essence of love. If you cannot understand, you cannot love." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llunabelle heart = warmth, mind = coldness... spleen = worry, liver = anger, lungs = sadness, kidneys = fear ... ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDailyLove The hot & cold nature of love is a dance between heart & mind.Heart says yes but mind says I'm scared.Heart is always right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dianecesa "We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -Tom Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love does not claim possession, but gives freedom." - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Health is the greatest gift, contentment the greatest wealth, faithfulness the best relationship." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BirthQuotes: "No language can express the power and beauty and heroism of a mother's love." -  Edwin H. Chapin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "When there is more gratitude, there is less distrust." ~Cheng Yen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just keep coming home to yourself. You are the one you’ve been waiting for." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honest disagreement is often a good sign of progress." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love life and life will love you back. Love people and they will love you back." - Arthur Rubinstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love's greatest gift is its ability to make everything it touches sacred." - Barbara de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Many things—such as loving, going to sleep, or behaving unaffectedly—are done worst when we try hardest to do them." - C.S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: Let yourself be silently drawn by the stronger pull of what you really love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is uttered from the heart alone, Will win the hearts of others to your own." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UpliftingQuotes "A true friend is somebody who can make us do what we can." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow Friday @HisHoliness @UpliftingQuotes @DeathQuotes @BirthQuotes @RumiQuotes @JalaladDinRumi @tinybuddha @MasterMindCoach #followfriday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A slight touch of friendly malice and amusement towards those we love keeps our affections for them from turning flat." - Logan P. Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let us be grateful to people who make us happy, they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom." - Marcel Proust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilikenatalie funny :) i was wondering if anyone would see it that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is through the cracks in our brains that ecstasy creeps in." - Logan P. Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without love, what are we worth? Eighty-nine cents! Eighty-nine cents worth of chemicals walking around lonely." - M*A*S*H, Hawkeye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Quotes is now on Facebook! Become a fan and keep sharing the Love: http://bit.ly/2vQR4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A successful marriage requires falling in love many times, always with the same person." - Mignon McLaughlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Beauty is not in the face; beauty is a light in the heart." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: that link should have been to "This", a video with a spoken poem by Frank Owen: http://bit.ly/30ZlMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now slide the key that is vulnerability, into the lock that opens up the vault behind your ribcage" Frank Owen http://bit.ly/3vFHQ? lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All of creation is alive & conscious, & all of creation deserves our burning, churning, yearning love" R Brezsny http://tinyurl.com/yl8vh46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you want to meet the love of your life? Look in the mirror." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love comes from the most unexpected places." - Barbra Streisand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Listen to another person's heart, not their words." - Numi tea bottle cap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And ever has it been known that love knows not its own depth until the hour of separation." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's hardly any activity, which is started out w such tremendous hopes & expectations, & yet which fails so regularly, as love" -E Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The family is one of nature's masterpieces." - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love you, & because I love you, I would sooner have u hate me for telling u the truth than adore me for telling u lies." - Pietro Aretino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is of all passions the strongest, for it attacks simultaneously the head, the heart and the senses." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I came to see that there was nothing to forgive, that I was the one who caused my own problems." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man who has not passed through the inferno of his passions has never overcome them." - Carl Jung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that was four for follow friday. we are grateful for all your follows & retweets. have a loving weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes This is how I would die into the love I have for you. As pieces of cloud dissolve into the sunlight. Rumi #FollowFriday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JalaladDinRumi The garden of love is green without limit and yields many fruit other than sorrow & joy. Love is beyond either condition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "Romance is the glamour which turns the dust of everyday life into a golden haze." -Elinor Glyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuakerQuotes In marriage the independence of husband & wife wll b equal, their dependence mutual, &obligations reciprocal. Lucretia Mott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love does not die easily. It is a living thing. It thrives in the face of all life's hazards, save one-- neglect." - James Bryden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the expansion of two natures in such fashion that each include the other, each is enriched by the other." - Felix Adler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MindfullyChange: Words have the power to both destroy and heal. When words are both true and kind, they can change our world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuakerQuotes: To turn all we possess into the channel of universal love becomes the business of our lives - John Woolman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The course of true love never did run smooth." - William Shakespeare in A Midsummer Night's Dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gratitude is the memory of the heart." - French Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we are grateful we open a channel of receiving in ourselves." - Daphne Rose Kingma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT quote from me, then Tweet something ur #gr8ful for. 1 winner chosen randomly Thurs at noon will receive: "Attitudes of Gratitude in Love"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 winner chosen at random. enter just once or up to once per day (5 days) for better chances. @LoveQ RT & #gr8ful tweets must be consecutive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Begin to look at what is positive about your relationship & the person you are sharing it with." - M.J. Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 contest winner (in USA only) chosen Thursday at noon will receive book: "Attitudes of Gratitude in Love" by M.J. Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[having a Thankfulness in Love contest. RT a quote from me, then Tweet something you are #gr8ful for, each day until Thurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one happiness in life, to love and be loved." - George Sand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OSHOtimes "Falling in love you remain a child; rising in love you mature" - Osho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must love in such a way that the person you love feels free, not only outside but also inside." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love must be learned, and learned again and again; there is no end to it." - Katherine Ann Porter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article: questions to ask LT partner on date night to clear dust, "Essential questions for loving relationships" http://bit.ly/r072d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://twtlong.com/xkwldc "...the more it seems that 'love' hurts, the more you can be sure it's something else."- Mike Dooley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll results: "If he lets you buy his underpants, you're 'The One'" Reuters: http://bit.ly/22YYXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best proof of love is trust." - Dr. Joyce Brothers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mission2be: I really need to stop listening to other peoples opinions of what are good and bad relationships. Some people will alway ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Loving, are the daring." - Bayard Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Spare yourself from seeking love, approval, or appreciation—from anyone. & watch what happens in reality, just for fun." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -  Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we embrace the gifts within our soul we create a blissful state of happiness 2b savored,pondered &cherished" Micheal Teal #bestfeeling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "Try praising your wife even if it does frighten her at first."-Billy Sunday, d 74y ago today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: There is nothing outside of yourself.  Look within, Everything you want is there- you are That.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's that withholding of the TRUTH that chisels away at affection and commitment." - Christian Carter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If your heart is a volcano, how shall you expect flowers to bloom?" - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealMoonChild: @LoveQ “True Love burns the brightest, But the brightest flames leave the deepest scars.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is not the dying moan of a distant violin - it's the triumphant twang of a bedspring." - S.J. Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2of2) ...Tomorrow, when resurrection comes,
The heart that is not in love will fail the test." - Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1of2) "Love is from the infinite, and will remain until eternity.
The seeker of love escapes the chains of birth and death...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "The roaring of the wind is my wife and the stars through the window pane are my children."-John Keats, would be 214 today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Outside show is a poor substitute for inner worth." -  Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any time that is not spent on love is wasted." - Torquato Tasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How people treat you is their karma; how you react is yours." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is a glorious cycle of song; & love is a thing that can never go wrong; & I am Marie of Roumania." - Dorothy Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maxim for life: You get treated in life the way you teach people to treat you." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love makes us poets, and the approach of death should make us philosophers." - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True love always involves a choice." - Ray H Wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All love is sweet, given or returned." - Percy Bysshe Shelley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EckhartTolle: Every loving thought is true. Everything else is an appeal for healing and help. – A Course in Miracles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we fully embrace the truth of what we are doing in our relationships - healing & growing - then something miraculous happens" M.J. Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be who you are & say what you feel because those who mind don't matter & those who matter don't mind." -  Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When love and skill work together, expect a masterpiece." - John Ruskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be friendly to everyone. Those who deserve it the least need it the most." - Bo Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love and the gentle heart are but a single thing." - Dante Alighieri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pains of love be sweeter far, Than all other pleasures are." - John Dryden]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>