<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BKCHarvard: We documented Internet censorship through empirical testing in 45 countries of the 2,046 most-trafficked and influential si…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmember: Science and Human Rights Coalition Announces 2017 Student Essay Competition Winners  https://t.co/RxXGopqYb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please use this URL to read this story: https://t.co/s8GchD2cE9 https://t.co/VbRxnOOTQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaydaronson @aaas Thanks, Jay. You are right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Honor an exemplary scientist - nominate them for the AAAS Award for Scientific Freedom and Responsibility by Sept 1: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: We urge @POTUS and federal agency heads to appoint scientists to scientific advisory committees, make data available https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmember: Have you used the AAAS Advocacy Toolkit?  https://t.co/fZLcHnYT3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRights: Torture is 100% illegal, 100% immoral &amp; astoundingly ineffective. June 26 is Intl Day in Support of Torture Victims http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Join us at AAAS HQ as experts discuss issues at the intersection of science and human rights https://t.co/vgh9WxF36O #shrcoalitio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theNASEM: ICYMI: “Why Eyewitnesses Fail” TED talk with Thomas Albright: https://t.co/70scBVleEd (read the report here: https://t.co/um4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CliffDuke: Why a #HumanRights tribunal on #fracking? https://t.co/3OotC3PhBl @AAAS_SRHRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samswey: 1. State deadly force laws: https://t.co/Jlfq9kQaCa

2. Use of force policies: https://t.co/utWgk3Fcdi

3. Case law: https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 7/27-28: Registration is open! #shrcoalition meeting on the #RightToScience: https://t.co/N1KVqTqXUR https://t.co/ZaXAPx8vJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: We remain committed to engaging in the exchange of scientists &amp; scientific knowledge between US &amp; #Cuba - @RushHolt https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SRtoxics: A strong statement on #humanrights &amp; pollution just adopted. Congrats to the States, @WHO_Europe @UNECE @UNEP #EuropeEnvHealt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure to stop by the @aaas booth at #AwesomeCon this weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 07/27: How does the #RightToScience affect your work? Find out at the upcoming #shrcoalition meeting! Register: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IBJIYONGI: https://t.co/C7afIBoLBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @orlandomayor: We'll forever be grateful for the brave, compassionate actions of our first responders &amp; medical professionals a year ago…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: AAAS reinforces the need for the use of proven science in @TheJusticeDept forensics in a public comment - https://t.co/AKpet7eF10…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_GR: We weighed in on future of forensic science policy today; deadline is midnight ET, make your voice heard now!
https://t.co/D2J…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tiffanylohwater: .@AAAS submitted this public comment on need for science in #forensics at @TheJusticeDept: https://t.co/jR6rNiChkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmeetings: Do you love the arts as much as #STEM? Enter to design the 2018 #AAASmtg tote bags. Deadline is July 25! Learn more: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Notice for comment closes this Friday, 6/9. Tell DOJ to ensure justice depends on sound forensic #science: https://t.co/WeV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MiamiHerald: Plane hits gator on Orlando airport runway. Plane wins. https://t.co/k37LB7duoL https://t.co/ap9g8Kdboy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tiffanylohwater: Public comments on #forensic evidence due June 9. Speak up for use of forensic science in the law: https://t.co/dWJzhj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: We must ensure rigorous forensic #science is used in convicting the guilty &amp; exonerating the innocent. Speak up: https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tiffanylohwater: Scientists doing public engagement: Apply for this @AAAS award, get recognized, change the world! https://t.co/0w04zfT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @APHAHumanRights: Check out our program for the @APHAAnnualMtg in Atlanta! 
Join us in discussing #HumanRights in #PublicHealth!
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SciClassroom: Now more than ever we need leaders in the fight against climate change: https://t.co/jrr2uXwsQD #ParisAgreement @EliseAme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AstroKatie: Scientists: We built a machine that can measure the warping of space to 1/1000th the width of a proton
Politicians: Let's g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same here, Alice. Same. https://t.co/IIYZl8qcOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @astepanovich: We recognize human rights heroes and villains every year, and we need your help to find them: https://t.co/KQC8Qz8jPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRights: UN #HumanRights Chief #Zeid on the #US withdrawal from #ParisAgreement https://t.co/JsyeA7EIYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Ignoring #climatechange “abdicates our leadership role ... [putting] future generations at great risk.” - @RushHolt https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattHourihan: Here's the list of @USDA_ARS labs the Administration wants to close in 2018. More: https://t.co/RK2RuQzuw6 #science #agri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to it! https://t.co/aw2HvbLrPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichelleAKline: Hi, 

We tried this once &amp; scientists did horrible things to vulnerable people.

Yours,

History of Science https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForeignPolicy: Failing to appoint scientific advisors to the president is putting national security as risk. https://t.co/sozJlDuCJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @priyology: "Between 30 &amp; 50% of programmers were women in the 1950s, and it was seen as a natural career for them" 

https://t.co/j9E2j…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ranitmd: AND medical groups. They don't listen to patients or doctors. ABOUT HEALTH. What have we become? https://t.co/YIvha3NjYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Tomorrow, 7/27: Check out livestream of meeting on the right to science: https://t.co/N1KVqTqXUR Keep up on Twitter with #s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SciStarter: Girl Scouts’ Think Like a Citizen Scientist Journey on @SciStarter #citizenscience @girlscouts https://t.co/ZMXcnvVH4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Submit your nomination for AAAS' award honoring scientists who have fostered scientific freedom and responsibility https://t.co/I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EJHBCU: A promising new coalition looks to rewrite the politics of urban housing https://t.co/kbc9chueng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Last chance to register for July 27 Coalition meeting! Join us: https://t.co/N1KVqTqXUR https://t.co/VQ7X6IZ4mF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Join experts as they discuss issues at the nexus of science and #humanrights during the 2017 #shrcoalition meeting https://t.co/v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[July 27: How #righttoscience is impacting genomic research, patient advocacy, &amp; science funding https://t.co/jv8cIX9c2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the #righttoscience? Here's what the ICESCR says - https://t.co/UV7pxRa8ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the #righttoscience? https://t.co/RxQ0sIWu9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the #righttoscience? Find out: https://t.co/jv8cIX9c2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SREnvironment: ICYMI - Unmitigated climate change will make the United States poorer and more unequal, according to a new study: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: .@RushHolt wants you to know: evidence isn't just for scientists
https://t.co/EGxwWHdjex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bermaninstitute: Zika rewrites maternal immunization ethics - w comments from our @ckrubiner https://t.co/WDQ3yE1NVR #Bioethics @Pregna…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Older Refugees Find No Shelter From Violence:  https://t.co/BHU9DuZhEM via @aaas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't get the Purple Line built, but ok. https://t.co/UU7cl4vaDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @j_zelikova: The UCS Scientist Protection Fund launched today. So needed at this time of unprecedented attacks on scientists  https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changed my profile pic to my dog, Alice. She is much cuter than me and is the reason I get invited to parties so it seems appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelpAge_USA: Older people living in long term displacement are at risk for violence including #GBV. Read @aaas report: https://t.co/c6L…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: . @AAAS News covers our 1st-of-its-kind report which found that refugees &amp; IDPs age 49+ are still vulnerable to #GBV https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScienceMarchDC: Science. Not silence. https://t.co/vYPGgXFWJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: ¡Estamos emocionados por el lanzamiento de nuestra cuenta en español @scipak_es !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThrivingEarth: Seeking a scientist near Flint, MI to design a #greenroof for a youth center  #citizenscience @landarchitects
https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But if you are in DC, please join us! https://t.co/jv8cIX9c2r https://t.co/fBvKlzC2up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official statistics on #GBV among refugees &amp; IDPs don't collect data from ppl 49yo+. Why? https://t.co/idzbaKraKW @HelpAge_USA @AAAS_SRHRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Turkey prosecutes, refuses bail for Ali Gharavi and Peter Steudtner, technologists seized at human rights event: https://t.co/cF5P…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelpAge_USA: Did you know older people are at risk for #GBV? Together we can raise awareness--read our report w/ @AAAS_SRHRL : https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you aren't asking older people about GBV, you won't get a full understanding of the problem or how to address it. https://t.co/inCfKeGoIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelpAge_USA: We partnered with @AAAS_SRHRL and found prevalence of #GBV among #olderpeople--read more here: https://t.co/5ZIWHEWsaP. #e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: JUST IN: Tillerson to shut down State Department office on war crimes: report https://t.co/N9oDnzpJZY https://t.co/JuU04QCxk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you signed up for the Science &amp; Human Rights Coalition meeting yet? Don't miss it! https://t.co/jv8cIX9c2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EngnRoom: Join us today, 5pm CET for a community call on #humanrights + technology! All welcome (listeners, speakers): https://t.co/4t3…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thisishellradio: Weird to live in a time when radical change to society is inevitable very soon in our lifetimes, but have no idea whic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattHourihan: This Week in #Science Appropriations: In House, Another Billion for #NIH; Others Not So Lucky:  https://t.co/w1CCIkUnIn v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bermaninstitute: Is a healthy environment a human right? Testing the idea in Appalachia https://t.co/AIH0POb0lx via @ConversationUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ezeitler: @MarieCWhittaker talks how data can bring out ppls voices Individual experiences are valid &amp; data can tell you if they scale…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SalaehaShariff: I'll be chatting w/ @DrAmberHewitt &amp; @danieljhicks on using #socialscience to impact #policy. And taking your questions…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 7/27: P. Carbajales @ClemsonGIS moderates panel on #righttoscience in policy &amp; practice. Register: https://t.co/N1KVqTqXUR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 7/27: Also hear from B. Knoppers @genomics_policy, @boggioa &amp; @mwfrick on the #righttoscience in policy &amp; practice: https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OmidyarNetwork: We're proud to be a part of The Ethics and Governance of #AI Fund, which announced its first round of funding. 
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieESuess https://t.co/oyN1whPtnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShorensteinCtr: In Flint, "National media utterly failed to capture &amp; depict the agency...of the populace to speak for themselves." htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essential reading for every "credentialed" scientist, engineer, and health professional working in communities https://t.co/9qFTZYfsJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carl_Hiaasen: Official who nixed Everglades from UN endangered-site list gets Trump job https://t.co/0qL177sQh1
#LeastShockingHeadlines…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: A comprehensive AAAS forensic science report pinpoints gaps in the science behind fire investigations - https://t.co/50Kf61TQny @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: Our new report looks at the inaccuracies in existing fire investigation literature &amp; inadequate scientific training: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @openRights_oD: @openRights_oD’s  has moved! Check out our new website here:  https://t.co/GtZhfQx6Ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigadores del GIEI dicen que fueron espiados para entorpecer la investigación del caso Ayotzinapa https://t.co/VmjoiPaxpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spyware Sold to Mexican Government Targeted Forensic Investigators #Ayotzinapa https://t.co/QSVbEClfNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MOrellanaHRW: "We've been studied. And now we're to the point, the island's going down" says mayor Tangier Island, Chesapeake Bay. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieESuess What???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UCSUSA: This historic treaty is "a powerful expression of conscience and principle on behalf of humanity" https://t.co/aqdbxflj2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SciNetUCS: Historic Treaty Makes Nuclear Weapons Illegal (this is a BFD) https://t.co/AD8ua84qxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 7/27: Afternoon panel focuses on realizing the #righttoscience in policy and practice. Check out speaker line-up! https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maxgladstone: Someone let me write the movie where a young woman archaeologist in ~1980s faces her greatest challenge: Thesis Advisor I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAASmember: #AAASmember Julie Fleischman analyzed skeletal remains from the mass graves at the “killing fields” of Choeung Ek  https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SciDip: New Deputy Director at Center for #ScienceDiplomacy brings experience from academia, White House https://t.co/IYI7DvytUM https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hope is not the same thing as optimism." https://t.co/CmP9JuxhGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaas: Join experts at AAAS HQ for the #shrcoalition meeting as they discuss issues surrounding science and human rights. https://t.co/v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AAAS_SRHRL: 7/27: What will the right to science mean in practice? Ask @MMancisidor1970 &amp; Stephen Marks @HarvardChanSPH:  https://t.co/…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>