<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance is not a long race; it is many races one after another. -Walter Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cure for boredom is curiosity. There is no cure for curiosity. -Ellen Parr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study while others are sleeping; work while others are loafing; prepare while others are… https://t.co/lgWeoAzJfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People with goals succeed, because they know where they are going. -Earl Nightingate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Quotes https://t.co/hI92kyvCUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the extra mile.  It’s never crowded. -Unknown

#quotes #sayings #proverbs #thoughtoftheday… https://t.co/MBpE6N3LiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny Quotes https://t.co/h00b1lQ9MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must never be afraid to go too far, for success lies just beyond. -Marcel Proust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have all the reason in the world to achieve your grandest dreams. Imagination plus… https://t.co/WKl0g2hRYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Did You Die Poem https://t.co/bVzuWymyYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not because things are difficult that we do not dare; it is because we do not dare that they are difficult. -Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget everything you thought was true about remembering. 
https://t.co/mrW2U4ns0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dare Mighty Things https://t.co/dL6WmuZOTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are made strong by the difficulties we face, not by those we evade. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas won’t keep. Something must be done about them.

#quotes #sayings #proverbs #motivational… https://t.co/oZwQ6Tx6QC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnify Your Strengths https://t.co/mgPZL9LI7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas can be life-changing. Sometimes all you need to open the door is just one more good idea.… https://t.co/MMnoDf7n1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Competition Quotes https://t.co/0goIbO1MIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t worry about failure. Worry about the chances you miss when you don’t even try. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatness Quotes https://t.co/5eK77ZI4jU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your diamonds are not in far distant mountains or in yonder seas; they are in your own backyard, if you but dig for them. -Russel Conwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we do not plant knowledge when young, it will give us no shade when we are old. -Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of what does not concern you, say nothing good or bad. -Italian Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. -Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since you are like no other being ever created since the beginning of time, you are incomparable. -Brenda Ueland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's never crowded along the extra mile." -Dr Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have lived my life according to this principle: If I'm afraid of it, then I must do it. -Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure after long perseverance is much grander than never to have a striving good enough to be called a failure. -George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance is failing nineteen times and succeeding the twentieth. -Julie Andrews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content makes poor men rich; discontent makes rich men poor. -Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacular achievements are always preceded by unspectacular preparation. -Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practice, practice, practice until you eventually get numb on rejections. -Brian Klemmer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improvement of one's economic position is helped more by cool persistence than by hot enthusiasm. -William Feather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is because they took the easy way out that rivers, and people, go crooked. -Jill Peterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other people's interruptions of your work are relatively insignificant compared with the countless times you interrupt yourself. -B Francis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Small opportunities are often the beginning of great enterprises." -Demosthenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Determination is the wake-up call to the human will. -Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the world you may be one person, but to one person you may be the world. -Paulette Mitchell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With ordinary talents and extraordinary perseverance, all things are attainable. -Sir Thomas Fowell Buxton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always prefer to believe the best of everybody -- it saves so much trouble.
- Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntZ56 I haven't decided yet.  Ask me again in a few days. lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obstacles are those frightful things you see when you take your eyes off your goal. -Hannah More]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visualize this thing that you want, see it, feel it, believe in it. Make your mental blue print, and begin to build. -R Collier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good things happen to those who hustle." -Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human beings, by changing the inner attitudes of their minds, can change the outer aspects of their lives. -William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defeat in doing right is nevertheless victory. -Frederick W. Robertson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life brings simple pleasures to us every day. It is up to us to make them wonderful memories. -Cathy Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The closer one gets to the top, the more one finds there is no "top." -Nancy Barcus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your sorrow come higher than your knees. -Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is a detour, not a dead-end street. -Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtesies of a small and trivial character are the ones which strike deepest in the grateful and appreciating heart. -Henry Clay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When thought becomes excessively painful, action is the finest remedy. -Salman Rushdie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn all you can from the mistakes of others. You won't have time to make them all yourself. -Alfred Sheinwold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Begin somewhere; you cannot build a reputation on what you intend to do. -Liz Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is the daily bread of the eyes. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOW - Poem https://t.co/67ou9Z6YOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A winner makes commitments. A loser makes promises. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poster on the wall at the #facebook office in Toronto. Note the byline at the bottom. https://t.co/mo1rPep0b6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human beings hardly ever learn from the experience of others. They learn, and not often, on their own, the hard way. -Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difficulties increase the nearer we approach the goal. -Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope sees the invisible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible. -Charles Caleb Colton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If u would not be forgotten as soon as you are dead, either write things worth reading or do things worth writing. -Ben Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to do uncomfortable things. It's weight training for life. ~ Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gent who wakes up and finds himself a success hasn't been asleep. -Wilson Mizner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A word of encouragement during a failure is worth more than an hour of praise after success. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation alone is not enough. If you have an idiot and you motivate him, now you have a motivated idiot. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening Quotes https://t.co/IMv5oSIMVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can live for two months on a good compliment." -Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest test of courage on earth is to bear defeat without losing heart. -Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing in the world so much admired as a man who knows how to bear unhappiness with courage. -Seneca the Younger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victorious warriors win first and then go to war, while defeated warriors go to war first and then seek to win. -Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man is a damn fool for at least five minutes every day; wisdom consists in not exceeding the limit. -Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you intuitively desire, that is possible to you. -D.H. Lawrence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is to be found along the way, not at the end of the road, for then the journey is over and it is too late. -R Updegraff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past does not equal the future. -Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to say "no!" when there's a deeper "yes!" burning inside. -Stephen R. Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norman Vincent Peale Quotes https://t.co/JQhfiQNreB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination. -Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let a fool hold his tongue and he will pass for a sage. -Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you put off everything till you're sure of it, you'll never get anything done.
- Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The man who does not read good books has no advantage over the man who cannot read them." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slander is like a hornet; if you cannot kill it dead the first blow, better not strike at it. -Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The leaders of mankind are those who lift their feet from the dusty road &amp; lift their eyes to the illumined future. -W. Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do each daily task the best we can; act as though the eye of opportunity were always upon us. -William Feather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE #4: @facebook closed my 2nd ticket w/ the same generic reply: ask the thief nicely to return my stolen page. Re-opened ticket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who lack the courage will always find a philosophy to justify it.
- Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The superior man acts before he speaks, and afterwards speaks according to his action. -Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difficulties Quotes https://t.co/AlxaRTMrVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have the extraordinary coded within us...waiting to be released. -Jean Houston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking much is a sign of vanity, for the one who is lavish with words is cheap in deeds. -Sir Walter Raleigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE #3: Reached out to many @facebook employees asking to help get my stolen Page back. One has taken interest &amp; given us SOME hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause change and lead; accept change and survive; resist change and die. -Ray Norda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words may show a man's wit but actions his meaning. -Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it." -Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People might not get all they work for in this world, but they must certainly work for all they get. -Frederick Douglass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update #2: @facebook said can't give page back b/c they can't prove it was mine. Suggested I ask thief nicely to give it back. Re-opened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel an earnest and humble desire, and shall till I die, to increase the stock of harmless cheerfulness. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An inventor fails 999 times and if he succeeds once, he's victorious. He treats his failures as practice shots. -Charles Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update #1: Still no resolution on my stolen FB page. Still waiting for @facebook to even look at my trouble ticket from Friday.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>