<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas about what's good for kids change. Check out these bright (and not-so-bright) ideas about baby care! http://t.co/gP955S9Ycq - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sexy face you make when you have something in your eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just hurts for me to go through all these shit and realize that deep down, you never actually cared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my heart and soul, please grind them into hamburger, and enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every exit is an entry somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real loss is only possible when you love something more than you love yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I've "stopped liking you," every time someone says your name, my head turns right towards them and my heart skips a beat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you're busy looking for the perfect person you'll probably miss the imperfect person who could make you perfectly happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd risk everything just to make you happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I see you smile and know that it is not for me, that is when I will miss you the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you truly want to be with a person, listen to your heart and not all the voices from all the people around you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our life won t get easier, the only way to deal with is to get stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Retweet If you love your family and you would do anything for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never understand someones PAIN until you re the one who feels it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't live your life for other people. You've got to do what's right for you, even if it hurts some people you love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so hard when he's your Prince Charming, but you're not his Cinderella?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream as if you ll live forever. Live as if you ll die today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to someone telling a story and thinking: Lie, lie, lie, b.s., lie, lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spongebob: Squidward, you look like a steamed vegetable, only smarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl: What's your favirote colour Boy: Beautiful Girl: That's not a colour Boy: Yes it is, it's the colour of your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to be grateful enough for the first chance, in order to be lucky enough for a second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone try to impress you it means he or she is already impressed by you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life doesn't get easier, you just get stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me smile more, than when you tell me that you'll allways be mine after saying I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come if alcohol kills millions of brain cells, it never killed the ones that made me want to drink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel lonely every single day of my life...but I'm ashamed to admit that to the people who love me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anatidaephobia- the fear that somehow, somewhere, a duck is watching you. ~ I would like to meet a person with this fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm okay, I be alone, but I'm doing fine. I locked my heart up to feel no more pain, it sucks being alone, but hey I'm doing okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not even gonna get mad anymore. I'm just gonna learn to expect the lowest out of the people I thought the highest of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who wait. Better things come to those who get up off their asses and grab it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will always be that one guy. That one kiss. That one moment, that she'll remember for the rest of her life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You as a person make this world shine brighter every second of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lust is wanting to sleep with someone. Love is wanting to wake up next to them in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitch you can't handle my SWAG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move on. If he loved you in the first place he wouldn t do anything to hurt you like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will be happier when you realize you can do without those things you thought you needed the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you watch a romantic movie and it makes you feel like shit because you have no love life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for just the right person to come along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You turned out to be someone I thought you would never be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiter : "Would you like your coffee black" Customer : "What other colors do you have"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying you are on the way when you are actually still at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want A Slim Body That Looks Great Naked? see here... http://t.co/ovLXkq8cEm - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She s been hurt but she s stronger, lied to &amp; now she s smarter, with heartbreak comes wisdom &amp; now she refuses to settle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can be explained through words but is better expressed through actions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a real man doesn't mean you f*** a  girls. It means you fight for one girl even when  others are chasing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only limits of tomorrow are the doubts we have today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After continual disappointments, I'm pretty sure that you're not the one for me. But for some reason, I cant seem to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stay online, until he signs out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I should die before I wake, it's because you took my breath away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn t make the world go round. Love is what makes the ride worthwhile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is all about the improvisation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All it takes, is one simple hello...and the rest of forever could start with just that one person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you judge me on what I did in my past, then you don't belong in my future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's a funny thing, and we've all had our fair share of that comedian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When one thing ends, another thing begins. Sometimes ending hurts, but a new beginning is worth the pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so unfair. In my dreams you're mine, in my life you're a dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how many fish there are in the sea. I don't want a fish. I want you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You find yourself gazing at the sky in the direction he lives and feeling some peace in knowing that you live under the same sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone deserves to laugh. Everyone deserves to be happy. Everyone deserves to be loved Not everyone gets what they deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not sory you did it... you're sorry, I found out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many people go through life waiting for things to happen instead of making them happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies, he was never a waste of your time. he was just the harsh realization that you can do better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its funny how fake people are usually always the first to claim their real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby I'm not lost, I'm just a little confused on what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love someone when there is no chance of that love ever thriving, that is romance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman looks for love in the form of a noun. A man looks for love in the form of a verb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't hate you for not loving me anymore, but I hate myself for still loving you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes a few carefully chosen words can accomplish amazing things. Think twice and speak once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't realize the distance you've walked until you take a look around and realize how far you've been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple thing becomes complicated when you expect too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, you're cute can I sit next to you and watch you smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the world's a stage and most of us are desperately unrehearsed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever loved somebody, so much that you were just too blind to see all of the pain they were causin' you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to give up on people. Chasing after them is a heartache, especially when they don't try to meet you half way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can catch your eye but it takes someone special to catch your heart...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you call it love when you're crying more than you're smiling Something to think about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every hug from you is torture, it's like a taste of what I can't have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never pictured it ending the way that it did, but then again, I never pictured a day when I wouldn't love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A heart can only take so much abuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It s funny how the people who know the least about you, always have the most to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've accidentally fallen % completely and utterly in love with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have time to hate the people who hate me, I'm too busy loving the people who love me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were always there to love me, when I didn't even love myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it ironic that in life the person who brings out the best in you &amp; makes you strong, is actually your weakness?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can tell you how much I love you, but I think it's best if I just showed you how much I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make mistakes; I'm only human. I f*** up; I'm only living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does everything I think about lead to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding more of the same letters behind your last letter to make the word sound less formal. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admit it. We all tried to see if we could fly some point in our life. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not Ken...don't expect me to be Barbie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1Too tired to hold on, but too in love to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing how powerful my words seem in my head and how pointless they seem to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the gravity which holds me towards the earth, it's you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m the girl that always has her phone in her hands, headphones in her ears and that one guy on her mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the kind of girl that will run into chairs and say I'm sorry...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go ahead and tell me everything is fine, I ve always been known for believing lies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no feeling more depressing than waking up believing it all to be a bad dream, and reaching over to a cold pillow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you, because I couldn't find anyone else who is better and will love me back. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never say goodbye if you still have some TRY left in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you leave without a reason, Don t come back with an excuse.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>