<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[All US Civil Servants Perform Above Average (or the Government Needs to Fix Its Performance Rating System) … https://t.co/UgvCQj0ah7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[proud that #CEB has signed the #WhiteHouse pledge on gender pay equity https://t.co/fHr51XZCgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Plan to Acquire LinkedIn: Reactions &amp; Analysis https://t.co/rFAkQJoS0n

In the $26 billion acquisition a… https://t.co/ZD14WpKKJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Gig Economy and Automation Make Basic Income Inevitable? https://t.co/rMLEzXklpM

Universal basic income,… https://t.co/R4H0pTIL1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain’s Other Immigrant Worker Debate https://t.co/ED1ukPs7hm

The prospect of the UK leaving the European Union… https://t.co/SouzSeMHAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The Glass Ceiling’ Half Empty? https://t.co/DaDRuejndu

Jena McGregor at the Washington Post explores the origins… https://t.co/typkH99oi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Kill Schrödinger’s Employee https://t.co/5V4JaiESju

In quantum physics, the observer effect refers to the p… https://t.co/9FqaBQitsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft to Acquire LinkedIn for $26 Billion https://t.co/eNfYwX4fkF

Microsoft announced on Monday that it had r… https://t.co/KZdsM6kMob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Smartphones Making Employees Stupid? https://t.co/VcukkRglGB

No, but many employers believe they’re making ma… https://t.co/IXBcan3et5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burger King Shareholders Reject Resolution to Add Women to Board https://t.co/BQ5rf3g37Y

When Burger King merged … https://t.co/HAtvxdVAzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Vacation and Parental Leave, the Boss’s Attitude Matters https://t.co/z3AtIQtMXc

Employers in the US have been… https://t.co/fpUDR4IeNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Just a Matter of Time Before Chatbots Learn Corporate Jargon https://t.co/AiAQJqdZkp

While Slack is banking … https://t.co/kioOQ1AEp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the Value of a Master’s Degree? https://t.co/yw0dSG8Crz

At a time when the value of a bachelor’s degree is… https://t.co/JoHjEOZRLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Airbnb’s Pledge to Tackle User Discrimination Help Its Employer Brand? https://t.co/wdZHWv1bxP

Amid controve… https://t.co/SkVDqMrsLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind the Generation Gap in Brexit Polls https://t.co/AQToiZRaFy

The vote to decide whether the UK remains a part … https://t.co/JccSANo1BJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Asian Labor Costs Rise, Manufacturers Embrace Reshoring and Robots https://t.co/BjGTBmosyX

With manufacturers … https://t.co/Rt2A7jq1Fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be a Thought Leader Without Really Thinking https://t.co/Ixz7xnbCxw

These days, it seems like everyone is … https://t.co/6EBGWw4Ngs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Change of Place, a Change of Perspective https://t.co/A2VV0JJ9fg

Jillian Richardson, a freelance journalist and… https://t.co/sFLPNBvDat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rethinking the Workday https://t.co/Bt8EkBdYb8

As the traditional eight-hour workday has steadily grown into 10 o… https://t.co/tWl6XCAfbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Students Leave College With Little Else but Debt https://t.co/rOgwllgUpK

A new working paper from the Nation… https://t.co/lEoUyGDpbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Embraces $15 Minimum Wage https://t.co/bMH6KPrSBH

The Washington, DC city council voted on Tuesday to raise th… https://t.co/QfbbMKLGN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jenamcgregor: This big change was supposed to make performance reviews better. Could it be making them worse? https://t.co/SSnZy3bhd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody Knows the Company Like Slackbot https://t.co/EguZ1nJput

If your organization is on Slack, you may often fi… https://t.co/XCbSYj1Lmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will GE Get Rid of the Annual Raise? https://t.co/9cEjy54JYA

Executives at General Electric “are reviewing whethe… https://t.co/Mw05TGQQuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the ‘Honor’ of Long Hours Survive the New Overtime Rule? https://t.co/FHKHZ5W98i

The new overtime rule annou… https://t.co/zx1Zr89jg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Sports Metaphors Strike Out https://t.co/csqCL1LFcs

Allusions to sports are woven into the very warp and weft… https://t.co/U3SRjLafSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit Rattles European Employers, Too https://t.co/87CUoMA08j

With the June 23 referendum on whether the UK shou… https://t.co/Z8IHe2COT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Value of Deceptively Strong Leadership? https://t.co/Xz1nSxzrfA

By now, it is firmly established in the conve… https://t.co/XYLSA4fHQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Continuing Rise of Big Business Casual https://t.co/3ybHYbmJr5

JPMorgan Chase has relaxed its dress code, iss… https://t.co/PZWDjjwh6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Suisse Makes Its Employees Take Tonight Off https://t.co/JePrcZnUWJ

Unless they’re working on a major deal… https://t.co/NKDlEdAksd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ‘Ban the Box’ Backfires on Minority Job Applicants https://t.co/f0oCzQAAM4

“Ban the box” laws, which prohibit… https://t.co/a5DMpsQwuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Very Weak’ May Jobs Report Makes Fed Rate Hike Less Likely https://t.co/h2aHeFXkRl

Job growth in the US fell wel… https://t.co/t8XoFbvoHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Six-Hour Workday? Make That Five https://t.co/coH28YoL3W

While some European employers have been experimenting … https://t.co/XRJBacGHdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want Dads to Take Paternity Leave? Pay Them https://t.co/x6ceqRdI7d

The UK’s Shared Parental Leave policy, which … https://t.co/IN1x5CI1vI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bias of Hiring From Within One’s Academic Strata https://t.co/VS9a06hww9

Writing at SourceCon, Paul Wolfe, SV… https://t.co/WiiaOBc7gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOL Jumps on the Internal Incubator Bandwagon https://t.co/yz3okJiTEX

The hottest tech company of 1995 is looking… https://t.co/A500bnpAxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coworking Economy https://t.co/rTDlMgHe1a

A new report from the Instant Group, a serviced workspace provider,… https://t.co/bvXXrJmXIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programming AI to Create Jobs https://t.co/Mb4N6qSTYw

Will the current wave of automation driven by robotics and … https://t.co/b45Xlp5yfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Leaders Left Hanging on the ‘Glass Cliff’ https://t.co/XXvbLgykNi

Theresa May, the UK’s new prime minister,… https://t.co/ROF3PyiOr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New US-EU Data Sharing Agreement Goes into Effect, But Challenges Await https://t.co/ZQYcjUazu6

A new data-sharin… https://t.co/6mkVwdSpNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your New Wellness Coach Could Be a Bot https://t.co/rjAZltKaDE

Robin Mestre, the principal strategic advisor at G… https://t.co/o2CEqfrRO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Criticized for Blaming Poor Diversity Numbers on ‘Pipeline Problem’ https://t.co/b7YCv76xrT

Facebook dro… https://t.co/ossjI3zzkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When It Comes to CEO Pay, Who Should Decide? https://t.co/W9N3z66guM

As employees across the developed world watc… https://t.co/UxbaFyzuNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Not Just You: Workplace Political Tensions Are Particularly High in the US This Year https://t.co/uCrTjZteO0 … https://t.co/Hz2xmysyDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wage Stagnation Should Worry Employers, Not Just Governments https://t.co/pSTQ0UkW9N

Between 65 and 70 percent of… https://t.co/npzRbEZokS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Market for Brexit Managers https://t.co/1ThGuhXlWG

To manage the UK’s disengagement from the EU, the new pr… https://t.co/kWiNTRjYF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ElaineKTurville: Great fundraiser at @scoutandmollys in Mosaic team Fox for Parkinson's and @ashleywane @AccentureCmty @AccentureFed ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Fasting to Monitoring Brainwaves, ‘Biohackers’ Pursue the Optimized Self https://t.co/l1E0IbpDNw

New technol… https://t.co/lJhiDPxXNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Boards Can’t Say They Can’t Find Qualified Women Anymore https://t.co/NRRbcrFq8a

One major reason why the pa… https://t.co/o5vvcNVl74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Holacracy Too Bureaucratic? https://t.co/MumcLQQqnB

Holacracy, the “flat” management philosophy popularized by… https://t.co/BxcACXm0i1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shifting to Tiered Health Coverage Creates Winners and Losers https://t.co/wlFqNJ6u6M

As part of a series of chan… https://t.co/uDinsEcQnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investment Bank Recruiters Court Non-Finance Majors https://t.co/HzU3Y8Z57U

The financial sector has really been … https://t.co/Jp9hWm7yE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Fasting to Monitoring Brainwaves, ‘Biohackers’ Pursue the Optimized Self https://t.co/iZvGyXW9tY

New technol… https://t.co/cdawhNFJLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Boards Can’t Say They Can’t Find Qualified Women Anymore https://t.co/p4BxIOrydb

One major reason why the pa… https://t.co/nVP44690ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Holacracy Too Bureaucratic? https://t.co/Hh0KqFDoNy

Holacracy, the “flat” management philosophy popularized by… https://t.co/gobrtbLgAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shifting to Tiered Health Coverage Creates Winners and Losers https://t.co/0zttbQsSZK

As part of a series of chan… https://t.co/AWynMRG0MQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investment Bank Recruiters Court Non-Finance Majors https://t.co/KwFgszTHMA

The financial sector has really been … https://t.co/TNfAMRZ4O0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is HR the New PR? https://t.co/L830KHz2eG

Most people have seen GE’s “What’s the matter with Owen?” ads, promotin… https://t.co/tlwRXe9ACI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain’s Brexit Government Vows to Work for Workers https://t.co/pYxQhGA7Xm

The decision by UK voters to withdra… https://t.co/xBqrbXaWVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compensation Is a Great Attractor—Just Don’t Think It’s All That Matters https://t.co/uRwF3uL7xM

Suzanne Lucas at… https://t.co/LoF6p9YqZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Samantha Bee Brought Diversity to Her Writers’ Room https://t.co/oSG8Hfouwd

When her hit show Full Frontal pr… https://t.co/Wh8Qb8fnz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing in Employees’ Mental Health Pays Off https://t.co/HUOHCCm8DZ

At the Harvard Business Review, Influence … https://t.co/1GOSneFqoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Chatbot to Handle (and Respond to) Your Job Applicants https://t.co/5L5TbAthdM

Candidates may not like getting … https://t.co/ZQluWowwpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Mechanical Turks’: Young, Educated, and Underpaid https://t.co/NCmeBWhB4R

A new Pew study looks at Amazon’s Mech… https://t.co/KcSU96IUO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can America Bring Back Its Missing Workers? https://t.co/vPK9C3fccM

US Secretary of Labor Tom Perez is encouraged… https://t.co/xiiWqpxgZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Black Lives Matter in Your Workplace? Your Black Employees Need to Know https://t.co/ZG7h0Lo4uv

The recent sho… https://t.co/QL2yMMl0I5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Leaders in UK Look Toward Strategic Transformation https://t.co/q0JtsyHAq2

A new survey has found that 74 perc… https://t.co/f4hs9VW6Wt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pokémon Go Back to Work https://t.co/XkJXWLLBeg 

First world problems. #Pokémon #Pokemon #PokemonGo #gottacatchem… https://t.co/41Mk0vzKEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase Raises Minimum Wage https://t.co/HQnW3bjvqo

In a New York Times op-ed published on Tuesday, JPMorg… https://t.co/P3KYoyOH0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Survey: Living Wage Not a Big Job Killer, But Post-Brexit Inflation May Undermine It https://t.co/GwGq5UBPTc

A… https://t.co/K6D9iPgKct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Startups that Reject the Gig Economy https://t.co/VjDWcbBudg

Glenn Kelman, CEO of the online real estate star… https://t.co/1cbnXqtlmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come for Work, Stay for Dinner https://t.co/8GnfeMoifQ

We’ve heard about the trend of coworking where you work ou… https://t.co/i6O4bm1XnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can London Remain a Global Financial Capital After Brexit? https://t.co/Xo8wEZ1CEs

In the immediate aftermath of … https://t.co/rK8ZElcaMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive June Jobs Report Calms Fears of US Labor Market Downturn https://t.co/vJc2UW7zqD

After posting disconcer… https://t.co/P4dHia8wYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Companies With Women CEOs More Likely to Have Women on Boards https://t.co/Qr8mMFD1d1

The ET Intelligence … https://t.co/3aA82JCKRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials: The Purpose Generation? https://t.co/Xbs36NlVoJ

In a recent global survey of millennials, a majority… https://t.co/qAHbvE8JBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Nestlé Tapped an Outsider for Its New CEO https://t.co/nN8nWlokIH

Last week, Nestlé announced that Ulf Mark S… https://t.co/opVM5VIPuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Video Kill the On-Campus Interview? https://t.co/eilEmjy5CZ

As part of an effort to cast a wider recruiting … https://t.co/5KGKOtPmhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internships and Mentorships: Not Just for the Young Anymore https://t.co/kWzSASi9r1

At the Harvard Business Revie… https://t.co/v2tC71w7bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JolyonMaugham: Just wow. Seven. Hundred. Thousand. fewer jobs advertised post-Brexit (h/t @PickardJE) https://t.co/vgS99xGgg5. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smart careers strategy: singtel gives employees 2 additional days per year to pursue skill building.  @singtel https://t.co/5Zfz0MBvUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bad Science Behind Eliminating Performance Ratings https://t.co/i0Mpx4zJy0

In a short but insightful article … https://t.co/J1TLG5Hg8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College Degrees Have Graduated to Requirements in Today’s Job Market https://t.co/7rLPreKHKx

Justifying the cost … https://t.co/h42EsAwjCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon Drops Ban on Transgender Soldiers https://t.co/wzOblALCZl

Last week, the Pentagon officially lifted its … https://t.co/j1ElKVLCTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Automation Shrink the C-Suite? Or Lead to More Democratization? https://t.co/ABFpP77tzG

A study McKinsey con… https://t.co/Wgcqad0shx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@One_Page_Talent smart insights on why performance ratings are better than the alternative https://t.co/7uFb16WmDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If All of the Leadership Competency Models Are Wrong? https://t.co/SkTkB7HgrN

If you were to stack up all th… https://t.co/t4uKp9OeWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debunking the Myths of Queen Bees and Wannabes in the Workplace https://t.co/WXA5jJdTH8

The stereotype of the “qu… https://t.co/fjZMeDqX3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Practices Aren’t Always Best https://t.co/9whM5s6vPC

At the Harvard Business Review, Stanford professor Pame… https://t.co/bO1YDhdFhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise of Coworking Where You Work Out https://t.co/U5tMapIFsO

Capitalizing on the growing market for coworking… https://t.co/TZxuyS3BRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lean Staffing Compounds Brexit Challenge for UK Civil Service https://t.co/fqVcHEnvJU

We’ve talked about how Brex… https://t.co/tKO5RfmcVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Future of Work, Who Provides the Benefits? https://t.co/UWihC0tJdt

Katy Steinmetz at Time highlights a sur… https://t.co/Jz1S9dMRJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OscarsSoWhite: New Academy Invitees Are a More Diverse Cast https://t.co/BuiMboo0Tx

In response to the controver… https://t.co/6zPiLWkfog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Entry-Level Workers Ready for Day One https://t.co/e9YMSilW5W

Quartz’s Michael J. Coren interviews Alexis… https://t.co/7e60fRvPfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Your Employees Are Using Social Media at Work https://t.co/mU4v9QAKFS

Now that Microsoft’s LinkedIn acquisit… https://t.co/30VoqVW5OQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That ‘Useless’ Liberal Arts Degree May Be Worth More Than You Think https://t.co/Zvei2KKhzK

It’s a truism among s… https://t.co/begvHk3Uq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGBT Discrimination Lawsuit Ends in Settlement https://t.co/cYhTizbI56

Earlier this year, the Equal Employment Op… https://t.co/0vfk7wC3n9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Brexit Means for the Tech Sector https://t.co/s7oDNa5c3y

While Brexit will have a variety of effects on diff… https://t.co/rOjX9EOs1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Business Lessons of Brexit https://t.co/JGg1crrk0N

Thursday’s Brexit referendum will surely be appearing in p… https://t.co/VEDzXRDqH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Market Greets Brexit With Hiring Freezes and Job Searches https://t.co/IZy0NqDh0P

Last Thursday’s Brexit re… https://t.co/Y9CESkh8zn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>