<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact of the day: The female fruit bat is the only non-primate known to perform fellatio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BryantMcGill: Another person's thoughts about you are outside of your jurisdiction; you have no authority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Slate: The trailer for the Coen Bros.’ new movie has everything we love about their old ones: http://t.co/z5erJVeY1f http://t.co/KqAGhg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beckett leaving Castle is a shark-jumping moment: out-of-character twist for the sake of shaking up the show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: French girl speeding on a scooter, 1984. http://t.co/z9rWaBLFkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Michael J Fox and Huey Lewis on the set of "Back to the Future", 1985. http://t.co/4Gw99Rmdn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephenfry: When a YouTube video automatically plays after the one you’ve chosen to see. Most distressing to one with a finely tuned ne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @onthepage: Tip:  The more specific the backstory, the more it pulls focus from the story you're telling in the moment. So make sure it'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he thought he felt happier then realised it was merely the sweet, fleeting embrace of alcohol. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethStelling Isn't there a better term than "female comic"? "Comicess" perhaps, like "poetess" or "authoress"? @miss_nomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Sigourney Weaver and Jonesy. Alien, 1979. http://t.co/atM2Xutmpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: A German soldier finally arrives home, only to find his family gone. Photograph by Tony Vaccaro, 1946. http://t.co/RiuZd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GonzoVice: "Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new." -Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: It doesn't take courage to be a writer, but it does take courage to be a bad writer which, alas, is a stop along the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because the NME is here to photograph his all-cat indie band &amp; he's the only member who seems to care. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: All in-stock Blu-rays and DVDs are 50% off for the next 24 hours at http://t.co/BPV0mR4gLr with promo code: SUZY http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he is on his way to the shops and has realised he has forgotten the money and list I gave him. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: The Others
(2001, Alejandro Amenabar) http://t.co/Cf3rGpZL4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers The dark side of fries? That just makes 'em crispy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Christina Applegate and boyfriend Brad Pitt, on the town, Los Angeles, 1988. http://t.co/AR5mCkQVe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Nearer to Pajo's Fish 'n' Chips -- one of the best places around here to get fish 'n' chips!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like film noir? Do you like the Coen Brothers? Sure you do! Watch "Miller's Crossing" right now! https://t.co/1Fvup56eBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: Miller's Crossing
(1990, Joel &amp; Ethan Coen) https://t.co/pv0akpSeql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colinmochrie: Bananas are considered unlucky on fishing boats. Also unlucky to find fish in your banana split.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Lift with your legs, not your back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Dreaming up a new project! It's billable time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Michael Caine and wife circa 1970s. https://t.co/UeLcAQAL66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@videomaker One of the most common expressions I use in After Effects is "God damn it!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katemicucci Don't take acupuncture! The "acu" part is fine; it's the "puncture" that gets you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brenopolis: SCAMMERHEAD wins "Visionary Award" at @lcifilmfest!!! https://t.co/KAHAOG7AkR https://t.co/gePgiqaZp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because I caught him walking around on two legs, pretending to be human and work in a nice library. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Last known photo of Nikola Tesla, 1943. https://t.co/OWa3zD080j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Slate: Adorable finch tap dance, invisible to mumans, captured on video for the first time: https://t.co/j74CI3rInA https://t.co/5RPMcX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck To be fair, he was retired. Although I don't think much of the Jedi pension plan, if that's where he had to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson As an old guy, I can affirm that all that shag carpeting was warm and cozy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he can see into your soul and feel every contradiction and frustration of the human condition. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marlene Dietrich and Edith Piaf, circa 1940s. https://t.co/AGvV7vZ9lE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The Wizard of Oz, 1939. https://t.co/UCn3QFxZZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he is remembering a ladycat he met on holiday many years ago and crying for their lost love. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: Planet of the Apes
(1968, Franklin J. Schaffner) https://t.co/gpkj76F187]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because the lemons life gave him have been stolen by a happier cat who is using them to make cocktails https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because my other cat is trying to do CPR on this vole but unfortunately it looks like it's too late. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminluk That's how we know you're really a professional photographer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect that this caption may have been intended for a different photo. https://t.co/Mg3C0hNVXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck We were out on a date in my daddy's car, my love for you will never die, somewhere up above. Crash!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tarakjpratt: Rice crackers are lies because you end up eating the equivalent of half your body weight and you shoulda just had real god…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Nicole Kidman in the 80’s. https://t.co/dBC9kyqa4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Depends. What was your time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeerJeet: Just visted the alternative reality where George Lucas directed Apocalypse Now! &amp; Jodorowsky's Dune was defining science fict…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Do you mean the beverage thing, or the programming thing? Either way, I have my doubts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he played one of his favourite albums to my other cat, who called it "annoying and whiney". https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scammerhead: Cheers to @eyeCatcher_FF for SCAMMERHEAD"S nomination for
"Best Action Feature Film"! #filmfest #indiefilm #noirfilm https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UCLAFTVArchive: Jack Nicholson &amp; dir. Miloš Forman filming ONE FLEW OVER THE CUCKOO'S NEST, which premiered this day in 1975. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Krizanovich: The Producers: #film satire that launched Mel Brooks’ career https://t.co/VO7NrIwWkp https://t.co/I5vUVxkiMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiration comes from doing the work, not the other way around. https://t.co/V6CPVx32WV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: "Even award-winning playwrights make someplace between $25,000 and $39,000 a year..." Gretchen Cryer, The Dramatist  htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because morning has broken (him). https://t.co/cJIaTrumDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabathaSouthey: #fatsquirrelseason https://t.co/jmwiiRh6me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Here's hoping you can step up to "meh."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tarakjpratt: #FightLikeAGirl #GetBackUp https://t.co/OZfrpDqWB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like dance numbers? Sure you do! Watch this right now! https://t.co/bwb5t96Hbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wilw: Straight outta crafty. #SetJokes https://t.co/XXrUux8wxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReneeStephen: Today is #WorldPhilosophyDay everybody! All those with philosophy degrees join me in holding it to your face while sobbin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @miss_nomers: I come from a long line of non-morning people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried @Celtx for the first time in years. What a piece of junk! You can't even write on your own machine. Highly not recommended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: The longer it takes to write the first draft, the more you invest in it -- in a bad way. Write it fast so you can scoff …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @veschwab: My writing advice? KEEP WORKING. If 1st book does well, you'll need another, and if it doesn't, you'll need another. All road…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beardedstoner: I want to see Creed (the movie), but I'm afraid if I tell people they'll think I mean Creed (the band). I'm trapped in m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Don't be one of those writers who believes in the talent he had yesterday and the discipline he'll have tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Welcome APU to Criterion! On how the trilogy came to be, &amp; the beauty that makes it last: https://t.co/r4i3BuNY3o https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because hurtful, thoughtless comments have been made, leading to an atmosphere of tension and regret. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: Alan Parker’s MISSISSIPPI BURNING (photos by David Appleby &amp; Merrick Morton). For more: https://t.co/hLeKpTm6YE https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AKellumCreer: @VPL is streaming #CriterionCollection films for patrons - all you need is a library card. https://t.co/PdyTWSn0U2 https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRimer My money's on the lesbians for assembling Ikea furniture. They're using to doing things without tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: 1st draft, choose: story, plot, characters, style, setting, scenes, dialogue, title, names, stage directions. Don't get …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The Beatles, moments before making history on August 8th, 1969. https://t.co/uywa7ZPfvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SonyProUSA: Home Alone Hit Theaters 25 Years Ago-How They Filmed Its Crazy Finale https://t.co/SdNmiTyNWF via @Slate #Filmmaking https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: The idea that character trumps plot comes from a time when plot was assumed. Playwrights, learn to tell a story; take sc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fgonzalezse: Jean Renoir - Ingrid Bergman -  Jean Gabin https://t.co/2XhRgv72yY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Jean Seberg, effortless in BREATHLESS (1960). https://t.co/MWOF8sVbKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @toddlevin: I sincerely want the entire editorial staff of this website sealed into a tomb filled with diarrhea: https://t.co/esvkg1GmAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson As opposed to English kiss, which is where you both sort of awkwardly purse your lips until one of you goes away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: I can always tell when one of my cats has been up to no good because they try a little bit too hard to look casual. http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depressing thought for movie-makers: "the suits are firmly in control of a fundamentally uncontrollable business": https://t.co/9kpRqvuV4Z.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LizRoseMorriss: On a Clear Day You Can See Ferenginar #nerdbroadway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NerdBroadway -- "Guys and DOS", "BrigaDOOM", "Syncin' in the Rain", "The Book of More Manpages", "Phantom of the Opera Browser", "/cat/s".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck I'll record the audio! It's just grunts and swearing, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kalebhorton: Time to sell out. Here's my Back to the Future 4 script. Bidding starts at 5 million. Wait. 10 million. https://t.co/GULOv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Audrey Hepburn in 'Sabrina,' 1954. https://t.co/whWVOF9st8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Literature should not disappear up its own asshole, so to speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alyankovic: Okay, Starbucks, NOW you’ve gone too far. https://t.co/bYOVgxo91f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Modern master Michael Haneke shares a glimpse into his filmmaking process: https://t.co/4VrUsMCBuc https://t.co/WKQzBsXjAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just used some silicon spray to re-waterproof my bicycle rain-gear. Now my lungs are nice and waterproof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee I've wondered the same thing about "Doubleyou Doubleyou Doubleyou" versus "World Wide Web". It's literally three times as long!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Janis Joplin at Woodstock, 1969. https://t.co/apK5PblXIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are intelligent, kind, &amp; good-looking. Naturally, I hate them. If you're smart and nice, you should have the decency to be ugly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: One of New York Central’s “Mercury” engines in Chicago, 1936. https://t.co/N2cK2RD4fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Take an acting class. No, this is not optional. Highest praise for dialogue is "actor-friendly," so you need to figure o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: We have to talk to keep our voice boxes working so we'll have good voice boxes in case there's ever anything really mean…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley I think that what they really object to is the Starbucks corporation's deep support for the communist revolution ... comrade.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>