<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankFeighan: Miraculous medal found  in ballot paper at Roscommon count http://t.co/jHBFWMM2vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankFeighan: The bundles of votes in Roscommon suggest No 18500 Yes 17000 approx #rssl #marref http://t.co/5AIEfvyy3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Dem: Right now the Roscommon constituency is leaning No (it seems).Was 64%+ anti-divorce. But even so, its close #MarRef  https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AodhanORiordain: I'll be a guest on @RTESatnightshow this evening to discuss my new responsibility for the National Drugs Strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbassadorPower Dear Ms Power, hope you're well. I'm a journalist with the Sunday Independent. Can you please follow me for a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nycinews: Current voter reg system needs to be reformed per article by @ClaireMc_C 19th century system in 21st century should be simple…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 120,000 under-25s 'are not registered' to vote @nycinews http://t.co/ZGqrFLILSQ via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bodywhys: #Media - Jacinta Hastings from Bodywhys recently spoke to @ClaireMc_C in relation to the internet http://t.co/j7OsruJwDY @Ind…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateCarbery Hi Kate,I'm a reporter with the Sunday Independent. I was hoping to speak to you about a story. Can you follow me for a DM? Tks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom!! @e_mcguire @denmahon @MichaelOnassis @gisacdcu @James_Proclaims @Dzean0 @gavmcloughlin #maj #dcu #grad http://t.co/HbiuTxLEoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @e_mcguire: Lookin good @ClaireMc_C @denmahon ! #maj #dcu #graduation http://t.co/sBpOGK8VlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We did it :) @e_mcguire @denmahon  #graduationday #dcu http://t.co/6ZVQnhf8f8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearbhailDibs Brilliant interview and insight on @thelatelateshow Well done on all your fantastic coverage #grahamdwyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MollyMuldoonNYC Looking good on @ClaireByrneLive, what a pleasant surprise :) Hope all's good in NYC misses :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass youth emigration leaves gap in society, and it's just the beginning http://t.co/Zl7urZmFE9 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GAA bans ref from wearing Rainbow Gay Pride wristband at Croker http://t.co/k32K6TpwED via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failing rural towns: Eerie silence falls on famed town of the 'Four Roads'  http://t.co/kr2MimOawr via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SterlingMolly Hi Molly, I'm a reporter with the Sunday Independent. Can you follow for me for a DM please? Thanks, Claire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful. "Elderly man had ‘nappy down around him’ in Beaumont Hospital" http://t.co/nNPn7OHlZ7 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Drennan's Guide to Politics http://t.co/ryaRv9uDiE via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OborneTweets: Why I have resigned from the Daily Telegraph: https://t.co/dgqWwfo9LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cari_ie: *TW: 'Porn In Playground' Fuels Rise In 'Child-On-Child' Sex Assaults @ClaireMc_C @HSElive @Education_Ire @DCENR http://t.co/4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends and countrymen, lend me your (jug) ears ...  http://t.co/TaZfZpHXpq via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megansmolenyak Hi Megan,hope you're well. I'm a reporter with an Irish newspaper. I was hoping to quote your research. Can I DM you please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sagelyriard Thank you for reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @megansmolenyak: Fun piece by @ClaireMc_C in @TheSundayIndo about my research on @springsteen's #Irish roots! http://t.co/gqpc2V3M0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spirited rugby fans tell world that 'Ballymore needs a priest' http://t.co/yx4fye8SwN via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnjgreene: Nice sunny day to watch loads of sport on tv . . . plenty of time to have a read of this too http://t.co/y9o5DGC8Jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Womens_eNews: 4 Years Reporting for @Womens_eNews http://t.co/S7oCdBDj7s @ClaireMc_C @Gagandeepjourno #womenslives @Alirosa http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hill16dublinma1: Hill 16 Dublin Macra prepping for busy year ahead @ivyhousedublin #Macra #recruitment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rural homeless crisis as sheds used for shelter http://t.co/Aw2AJdtNDJ via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum's diet before birth will decide if baby is a fat adult http://t.co/L06T5XJ5JP via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReyhanaPatel Sure,  can you follow me for a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saatchi torn by demolition of home http://t.co/CEaHd44jC5 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educated for export: young Irish teachers making a buck in UK http://t.co/XOdBCAqoMG via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hello grandma...' - Berkeley survivor Aoife calls home for first time http://t.co/a0XOBu9XEE via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NERI_research: . @TomHealyNERI on @TodaySOR  discussing #precarious jobs—what are they, who's affected and possible solutions http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We're being incentivised to stay on the dole'  http://t.co/nrPb727I5O via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm so fed-up ... I'm moving to Spain and I may not return' http://t.co/GspnRUghoB via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touching 30 but a decade from owning a home   http://t.co/S7STzxNpi7 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Getting married is tougher than Tour de France' - Nicolas http://t.co/ED79dg2dSV via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are midland kings buried in our raised bogs, say experts http://t.co/56gl2DqXo7 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surge in illegal Irish in Oz as visas expire http://t.co/MCEesbBgYs via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel: Austria - a fairy tale come true  http://t.co/McNAyeX9qW via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aideennally: @8Outof10Cats_TV where is @RonJichardson ???? It's been too long #missingjon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnceMusicalDub: 'Every line lands, every joke lands' @meganriordan on bringing #Once home to Dublin @olympiatheatre http://t.co/bKi0J8B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mojos Supporting Westmeath" flying over Croke Park #LeinsterFinal #GAA http://t.co/AwstCFCJge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westmeath team "chomping at the bit" says legendary Lake County player Paddy Flanagan #Leinsterfinal #GAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnjgreene: A few words with Paddy Flanagan ('aged 80 plus VAT') - and a fantastic GAA man http://t.co/GZeUXRU8Dr via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isil trolls social media for Irish jihadi brides http://t.co/tGUGSSCMaq via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @westmeath_gaa: The famine is over !! Westmeath 3-20 Meath 2-18 anyone with a spare heart as mine is banjaxed!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dessiedolan: Come back of all come backs!!!!
Amazing performance from the boys!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheSundayGame: We've @dessiedolan on later with @SportsDes - can't wait! #Westmeath #SundayGame http://t.co/2a8wISF3t6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheSundayGame: "This was a brilliant game of football, it was Gaelic football as it should be played." - Pat Spillane. #SundayGame http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnjgreene: All over and Westmeath win by 5 - 15 point turnaround in second half and one of most incredible finales you'll ever see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Leukaemia won’t stop me finishing my exams,’ says brave Alicia http://t.co/2mcw0j5gzY via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geary aiming to raise profile of women's sport http://t.co/Uf6WYQhnSY via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous article @DearbhailDibs #inspiration What success really looks like for the fairer sex  http://t.co/VYCmmxVIJo via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student digs crisis crushes dreams of university life http://t.co/Ta3cenZXhZ via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Bama's Irish mafia hold US reins of power http://t.co/QNbBXmWaDq via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Residents are in turmoil over new children's hospital http://t.co/9CNRx4Rx7U via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhonaTarrant Thanks misses :) Hope all is well with you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnjgreene: Don't forget this is with tomorrow's paper. If you've  any connection with a club, no matter how small it's worth it https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling Irish tennis remains an uphill battle fought by lone soldiers  https://t.co/ik5rJ0layF via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ellegordon3: Excited to be on @RyanTubridyShow with my Mammy discussing that time I have her control of my Tinder for my #sundayindepen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IzHayes Hi Isabel, hope you are well. I'm a reporter with the Sunday Indo. Can you follow me for a DM please? Thank you, Claire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndoSport: @Sineadkissane - 'Is it so hard to believe that women might just love sport too': https://t.co/G1D6lxGqUF https://t.co/0VUt7…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heroes of the high plateau appeal to Irish adventurers to visit Nepal https://t.co/i2lT7SCccM via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was ever a generation so misled? https://t.co/gsnFOUb9rB via @IrishTimesOpEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country legend Nathan Carter makes women swoon but he's still looking for love... https://t.co/ZkzdE46WmX via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ellegordon3: Cheers for hot chocolate Clear😂😇@ClaireMc_C https://t.co/TQ2rVQx3eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amyschumer: Beautiful, gross, strong, thin, fat, pretty, ugly, sexy, disgusting, flawless, woman. Thank you @annieleibovitz https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidconachy: Sindo legend Willie Kealy gets knock down salute on his last day https://t.co/SbGN8H7dYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @galwaygrrl: .@ClaireMc_C | #Isil and rebels a click away from #Irish teens | https://t.co/FKWXXTNKkN &lt;--- With (a lot of) comment from …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Paris attacks: 'I will not give you the gift of hating you' https://t.co/gAhtuArxNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donegal ace pounds old foe as shoppers cash in on cheap euro https://t.co/hux52wsKx7 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm on a new path and I'm stronger than ever' - abuse survivor Emma  https://t.co/vaIjhdnm4N via @Independent_ie @Womens_Aid @SAFEIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris Terror Attacks: Wexford woman caught in Paris attacks feels lucky to be alive  https://t.co/cRUpL4ZWKg via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiachraGibbons Hi Fiachra, hope you're well. I'm a journalist with Sunday Independent in Dublin. Can you follow me for a DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are any Irish people caught up in tonight's #Paris attacks can you please contact me or send a DM. Journalist with @TheSundayIndo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidconachy: @tim_cook dropped into the Sunday Independent newsroom to say hi @cormacbourke @RAE_Stephen @Independent_ie #Apple https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cormacbourke: Sunday Independent p1 https://t.co/vTNPFbpuTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are any Irish people caught up in the #Istanbul bomb attacks can you please contact me or send a DM. Journalist with @TheSundayIndo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rtenews: Local health officials say two Irish people have been injured in a suicide bomb in Istanbul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DermotLeary Hi Dermot, I'm a journalist with the Sunday Indo. Can you please follow me for a DM? Thank you, Claire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['If the town goes, it will be gone for good ...' https://t.co/zSFAznrIIA via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day the rural heartland revolted and cried: 'Where is our recovery?' https://t.co/Eap3mZbH5z via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mayo_LGFA: Tune in to Sarah Rowe on the Marian Finucane show talking about life as an inter county player and inequality within sports …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sheilareilly123: Maybe conditions would improve for women players if @officialgaa introduced gender quotas in county boards? .@RTERadio1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @e_mcguire: It's 10:30pm on day two of the count. I guess this is why they call it LONGford. #ge16 #ldwh https://t.co/Oc56ul6xyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wordbird_ie: @broadsheet_ie One person in West Cavan not that impressed with the new electoral area #Cavan #GE16 https://t.co/GfWb8OPv4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellegordon3 Haha!! Too cute, some classic moves :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We play wherever we can get a pitch' - Leacy https://t.co/JqA0i9fOrb via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamJClifford Thanks Graham! Good on you too. Keep going :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nj_sharkey Thanks a million Shark :) All good here, hope you're keeping well too :) Serious hair! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KDelaney4 Thanks Karen :) Hope you are keeping good x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnjgreene: Tomorrow's front page ... interview with @SarsRowe worth a read. Very honest portrayal of where women's sport is at https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomensGPA: Mayo's Sarah Rowe taking a stand against inequality. 
Via @IndoSport. #lgfa #gaa

https://t.co/JuCboXwfwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ellegordon3: A must read in last Sundays @sundayindo Tell the canvassers to start opening doors for disabled https://t.co/FKZIrZGihh vi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @megansmolenyak: Will Springsteen visit his ancestral hometown of Rathangan while in Ireland? https://t.co/t3CFWIhxCf via @Independent_i…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>