<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/zXFFMD2jyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/M1nYJD9c4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/tMyJq5dRpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/qpo1dRT3Kb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/gMNc4la2qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/gqEeG63i0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/TN9zbbCvA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/JxhkPNxBFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/se3Qeopfwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/7F4c2Bajkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/kyDDaXNrMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/jQsOTK8TsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/JFgN7TKCUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/E5e3hLWmcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/oRuUeETRDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/Iu0LCKcOAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/diMvoMeoDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Facebook-Top Tips for Business Success  http://t.co/6he1YImCzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dcAWgNXj3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/K2ZtJy91LZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/Pi8N7yKZnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/oJPjQDH6u1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/K7yLi6MHL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/cbgu8o0gwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/qyHFwvft7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/oeVCZyInm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is the first milestone on the road to the stars. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/AmhOy4k2OD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/A1xCsgHVnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/HGKUbqw0l8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/sxpzPHC8U5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/ZFrkKn4iBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/CgKIkaQxUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/m7gzZPtdTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/ktFWXbV6jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/gX5M9aYV0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/5OZqOibkKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/ltPSIQi9Of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/TLMIQFp6uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/pAO5R0GdPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/n0bS2saNHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/JKUDXZXtUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/bXwUU55i6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/q36GPbW72T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>