<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd/3rd line Infrastructure Engineer: 2nd/3rd line Infrastructure Engineer London To £38k + Bens Looking for career progression? Fast paced multi client customer facing environment? Skills:- On premises Exchange and Exchange Online, Office 365, Back ups,… https://t.co/o1tfDm1UCi https://t.co/Kxkr44L3up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK to probe fairness of personalized pricing practices in online retail: The UK government has announced an investigation into personalized pricing practices in online retail following growing concerns that vulnerable consumers are at risk of price… https://t.co/gjg4CrdvEo https://t.co/IyyLD7JNGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Ordnance Survey has an opportunity available for an IT Support Technician to join the team based in Southampton. You will join us on a full time, permanent basis and in return, you will receive a competitive salary of £25,000 per… https://t.co/uLeQF077IQ https://t.co/bWdAyBBXEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid record STD rates, doctors treat patients' partners sight unseen: If patients return to Dr. Crystal Bowe soon after taking medication for a sexually transmitted infection, she usually knows the reason: Their partners have re-infected them. https://t.co/ATzE7kQ6Lp https://t.co/OYlXdUPUCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre – Sales Engineer: Pre Sales Engineer / Solutions Engineer / Sales Engineer To be based in London Salary: £35-45,000 Permanent opportunity I have a brand new requirement for a Sales Engineer to work for one of my clients based in London. It’s an… https://t.co/eLm08Mixbr https://t.co/gQd8dUeiNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Developer: Blockchain Developer Edinburgh IF YOU CAN SEE THE FUTURE POSSIBILITIES FOR BLOCKCHAIN … Work with a world leading authority in Blockchain and Crypotography. Get directly involved in bringing ideas and technical innovation to life.… https://t.co/maUr9cpfbY https://t.co/o2wCdYEAjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Concur – Senior Director Product Management / Expense: SAP Concur – Senior Director Product Management / Expense Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP… https://t.co/n8r3ul9Ncs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: A strong Software Engineer with a C++ application development background is required by a market leading engineering manufacturer with an international reputation based in Bristol. The successful candidate will work on complex projects… https://t.co/CtHT0BzVpV https://t.co/yr1XkGXeIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – Trade and Tourism: My client in Newport, South Wales are seeking a Data Analyst on a 6 month contract basis. A division within this organisation deal with trade statistics and the way they are compiled is changing in order to meet growing… https://t.co/lxMUsO022h https://t.co/CsK4iOvELm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HBO Summer Intern: Digital Products Software Engineer: Search Display ******************************************************************************************* &amp; partnerid=391 &amp; siteid=36 &amp; jobid=****** &amp; codes=NIND Loading Close Your account has… https://t.co/hHONupH0Zg https://t.co/gcaSY1N0JG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Agile Business Analyst East Midlands £350 – £385 per day 3 month contract initally (2 year programme) Uniting Ambition are currently working with a high growth business in Leicestershire and we have an excellent opportunity for a… https://t.co/tcONPZWG56 https://t.co/EQsWT9cqfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Software Engineer – Mid Level: Purpose of Job IMPORTANT: Applicants – When filling out your name and other personal information below, DO NOT use any special characters or ALL CAPS. Use only standard letters in the English alphabet. Including… https://t.co/Q6UPZBQHqv https://t.co/gQeJPkGenF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Various Roles: Because there's more to policing than fighting crime on the streets, we're working to deliver new and innovative technology to enable the future of policing. It's a dynamic area that's creating exciting opportunities for IT… https://t.co/I3uazS2toT https://t.co/tHfCGqNckD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire George Soros wants to go on Fox News. But they won't book him.: Fox News talks about billionaire philanthropist George Soros a lot. He is a favorite bogeyman of the right, so Fox's conservative talk shows blame him for all sorts of ills,… https://t.co/RqOsLVJQ8s https://t.co/cCJNXgQrd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Integration Developer: ERP – Integration Developer in Arlington, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent… https://t.co/tmo0VUmraz https://t.co/kb74uqoexR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer – Waterford My client, one of Ireland’s top insurance companies, are seeking to hire a software engineer as the company grows. Come and work for one of Ireland’s top insurance companies where you will… https://t.co/sULZ4W0r5j https://t.co/x8RjFnXmE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California teacher caught on camera punching 14-year-old: A teacher and student at a southeast Los Angeles, California, high school came to blows Friday afternoon, and it was all caught on video. https://t.co/cLxOjIy4a7 https://t.co/Zo6YjVbzbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WordPress Developer: WordPress Developer with knowledge of HTML CSS PHP and JavaScript sought by a RAR award-winning design and branding agency based in Leeds. They are highly regarded as a market leader and have been recognised for creating design for… https://t.co/ZAb0Mx9XAe https://t.co/iLTSWm1INk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff DevOps Engineer: Requisition Number: ****** Position Title: Engineer (IV) External Description: Staff DevOps Engineer Cloud Foundational ServicesLocation: San Diego, California Introduction: Are you a problem solver? Does the prospect of solving… https://t.co/wXsLrHysml https://t.co/LxrJo9XwdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Business Development Executive (French Speaking): Graduate Business Development Executive (French Speaking) Reading – £27k (OTE £34k) Sector: Software Officially one of the fastest growing technology companies globally, our multi-award winning… https://t.co/yYQxbBOJqR https://t.co/dBbtgCY7yJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS DevOps Engineer: AWS DevOps Engineer 3 Month Initial Contract Immediate Contract Role! We’re looking for passionate developers with experience building clever web platforms who want to make a real impact on health research. Responsibilities. *… https://t.co/9AICnGWEHS https://t.co/chPNpcdQxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Direct Sales Executive: Graduate Direct Sales Executive Location: London Salary: £25,000 (up to £35,000 OTE) Sector: Telecommunications Providing managed communications for over 20 years, this established telecommunications organisation has… https://t.co/lUvOWD1shx https://t.co/hpAbD8uU7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineering Manager: Data Engineer Manager, SQL, BigQuery, RedShift Data Engineer Manager We are seeking an amazing Data Engineer Manager to own the creation, maintenance and delivery of the business intelligence layer of our data platforms, to… https://t.co/vnTCLAegI6 https://t.co/KyNnDxq6TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Bohemian Rhapsody' rocks the box office: "Bohemian Rhapsody" is the champion of the box office this weekend. https://t.co/yCuA1yGvLl https://t.co/TwuTtddnYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer: IT Developer – Up to £35k + Great Benefits Healthcare Redhill, Surrey This client has an opening for an IT Developer to join the Healthcare IT Development team to program and capture requirements for program fixes and systems. Mendix is a… https://t.co/a9lGYdWJIw https://t.co/ccvk1qDDWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Director: The Solution Director is a senior role within Capita Networking Solutions, aligned to large complex deals the candidate would be responsible for shaping and leading large technology based deals. The complexity of the designs demands a… https://t.co/xBY0CwxnRf https://t.co/Hsd8lbsQsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Developer: Durham Constabulary are looking for a Junior Developer to join their growing team in Durham. Job Title: Junior Developer (Business Intelligence) Location: Force HQ, Durham Salary: £22,221 – £24,273 Hours: 37 hours per week, based on… https://t.co/saX3TrZb7O https://t.co/lBMT7qDnTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#, .NET Web Developer Tunbridge Wells to £45k: Our client is  looking to expand their team of in-house developers to make the platform even greater. Thesoftware stack covers everything from online retail sites, order processing, stock management,… https://t.co/JEwU8RE6go https://t.co/ti7exh5bUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Administrator: Administrator (IT Department) – 3 month contract initially Location: Canary Wharf (Canada Square) Pay: £95.00 Days: FT Monday – Friday Contract Duration: 3 months (potential to extend) IT Administrator, Administration, Stock check,… https://t.co/3IMnV7PfXp https://t.co/SLHCNKLucR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Billion-Dollar Internet Co – Warrington: NET Developer – Billion-Dollar Internet Co – Warrington (Tech stack: .NET, https://t.co/QLOVMKjai2 MVC, C#, WPF, Angular, RESTful, Web API, SQL Server, Agile, Urgent) We’re pleased to announce the… https://t.co/iLxAPqRnc1 https://t.co/QEjNgCxDW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: When people camp out on your lawn, remember Gillum: President Donald Trump campaigns for Ron DeSantis in Pensacola, Florida. https://t.co/yU1IVu2Jhs https://t.co/RDhdFjvWUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer – Ethical Software: Job Title: Full Stack PHP Developer Location: Bristol Salary: Circa £35,000 to £38,000 Benefits: Pension, Bonus, 28 days holiday ples Bank Holidays, Free Parking Are you a Developer with a couple of years’… https://t.co/FhmW7rBmHx https://t.co/65xTkuqaFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Lead: Project Description Our team provides opportunities to build up a career developing applications, which are critical for the client, using up-to-date software technologies and tools within mature process organization and people… https://t.co/4d9dQ3rPxs https://t.co/QsGuoMR6nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (https://t.co/upUTtHQm6N): Full Stack Developer (https://t.co/upUTtHQm6N) Bristol £(Apply online only) per day A superb opportunity has arisen for a Contract Software Developer (C#/ASP.Net/MVC) to join one of the fastest growing… https://t.co/DbKqbH0xaV https://t.co/XBBUyVxdcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst – Newport &amp; Cardiff The Candidate The successful Business Analyst will have proven business analysis experience possibly gained in the Financial Services Sector, although this is not essential as experienced Business… https://t.co/6jm0vBtnik https://t.co/oVAYAnIM73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer: Senior Systems Engineer- £40,000-47,000 per annum- Permanent- Christchurch Do you want to design and build systems to provide a secure 4G communication networks for our armed forces? Could you create systems that can allow a user… https://t.co/4MQMHowkTv https://t.co/SBiH8mJJZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Line IT Service Desk Analyst: 1st Line Service Desk Analyst / 1st Line IT Engineer, with good 1st line / PC / Desktop support experience in a busy IT Helpdesk / Service Desk, is required for an initial 3 month contract (likely to be extended), based… https://t.co/drszl74xIH https://t.co/IsGufgIkGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['SNL' skewers Fox News' coverage of the migrant march: For its last show before the midterm elections, "Saturday Night Live" took on a familiar target: Fox News. https://t.co/4Erpgk1c9q https://t.co/dfrJIMuIgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Routing Design Engineer: Network Routing Design Engineer Location: Quantico, VA Job Code: 3843 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services… https://t.co/FlUAuEOP0Z https://t.co/colhe8XcrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics CRM Consultant – Birmingham, Midlands, UK: Role My client is a growing Microsoft Gold Partner is looking to bolster their project delivery team with the addition of a Dynamics CRM/D365 Consultant. As a subject matter expert you will be… https://t.co/iwIQoVMx23 https://t.co/Tgp5ERj2PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect for Cloud Infrastructure: Architect for Cloud Infrastructure Job Description and Summary Our client is a next-generation tech company, turning over £19 billion per year to date. With offices worldwide and over 150,000 staff My client uses… https://t.co/vZDwFdbmOB https://t.co/oOqD5PaeYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer- contract: Job ID 2018-4249 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Business Applications About the Job We are looking for a talented Salesforce Developer to help us define and integrate our customer migration process. Job Duties *… https://t.co/dvayPlY60v https://t.co/5swju3k2n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people killed when truck hits Girl Scout troop: Three girls and a woman were killed Saturday morning when a truck driven by a Wisconsin man struck them as their Girl Scout troop was picking up trash along a roadway. https://t.co/TE5BOHqnkg https://t.co/ThjfApZ0HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineer: Customer Support Engineer BathCustomer Support Engineer Bath £20,000 – £23,000 DOE   CMD are proud to partner with a leading local eCommerce platform provider as they look to grow their team of talented and enthusiastic e-commerce… https://t.co/0i0m2Kf2qj https://t.co/7B2BabwjYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Enterprise Records: Software Engineer, Enterprise Records Tyler Technologies is looking for a passionate, talented Software Engineer to join our public safety product development team. This is an exciting opportunity to develop the… https://t.co/HZw1yUBAzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Contracts Manager: iRecruit Partners are currently working with a company based in Twyford who are looking for a Commercial Contracts Manager to join their rapidly expanding team. MAIN RESPONSIBILITIES: * Refresh and maintain ISO… https://t.co/iT49zcur4F https://t.co/u9TlKDxArf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game Programmer: Game Programmer Edmonton Gaming and Production – Gaming and Production Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the creation… https://t.co/QSZFRUCwQY https://t.co/ltWnlosQiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump's secret weapon works so well: If the comedian George Burns were alive today to witness the current state of politics, he might say, "Authenticity is the key to winning elections. And if you can fake that, you've got it made." https://t.co/EoqWZBnyni https://t.co/g2pkeQcw8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magento Developer (Backend) – PHP – Bath – £25,000 to £40,000: Magento Developer (Backend) | PHP, Magento | Bath | £25,000 to £40,000 An exciting opportunity for an experienced Backend Magento Developer, with experience of ecommerce, has arisen to join… https://t.co/R6FvnzQnhA https://t.co/NureRF3lOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Line IT Support: 1st Line IT Support | Rochdale – accessible from Leeds, Halifax, Oldham, Bury and Manchester Are you passionate about providing an excellent service on IT related issues? If so, then we want to hear from you. Bowmay Consulting is… https://t.co/Hqh3rZuL1t https://t.co/8lzIPclQJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM is getting into the electric bike business: General Motors said it plans to bring two new electric bikes to market next year — one folding and one compact — as the automaker makes a broader push into electrification and other ideas that try to move… https://t.co/ZAVn2P7lTO https://t.co/9DnohZxm5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics CRM Analyst: Are you a Dynamics CRM Specialist who is on the lookout for their next exciting opportunity? We are looking for an experienced Dynamics CRM Analyst to join a leading Investment Management company in central London. The successful… https://t.co/HiwS1MzMIw https://t.co/wjXUjCOJ7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbi told Trump that hate speech led to synagogue massacre: In a short but impassioned sermon Saturday, Rabbi Jeffrey Myers blamed politicians for a rise in hateful rhetoric, saying it led to the massacre at his synagogue last week in which 11 Jews were… https://t.co/aDfSapuXAA https://t.co/H9Zgoi8Df4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Focal Engineer – Cloud (VMware): Senior Focal Engineer – Cloud (VMware) Location: Camberley Pay: £45’000 – £55’000 per annum Contract: Permanent Senior Technical Engineer, Cloud VMware, threat detection, Customer service provider, Network Security… https://t.co/Qt4FwtFxUD https://t.co/1n1ih68AKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Software Company): Project Manager (Software Company) A leading software solutions company in Warwickshire with office across Europe are looking for a Project Manager to join them having due their sustained growth during 2018. The… https://t.co/GL1XK9FjlN https://t.co/Z8EgBkHoEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician (1st Line Level) – Coventry – £22,000 DOE: IT Support Technician (1st Line Level) wanted for a leading manufacturing client that I recruit for based in Coventry. I need candidates with at least 6-18 months previous IT Support,… https://t.co/n7NDxwlsPl https://t.co/ib8W2nYGtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant – Networking and Security: Senior Network &amp; Security Consultant £60,000 – £75,000 + Bonus + Benefits. Work From Home Overview My client is looking for a senior network &amp; security consultant to join a constantly growing MSP in… https://t.co/0hgnT7h7Jn https://t.co/iPwWLJPyYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Manager: An exciting role has come up for a Service Desk Manager close to Newmarket for a Company who are market leaders in the provision of managed IT services to the retail and hospitality sectors. With customer satisfaction at the very… https://t.co/tQWPEdPKKA https://t.co/ak2UPOeFcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Legend to campaign in Ohio this Sunday: Call it a legendary campaign event. https://t.co/IAh63esUmZ https://t.co/3uqp4nQEex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer / Tester / Firmware / Embedded / Networks / West: Test Engineer / Tester / Firmware / Embedded / Networks / West Yorkshire / £39,500 Are you a proactive Test Analyst with strong firmware and embedded testing experience who wants the… https://t.co/3JyiEZ04WI https://t.co/pgnQqfMmcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Job Title – Service Desk Analyst Tier 1 Location – Newtownabbey Competitive Salary &amp; Benefits About the role The Service Desk Analyst will provide ticket logging, technical support and ticket resolution to a range of internal and… https://t.co/gtDWNExrQU https://t.co/FTRmmnkEdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant, Unified Communications, £60,000, Home based: Skype for Business Technical Consultant, Lync 2010, Microsoft exchange, Office 365, Active Directory, £60,000 Skype for Business Technical Consultant, Microsoft Lync 2010, Microsoft… https://t.co/S7NWTH7t3k https://t.co/LCvnNiL4PN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior GIS Consultant (GIS/ArcGIS/ESRI): Senior GIS Consultant (GIS/ArcGIS/ESRI) Brief Overview We are looking for a GIS consultant with around five years' experience to join our client's Edinburgh team. With a core focus on GIS, you will also have an… https://t.co/18ePt9xHRf https://t.co/4xsYR3V9Gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MyPart finds that next def jam: Picture it: you have the perfect song for Kelly Clarkson. It’s a mix of genres and styles best described as “Since U Been Gone” meets “911 Is A Joke.” How do you get it in front of Kelly so she can add it to her next album… https://t.co/S8tThTHbib https://t.co/WNrNqFuJBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Consultant: Job Description What you’ll be doing… We take the complexity out of IT solution management. We enable our customers to use the right technologies to improve the way they do business. Our brightest minds are pushing the… https://t.co/YQ1ENJFbhT https://t.co/V3Ddoc4H4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Birmingham Salary up to £45,000pa basic One of the largest outsourcing organisations in the UK is currently seeking an experienced Business Analyst to join a new team to support in the delivery of Robotic Process… https://t.co/tO9tdGV6UW https://t.co/U9BqVjfQQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Heavy Highway, Paving, Grading, Underground: San Rafael, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! Based in beautiful San Rafael, CA we have made a stamp all over the Bay Area… https://t.co/EpCFtnbkCH https://t.co/zD6wxvYQkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4:   Job Description – Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 (18018549) Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 Requisition ID : 18018549 Location : United States-California-El Segundo US Citizenship… https://t.co/9QZKWmGKvS https://t.co/LbZ0If007K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Control Manager: Change Control Manager We’re partnered with a service provider of a huge public sector client undergoing the largest digital transformation in the UK. The initial contract is 6 months in length initially, and the chances of… https://t.co/EgSD0PuvZX https://t.co/PXvKdfzGA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Financial Services (Waterford): Business Analyst Contract – Financial Services (Kilkenny / Waterford / Tipperary) One of my core Financial Services clients has just contacted me to let me know that they have just had approval come… https://t.co/dpDjHYjxmX https://t.co/8XtiocciAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Tester: Quality Assurance Tester Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3848 # of openings: 3 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to… https://t.co/5QtFx3LxG5 https://t.co/i5Hql2ZwCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruitment Consultant – Perm – Edinburgh – Basic + uncapped commissio: Recruitment Consultant – Perm – Edinburgh – Basic + uncapped commission Have you ever thought about a career in Recruitment? Are you in Recruitment and looking for a change? Does… https://t.co/AvLwYtB1NJ https://t.co/nM1lqNK0Mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect: System Architect ================ Location: Houston, TX, US Company: ExxonMobil [IMAGE] Job Role Summary The System Architect, as part of the Capital Projects team, will work to design and develop new IT solutions to meet the business… https://t.co/mFKvAOMps8 https://t.co/ISvrQqeO0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Technical Project Manager required to join my Gloucestershire based client, specialising in the provision of Web and Cloud based hosting services, solutions and products. The Project Manager is responsible for the delivery of new… https://t.co/YU6OJ9B1TI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – About – Benefits – Culture – Featured Jobs – Information Technology – Medical Products and Services – Sales and… https://t.co/3doSrD39iN https://t.co/JoSjDzcVfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Software Developer, Bristol, £36K: C# Software Developer, Bristol, £36K The Role Our client are on the lookout for an enthusiastic graduate eager to get their foot on the ladder for a career in software development. We need a logical thinker, a born… https://t.co/7kDV8A9OTH https://t.co/oqoBlD5Bbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two killed, four wounded in shooting at Tallahassee hot yoga studio: Five people were shot, one fatally, in Tallahassee, Florida, according to Chief of Police Michael DeLeo. https://t.co/b3wsUlf6Mj https://t.co/fCsOhAcWoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – US: Role Test Analyst – US Auto req ID 37204BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Infrastructure , Country USA State / Region / Province Illinois Rhode Island Wisconsin Work Location Chicago, IL Madison, WI… https://t.co/AXXe5UXNDW https://t.co/czsnRq9hwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intermediate Network Engineer: Background HM Revenue &amp; Customs (HMRC) along with Revenue &amp; Customs Digital Technology Services (RCDTS) are embarking on an ambitious and challenging digital transformation programme which will result in HMRC becoming one… https://t.co/1JCNa6XBSs https://t.co/mS4uA5cfyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PR Manager: PR Manager London, United Kingdom Marketing SwissBorg is a Swiss fintech company headquartered in Lausanne, Vaud, Switzerland, decentralized to the world. It is the first Swiss crypto-wealth management platform based on the blockchain,… https://t.co/qp3RyEbQi5 https://t.co/5NOAhOBDjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Manager: Senior Software Development Manager (Agile) This is a senior leadership role with responsibility for leading a full Agile-based software development function using the full Microsoft stack (.Net, SQL Server).… https://t.co/vwENO35NoN https://t.co/zvFQUhIilh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk says Tesla won’t make e-scooters, but might consider electric bikes: Tesla won’t be joining the scooter wars. But electric bikes? Yeah, maybe. During a lengthy podcast with Recode’s Kara Swisher, Tesla CEO Elon Musk talked about everything from… https://t.co/CbxukthSzy https://t.co/L1BE9NHsku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guidewire Architect (Guidewire PolicyCenter): Job Title: Guidewire Architect (Guidewire PolicyCenter) Grade: Senior Director Location: London (UK) – travel will be required Practice: Insurance Salary: Competitive+Flexible Benefits+Bonus Working Pattern:… https://t.co/uDfkWFPPuQ https://t.co/qXtx38njhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen girl beheaded after rejecting someone's advances: Concerns about caste-based violence in India are growing after a 13-year-old girl from a lower caste was beheaded in one of the country's southern states last week, with her alleged assailant coming… https://t.co/ycTfEQppAI https://t.co/XPejOssASL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Financial Services (Limerick): Project Manager (Daily Rate Contract) – Financial Services / Insurance Limerick. My client is looking for an experienced Project Manager to join their team in an exciting daily rate contract role. The firm… https://t.co/vQ1ZXTFiO3 https://t.co/1X6mwDhIy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.T Systems Administrator: Yoh Solutions are working in Partnership with a Global Aerospace &amp; Defence company who are looking to recruit a Systems Administrator to work on an initial 6 month contract in either Bristol or Milton Keynes. Are client has… https://t.co/Qe74KzqGom https://t.co/Qhqq59iyxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Support Consultant, £32,000 per annum, Hertfordshire: ERP / ERP Support / Enterprise Resource Planner / SAP B1 / SAP Business One / Sage 200 / Agresso / Netsuite / Epicor / Infor / AAT / Accounting / Finance / Hertfordshire / Buckinghamshire /… https://t.co/QEw9Iw8kmk https://t.co/Ed4WhGiSQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Our Client is Currently looking for an experienced Service Desk Analyst to provide 1st/2nd line support on a permanent basis. You will Deliver first line technical support to a large user base of internal UK-based staff. Providing… https://t.co/I4DIHoQItt https://t.co/ieb7nCj1tm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Chase and Holland are partnering with a leading employee in Lincoln to recruit for a Java Developer. The role is to build software using languages and technologies of the Java and AspNetCore frameworks. You will build applications from… https://t.co/qBqD4DGWsB https://t.co/g234ucO7vW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump aide's uncle: Asylum seekers are 'like our family': The uncle of White House senior policy adviser Stephen Miller said Friday that the caravan of Central American migrants seeking asylum is just like his Jewish ancestors who fled Europe and came to… https://t.co/cLIwNq40Yt https://t.co/1SSKUqI6Th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Business Liaison Specialist: Job Title: Digital Business Liaison Specialist Location: Forbury Place, Reading Salary: £39,413 – £52,055 depending on skills and experience + benefits Permanent Full Time with flexible working patterns available The… https://t.co/CXIlFiRBa3 https://t.co/oopa8K5QkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pricing Support Analyst: Overview At Exertis, we thrive in a company culture that is driven to deliver more for customers. Our employees are committed, proactive and motivated. This dynamic environment contributes to a thriving growth‐focused culture… https://t.co/klg4nq5MBW https://t.co/fAvPZ6hjg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Sales Distribution Module Business Adviser: SunIRef:Sales:title SAP Sales &amp; Distribution Module Business Adviser – Chula Vista, CA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home… https://t.co/WsRyg756c0 https://t.co/HN0iCwO1yK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WaPo: Trump had 1,100 lies, mistruths in 7 weeks: The Washington Post reports President Trump made an average of 30 false or misleading claims in the weeks leading up to the midterm elections. https://t.co/TQ7Fou6lxA https://t.co/a1877dHKD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Software Developer: PHP Software Developer Hampshire – Farnborough £35,000 – £45,000 per annum + benefits An experienced PHP Developer is required to join a busy and growing development team located in Farnborough. You will be responsible for the… https://t.co/Fe14h8KhG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLM Agile System Architect: Job Description PLM Agile System Architect Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Position Category: Software Development Company/Location (search) : Country (Full Name): : United States… https://t.co/fFwA3K8Aaj https://t.co/vV20emlO9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zume reportedly snags $375 million from SoftBank for its robotic food operations: Zume, the robotics and logistics company that got its start slinging pizza, just raised $375 million from SoftBank, the WSJ first reported. Another firm is also looking to… https://t.co/bkt20OBUv7 https://t.co/QdkiesLxwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA / Tester: Software Quality Analyst / QA / Test Analyst Permanent Warrington Competitive salary depending on experience and rewarding benefits package * Do you have experience in functional and non-functional testing? * Are you either a manual… https://t.co/zMMyCeZwXX https://t.co/IfqCSThBIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian TV host fired for racist remarks: An Australian TV host has been fired after he described Chinese visitors to Shanghai Disneyland as "black-haired, slanty-eyed (and) yellow-skinned" live on air. https://t.co/25LyJZNcut https://t.co/y32fzdTnih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Team Lead: Senior Software Engineer (Team Lead) Reading £70,000 The organisation is a highly innovative FinTech organisation, who are going through a period of growth. They are now for a Senior Software Engineer to work as a key member of their… https://t.co/NKzNcwNWO4 https://t.co/b7F22LZ8YA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>