<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/Hcdhdkn02X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/2ptpB2p9uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/NXWIF3mszf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the confidence that makeup gives me. --&gt; Tyra Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/vbiJKPDrry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/i6PfeVXyEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/w7ll4AJ67Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/UjjquOFTE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/IgrwE4bkJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/qkWKvDTM2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/ByO28IKWJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/pePBSOC7e6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/YHD8vOnEMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/0qWjiynQ7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has George Clooney dated over the years? - theband4: http://t.co/fmdQ5mgo9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want! - GoPro! - theband4: http://t.co/cJoOdVZqSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under $100!!! WOW Fire - theband4: http://t.co/LmaRICMsUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is SpaceX? - theband4: http://t.co/lA663W9IUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplies Needed for a New Kitten - theband4: Too overwhelmed on what to buy for your new, adorable kitten?... http://t.co/PD1MjipSx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Swatch - theband4: Learn about the interesting history of this famous plastic watch.... http://t.co/y554tby8Wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Fitness Gadget Better Than a Personal Trainer? - theband4: Or the “old school” way of having personal... http://t.co/TZX6SFlGFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/OwwvfjwfXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/WhNm0tSJSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/Gjz4yThjZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/h6nJA5PtcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/mXF1Lf1ln8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/aVudytu8MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/XxkVfBIQaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/IGmJQeyQYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/iFPYHhlK6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/8eGz6LQPyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/PqAsBhRxqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/wldxNqkPUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/d1PRue7iJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/jXGjeo8mXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/UlvAwg4CGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/XbKCvOhwu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/Ue90PAZMXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/V41V6YtuEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/D9fmRi2EVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/n4n2xyWhk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/RlR3nOF36Y]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>