<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Bustillo10: When you're in the middle of taking a pic and your girl's song comes on https://t.co/WMGV0fE6wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jairamiller: Drop anyone who dismisses your feelings by saying they have it worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @byesline: Cavs up 30 in New York. The disrespect level at an all time high. https://t.co/jEk5nFOGnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NathanZed: when you on FaceTime with her and you just watching her eat but she still look cute as hell https://t.co/xNqF2e5YOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @notquay: How black movies start http://t.co/Oa24a5Ysh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyGarcia212: How you thought 2016 would go vs. how 2016 actually went https://t.co/VBhWqfoZkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @justjamiie: H&amp;M and Forever 21 need to stop making nice clothes then sticking some bull shit phrase on it like "I feel like a taco :3"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Stew2HUNT: Rain drop 
Drop top
Mariah Carey's career ended before the ball dropped

 https://t.co/U21CrBfXUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Itu_Pacify: Parents need to stop guilt trippin us.On some "I birthed,clothed &amp; fed you" Who was supposed to do all of those things?The…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dame_Lillard: Hope Rousey is fine mentally and spiritually after this fight. Most of you will never know the pressure! Yet y'all gone t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thofiqhussain I heard Ronda is on suicide watch now 😭😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thofiqhussain Ronda lost :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's go Ronda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thofiqhussain give me my mango lassi n kulfi or I'll report u to the Bangladesh authorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thofiqhussain you gotta have money if you wanna go to Dubai just sayin lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna work hard to get out of this city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @reBELLYus: I'm not slept on.. it just takes a different kind of mind to understand a vibe like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: If I ever stopped fucking with you, no love lost. I still wanna see you eat, just not with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: All that shit you do for attention is the reason you don't have mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: You gotta remember everybody wasn't raised like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @romanrochelle: When you tell your mans all the tea cause he your best friend too https://t.co/emSgRRWPdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a fuckin walkin ATM machine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all can catch these fuckin hands today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @omgAdamSaleh: We got kicked out of a @Delta airplane because I spoke Arabic to my mom on the phone and with my friend slim... WTFFFFFFF…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kervgotcurves: You'll be looking at a nice ass jacket at Forever 21 and when you turn it around and it says "MONDAYS SUCK" on the back…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 more pounds and I'm at my goal weight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want a big bowl of banh canh cua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao where you findin these girls.. Backpage, tinder or Craigslist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your neighbours are havin a rap battle.. BRUH it's fuckin cold outside. Stfu n drink hot coco by da fire place, dawg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you tell your boss you're here to make a statement and not to asks questions lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @superdeluxe: @joanneprada and @KhadiDon in Khadi &amp; Joanne https://t.co/FKDwHylHlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeekJack_: When you wake up from a 3 hour nap and have 0 messages 😓 https://t.co/6cYAhTM184]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Whether it's a friendship or a relationship, my loyalty is something you'll never have to question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: There's times I think my attitude is fucked up but then I come to a realization that people just be having me fucked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crazyrebeccavu there's a movie on Netflix called White Girl. Really good!! please watch lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FunnyVines: Candidate for weirdest laugh of all time https://t.co/CC2Ep7iL9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @queenkimbaby: Men don't ever break up with women anyways. They just gradually do less and less and they wait until the woman gets fed up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 will be the year of the savage.. I'm not gonna be nice. No more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You didn't respond so I got the message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget the people who put you thru tough times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the fuck can I buy a rocky tshirt :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @abedelrey: White people: "I don't see color, I see people. Let's stop making everything about race"
Mall of America: *Has a black Santa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your mom thinks you're a hooker cause you have several lingerie items lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't play with other people's emotions because you're unsure of your own. That's called being selfish and an asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the pants I like to wear are not fitting me anymore :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KeriHilson: Usually, a person will not understand how they made you feel until someone does it to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The accountant was the sickest movie ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does your bed get more comfy when you have to get up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OBJ_3: They got somethin to say when u win they got something to say when u lose. Regardless all that talk is irrelevant and not import…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joanneprada: I normally steal within the first 1 month of dating. I'd say give him time to develop feelings, then rob his ass blind. ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iamBrILLYant: this new month is yours. claim it. affirm beautiful blessings into it. speak love and goodness into it. make it magical a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thatmanztyy: If you get curved twice then you didn't get curved at all. Two curves make a circle which means you're at your starting po…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: This Iranian-American man broke down in tears as he spoke of his brother, who was detained at LAX and about to be deported. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ParkerKitHill: how i look when im having a casual anxiety attack https://t.co/qe8Fuc6lGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jk_rowling: He. Is. A. Terrorist. Not. A. Lone. Wolf. https://t.co/OO3qDGhzwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes gettin no response is a response]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iRap4Food: WE TRIED TO TELL Y'ALL https://t.co/dG6mCJlpZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mikel_Jollett: Which one of these two people looks like they've been in a fight? https://t.co/n29rVbms41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save save save save]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jckmdsn NO JACK! THERES ONLY 1 JANNY! I'm gonna beat you up now 😡😡😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alix_x33: When the henny start kicking in https://t.co/XOzXt6gzRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @5eean: Smuggling my dog back to college. https://t.co/R2ZvjPZfYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: You never have to tell a real nigga how to be one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: President Trump, you made a big mistake. By trying to divide us up by race, religion, gender and nationality you actually b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol girrrllll better change that body suit before you get a yeast infection hahahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bekgurk: ya really gotta watch how people joke with you. people throw shade and jealousy on the low and cover it up w a laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: If I fuck with you, I fuck with you for who you are, not for what you've got or who you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn girls really love blockin me for no apparent reason.. Scary ass hoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @basicjackz: I get "ight bro hmu when you done trippen" https://t.co/HiOXfGjtMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @odysseypeach: My uncle went to Japan and a man liked him so much he made him out of sushi https://t.co/kAvDaR9icP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KBVnnCXomI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think you know someone but your whole relationship wit them has been a lie 😊😊😊😊😊😊😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: When you're trying to get the top and your mans opens the door and fucks the whole situation up https://t.co/LdxUBr04Wy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You fuckin dirty, stupid and gross lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lily u my girl hahahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww more sad and pathetic individuals who don't like me for bein real lol join the others in line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Chibuzo: My dog refused to go on a walk with me today, look at how extra he is https://t.co/Zyfbi32Siu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone wants size 25 jeans you can have them for free lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barkmuan: My dad's been using a beatmaker app all week and I came home to this 🔥😂 https://t.co/fL6pHkhoKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Real niggas just want a beautiful, intelligent, witty girl with a low follower count who doesn't have a booking email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When lily notices your leg gainzzzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlyciaTyre: Overthinking is the killer of all happiness. Sometimes you gotta let good shit be good and stop trying to find problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey ladies, do you know any good concealers for under the eyes?? Please n thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My eyebrows look bomb af rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I'm hungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ppl get mad because you tell them to their face that you think they're fake lolololol I ain't no bihhhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the fuck do I keep losing my expensive ass lipsticks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never lose your value just to make someone else happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I give you my trust, don't abuse it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jckmdsn @Vancity OMG JACK NOOO WHAT HAPPENED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chancetherapper: One thing that she didn't do... she ain't leave when I was broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colesprouse: A #Riverdale origin story https://t.co/D1gAi5QzqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is unstoppable after she realizes she deserves better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VOULOlR: After 27 years of waiting, my dad finally received his residency approval to the United States. https://t.co/qd6OYjfdZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[girls get body enhancement surgeries and all of a sudden they are fitness gurus????? Um LOL bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @meechonmars: How It Feels When Someone Eats Your Food https://t.co/o3cnaumdRm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>