<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not too bad being me. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a world of laughter, a world of tears. It's a world of hopes, and a world of fears. –It’s A Small World]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get it if you really want, but you must try try and try. You'll succeed at last. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen with your heart, you will understand. –Grandmother Willow (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your darkness belongs to you, just the same way your light does. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t want him in my heart. I want him here with me. –Victor (Frankenweenie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what happens to me, I'll always be with you forever. –John Smith (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice: “This is impossible.” | The Mad Hatter: “Only if you believe it is.” –Alice in Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I really don’t belong here, like I’m supposed to be some place else. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your organization on this weekend pickup some #Rubbermaid All Access storage containers! http://t.co/fn4iyKnrpo #ad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be so nice if something would make sense for a change. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing can go wrong if everything is right, and everything is right somehow. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the problem with doing the right thing. Sometimes you do it on your own. –Genie (The Return of Jafar)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong. Never give up. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To laugh yourself is to love yourself. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you read 'The Great Gatsby' and you want to see the movie&gt;&gt; http://t.co/GyrucDgmsc #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close your eyes and pretend it’s all a bad dream. That’s how I get by. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn’t a dream at all. It was a memory. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile, and get it over with. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not fear death, but rather the unlived life. You don't have to live forever. You just have to live. –Tuck (Tuck Everlasting)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying won’t help. –Doorknob (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about me. Go and enjoy yourself. I'll stay here and be miserable. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilo: “Stitch, are you okay?” | Stitch: “I'm okay. I'm fluffy.” –Lilo &amp; Stitch Series]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a damsel. I'm in distress. I can handle this. Have a nice day. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends will stick with you until you’re unstuck. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends are more important than anything else. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SimplyRight COMPLETE Instant Formula provides complete nutrition like the national brands but costs half as much #ad http://t.co/exQapwgcXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your mind is open and your heart just has to know, your wings can take you farther than you ever thought you'd go. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#prayforboston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think, believe, dream, and dare. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to do. Nothing to do. What a happy thought. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest part is what to leave behind. It's time to let go. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be in my heart, no matter what they say. You'll be here in my heart, always. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends can be new, friends can be old. All of them are as precious as gold. –Roo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hakuna Matata. It's something I learned out here. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in the future. The world is getting better. There still is plenty of opportunity. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to stay close to you, no matter what, because I love you. –Naveen (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/m8gAENjNmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s about staying focused on your goals. –Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just a part of growing up. A little adventure, a little rebellion, that's good. Healthy, even. –Flynn Rider (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you leave, I just, I remember things better with you. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think you know Disneyland? Checkout these secrets I bet you didn't know: http://t.co/nx3Aj2HZAL #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sure I’ll get along somehow. Everything’s going to be alright. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do we have to grow up?  I know more adults who have the child's approach to live. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I'm supposed to be looking for someone, but I just can't remember. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gone, but then I'm not gone. So if I do leave, you can never be sure that I am gone, can you? –Merlin (Sword in the Stone)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't never let anything happen to him. Then, nothing would ever happen to him. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wish and you dream with all your little heart. –James (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One look at your smile, and I could see the light shining everywhere. –Jasmine (The King of Thieves)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love someone so much and then to lose them so suddenly, I can't imagine how awful that must be. –Sara (Haunted Mansion)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s okay to be afraid. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You aren't just some prize to be won. You should be free to make your own choice. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody wants to live happily ever after. Everybody wants to know their true love is true. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something feels funny, I must be thinking too hard. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admit it. Whenever you see a clown fish, you automatically think “It’s Nemo!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy, someday I will meet my Prince Charming, but you will always be my King.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is the comfiest place to be. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in loyalty and trust. I believe loyalty is built on trust. –Disney Princess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do love her, shouldn't you tell her? –Koda (Brother Bear 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't just run away from who we are. –Elinor (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing to do isn’t the easiest thing to know. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you think these Disney Couples are the cutest: http://t.co/WS9VryrFhd - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a damsel. I'm in distress. I can handle this. Have a nice day. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megara: “He would never do anything to hurt me.” | Hades: “He's a guy.” –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You try. You fail. You try. You fail. But the only true failure is when you stop trying. –Madame Leota (Haunted Mansion)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream. All you have to do is think about it, work on it every day, and you'll get it. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How lucky I am to have something that makes saying goodbye so hard. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know the Boston Bomber has a Twitter? Check out his tweets: http://t.co/OdznD7qLWv - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve just met you and I love you. –Dug (Up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re mad, bonkers, off your head. But I tell you a secret. All the best people are. –Charles (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your eyes and soar above the blue, take a breath, and believe you can do anything. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you never knew of these Disney Myths: http://t.co/Tcbz4QlSlo - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mother is someone who loves and cares for you and tells you stories. –Wendy (Peter Pan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have forgotten who you are, and so have forgotten me. –Mufasa (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being normal is vastly overrated. –Aggie (Halloweentown)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toy Story 4? Finding Dory? Monster Inc 2? Here's the list of next Disney movies until 2014: http://t.co/tni2FGiRbk - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t let the most important person in your world slip away. –Gary (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/FQYHpxWcr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little friend, don't be too sad, because miracles never really die. –Make Mine Music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you want a Disney Wedding like this: http://t.co/HCqQRAycIu #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/OqDmxok4F6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you believe in a thing, believe in it all the way, implicitly and unquestionable. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they’d look closer, they’d find out there’s so much more to me. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're my ohana, and I'll always love you. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s someone for everyone. –Laverne (Hunchback of Notre Dame II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotso: “There’s a hundred million just like her.” | Ken: “Not to me, there’s not.” –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want someone to love me, for me. –Anastasia (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my dream. I'll decide where it goes from here. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t help myself. I like good food, ok? –Remy (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, teamwork isn't about ego. It's about "we go". –Mushu (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew it. Why did you lie to me? Did you think I was stupid that I wouldn't figure it out? –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you turn your back on me, don't you walk away, don't you tell me that I don't care cause I do. –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen, and you can't do anything about it. –Timon (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really can't judge things by the way they look. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to fit in. I really do. I just can’t. Sometimes I feel like I really don’t belong here. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever wished for something so much you could feel it in your heart? –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not crazy. My reality is just different than yours. –Cheshire Cat (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second star to the right shines with a light that's rare, and if it's Neverland you need, its light will lead you there. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I do marry, I want it to be for love. –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tutor for Good is a cool website that provides free online tutoring for students. We've checked it out. Have you? https://t.co/ySl0IVL967]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>