<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Red, white, blue's in the sky. Summer's in the air and baby, heaven's in your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your imagination is your greatest tool to success." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I had a chameleon soul. No moral compass pointing due north, no fixed personality." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RESIST MUCH. OBEY LITTLE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous! RT @ashajaay: @LanaQuote http://t.co/w1l4yoLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can only have true hate, if you have true love." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's amazing what happens when you put your interests out into the universe and make it known what you want ." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world I've created on the outside is finally as beautiful as it was in my mind's eye when I first began writing &amp; dreaming." —LanaDRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for @LanaDelRey at the 2012 MTV EMA's for 'Best New Artist' 'Best Alternative' &amp; 'Best Push Artist'. VOTE HERE: http://t.co/3vLt6QYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was in the winter of my life, and the men I met along the road were my only summer." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If nobody love you, I love you. If nobody wants you, I want you. I'm your dark Queen." http://t.co/UdLgrO4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes I wish I was a beautiful machine so I could resist your kiss &amp; not cry when you're mean." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We had nothing to lose, nothing to gain, nothing we desired anymore - except to make our lives into a work of art." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was born to be the other woman. I belonged to no one - who belonged to everyone, who had nothing - who wanted everything." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my bad baby by my heavenly side. I know if I go, I'll die happy tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haters: Lana's voice is terrible! | Me: Well... http://t.co/1ocXnXnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want him back, but I'm flat outta luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was always an unusual girl, my mother told me I had a chameleon soul." —Lana Del Rey http://t.co/CmI5Fbs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♥ RT @LanaDReyOnline: Lana Del Rey | Ride | By Chuck Grant http://t.co/h2hVFuZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love you. Thank you for letting me tell you my story x" —Lana Del Rey's comment on Ride Music Video. She adores us! http://t.co/EZ7N6GSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Of the Year! @LanaDelRey "RIDE" http://t.co/K6eiqiGX — http://t.co/lPtSLdpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you in touch with all of your darkest fantasies? Have you created a life for yourself where you're free to experience them? I have. —LDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You only live twice or so it seems. One life for yourself and one for your dreams." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fucking crazy. But I am free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You make me crazy, you make me wild. Just like a baby, spin me 'round like a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was a singer, not a very popular one, who once had dreams of becoming a beautiful poet." —Lana Del Rey http://t.co/yP9MXlIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of Masterpiece: #RideMusicVideo @LanaDelRey http://t.co/jPOggbye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey's new music video "Ride" is GORGEOUS. Watch it now! #TeamLana : http://t.co/0ZnWMaWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride Music Video: http://t.co/VsV4XJNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the day. Ride Music Video will premiere on VEVO! - http://t.co/jrOWE1sC ( via : @LanaDReyOnline )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE FAST. DIE YOUNG. BE WILD. AND HAVE FUN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is that you express in your eyes? It seems to me more than all the print I have read in my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby put on heart shaped sunglasses, cause we gonna take a ride. http://t.co/qmjWCVhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride Music Video will be released tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And my motto is the same as ever- I believe in the kindness of strangers. And when I'm at war with myself, I Ride. I just Ride." —LanaDRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life isn't always easy, but sometimes you're blessed enough to meet your artistic soul mates along the way." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS! RT @DelReyLane: A fan asked Lana Del Rey to collaborate with Lady Gaga and she responded, "I love Gaga, maybe sooner than you think."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride Video Premiere now at the Aero Theater in Santa Monica, CA and I think it will be released soon on youtube. KEEP CALM AND RIDE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIDE VIDEO PREMIERE. NOW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CountdownRide #CantWaitForRide We're so excited! @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried so hard to act nice like a lady. You taught me that it was good to be crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's nice to be able to try and build the life you want for yourself." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you excited for @LanaDelRey's 'Ride Video Premiere' but you can't watch it in Santa Monica.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything was beautiful. Nothing Hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so sorry #TeamLana, my last tweet isn't Lana Del Rey's quote. That's Marylin Monroe. Forgive me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Imperfection is beauty, madness is genius. And it's better to be absolutely ridiculous than absolutely boring." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RideMusicVideoLaunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my idea of fun, playing video games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should trend something about @LanaDelRey 's new music video "Ride" #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you picture it, babe, the life we could've lived?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She prays the rosary for my broken mind. I sing the body electric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Sleeping Beauty ♥ #Retweet http://t.co/SQKAfodC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like to write about the way things used to be and paint pictures of my memories with beautiful words and melodies." —Lana in @HM Magazine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffingtonPost: Doesn't Lady Gaga look like Lana Del Rey? It's the hair ... http://t.co/sv8x4hRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for @LanaDelRey at the 2012 EMAs for Best Alternative Artist, Best Push &amp; Best New Artist : http://t.co/3vLt6QYX — http://t.co/0HLs5Rim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think she cares about the art that she is creating. I don't think that is fake at all." —Noah Levy on Lana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you adore this Queen ♥ http://t.co/Qu9ctETT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be bad and have fun. Trust no one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby, if you like me you'll call me a bunny. Tell me I'm just a baby honey. Meet me and tell me no one will love me, better than you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["LanaDelRey, she's got some fantastic charisma and this is a very interesting thing, it's like she's born out of another time." —David Lynch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So in the end, what I want is to have someone to help me feel delicate and sexy again." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN'T WAIT!! RT @loveLDR: 35 DAYS, 9 HOURS, 56 MINUTES AND 18 SECONDS UNTIL THE RELEASE OF THE PARADISE EDITION!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't get another chance, life is no Nintendo Game." —Eminem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm feelin' electric tonight ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing magic makes us free, to be what we wanna be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of fighting you, seems like everything I do. Even when I win, I lose wit' you, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I always felt like life was a beautiful sad song." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_PaulMLP: BLUE JEANS. ♥  @LanaQuote http://t.co/yeklVKQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for Ride and Favorite for Blue Velvet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got the world. But baby, at what price? Something so strange, hard to define.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliviaCareyx RT @LanaDReyOnline: Lana Del Rey will reveal tour dates very soon! http://t.co/iGhnFfh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wanna get high with me, I'm in the back doing crack drinkin' pepsi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lana is an amazing woman. She has a beautiful soul and she's so much fun to be around." — @Defff666 on Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES, I WILL! ♥ @LanaDelRey http://t.co/PzldzlW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard that you like the bad girls, honey, is that true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I make you feel like Chrismas time? Put me in a party dress one time. Love me till I see the sunshine, say you'll never leave me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you're excited for @LanaDelRey's world tour. #BornToDieTour will Slay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you're excited for @LanaDelRey's new album! #BornToDieParadiseEdition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't do controversy in my personal life. If it comes, I deal with it peacefully." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're the children of the bad revolution, and partying is the only solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood's dead, Elvis is crying, Lennon wake up, Cobain stop lying there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't know if I deserve a good man, but I think about it - sometimes." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want my record to sound famous, like a sad party." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving you forever, can't be wrong. Even though you're not here won't move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born so bad, young, and truly right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just look for someone who makes me feel like life is an exciting opportunity." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My music is a luxury." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's becomes an art again, when people tell you they hate your music because it's between you and yourself again." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love you more, than those bitches before. Say you'll remember, oh baby. I will love you 'till the end of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BornToDieTour  @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got so scared, I felt no one could save me. You came along, scooped me up like a baby :')]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that's real to me, is Halloween and Jesus. Coney Island beaches, chandeliers and seizures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For me, I didn't want anything except to feel new everyday." —Lana Del Rey #WeLoveYouLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeLoveYouLana @LanaDelRey You're the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TEAMLANA IS THE BEST!!RT @SyrineOsbourne: @LanaQuote We did it ! #WeLoveYouLana ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeLoveYouLana TRENDING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeLoveYouLana ♥ http://t.co/zfKJfFaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeLoveYouLana till the end of time. RT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a totally different life experience when you have to learn to love the things that don't love you back." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I listen to a little @MarinasDiamonds, She has a song called 'Teen Idle' that I really like." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>