<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess you can't blame that on the rich people who don't join them. Come hang out on Twitter with the rest of us goons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which sound ... celebratory rather than manipulative?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to be a Fraud Scene Investigator?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For instance, never do a corporate parody video is good CEOing advice, and I will stand by it until I die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I learned on this Longform podcast with Carol Loomis is that she might have invented the term "hedge fund."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man. A fun fact is that the English language actually has a word to express the concept of "right, but in the opposite direction."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People lack direction. People are uncertain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe an evil lobbyist will convince you to leave a good one off the list, or put a bad one on, knowing that no one will really notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't want your audience reading your slides; the slides should be visual aids with at most a few bullet points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That reputation is deserved, by the way; his targets are down an average of 11 percent in the first week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does seem like a stretch, but Oystacher has been quoted saying "If we click quicker than most, it is a skill," so who knows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd imagine that Bank of New York would not want to stand for re-election at that point, though. It's been through a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Wall Street regulation, no matter how tough, will be good for some elements of "Wall Street."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This is not particularly true of mutual funds.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a little skeptical about a prior version of the survey, but I guess the main question is the control group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And some Republicans don't like big banks, which could be a problem for big banks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except on the breadsticks: At least in New York, Olive Garden is adhering to its old policy of N+1 breadsticks for a table of N.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the whole thing is very much worth reading, a defense of nuance against snap black-and-white moral judgments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nirkaissar Did the Bank of England participate in currency market manipulation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you make up a high number. But ISDAfix is good old-fashioned manipulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We still don't talk about his gold fund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand basically all stock markets are closed most of the time, which is a bit weird for market efficiency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kind of don't get why they had to to this? The covenant was, like, "you need to have at least 100 people living at the center."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google 
pays its executive chairman
 well. What would happen if everyone was paid what Gawker writers thought they deserved?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And what's Charlie Shrem up to in prison?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gross's personal financial advisers works." Now, there are of course several possible explanations of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forward exchange rates have important theoretical implications for forecasting future spot exchange rates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappearing primary dealers! Record bond allocations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But here is Felix Salmon on "Why staying private sucks, if you're a tech company."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the Justice Department wants to pay them more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At times, they manually changed the price to a value that they preferred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone gets a chance to try to talk the Justice Department out of filing charges against them, though to be fair banks usually do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get what you pay for, so I that seems like a positive sign for those who want banks to be lower-risk and more client-servicey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can find the people who generate alpha, and convince them to give you some of it, then that's great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he's submitted a nonbinding proposal for JPMorgan to study that possibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One assumes that unicorns do not drive pickup trucks, or deck them out with TruXedos. You could tell a few stories: I don't know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, this is a rare example where I prefer the extremists to the moderates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the one hand, he wonders, "Were some investors aware of the decision before others?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, a bot read a tweet and made a lot of money trading Altera call options. ("I personally lost $100,000 in one second.")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High fives all around, good boiler-rooming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like with just a few small tweaks the story of Martin Shkreli could be a very satisfying financial thriller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But there's something else going on here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the financial crisis, there was another reason for the government to want to zero the shareholders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I assume the "legal protections" that Shkreli negotiated are supposed to prevent that, but maybe they could release a close substitute?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Carl Icahn, among others, gets a pass here, since he's basically playing with his own money.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fed meeting begins today, and tomorrow it announces its decision on whether to raise interest rates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These hackers and traders are charged with reaping more than $100 million in illicit profits," says the SEC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, that's all financial supervision and regulation, not just AML.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's paragraph 267. See paragraphs 243 to 245 of Madsen's complaint for his story of worrying about being fired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Janet Yellen is more polite than I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere: "Third Avenue Portends Regulators' Fears and Could Spur New Rules."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under current law, if Icahn told you, "I'm about to buy Apple and you should too," you probably could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ProPublica's Carmen Segarra article is worth another look today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Here is Bob Benmosche having a lot of fun indeed; here is a greatest-hits roundup.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are also enforcers who perhaps go too far in viewing finance as the enemy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you get around the leveraged loan regulations with holdco PIK bonds? Intuitively the answer should be yes, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who made money selling bonds to the Fed during QE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here you can look at some 
early hedge fund ads
. But probably don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's ... that's not a great sales pitch to whoever is buying the core business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me yesterday. I wrote about Yahoo's potential sale of its core business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should you issue bonds in euros, or dollars, or francs, or what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd want to deliver the cheapest possible bonds into the auction, to maximize your CDS recovery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want extreme financial advice, provided over the internet, financial adviser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can be like, "that's not a scam, that sounds great!," in which case you have a bright future in clichés about used-car salesmen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except that here JPMorgan, one of the three bookrunners leading the underwriting of the deal, was also a Series E investor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazingly Bitcoin isn't mentioned until the last paragraph.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The data sources are real time and the markets are real time, so the HFT firms' decisions and price changes also occur in real time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“But the government needs to be careful that it doesn’t turn a guilty plea into a D.P.A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can follow smart people who care about that sort of thing, or at least journalists, and read their tweets about the prize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, here are Nicolas Veron and Gavyn Davies on the European stress tests. And even in the Treasury market, liquidity is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“And it’s possible to pay a lot in options and not have a product recall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was Barclays thinking with its dark pool advertising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said the phenomenon has been part of a general “frothiness” in late-stage valuations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, at the end of the summer, he's going to kill them. This will teach the goats about Bank of America settlements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently Blythe Masters wanted to go with JPMorgan's physical commodities business as chief executive officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes the entire finance industry more fragile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Big Short does a great job of showing how each of these actors’ poor decisions amplify the damage the others could cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "It's like the Death Star but for your lunch."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the buildings in this version are gray, but I guess you could color-code for sectors, though which would get red?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a company goes bankrupt and owes you money, you will probably want your money back as soon as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prominent financial company holds shareholder meeting in out-of-the-way place. No, not Citi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Wall Street regulation, no matter how tough, will be good for some elements of "Wall Street."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“They used the term ‘Ponzi,’ or ‘Ponzi-like,’ which is nowhere near reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important charts in the world."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honest, we didn't make these up," says Fortune, but I feel like I made up "quinquagintacorn"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should have a recurring "I am worried about Twitter" section. I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, I am not confident that reducing inequality solely by disproportionately evaporating the wealth of the top decile is a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The statute of limitations for bringing securities fraud cases is five years. Do you see the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am of course sympathetic, though actually existing attempts to codify insider trading are sort of underwhelming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The way to think of the inversion of the swap spreads is not a mathematical break-down, but rather a spike in the term premium."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's interest rates all the way through. I am worried about him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The index funds have the advantage of free-riding, but the disadvantage of being predictable. Stocks should go up when they join an index.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then Morgan Stanley wealth management president Greg Fleming agreed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also enjoyed the part about how these kids want to be "The Wolf of Wall Street," but understand that you're not supposed to say that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We talked last week about the value proposition that sell-side research offers to its customers, and this is a big part of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also this stops somewhere short of saying that the indictment is wrong: “The indictment itself is lacking rigor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But as we’ve said before, the Fourteenth Amendment does not give the President the power to ignore the debt ceiling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this one of those cases where the media simply doesn't appreciate the realities of the industry that it covers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The French finance minister is bullish that BNP Paribas is in line only for "more equitable sanctions" for violating U.S., um, sanctions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Businessweek article has a good swirly graphic of the death spiral that captures this dynamic, and I commend it to you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>