<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin Reckon the circumstances of the equaliser probably shades that one alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin What a fucking game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry in motion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooalMouth If you're basing it purely on what he achieved in Europe, Lampard achieved as much yet I wouldn't have him in that conversation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooalMouth Alonso clearly the better player. And I'd argue that Zidane - a top 10 player of all time - should be in that team. Or Modric or a genuinely world class midfielder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooalMouth Or the best midfielder in that Liverpool team either being honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooalMouth He shouldn't be anywhere near a European team of the decade/century. Not even the best English midfielder of his generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerStash UEFA's team of the century so far. In bits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerrard hahahahahaha https://t.co/uI1xIp8fCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDiss An inspiration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature This]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWrafter Just the constant need to appear virtuous and shutting down debate with people I respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl Just incessant flip flopping so he can appear virtuous. It's relentless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still not entirely sure why it took me this long to unfollow Owen Jones. Rectified now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word https://t.co/r5SatgndRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilbronikowski Hahaha that sounds great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephenmaaaaac I've became a light weight a couple of years ago and stopped taking sugar in hot drinks. Gradually drinking less tea due to coffee consumption as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilbronikowski War Games is an old wrestling match in fairness haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, War Games was absolutely nuts. Buzzing for Survivor Series. The graps is great right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephenmaaaaac Thought you exclusively drank coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyCowanIRL Considering one of my mates is admin, I probably should've known this was a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Simpsons Fans closing down its Facebook page. End of an era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFinal_Third: 🔥COMPETITION🔥

Thanks to @Con_Artistes we have two tickets to give away to their live event featuring @jonawils and @em…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Usos vs the Bar surely motn ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steviegrieve No one will be CM Punk, with respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pep Guardiola after Manchester City keep a clean-sheet with Fabian Delph, Mangala and a half fit Kompany in their defence https://t.co/1lxWzF15VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon City will have the league wrapped up in March]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Roma get a big cut of Mo Salah's sell on fee to compensate for the heist Liverpool have performed in getting him for under 50 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidpreece12 If Phil Jones needed injections to play for England, obviously means he was playing through injury for United as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically a mini-episode of People Just Do Nothing. Big ups @NoiseyMusic https://t.co/qPYJOyJguE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastPeldroed We've already got our own former-Manchester United legend waiting to fuck everything up as our manager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastPeldroed ABBG (Anybody but Giggs)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Sunderland need a revolution, Coleman can definitely do better and Wales will probably hire a Pulis type. All she wrote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a terrible move for all concerned https://t.co/cF5ooRff6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*gets popcorn* https://t.co/5XLrWWfOuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @j0hnardy: is there anything Kanye can't do? https://t.co/5wS5jYWtM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MundialMag Pretty sure that happened on this day as well, as I got a notification of an old Facebook status in which I was pissing myself laughing at this at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priya8Ramesh @wolfalicemusic Quality live band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/1HHLi82mxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bon8ghties @BetBright Thanks for your valuable output today. But I don't feel the need to place trust in a mythical being. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Well, this is true. She's some form of physical manifestation of the devil anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Or maybe she's just a cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TifoFootball_: NEW: Italian football is in far healthier shape than it was after conquering the world in 2006, but @ConorPacKelly expla…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies @F365 should be sent to every Mourinho presser just to correct all the inaccuracies he spews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Lol. Best part is I doubt anyone pulled him up in his presser on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priya8Ramesh At FC Hollywood no less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For @BetBright, I took a look at Italy's failure to qualify for the World Cup and pointed fingers https://t.co/obj67fe5DV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning https://t.co/8G6YfRrQug Just read your piece and then followed it up with this and come to the conclusion that you're being *just a bit* overly simplistic to suggest City are a one player team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BetBright: New - @ConorPacKelly Believes Italy’s Failure Is In The Hands of Those In Charge...

https://t.co/TdqG2eSoyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebSB @BenMcAleer1 @stighefootball MADRIOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning Ancelotti obviously left him the number of his finest Italian tailor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xabi Alonso already looks like a manager https://t.co/YhWoBOVY7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to @whitesfan &amp; myself talk about how we prefer club football anyway. Plus, @JamesHorncastle on Italy's World Cup failure https://t.co/Tesq5NlBPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheFinal_Third: INSTANT REACTION: The lads give their thoughts on a dire night for Irish football. 

🔊 https://t.co/ZW5QSDn2XR https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_Flynn4 Well, very occasionally I take a break from talking shite tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Bizarre and pretty hard to fathom what he was thinking. It was a 90s Premier League substitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robbie Brady seems to have the Cristiano Ronaldo illusion in which people think he's good at freekicks based off a few screamers over the years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving Bendtner the peno to score the fifth is actually great banter tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRyanMOT Where did I say we shouldn't have brought on Wes? And you do realise to create chances we need the ball, and to get the we need some structure in midfield? 10 year-olds on FIFA make smarter substitutions tactically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 Not even being intentionally prickly. I just honestly don't think O'Neill works on any of those details haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Ward reverting to his pre-2017 form]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 Or even devise a plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 It would help if, yaknow, the coach devised a plan which didn't involve simply vacating the space in the middle and allowing Eriksen all the time in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Neill removes two of our central midfielders and Christian Eriksen - Denmark's best player who plays centrally - gets acres of space to do as he pleases. Imagine that 🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiejowe Trying to figure out what O'Neill thinks or does in general is difficult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Neill must literally be the only person on the planet who still thinks McGeady should be involved in this team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balls. Outrageous finish in fairness, but what the fuck was Ward doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck. That was coming tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie is all over the fucking shop here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck, it's too early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yaaaassssss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nerves shredded #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz Hahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gian Piero Ventura: The Italian Steve McClaren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, how the fuck did it take Ventura this long to realise what everyone else did and play his best midfielder Jorginho?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIFA still haven't sold their World Cup tv rights in Italy: Italy avail of some 'favourable' refereeing decisions. I'm very cynical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darren__holland Toronto g. Yeah, LCD and Gorillaz playing on my doorstep is a kick in the nads too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darren__holland I'm exactly the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priya8Ramesh Don't ever come to Ireland so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nature Boy wearing classic gazelles is my favourite picture of the day https://t.co/MhW8ZxXXpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin Feel your pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tottenhamarmy01 Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munnelly_ryan Just let Kanye be Kanye, that's what I've always felt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0-0. Take that #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing ovation for Lord Bendtner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl Fucking right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bar in Dublin full of Danish lads. Massive cheer when Bendtner came up on screen. He really is a lord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early observation: it's great seeing Denmark wearing a Hummel kit, as they should]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys @RichieSadlier was right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More attacking team than expected, think MON sees the importance of the away leg. Plus, no Whelan is always a bonus. #COYBIG https://t.co/6J2BqJ81tT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Boredom I'm guessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Just said this to my Dad. Darkest SA kit I can remember and a weird Irish one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJDeece Madlib and Freddie Gibbs did well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rise911 Popularity doesn't necessarily mean it's bad. I generally categorise music as good or bad regardless of popularity. AC/DC are just one of those bands I don't get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX Nah, I like Zeppelin. Every AC/DC song sounds the same to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AC/DC https://t.co/DKa1aKXSyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youngmallgrab @ShineBelfast Can't wait man! Hopefully get to say hi to you after :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @m_brosnan: After hearing a lot of people debate this, piece on national identity and the residency rule. https://t.co/UeyQQbn2tr https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once every so often, I flake in a darkened room and get lost in a transient state listening to DJ Koze https://t.co/GkAseh3gwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Well played]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>