<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jake4TO @mirtle I was gonna claim Cole as well. Keep it up JM its subtle good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 like this that guy DGM. "Didn't Get the Memo" or do you go DGTM. Asking for a hashtag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 I have a real problem. I am undecided on what to do with articles when developing a cool acronym. Convention says drop them. I disagree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a real problem. I am undecided on what to do with articles when developing a cool acronym. Convention says drop them. I disagree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmonssteve @HayesTSN @TSNDaveHodge @garylawless @TSNDaveNaylor  Hayes killing it on the reporters this AM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne and 2 Jackie Wilson's original. Smooth but not the same Soul as Otis http://t.co/km6dFKKvkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne 1 half of a great Under the Covers piece from this mornings #cbc2 morning this just cracks. http://t.co/sZXCidNSgR
Jackie Wilson NXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @heylandsberg: I heard from a friend who says hearing 2 guys talking on TV about their depression saved his life. Fact: Sharing saves li…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: I want my videos and my weather reports to be featured on CNN and FOX World News since i am real good at my youtube videos…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: I always ignore negative comments and rude comments and I ignore false doomsday predictors trying to predict end of the wo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more heartwarming and life assuring than this http://t.co/uCpvHVY4uq @frankiemacd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: One of my fans edited the picture myself and I like that and it is done by my fans. http://t.co/aUPijMjjAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: i am getting a ton of fan pictures of myself now. http://t.co/3WnnTfo3Qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArashMadani No!  The rush to prediction dilutes reporting. Can King James carry this adversity to the championship is the story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rumble And Sway by Jamie N Commons, found with @Shazam. Listen now:y http://t.co/dlW9Nmr5vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFarber3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelFarber3: Nice work by GM Marc Bergevin in signing Petry, a nice fit from the start. PK and Petry, two pretty good right-shot D-m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many know the difference between being righteous and self-righteous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: Man. @WillieGeist: Statement from @VP Biden on the death of his son Beau. http://t.co/jSrLDGtOHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@13inklings meanwhile maybe they were onto something. 3-0 is a but if a Buzzkill to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda hypnotic  MashUp of Florence and the Machine and Taylor Swift https://t.co/KEwXIlnZuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[exciting game 7 and #CBC / #Sportsnet #coachescorner is talking about anything but. Buzzkill. I'm watching #NBCSportsChannel DOC Emirick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give them Light Sabres and fight it out. GRRROLF http://t.co/tT4CSExduQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #trivagoguy was likeable in a way. The #intactguy is a pretentious moron. Pull those commercials http://t.co/CYdiW0TvYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill Damaged!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__mshill http://t.co/SyXwdsGyGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill http://t.co/HHkSp0G2y1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle never tell the opponent what it was you saw. Zip It and get ready for the next game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jamesonratchford's photo https://t.co/pUez2DJ8xz Return leg of  ROADTRIP2015   5500K and 1 Awesome Daughter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jamesonratchford's photo https://t.co/pUez2DJ8xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill https://t.co/1iZIg3SxQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_msHill Quackmire is How the fuck can I become This Duck. http://t.co/d7gcGieN6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill and one big fucking Quagmire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill and I have 1 concern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill Perfect I have an hundred ?'s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill U doing an AMA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLozo What are you having for dinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamieRatchford: Just loving life http://t.co/iZdrkJhYWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford Uhmmm. I'm right over here  and I can hear you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamieRatchford: Goal of this trip is to let my dad talk about as much dumb boring stuff as he wants without getting frustrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a 1 Day hiatus in Stanley Cup drama I suggest you follow this. If a bracket is possible a bracket there will be https://t.co/B47jfNUqMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Oliver: You can't say you love moms then reject paid leave policies that support them http://t.co/K3GSAk52Ts via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future Islands: "The Chase" - David Letterman https://t.co/yXropIBqMw via @YouTube Trying too figure out why I like this band so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commlabs @saulmacneil or I may have to make some up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@commlabs @saulmacneil Can't we at least get a best of  #peggyquotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFTompkins @colbycosh often. More often than not. Zenith Chromacolor II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weathernetwork in a red dress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: Florida Man has a family?: Florida parents accused of bribing daughters w cocaine, pot to get them to complete chores http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briannemett @GraphicMatt She wanted them in Orange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postedtoronto Nope. That honour goes to Captain John's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DWHauthor: The Duffy trial will last so long it will comprise a distinct society, seek nationhood, and settle for a Senate seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kady everyone laughs at them but it's all about the base. They need a new song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationalpost Happens a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reporterdonpeat onward to the Perpetual Re-Election Campaign otherwise known as the easy Re-Cumbantcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Playing_Dad: If Toby Keith sees his shadow on the 4th of July, we get 6 more weeks of freedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald And the mail comes at four and the mailman's old but he still dreams his dreams of silver and gold. Sonny's Dream Ron Hhynes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: So ignore the negative and bad guys especially they trick me online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IntegrativeGolf: Bill Coore &amp; Ben Crenshaw inspect hole 17 tee ball #CabotCliffs #Epic #preview @MattGinellaGC @KeithRhebb @cabotlinks …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReaIWilIFerreII c'mon you so know that answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ginohard_: RT to ruin a Bruins fan's day. http://t.co/XKSpWhDPGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 They are rapidly approaching " non streaky" status. And the 1 run holds/wins are what creates that confidence in them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Wilnerness590: If memory serves, #Bluejays were 3-12 in one-run games earlier this year. Which would mean #Jays have won 6 of last 9 on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueAnnLevy and if your info is true on press access. Freedom of press. I support pride wholeheartedly. Where would pride  be without it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CityTOjobs: Looking for a place to read outside? Take a look at @torontolibrary outdoor reading gardens: http://t.co/NMWuDdmuwE http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DKingBH so much respect for those Builders. Torrey, Bowman, Pollack, yep even Sather. Don't know about Punch but what the hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankiemacd: I am the worldwide celebrity now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justin_Ling @acoyne what about being like "a bit coyne" ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heylandsberg you are a strong voice. Keep talking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @heylandsberg: It's always amazing to me how deep depression changes how we see ourselves, how we see the world and how the world sees u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterjkostis: Just finished 36 fantastic holes of golf at Cabot Links &amp; Cliffs! Coore/Crenshaw have designed the best new course I've s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterjkostis: The Links course is fantastic but the Cliffs is spectacular! It's a perfect blend of fun,pretty,challenging and great str…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterjkostis: I'm so down on courses that beat you up and call themselves great. Cabot is fun and the staff is great! This is the way g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJohnsonPGA just hit a 5 iron 245 yards!! That's what keeps us coming back #USOpen2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankiemacd Thanks for the updates Frankie.  @carlamwhite @jamierat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cloud. Ever watchful on our fair city http://t.co/7jFDmFKT17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHLhistorygirl  5th Overall. And folks get so bent about being anything less than 3rd in the order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lizzie_McD: @FanSince09 It's not the logo that people find offensive.
It's the Redskins name. Many sports teams have Native American lo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FanSince09 not the same. U know that. Think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace @KathyBuckworth @HughWallace @sleepdoula ? Do penguins Toot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyBuckworth @greenwooddavis yes. I have a great number of Professional Designations. But I am a humble man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenwooddavis @KathyBuckworth ha! Yes. Personal cultural tour guide and interpreter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyBuckworth @greenwooddavis Absolutely. You both have the Be Friendly Wonderful People Lesson aced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have a Tin Ear but it's laced with Gold. @terralightfoot is the newest incarnation of great Canadian music http://t.co/7vlq1AFwSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford Hmmmmm. I think that's what I said to me when i was discussing you with me the other day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC Again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin @RDiManno two journalists with no proof or columnists with no substance? Say it! Don't use weasel words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin say it or don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy People. He obviously thought that MP stood for Mug Peeer. #peegate Bullies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurkieNHL @AmyKNelson in the words of Harry Callahan " Nobody. I mean nobody puts ketchup on a Hotdog" https://t.co/m5R7KAeAmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurfAD @SimonDingleyCBC C'MON that only happens in the movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have more than an inkling that @justinbieber and @geniebouchard are the same person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur @bnicholsonsmith @Sportsnet That is an Athlete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for September. This is what it's like in a pennant race. Live and die with every pitch #BlueJays And that's the fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. Defence has Ben and will be fine. The charge ball, I want him being that aggressive all day. Tonight was a bad bounce. Glove was set]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford #smilesallaround™ ➿©®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKentMurphy @JamieRatchford hah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealKentMurphy: ESPN couldn't understand this kid when he said One Direction 😂😂  http://t.co/vsuKBG9ZSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She could have shared and made at least 26 Instant travelling friends.  https://t.co/81eP4hYLg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford Ha! Is that the Minions one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JesseBarfield29: I'm looking forward to being with my outfield partners and sharing our bubblehead trio together this is a great honor …]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>