<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/OLZk6UKAhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/IGrSHzcJbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/gcmBxhw2Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/XNGNLPF0vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/aCDS8cks4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/wmmlfkeZdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/12BYkredgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/gjSPU5DMd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/EzvP7pDPsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/wmmlfkeZdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/XYyZGJ1OBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/gvlaU5dmhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/vPZJkMfZ5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/VPaBaROg0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/7oSwRmOvCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/IRvC7S7pKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/A6f4FI1Vyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/aQLYN9bzDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/ORlBOlzAoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/EWLqlAo5mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/1f9oG5jwc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/Iw8D4Td9sT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/u48R5TaZgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/9hO5tpqleB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/TFrteYMgwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/Xom94mThzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/iBB08hQ1hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/ZkfdVA8je0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/tsg5xvZjpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/mTLwUjJjfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/e2ZrPaf8hd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/OEHmBeDmdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/8PagtGOPWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/0p54gQAn0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/iTBkHefpgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/yrGsnzAhp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/GLyXccWO4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/z88g3ViSNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/Co6DFoZR3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/9sxELCN5PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/LDmoiZVhqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/RJzEfzky9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/wJhoJ44sb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/pDoUZaeuT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/VAZo678CFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/jiLjzO53oX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/h7nodZQMSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/RyKOwJQees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/II7QGbgQu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>