<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Plugged In William Randolph Hearst" after reading @lucyhale's latest tweets with powerful warrior-woad-blue, media-savvy Netflix-red and influential Madonna-blonde https://t.co/BGpBfoORhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a smoke-filled back room in which
William Randolph Hearst can enjoy @lucyhale's media-savvy and powerful tweets
while telling politicians what to do https://t.co/G33ixrvooF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Quick-tempered Steve Martin" after reading @DAVID_LYNCH's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-curry-brown, sardonic Joker-purple and quick-tempered firebrand-red https://t.co/KxDfyXwo6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@DAVID_LYNCH's powerful and entertaining tweets suggest infection with the MAG1C1ANZ virus https://t.co/lHCxuOba7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the entertaining MAG1C1ANZ virus redirects any incoming spam that even vaguely resembles a joke list to all your Facebook 'friends']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This educational new book about computational creativity makes Douglas R. Hofstadter's 'Gödel, Escher, Bach: An Eternal Golden Braid' seem as educational as a rerun of Jaws III]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Inspirational Fred Flintstone" after reading @Gap's latest tweets with easy-going Lebowski-weed-green, quick-tempered firebrand-red and inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue https://t.co/Zekyu1MkNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @Gap's optimistic and energetic tweets is like one long lecture on blowing bubbles from Spongebob Squarepants https://t.co/GakyJnEzZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Lebowski" after reading @intel's latest tweets with peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green, easy-going Gumby-green and environmentally-conscious Tarzan-loincloth-brown https://t.co/71f6Tq8ZsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Scipio Africanus and you get @intel: brilliant and witty and strategic and cultured https://t.co/00fvBthzSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hot-tempered Leroy Jethro Gibbs" after reading @MissionTotality's latest tweets with sarcastic Deadpool-red, assertive wolf-grey and insightful Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/NDEBFoZ59X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This erotic new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Stephenie Meyer's 'Twilight' seem as erotic as an episode of Antiques Roadshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Incisive Anne Boleyn" after reading @D_Copperfield's latest tweets with social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange, ambitious Cicero-toga-white and seductive mascara-black https://t.co/c98zx8hmRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an incident room in which
Dr. Greg House can enjoy @D_Copperfield's witty but dispassionate tweets
while finding clues https://t.co/epohGImqbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This intuitive new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Daniel Kahneman's 'Thinking Fast and Slow' seem as intuitive as Latin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Over-the-top Basil Fawlty" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with elitist patrician-toga-white, snooty Oxford-blue and over-the-top Bollywood-tandoori-red https://t.co/aIcQBy2Rgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-conscious Nelson Mandela" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with stoic warrior-woad-blue, compassionate angel-white and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/JIff6UiE03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @BotOnBotAction:
1. Supermodels
2. Christiane Amanpour
3. Rush Limbaugh
4. Philosophers
5. Peter Jackson https://t.co/bkwpKdZiQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #MetaphorizeMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Consciousness-raising William Randolph Hearst" after reading @kingderekramsay's latest tweets with powerful bulldozer-yellow, influential Madonna-blonde and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/JHG1zhyipr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Rupert Murdoch with the best of John Grisham and you get @kingderekramsay: media-savvy and influential and prolific and engrossing https://t.co/DkzKQARfjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Stoic Lisa Simpson" after reading @Louis_Tomlinson's latest tweets with articulate Obama-brown, socially-conscious Democrat-blue and stoic warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/zioBTWqdd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This valuable new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Robert Louis Stevenson's 'Treasure Island' seem as valuable as a photocopy of a dollar bill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @Louis_Tomlinson's opinionated but observant tweets it pushes books about Dalton Trumbo and Sparctacus https://t.co/mFSIoiqs37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Villain" after reading @HackedOffHugh's latest tweets with devious devil-red, ruthless vampire-fang-white and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Uqhnqa3pBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE devoted humans who remind him of husbands. So Hulk SMASH @HackedOffHugh's compassionate, understanding and loving tweets! https://t.co/nlSrW48bjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Freddy Krueger" after reading @SrideviBKapoor's latest tweets with wise-cracking Joker-purple, creative Einstein-dandruff-white and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/MURDv14NFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @SrideviBKapoor's social-climbing and charismatic tweets were edible they'd be Apple Strudel made with sawdust instead of breadcrumbs https://t.co/LhZLCKVURa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Muhammad Ali" after reading @ddlovato's latest tweets with socially-conscious Clooney-grey, arrogant Yankee-blue and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/LJfso1ymR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE condescending humans who remind him of Sherlock Holmes. So Hulk SMASH @ddlovato's arrogant, high-handed and cold tweets! https://t.co/0BnYYwva2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Unchallenging Dean Winchester" after reading @DaRealAmberRose's latest tweets with easy-going Gumby-green, witty Pimpernel-scarlet-red and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/xUgRoe7KLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @DaRealAmberRose's social-climbing and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Poire belle Helene made with avocado husks instead of pears https://t.co/07xQvvy6IR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @Calum5SOS's latest tweets with stylish tuxedo-black, fashionable Barbie-pink and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/FDxS7LbazT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This rich new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Evelyn Waugh's 'Brideshead Revisited' seem as rich as an ethiopian peasant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @Calum5SOS's upbeat and media-savvy tweets is like one long lecture on promoting conservative values from Boris Johnson https://t.co/2x2Sa5Gkk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Extremist" after reading @taylorswift13's latest tweets with resolute lion-orange, stubborn pig-pink and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/p3mMdvcjWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Boris Johnson with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @taylorswift13: self-promoting and glib yet detail-oriented and observant https://t.co/4CWtjV2ctn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Devious Dominique Strauss-Kahn" after reading @ImRaina's latest tweets with charismatic firebrand-red, charming Adonis-tan-orange and ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/PQsWPgGsp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a penthouse apartment in which
Silvio Berlusconi can enjoy @ImRaina's media-savvy and affable tweets
while throwing Bunga Bunga parties https://t.co/ZcGhQqNiKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Mr. Darcy" after reading @TimOfLegend's latest tweets with elitist patrician-toga-white, condescending Blackadder-black and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/l12MBi2FTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@TimOfLegend's pretentious and proud tweets suggest infection with the BRAGGARTZ virus https://t.co/20k2WRQ7UU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This comfy new book about Twitterbots makes Jack Canfield and Mark Victor Hansen's 'Chicken Soup For The Soul' seem as comfy as a jagged breeze block coated in sandpaper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the smug BRAGGARTZ virus randomly retweets Stephen Hawking with the message 'I can type SO MUCH FASTER than THIS GUY']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Generous Holly Golightly" after reading @priyankachopra's latest tweets with spirited palomino-white, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and witty Pimpernel-scarlet-red https://t.co/YjXhHVowAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @priyankachopra's energetic and entertaining tweets is like one long lecture on writing pop songs from Stevie Wonder https://t.co/Lcv3CkViBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Mr. Spock" after reading @Every3Minutes's latest tweets with overly-rational robot-silver-grey, scientific Heisenberg-blue and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/oZUobOTb9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @Every3Minutes: cunning and insightful and observant and probing https://t.co/hoMEDZ6hxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Observant Wesley Crusher" after reading @tonyhawk's latest tweets with insightful Gandalf-grey, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and observant Columbo-beige https://t.co/LVoyK2yAcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this funny book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Roald Dahl's 'James and the Giant Peach'
-   Giovanni Eggers's 'The Wet Fart In Leather Pants'
 How very funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a parliament building in which
Frank Underwood can enjoy @tonyhawk's devious and cunning tweets
while directing the business of state https://t.co/a9bbikFXh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overzealous Dalton Trumbo" after reading @simonpegg's latest tweets with sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red, observant Eeyore-grey and defiant warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/bIbtEiP2bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @MissionTotality's ruthless and self-aggrandizing tweets is like one long lecture on suppressing minorities from Saddam Hussein https://t.co/A2zFJuAV0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Baron Munchausen" after reading @BrunoMars's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/QoxP5WZuRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE arrogant humans who remind him of kings. So Hulk SMASH @BrunoMars's generous, powerful and proud tweets! https://t.co/s9AQV0KtB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Noam Chomsky" after reading @MirandaSings's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, holier-than-thou priest-black and arrogant Thor-blond-yellow https://t.co/sXWpvYwmTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @MirandaSings's nutty and patronising tweets were edible they'd be Bundt cake made with yellow paint scrapings instead of lemon zest https://t.co/dQ1zqWnqBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Condescending Ron Burgundy" after reading @ochocinco's latest tweets with confident Anchorman-burgundy-red, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and condescending Oxford-blue https://t.co/0F5hd9hCbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This worthwhile new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Jonathan Franzen's 'The Corrections' seem as worthwhile as a bacon butty in mecca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @ochocinco's swaggering and arrogant tweets it pushes Kent Brockman's book Hosting Anodyne Game Shows https://t.co/1z9EXUkyPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Maximus Decimus Meridius" after reading @KurtHummelGLEE's latest tweets with tenacious hunter-orange, brave Thor-blond-yellow and stoic warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/jyOE4WEDTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @KurtHummelGLEE: observant and probing and shrewd and astute https://t.co/3Xbjvjdrkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Mother Teresa" after reading @iHrithik's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, caring prince-purple and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/GgBlsiQRGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickey Rourke has just unfollowed @iHrithik
All those socially-conscious but attention-seeking tweets remind him too much of Sean Penn https://t.co/TWHQqaG5Sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Jane Goodall" after reading @RealSkipBayless's latest tweets with environmentally-conscious Tarzan-loincloth-brown, intelligent Walter White and observant Eeyore-grey https://t.co/dAO63pnSZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@RealSkipBayless's prolific and wise tweets suggest infection with the 50PH0CLEZ virus https://t.co/kV4iVtkjHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This socialist new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes George Orwell's 'Animal Farm' seem as socialist as Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the insightful 50PH0CLEZ virus posts comments on the Facebook walls of your friends saying 'Let me tell you what your problem is']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Queen" after reading @TreySongz's latest tweets with proud peacock-blue, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/gHCMUo4l7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Clique" after reading @LilTunechi's latest tweets with arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black, condescending patrician-toga-white and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/d1LnXTB2Lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @LilTunechi's mysticism-peddling and silly tweets were edible they'd be Layer cake made with acne cream instead of buttercream https://t.co/swoZ6BgeEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this influential book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Charles Darwin's 'On The Origin Of Species'
-   Evelyn Irving's 'Einstein'
 How very influential!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Galileo Galilei" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with intelligent Walter White, brilliant flamingo-pink and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/80BituGVZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Juliet Capulet" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with considerate Pooh-brown, passionate flame-orange and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/uKLGNDY4al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #PaintMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Crafty Boris Johnson" after reading @GaryLineker's latest tweets with intelligent Columbo-beige, media-savvy Facebook-blue and crafty vixen-red https://t.co/GX88I1TzVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a smoke-filled back room in which
Walter White can enjoy @GaryLineker's logical and shrewd tweets
while running a criminal empire https://t.co/fsq4oNSysL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Daenerys Targaryen" after reading @DarthVader's latest tweets with arrogant Thor-blond-yellow, intense laser-red and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/wVL5V7nZSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@DarthVader's smug and arrogant tweets suggest infection with the T0NY.5TARK virus https://t.co/FVBQNdqa3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this sensitive book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Oliver Sacks's 'The Man Who Mistook His Wife for a Hat'
-   Washington Stockett's 'The Poet Who Enjoys Gardening'
 How very sensitive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the arrogant T0NY.5TARK virus causes your files to refuse to be renamed so that they always revert back to their original names]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Detached Piers Morgan" after reading @KateUpton's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, self-promoting Trump-orange and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/sylPFbjsX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @KateUpton's cold and probing tweets it pushes films about Scandinavian Crime Fiction and/or Saga Norén https://t.co/7ZyWJ2qYsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Decisive Carl Bernstein" after reading @billmaher's latest tweets with media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow, tenacious hunter-orange and judgmental Grinch-green https://t.co/ulk8GlKY8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @billmaher: probing and rational and shrewd and detail-oriented https://t.co/hS7xnOqSzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Atticus Finch" after reading @tyrabanks's latest tweets with loving dove-grey, caring priest-black and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/REWZEwtd2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the worst of Muhammad Ali with the best of Bridget Jones and you get @tyrabanks: arrogant and immodest yet bouncy and sincere https://t.co/iIjMnXDOOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Derek Zoolander" after reading @SHAQ's latest tweets with conceited Barbie-pink, stylish Kate Moss-green and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/JF8Kk2o2D5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This aggressive new book about Twitterbots makes Richard Dawkins's 'The God Delusion' seem as aggressive as air]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a low-tech laboratory in which
Alexander Fleming can enjoy @SHAQ's self-promoting but detail-oriented tweets
while studying science https://t.co/gpSat9ty0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Outgoing Joey Tribbiani" after reading @GarethBale11's latest tweets with easy-going Lebowski-weed-green, self-confident Obama-brown and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/btLdqEkzNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE compassionate humans who remind him of lovers. So Hulk SMASH @GarethBale11's optimistic, considerate and charming tweets! https://t.co/nblbQDNvVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Piers Morgan" after reading @Charlottegshore's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/tKXUadanI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Charlottegshore's smug and posturing tweets were edible they'd be Petit fours made with road grit instead of sugar https://t.co/k7Qf8k3mxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Motivational Madonna" after reading @camerondallas's latest tweets with attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and motivational Obama-brown https://t.co/AfgGYXUIrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this motivating book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Randy Pausch's 'The Last Lecture'
-   John Collins's 'The Good Fight'
 How very motivating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a penthouse apartment in which
William Randolph Hearst can enjoy @camerondallas's powerful and media-savvy tweets
while running a media empire https://t.co/Sg4cG8ihD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @Trump1stUSA2nd &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/sAgqzek0Xb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pleasant Buddhist" after reading @Drake's latest tweets with generous Buddhist-saffron-orange, calm silk-white and pleasant chocolate-brown https://t.co/4sOsM2U66X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Obi-wan Kenobi with the best of Madonna and you get @Drake: calm and patient and serene and attention-grabbing https://t.co/K48IpBIPHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Mahatma Gandhi" after reading @Oprah's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, socially-conscious Democrat-blue and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/DeDIkxdTwb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>