<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenMangan: Yeah! Brexit shook the establishment to its core!! https://t.co/VwpcicbjnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UXDesignTop Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GA_London: Learn about the core rules &amp; best practices of UX design for ecommerce sites w @ishmatt &gt;&gt; https://t.co/rHjMafOLp2 https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “Why you should use a carousel” https://t.co/jUHWBJrXEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world may seem like a more uncertain place but you always know where you stand with England #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuckyCart_UK Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lakey Are they just waiting for the pound to collapse further? Beacuse surely it should boost foreign sales...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good day for fans of MP's letterheads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewingram Is there a word for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesLawley @Undeliverable8 Whilst rapidly running out of partners to join him at the crease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this politics oddly compelling. Like watching an England batting collapse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilviaDG_IxD Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freeagent: Stop, collaborate, and listen. The 3-step guide to client happiness https://t.co/S67exGavga via @ishmatt #ux #design https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vinarathbone Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see we're all thinking the same thing https://t.co/lRyU9UCl75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomvictor: Antoine Griezmann looks like a Lisa Simpson love interest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WandaWalsh91 Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAllenGreen: If there's any populist politician capable of 'winning' two referendums saying opposite things it is Boris.

He'd quit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xav_pires Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAllenGreen: No Article 50 notification, no Brexit. 

It is that simple.

The greater the delay, the less chance it will happen. ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @benfurneaux: If you liked The Phantom Menace you're going to love the next 5 years of trade negotiations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joelgolby: well it’s good everyone went into this with their eyes open  https://t.co/0uJpcerI9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I preferred it when it was all football on the TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much irony https://t.co/rKyMp9vmIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarinaHyde: Our newly-minted Tractor Beam of Shit pulls in its first craft https://t.co/AcuE5dDvMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danbarker: Just took 93yr Mum to the shops, she's registered blind. She asked, "How much is a freddo?" A cheer went up as they took her…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @twlldun: No, it doesn't, Julian. Enjoy the Embassy stock cupboard.  https://t.co/CCpCVljE5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Carney for PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: It's important to just accept the result and move on, possibly to another country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amitpateluk Yep, keen to join you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davelee: Meanwhile... https://t.co/XFCXZIr50S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes their uncertainty served with a side of uncertainty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Herring1967: The joke's on UKIP. Soon there isn't going to be a UK and their name will look silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAllenGreen: The legal form and timing of Brexit is still *entirely* to be determined. Referendum itself was advisory, not binding:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewingram @SimonNRicketts ha true, they're the only ones who realise the existential threat it poses to their party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesLawley: 0% of UK charities want Brexit. A vote to remain is a vote to help those who need help most. https://t.co/CnshUQcnDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mr603: VOTERS BEWARE! If they can rub out your pencil crosses, they can also tear up your polling card. Remember to take a PEN and a LA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I followed the Johnnie Cochran formula today:
'If it does rain, you must vote remain']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealBobMortimer: What the UK spends its money on. Puts EU spend in proper context  https://t.co/F9QpPPMDFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonblackwell: https://t.co/Of5IV6mWgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MclgsuZhanna Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimCampbellTFR And Wales win the tournament. But we've beaten them so we all know who the real winners are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've done well out of this match #HUNPOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bill_tribble: Because that is my UNMET NEED https://t.co/RlnpAJsvtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much money do The White Stripes make from international football tournaments? #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: We curated our #Brexit coverage so you don't have to. A one-stop guide to the #EUref   https://t.co/QYcs5Veqbo https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BenHatch: And here's what #BorisJohnson said about Brexit 4 months before he thought this was his chance to be PM https://t.co/IEvOQ1Lp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhillipRowntree: Well played Laurence... #VoteRemain https://t.co/fFWO4MM7lW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tom_Gatti: BBC neutrality overload: pro-remain letter from 1300 businesses and pro-leave letter from 1 boss (Tate&amp;Lyle) presented almos…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never do politics in an arena again BBC—take the worst QT and multiply by ten #BBCDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bengoldacre: All this Brexit waffle about "choice". We had the choice to build more houses, schools, train staff, invest in education.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidAllenGreen What about best of three?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DickGraceless: Dear England

You voted for cuts. You got cuts. 

That's why you can't get a GP appointment, not because of Hungarians.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How not to pay the bill https://t.co/SjWcLkhUvS https://t.co/KlPfIKZPzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webmobiletips Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdEEkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guide to designer/client happiness https://t.co/t9ZY2cMfaR #freelance #design]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthewsumi: Data-Driven UX Design: Metrics | Book by Matt Isherwood https://t.co/xIe8hz4Z9B via @ishmatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewsumi Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeaaronmoore Other than that Vardy chance have we tested the keeper though? Frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England seem destined to play the same match over and over again #ENGSLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone scored from a corner this tournament? #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hengdesigns Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdEEkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handy advice from @pjrvs on how to make podcasting quick https://t.co/S1mvf4aZI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How We Lost 47% of Our Users After a Redesign https://t.co/panxGrHcqa (or how it could have been avoided with a bit of user testing)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francis_reardon Congrats on smashing the record! Impressive work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobbyllew: Please watch this before Thursday
https://t.co/62vcb5bGTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice piece on what makes content spread/go viral: Anatomy of a Post With 500,000+ Likes https://t.co/tqcBA6DMlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crolluxd Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/wmwJrX1bfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrLeonardKim Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdEEkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kwr66: The Express, working to an agenda. Staggering when laid out like that. https://t.co/S48YgEK3KS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballEOnline Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much choice do you want when buying? https://t.co/0Z82tqKtmB https://t.co/Bkx3dKE15U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy, masters of the sucker punch. #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selfbios Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handy checklist on framing, executing, and measuring digital products and product teams https://t.co/l9MB6XkR9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office in a bag – tools for UX design https://t.co/smgoF1ox2x https://t.co/xepPHRoDPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardiannews: Jo Cox's husband Brendan: 'Jo believed in a better world and fought for it every day' https://t.co/5tHajOYYh3 https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the boundary between mobile apps and real life is disappearing https://t.co/mIjEoniQgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joelgolby: VINNIE JONES, GAVIN HENSON, GLYN FROM BIG BROTHER: YOUR BOYS TOOK ONE HELL OF A BEATING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching this England is much like watching LvG's Man United team. Unthreatening possession. #ENGWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gareth Bale proving you just need to get free kicks on target this tournament #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesRowlands: #ENGWAL satisfying the curiosity of any continental Europeans who wondered what a League One play-off final looked lik…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is apt following another shooting: The Reductive Seduction of Other People’s Problems https://t.co/IsLjZpfTvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bonn1eGreer: "All you have to do is tell them they are being attacked
Works the same way in any country"- Hermann Göring
#Farage
https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Indix Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick and cheap personas from Google Analytics data https://t.co/NSKAmAmMdE https://t.co/Ue29gl9CTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ID8UX Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ID8UX: The Vanilla Ice 3-step guide to client happiness https://t.co/W1nygjJJmQ via @ishmatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EPIC_AppTools Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this golden rule of UX design https://t.co/xDQ7akTQ29 #ux https://t.co/ZjnMx8GtFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1alexsong1 Thanks for following! Here's a free chapter from my new book https://t.co/Bbv0OdWfJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy https://t.co/syjZZDsUJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good summary from @Baymard on what you should have on your search/browse pages https://t.co/iqjmNp9zIx #ecommerce https://t.co/LzbytOv4aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelPDeacon: Farage's boat isn't actually heading to Parliament. We're just sailing in a big circle, being pursued by Bob Geldof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GA_London: Companies! Meet &amp; Hire our fresh UX &amp; web dev talent, 23 June at @CampusLondon. RSVP here: https://t.co/IEYBSvYpea https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProfBrianCox: It's possible to get people to vote to abolish gravity, but there will be a constitutional crisis when they discover they…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trinifood Ha, who knew what a multi-talented guy he was!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vanilla Ice 3-step guide to designer/client happiness https://t.co/MVoEAmwYuz #ux https://t.co/KQIHMo3McM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdbrad Might have to head further north if they start flooding over the border!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdbrad Ha, well it's all looking a bit worrying]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>