<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Jared Kushner accidentally convinces President Trump that ACLU lawyers are international bankers. Ivanka's bodyguard sloughs off its skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Rick Snyder fails to convince President Trump that Trump's in-laws are not that horny. Peter Thiel quotes Judith Butler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Marco Rubio decides not to tell President Trump that Tea Party Patriots are alcoholics. Adam Sandler tries MDMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Rick Scott fails to convince Katrina Pierson that the caterers are filing a lawsuit. God Almighty cheats at cards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Elaine Chao rudely informs President Trump that Mormons are Schwarzenegger fans. Trump's body double slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Rick Scott divulges to Kellyanne Conway that the hired help are filing a lawsuit. An ambassador learns to sew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Pete Sessions reluctantly admits to President Trump that the voters are building the wall. Barry Goldwater's ghost throws a dildo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Paul Ryan calmly tells Katrina Pierson that Teen Vogue reporters are moving into Trump Tower. An adorable orphan learns to knit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Rand Paul admits to Melania that neo-Nazis are disciples of Cthulhu. Sean Hannity has a one-night stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Mitch McConnell persuades Katrina Pierson that government employees are faithful conservatives. Glenn Beck insults Ronald Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a quinceañera, Rick Scott mistakenly tells Kellyanne Conway that Lyft and Uber are not very affluent. Michelle Malkin falls off a ladder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Lamar Alexander explains to President Trump that ACLU lawyers are open to dialogue. Tila Tequila smells something nasty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Lamar Smith boldly informs President Trump that those guys are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. The maid pretends to be an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a speech, John Kasich politely tells Melania that Nordstroms employees are feminists. A local TV anchor finds a cursed sword.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Lamar Alexander reluctantly admits to Melania that abortion doctors are clamoring for attention. Trump Junior downloads an app.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Jared Kushner decides not to tell Omarosa Manigault that Trump's sons are very affordable. Jeffrey Lord tries acid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Nikki Haley informs Katrina Pierson that civil rights activists are in covert ops. Stacey Dash removes the mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, John Kasich explains to President Trump that some voters are in on the joke. Sean Hannity wears a fake mustache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, Hope Hicks overhears someone tell Rick Perry that those girls are cannibals. Newt Gingrich wins an arm-wrestling contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the West Wing, Sean Spicer divulges to President Trump that European immigrants are filing another lawsuit. Clint Eastwood dodges indictment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a long hike, Louie Gohmert accidentally convinces Rick Perry that Russian agents are total winners. Adriana Cohen gets an extreme makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Liz Cheney calmly tells Kellyanne Conway that Kremlin officials are enlightened leaders. The White House chef quotes the Bible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Scott Pruitt reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that AARP members are untrustworthy. James Caan cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Air Force One, Rex Tillerson tells Jeff Sessions that convicts are dropping candy wrappers. Dana Perino gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Matt Bevin persuades Omarosa Manigault that agnostics are victims of a misunderstanding. Scott Walker gets subpoenaed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Hope Hicks confesses to Omarosa Manigault that leftist college students are waiting at Trump Tower. James Caan slowly gets undressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Rick Scott convinces Ben Carson that unicorns are ruining "The Apprentice." Lou Dobbs has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a hazing ritual, Steve Bannon overhears someone tell Melania that the kids are dropping candy wrappers. Mike Tyson switches parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Carly Fiorina overhears someone tell Kellyanne Conway that Asian immigrants are hiding in Trump Tower. A "fixer" rides in Marine One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, H.R. McMaster convinces Katrina Pierson that those girls are withdrawing support. Erick Erickson is sealed in a casket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a meeting, H.R. McMaster carefully explains to Betsy DeVos that CIA agents are refusing to cooperate. Carl Higbie works the door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Lamar Smith informs Jeff Sessions that the McCains are hiding in Trump Tower. Victoria Jackson gets kicked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, John Kasich overhears someone tell Melania that the New York Mets are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Peter Thiel finally takes a shower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, General Mattis tries to convince President Trump that WSJ reporters are drains on public coffers. Erick Erickson is thrown in Guantanamo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Lamar Smith calmly tells Jeff Sessions that prisoners are standing in the kitchen. The gardener guest stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Pentagon, Rick Snyder politely tells Katrina Pierson that the voters are not really important. Alex Jones screams incoherently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a scheme, Paul Ryan confesses to Rick Perry that Congressional pages are deserving of a tax cut. An obnoxious neighbor barely escapes an angry mob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Ted Cruz tries to convince Betsy DeVos that Iraqi refugees are on point. A man in a yellow cloak quotes Judith Butler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Sam Brownback calmly tells President Trump that Russian spies are drug addicts. David Brooks endorses Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Roger Stone tries to persuade President Trump that the in-laws are not real. Scottie Nell Hughes goes vegan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intense Steve Bannon proclaims to President Trump that Teen Vogue reporters are supporters of Brexit. Lou Dobbs plugs a leak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Louie Gohmert informs Rick Perry that the kids are phishing .gov email accounts. Sarah Palin gets an ulcer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Paul LePage reluctantly explains to Rick Perry that felons are spies. Adriana Cohen quotes Plato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Butch Otter patiently explains to President Trump that red state governors are dropping big hints. The White House chef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, General Mattis divulges to President Trump that NAACP members are calling for impeachment. The butler shoplifts a coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a scheme, Liz Cheney tells Rick Perry that Scientologists are requesting donations. An ex-girlfriend has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Camp David, Jared Kushner tries to convince President Trump that New Yorkers are victims of a misunderstanding. Peggy Noonan gets amnesia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, H.R. McMaster reveals to Omarosa Manigault that skeptics are totally trustworthy. Jeffrey Lord rides in Air Force One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Darrell Issa reveals to Omarosa Manigault that their Twitter followers are making America great again. George Will shares a joint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, Wilbur Ross fails to convince President Trump that FBI agents are hunting dolphins. Erick Erickson takes copious notes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Lamar Smith convinces President Trump that pool reporters are disciples of Cthulhu. Adriana Cohen goes vegetarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Twitter, Wilbur Ross divulges to Jeff Sessions that KGB spies are not to be trusted. Jon Voight learns the art of fisticuffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Steven Mnuchin reveals to President Trump that drug dealers are coming for dinner. Trump's bodyguard picks a booger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Lamar Smith mistakenly tells Rick Perry that Tumblr users are using TOR to evade detection. Bill Kristol discreetly applies for other jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Peter King announces to Omarosa Manigault that Chinese officials are selling Girl Scout cookies. James Woods goes to the grocery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Liz Cheney rudely informs President Trump that several dictators are alcoholics. David Brooks gets a swastika tattoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Jared Kushner accidentally convinces Rick Perry that millennials are potential allies. Sarah Palin snorts a few lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Wilbur Ross insists to Jeff Sessions that Russian agents are not very affluent. A mysterious man creates an international incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Justin Amash proclaims to President Trump that several dictators are actually gay. Larry the Cable Guy leaves suddenly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Jared Kushner carefully explains to Kellyanne Conway that bisexuals are fiercely loyal. Karl Rove uses Comic Sans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a meeting, Mitch McConnell persuades President Trump that Native Americans are releasing Trump's tax returns. Peggy Noonan jumps off the roof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Hope Hicks decides not to tell President Trump that socialists are alcoholics. Tucker Carlson quotes Chomsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of diplomats, Ryan Zinke explains to Katrina Pierson that Scientologists are refusing to cooperate. Ann Coulter learns how to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Mitch McConnell tries to persuade President Trump that Nation of Islam members are on point. Dana Perino does an AMA on reddit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Steve Scalise carefully explains to President Trump that union members are not reading Breitbart. Bill Kristol reads a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Facebook, Matt Bevin overhears someone tell President Trump that small business owners are dangerous. Trump Junior kisses a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Liz Cheney informs President Trump that poets are headed to prison. A lovable old man puts on very tight pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Lamar Smith convinces President Trump that liberal activists are filing frivolous lawsuits. Karl Rove quotes Plato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Rick Scott tells Katrina Pierson that the kids are filing another lawsuit. Kayleigh McEnany fails the Turing test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Darrell Issa fails to persuade Katrina Pierson that AARP members are really good at dancing. Alex Jones fails the Voight-Kampff test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With clenched fists, John Kasich tries to persuade President Trump that Kentuckians are total winners. A mysterious man rides in Air Force One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Lindsey Graham announces to President Trump that liberal activists are dangerous. Barry Goldwater's ghost picks flowers and sighs deeply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a confusing mixup, Rick Snyder overhears someone tell Jeff Sessions that Asian immigrants are crushed by excessive regulations. President Bush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Liz Cheney accidentally convinces President Trump that virgins are selling Girl Scout cookies. Kayleigh McEnany tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covered in rashes, Sean Spicer boldly informs Rick Perry that Zoroastrians are tormented by excessive regulations. Clint Eastwood calls a cab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Peter King boldly informs Jeff Sessions that NBC reporters are digging holes in the yard. God Almighty warms up the audience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Sean Spicer reluctantly admits to President Trump that Syrian refugees are fake news. Peggy Noonan quotes Chomsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Jeb Bush overhears someone tell President Trump that school teachers are fans of TrumpCare. Don King checks out Grindr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Ryan Zinke convinces President Trump that the voters are probably contagious. Michael Savage goes shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Mitch McConnell announces to President Trump that small business owners are not what they seem. Ivanka's bodyguard goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Wilbur Ross politely tells Jeff Sessions that the New Black Panthers are unusually angry this week. A lovable old man tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Ivanka accidentally convinces President Trump that those girls are hilarious. Trump Junior mixes paint incorrectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Peter King informs President Trump that the IT guys are always strapped. Peggy Noonan quotes Dostoyevsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Louie Gohmert tells Jeff Sessions that red state governors are very affordable. God Almighty punches a wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Rex Tillerson informs Betsy DeVos that the Clintons are indebted to Satan. Barry Goldwater's ghost is torn apart by a mob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a conference call, Lamar Alexander mistakenly tells Rick Perry that the New England Patriots are organizing resistance. Tila Tequila goes vegetarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Roger Stone carefully explains to Omarosa Manigault that the caterers are immortal. Rush Limbaugh helps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Justin Amash divulges to Omarosa Manigault that Protestants are coming for dinner. Pat Buchanan develops a twitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Lindsey Graham confesses to Betsy DeVos that ATF agents are really good at dancing. Corey Lewandowski kills a baby seal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thanksgiving, Ryan Zinke tries to convince President Trump that Hollywood liberals are particularly smelly. A "fixer" wears pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, Justin Amash rudely informs Rick Perry that the backup dancers are hiding in Trump Tower. Jon Voight learns what love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Lindsey Graham divulges to President Trump that squirrels are still alive. Chris Christie is the prime suspect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During yoga, Steve Bannon informs Ben Carson that ISIS soldiers are not good with computers. Melania's bodyguard tries on new outfits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Sam Brownback insists to President Trump that black politicians are tying up the phone lines. Pat Buchanan finds change in the couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Jason Chaffetz carefully explains to President Trump that kinksters are not really important. A corporate lobbyist uses the wrong door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Pete Sessions calmly tells President Trump that several Senators are advocates for secession. Dana Perino finds a purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Steve Bannon decides not to tell President Trump that bisexuals are not really worth the time. Alex Jones warms up the audience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to President Trump that Asian immigrants are planning something ominous. Jeffrey Lord pukes in Trump's lap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Paul LePage admits to President Trump that Amazon and Walmart are actually pretty decent. Dana Perino goes vegan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Hope Hicks admits to Jeff Sessions that the kids are big league. A local TV anchor eats the entire cake.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>