<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I should really have a partner with my music.. It would be so much more fun. Any takers? haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having too much fun with performance mode on FL Studio!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance mode &lt;3 #FLStudio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upgraded to Fl Studio 11.... Excited!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how to react to @lqianoo @JulieQuitoskyy and @EmZ_N_EmZ 's game of Monopoly... #AaronsTheWorstBankerEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to get some music done. Lets hope its not another month late =P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xoKimbo: We fight *from* victory not for victory. In Christ, the battle has already been won! 
Thank You, Father! In Jesus’ name, Amen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: My salvation and my honor depend on God; he is my mighty rock, my refuge. -Psalm 62:7”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really want to start break dancing again....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JosephPrince: You don’t have to go to God with perfect prayers. The very moment you cry out, “Daddy!”, He runs to you and meets you at …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: As iron sharpens iron, so one man sharpens another. -Proverbs 27:17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 2 weeks of procrastinating, Im finally doing all the math hw I havent done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calvary__Tweets: "If God is your co-pilot, swap seats!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tedashii: Psalm 33:4 is heavy on my heart today.
If you've ever thought on God's concern for you, read this with me today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Lord, you satisfy my soul. Nothing compares to your LOVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: God, your plan is bigger than my worries. I look towards you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2 #Electronic #Trance #House #techno #Dubstep #BeatMaking #Beat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this kid --&gt; @CKrushel #Twitter #TeamFollowBack #Noob #NeedsFollowers #NoLife #Hashtag #MoreHashtag #Bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: God demonstrates his own love for us in this: While we were still sinners, Christ died for us. -Romans 5:8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Godly_Life: You can decide to trust God, or you can decide to be miserable."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: Commit to the LORD whatever you do, &amp; your plans will succeed. -Proverbs 16:3”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So tired... Someone talk to me or something, so bored too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Just because you found God doesn't mean you should stop seeking Him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Godly_Life: Make up your mind that you’re not going to quit until you see the fruit of what God has placed within you.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning peeps!! Long day ahead of me today. #Test #Practice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a productive day practicing with Karina for small ensemble! #Sarcasm #DidNothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: Create in me a clean heart, O God. -Psalm 51.10”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart to heart talks w/ Chelsea. Its weird how she's helping me instead. Hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: If anyone is in Christ, there is a new creation. -2Corinthians 5:17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today has been a weird daay....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have about 2 weeks left til I take my learners test. I should start reading...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was nice to get back in the weight room again. Its been so long since I last worked out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta think of a new idea for a song... Should I continue with electronic or move to hip hop..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God promises that if you will stay in faith, He will take what's meant for your harm and use it for good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: In your presence I am free!!! #worship #jesus #praise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your talent is God's gift to you.  What you do with it is your gift back to God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally done all my homework... I think...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: As a dog goes back to its vomit, so a fool repeats his stupidity. -Proverbs 26:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar sugar, do ya read me sugar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lqianoo honey honey ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Godly_Life: Father, help me to never be afraid to pray for the impossible.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: You are the light of the world. -Matthew 5.14”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Delight yourself in the LORD and he'll give you the desires of your heart. -Psalm 37:4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider it pure joy, whenever u face trials of many kinds, because u know that the testing of your faith develops perseverance. -James 1:2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the day that the Lord has made; let us rejoice and be glad in it. -Psalm 118.24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God only gives three answers to prayer: 1. 'Yes!' 2. 'Not yet.' 3. 'I have something better in mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: No matter who you are or what you have come to believe, there is nothing that can separate you from my love. #worship #pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12th Son Of Jacobon SoundCloud http://t.co/zy4n5HEq1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre' cool shot I got in Seattle http://t.co/PXkLMMeQ3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: It doesn't matter how young you are (1 Tim 4:12). God has called you to be a courageous voice of Truth. Stand tall &amp; be b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Godly_Life: Trust the LORD &amp; his mighty power. -Psalm 105:4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieQuitoskyy @lqianoo Meet at Bellis fair food court at noon. My parents and Aaron will meet you guys there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: But seek first his kingdom &amp; his righteousness, and all these things will be given to you as well. -Matthew 6:33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulieQuitoskyy: @decaiman67 @lqianoo ben ben ben!!! Where are you guys? I miss y'all :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Godly_Life: Father, help me to never be afraid to pray for the impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghetto? @lqianoo @JulieQuitoskyy http://t.co/AblJfaaW0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to you guys? @lqianoo @JulieQuitoskyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So just as we were about to look for a place to sleep in the states.... We ended up losing eachother. Now we know how important internet is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone give us $150 so we can stay at a hotel? #Seattle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @JulieQuitoskyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicken Joy for lunch!! #Jolibee http://t.co/VFuk3HuIbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @louiegiglio: Starting out in the arms of Jesus. Longing to end there. Any achievement/failure in between is framed by His embrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tedashii: This phrase appears enough in the bible that I should consider not being afraid. Today I choose to not… http://t.co/GK5hQaxoHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are times when God wants to use you in someone else's life; it may not be pretty or comfortable, but they need to see Jesus!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Whatever you ask for in prayer with faith, you will receive. -Matthew 21:22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: Noow On YouTube!! http://t.co/H5pu31XIBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remembered I'm off to Seattle tomorrow. Well I'm probs gunna do an all nighter and sleep during the car ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Fruit Of The Spirit - Self-Control’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/UtDDuQQqsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio:  http://t.co/uQAF1NktP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Fruit Of The Spirit - Self-Control http://t.co/vBvuUBt0cp on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you take time with God and listen to His voice, He renews your strength and enables you to handle life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Knock, &amp; the door will be opened. -Luke 11.9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: With God all things are possible. -Matthew 19:26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrianPuspos: Vancity is gorgeous today. Feeling lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing that has happened to you is a surprise to God. God will still get you to where you're supposed to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know &amp; rely on the love God has for us. God is love. Whoever lives in love lives in God, &amp; God in him. -1John 4:16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Yes it waas! Again on Tuesday? hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@AUDICID: Pains often draw us nearer to God, while pleasure can often drive us further from Him.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: I will give you a new heart &amp; put a new spirit in you; I will remove from you your heart of stone &amp; give you a heart of flesh.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Godly_Life: Peace on the outside comes from knowing God on the inside.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God never promises the absence of storms. He just promises to walk with us through them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: We wander from God, and blessed pains await..pains that send us running back to our Comforter. But there's nothing scarier tha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AUDICID: If something hurts, let it hurt. Don't anesthetize yourself &amp; harden your heart...otherwise you can be wounding yourself and n…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NathanMahey: Follow @decaiman67 if you want good quotes and he is a good friend of mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you fully obey, God's blessings will chase you down and overtake you. You won't be able to outrun the good things of God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the Spirit God gave us does not make us timid, but gives us power, love and self-discipline. -2Timothy 1:7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There was a time I believed in God yet  lived a life that did not honor Him. How can I even begin to judge those who have yet to KNOW Him?”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@iammcjin: “@De_Painkiller: @iammcjin two words: LOVE.THEM.” one word: amen.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tedashii: Be careful. Prayer is not you catching God up to speed. In prayer it is you who is being caught up to speed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know how to set up the Novation A-Station? #Novation #Synth #MusicProduction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just remembered that I have job applications for Tim Hortons.... I think I should fill it out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to look for a job soon....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 300 Soundcloud followers. Very good progress!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning to go for a run tomorrow morning. I hope the weather is nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brandon747: I suck at texting back. Sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a celebrity crush on @chachigonzales for like a couple years already. So can I meet you already? Like srsly...? Please. #VanCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: Galations 5:22-23  But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness,... http://t.co/8pVM2MwbId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos are also on my pinterest --&gt; http://t.co/tO4J06n6Id #Photography]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>