<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers: Senior Software Engineers, Saint Charles, IL: Analyze &amp; prepare workflows that describes the logical flow of the application. Integrate the application with interface systems like Oracle R12, AEM, Factory systems, Cybersource,… https://t.co/hj7048aX3Y https://t.co/i1FxVibPdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineering Manager #1816034: Senior Software Engineering Manager Needed by AT&amp;T Services, Inc. in Bothell, WA to design and deliver server to server software deployment systems using shell scripts and middleware features from Weblogic.… https://t.co/vkhvmm6fDI https://t.co/732H6diFRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: 605 is looking for experienced devops engineers who can help us build a devops culture, with infrastructure automation owned by the whole engineering team. Our work is in optimizing advertising and programming for the television… https://t.co/22SEiwttcz https://t.co/h4lnK7gbsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Job Description Senior Solutions Architect Job ID ****** Location US-CA-Cupertino Posted Date 5/3/2018 Company Amazon Web Services, Inc. Position Category .. Recruiting Team .. Job Description Do you want to help U.S.… https://t.co/ndX5kMAhRG https://t.co/sZADthxRVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Desktop Support Analyst (must be able to: Job TitleSr. Desktop Support Analyst (must be able to working a rotating schedule) – ID:22224 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsWindows 2000, VPN, Outlook LocationLos Angeles, CA Date… https://t.co/AQw5tbXT81 https://t.co/AEZ7RDRHkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Application Developer: Lead Application Developer Job in Atlanta Area, GA | SunTrustSkip to page content SunTrust Careers Home – Join Our Talent Network – Link opens a new window – Link opens a new window – Careers Home – Job Categories – Diversity… https://t.co/xulTyhgHxS https://t.co/wngcOEnCS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: CLIENT REFERENCE CODE: ****** JOB SUMMARY The Scrum Master is an essential process management role on Charters various development teams. This role is focused on working with the web development team, the development architect, development… https://t.co/39NKB1N7HG https://t.co/XkONaATix0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Associate: Software Engineering Associate Requisition ID: 180053684 Location: Columbus, OH, US Job Category: Technology Duties: Analyze the features and perform impact analysis, develops application to the requirements and testing of… https://t.co/iSVaAj8VfV https://t.co/pWe2KMkz9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Staff: Req ID : 417540BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : The Space Security division of LM Space in King Of Prussia, PA is looking for talented Software Engineers with recent and relevant skills to support… https://t.co/IpgtCy44jY https://t.co/tvwrxqpAuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Software Eng: 109221BR Sr Principal Software Eng CA – El Segundo 109221BR Job Description: The Software Engineering Center is seeking an enthusiastic and highly capable software engineer to develop embedded software for radar modes. The… https://t.co/WUwVAFrGtn https://t.co/rscMusrXpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Economist: Principal Economist IHS Markit’s Center for Forecasting and Modelling is seeking a Principal Economist with extensive experience in econometric modelling and knowledge of cutting-edge techniques in macroeconometrics and forecasting.… https://t.co/38u7t01ZNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: **CLIENT UNABLE TO SPONSOR AT THIS TIME*** ***PLEASE NO C2C VENDORS*** We are seeking a Senior Business Systems Analyst (BSA) to own solution definition and manage requirements for agile software projects. BSAs are responsible for all… https://t.co/TE6PCheFqs https://t.co/jiknz5nZpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Trunomi [*********************** is looking for a full-stack developer to help build out our product portfolio. A full stack developer is a master of breadth and quick learning and ideally has experience and expertise all across the… https://t.co/drHUmih0us https://t.co/PDhqtJsrX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineer: Our client is dedicated to helping our members lead healthy financial lives. They offer an award-winning bank account that doesnt charge unnecessary fees, gives members early access to their paychecks, and helps them save money… https://t.co/S0Le4ZXkfd https://t.co/fLUifSTgzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Systems Analyst In Ashburn VA, using Customer Service, Project Management SAP and HR management, leading a team of Systems Analysts, provide staff and users with technical support software problems. Lead teams to maintain programs and… https://t.co/3sA6tKJf9t https://t.co/oDNWM5EDJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer III: https://t.co/xz8dnMELdb Services, Inc. – Austin, TX. Software Development Engineer III – Deliver investigation plans &amp; reports, architectural documents, design specifications, software &amp; firmware source code &amp; build… https://t.co/p5h1hDMk5T https://t.co/L7ARKgWtOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Puyallup Tribe Of Indians Job Announcement Opens: May 29, 2018 Closes: July 11, 2018 Job Title: It Support Technician Department: Information Technologies Reports To: It Support Manager Hours: Full-time 40 Hours/week Salary:… https://t.co/w4tQJetNEo https://t.co/lTEUNtZqXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campus Solutions &amp; Human Capital Management Technical Analyst: CAMPUS SOLUTIONS &amp; HUMAN CAPITAL MANAGEMENT TECHNICAL ANALYST Washington State Board for Community and Technical Colleges, 1300 Quince Street SE, Olympia, WA 98504 – Act as a cross pillar… https://t.co/8OmgNSgumh https://t.co/QZKIAC8mJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: As a Project Manager II, you will manage the cost, quality, and schedule of wireless infrastructure projects for new site builds and for modifications to existing facilities. This involves preparing the scope of work, pricing,… https://t.co/mLhmsjyngD https://t.co/uibvUsSMhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law Partner: Washington, DC Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Let me guess. You've been working at a law firm for the past 7+ years, and you're feeling a little burnt out. You're starting to look at new opportunities, but want to identify… https://t.co/RSVpeIr88p https://t.co/6YnETUxEyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Superintendent: Minneapolis, MN Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Residential Superintendent with Construction experience, please read on! Based in Minneapolis, MN, our primary objective is to deliver exceptional… https://t.co/rNExjMmrYD https://t.co/EU01cz1YDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotics Engineer: Robotics Engineer (Murrieta, CA) Draft, analyze &amp; assemble automation systems for FANUC industrial robot equipment. Develop real-time robotic software programs &amp; vision-guided robot applications. Master’s in Mechanical or Electrical… https://t.co/d2VJhqfL4w https://t.co/DyjELicnbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Drive Technical Support At Periscope Data: Periscope Data’s mission is to provide the fastest data visualization product on the market. As a Technical Support Specialist, you will be responsible for empowering the Periscope… https://t.co/Oqxsoqsjqf https://t.co/svvH42I8Ov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications Specialist: IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking applicants for a Communications Specialist. This position will develop written and visual communication strategies for the ITS business unit. Responsibilities also include managing the… https://t.co/UJDoRj3QxC https://t.co/8sjslS8e7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Senior Manager: SOFTWARE Oracle America, Inc. has openings for Software Development Senior Manager positions in Redwood Shores, CA. Job duties include: Manage a team that designs, develops, trouble-shoots and debugs software programs… https://t.co/LmyoqnHeUy https://t.co/NinDxBtlE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: ENGINEERING Sr. Software Engineer (Code: SSE-MYJ) Dvlp &amp; maint sftwr infrastructure for an image-guided robotic surgery frmwrk. MS+3. Mail resume to Hien Nguyen @ Intuitive Surgical, 1020 Kifer Road, Sunnyvale, CA 94086. Ref… https://t.co/oKlG70jgZd https://t.co/7uXYKkhfy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: Developer for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to develop, maintain, and improve our automated functional test, integration test suite, and performance test suite. Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, or a related field… https://t.co/zNvYzppZpP https://t.co/5NjIxgHL39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician/Analyst: Swisher Electric Cooperative, Inc. is (SEC) located in Tulia, Texas, has an opening for the position of IT Support Technician/Analyst.  Swisher Electric is a rural electric utility serving approximately 8,100 meters across… https://t.co/wrOaKHEUHG https://t.co/uYCvCMLUbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Routing QA Engineer: Location: HQ-San Mateo Reports To: Distinguished Engineer Job Description: Routing QA Engineer PRIMARY PAYROLL REPONSIBLITIES: – Work on testing/qualifying functional and performance aspects of Aryaka SD-WAN technology. – Primary… https://t.co/PsAZ1Atf2M https://t.co/WB7JrptBmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Network Technician – TS/SCI required: Contract: I2TS3 Position Title: Lead Technician, Network – Network Administrator (L3) GDIT Job Code: WINW04 Grade: (N12) Location: TBD GENERAL SUMMARY: GDIT is seeking candidates to support the US Army… https://t.co/k3685ZH6WW https://t.co/4B1W8UuGkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Systems Engineering 1:   Job Description – Mgr Systems Engineering 1 (18008016) Mgr Systems Engineering 1 Requisition ID : 18008016 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/MswQKci0CL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: General Summary As a Principal Engineer in the Engineering organization, you design and deliver large, complex portions of the applications and platform that power our multi-tenant SaaS solution. You have a proven record… https://t.co/1w1vOaELbh https://t.co/fYn9ap9mtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC Technician: Summary: Duties include troubleshooting hardware and software in a network environment, configure and support operating systems, resolve personal computer problems, and install, move, and upgrade PC’s. Job Requirements Education… https://t.co/IdfvKechXK https://t.co/NWJT0pYfvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst VI – ACH: Business Systems Analyst VI – ACH Millsboro, DE THE OPPORTUNITY: Facilitates complex technical projects requiring system changes from proposal through post-implementation. Consults with internal application owners to… https://t.co/OlAEyMQhx8 https://t.co/XSAOHyFEKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sales Rep (KC): We are looking for a loyal, motivated individual who wants to make more money and move up on their own. This job includes 401k, benefits and the ability to earn substantial income. Our Project Managers are highly… https://t.co/uZMlK5gIgv https://t.co/cJqGRMYi17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator Senior Eglin AFB: Provide users with technical support in the areas of hardware, software, network, peripheral devices, and end-user/personal mobile devices. Support help desk operations by documenting user issues in a… https://t.co/IDTOETB0qW https://t.co/GMVC2RQPnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TS/SCI Full Stack Developer: OVERVIEW This requirement is in support of a member of the U.S. Intelligence Community focused on the geospatial mission domain. The work environment is very positive and collegial and co-located with the government at the… https://t.co/YzxtHNbCNw https://t.co/KHT0YXvyz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Data Warehouse): Are you passionate about software development, data and analytics? Are you innovative with broad development skills that you keep current? Are you a committed team player able to work with and support others as they… https://t.co/XzKpzb1ofI https://t.co/dEagR43Dek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineers: Engineers: Skyworks Solutions, Inc. seeks multiple Engineers in Irvine, CA: *Packaging Senior Engineer (CA1117MH): Responsible for dvlpmt, qualification &amp; high volume implmtn of new assembly processes &amp; PCB technologies for RF packages.… https://t.co/PDjJOowKdi https://t.co/nrh8J7B2wP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Technician: Overview * Provides technical and end-user support of computer software and related equipment. Responsibilities * Troubleshoot computer and basic telecommunications hardware and software to ensure that issues are investigated and… https://t.co/ZPf4TUDveo https://t.co/Zt9O5e2EU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple School Positions: Standing Rock Community School 2018/2019 School Year Job Announcements The mission statement for Standing Rock Community School: Standing Rock Community School will provide students with opportunities to excel academically,… https://t.co/sjmqybPY4L https://t.co/5exYTwwhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: Overall Responsibility for Quality Assurance Engineer: * Developing and executing comprehensive test plans * Performing test cases to verify functionality, data integrity, security, and overall usability. * Delivering quality… https://t.co/IJFwVw684J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk/HelpDesk Engineer, Entry-Level LA: Are you the first person people call when their computer breaks? Do you find zen-like tranquility in assembling your own high-performance PC rigs? Can you calm a frantic user who just deleted her entire… https://t.co/V7mvWATQZ1 https://t.co/JzDUscvvdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Administrator: Req ID 97291BR Business Title Linux Systems Administrator Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Bethesda Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Networks &amp; Telecommunication Services Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an… https://t.co/wrbwBBN8bw https://t.co/w6Qm9AzJDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USPA Back-End Developer: 1/9/2018 USPA – Back-End Developer Tracking Code 3073-736 Job Description Back-End Developer Ipsos is the global market research leader with over 16,000 employees spread across offices in 88 countries, who help our clients –… https://t.co/Hhu3rdNU9M https://t.co/3PgTvkSogr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watson Corporate Advertising Technical Architect: Watson Corporate Advertising Technical Architect, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Perform full-stack application design, development, deployment, and testing. Work with advertising and marketing team to… https://t.co/PMtHOPeNtI https://t.co/ZXbOr3p3Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Healthcare Technical Analyst: Systems Healthcare Technical Analyst Ref No.: 18-24293 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Job Title Systems Healthcare Technical Analyst Duration of assignment (in Months) 6-12 Months Work Location Philadelphia, PA… https://t.co/lNQTlC6O4Y https://t.co/E3Odntlpfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Data Warehouse and Visualization: Job Description Salary Grade: 508 Job Purpose: Incumbents in this role focus on data warehouse development, implementation and problem solving relates to data, types of data, and relationships among… https://t.co/eYi9vvmL6J https://t.co/vgvOtG8Nl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Ruby Software Engineer: We are looking for our Lead Software Engineer in NYC. If building a real time predictive analytics tool interest you, look no further. We build a predictive analytics tool used by some of the largest brands in publishing… https://t.co/QLe2hTTpdY https://t.co/KXLjwSZ86t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android &amp; iOS Developer: A Cupertino Silicon Valley technology startup, with an ownership group track record of success (previous startup was sold to a tech giant), is looking for a Android &amp; iOS Developer to assist in the development of their media… https://t.co/CkEe7dUsSq https://t.co/kjT38KZAVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Systems Analyst: TYPE: FULL TIME PERMANENT LOCATION: DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES Our client is a leading provider of construction and engineering services As part of the management of company-wide Business Intelligence &amp; Forecasting systems, our client is… https://t.co/UAzYPCWe1P https://t.co/HAvBxue3bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy Civil Construction Area Manager: Tucson, AZ Full-time $85k – $120k Posted Today We are one of southern Arizona’s leading heavy/civil construction companies, and currently we have an opening for an Area Manager of our Sierra Vista location. What You… https://t.co/1aUA9Gpvfp https://t.co/fjj9ztRTNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Analytics Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/27/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/e3dEQhf7r9 https://t.co/QEYmJ9tKKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Engineer (Java/UI, Oracle): Job Description Web Application Engineer (Java/UI, Oracle) (******EH) Position Purpose This position represents that of a senior web application developer on CWTSatoTravel’s E2 Solutions product, an… https://t.co/yZSKRE644Y https://t.co/C7E5cH0Pfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch Communications and IT Operations Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/1/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/xHkDinKBWJ https://t.co/Nd4EAlx0wP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Sr. Software Engineers – multiple technologies. Bachelor + 5 yrs exp. Code “ZSrSE-CA”. 3. Staff Software Design Engineers for software defined radio product line. Master’s + 1 yr exp. recblid uik6bzapbqte2jaqao2dol76vjo6y0 https://t.co/m2Rj3RWd7j https://t.co/LOecWZ4Jho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager-Construction: Construction Professionals, are you ready to take your career to another level with an organization that will have your best interest in mind? Since its inception, Timothy Jon &amp; Associates has matched top talent in the… https://t.co/4OxOJyGOsF https://t.co/pYgmDRoGfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modifications &amp; Sustainment Manager (Mgr 2):   Job Description – Modifications &amp; Sustainment Manager (Mgr 2) (18007366) Modifications &amp; Sustainment Manager (Mgr 2) Requisition ID : 18007366 Location : United States-California-Palmdale US Citizenship… https://t.co/IaGzbysgJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop support Engineer: Desktop support Engineer Ref No.: 18-18602 Location: palo alto, California Hi, This is Shipra from Enterprise Solution Inc. I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Please send your updated resume if… https://t.co/MqnzBn2nKz https://t.co/PSx3Azdk6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Aberdeen, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/90EB36Uk0a https://t.co/Njt09ZzyFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2: EMC CORPORATION (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Software Engineer 2 at its Durham, NC facility to develop software solutions for external clients based on detailed specifications from technology/systems consultants.… https://t.co/ln8cBh8P3A https://t.co/jcqLSkDc8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netsuite Implementor: Netsuite Implementor Base $110,000 to $125 Base plus Bonus Total 8 plus years of experience in Cloud-based accounting solution implementations. * Must have consultant experience and knowledge of end to end NetSuite implementations,… https://t.co/9Y3sIJCwRy https://t.co/Iqery4zX1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Cyberbridge International Inc. d/b/a Creospan Inc seeks a Sr. Java Developer with a bachelor’s degree in engineering, computer science or related field and 5 years of experience in the job offered or as a developer or related… https://t.co/1ds48tBFiZ https://t.co/ci6sAmFpjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Staff Cloud Network Engineer: Sr. Staff Cloud Network Engineer Ref No.: 18-20906 Location: Santa Clara, California Sr. Staff Cloud Network Engineer: Huawei is a leading global information and communications technology (ICT) solutions provider.… https://t.co/vPMgIvPjwp https://t.co/50Zaomin7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Economist: Principal Economist IHS Markit’s Center for Forecasting and Modelling is seeking a Principal Economist with extensive experience in econometric modelling and knowledge of cutting-edge techniques in macroeconometrics and forecasting.… https://t.co/09lt3UZYGl https://t.co/8Xr3TK76gS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Protection Studies (SPS) Project Technical Lead: Job Description System Protection &amp; Studies (SPS) Project Technical Lead System Protection &amp; Studies (SPS) Project Technical Lead (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering,… https://t.co/v0QfRP7MFm https://t.co/F729AielNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer/Architect (.Net, Full Stack, SQL Server, Cloud): Job Description The Alternate Investment Services – Client technology group is acollaborative development team with the goal of delivering a uniform,responsive user experience to… https://t.co/G0HDTaQTYI https://t.co/Rce6nR2Jx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Software Tester: Software Tester We are looking for a motivated software engineer, testing involves the use of access control, cryptography, and security monitoring software. The tester will need to provide status updates to the line supervisor… https://t.co/VVPqTw8N01 https://t.co/6MQk98PJQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer/Administrator: ServiceNow Developer/Administrator in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us… https://t.co/z0H5vQvEaY https://t.co/gVaD14RrMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Administrator: SENIOR SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR SUMMARY The individual in this position will provide analysis, design, implementation and support for Companys Microsoft infrastructure, LAN/WAN and VoIP systems, VMware environment, and DR and… https://t.co/B1OXSdQ7nS https://t.co/SuNLl1K9T3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Construction: Job Description Oversees and coordinates store construction and remodels. Acts as a liaison and helps to implement plant programs including facility repairs and maintenance. Responsibilities – Coordinate multiple store… https://t.co/h8ZUZtqU4O https://t.co/6Kfi0KvhVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Programmer: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed Search – IT Staffing – Our Story –… https://t.co/fr2cXjVInC https://t.co/EspvV75IBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Application Software Engineer (TS/SCI) – DMV SIGN-ON BONUS!!: Cloud Application Software Engineer (TS/SCI) – DMV- $5000 SIGN-ON BONUS!! ================================================================= Req #: ******Location: Suitland, MD USJob… https://t.co/FCKiK9Ug02 https://t.co/yXDgmC4cCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Information Security Officer: Grand County Information Systems Chief Information Security Officer Full time, full benefits position. Minimum rate $83,633. This company is an equal opportunity employer to all, regardless of age, ancestry, color,… https://t.co/ABpwSkC1TL https://t.co/IW6oarjvI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response Director: COMPANY BACKGROUND: Our client is a highly respected security advisory firm specializing in Data Breach Response and Risk Management. With a highly-successful track record of delivering mission critical cybersecurity… https://t.co/inYK0EsQUE https://t.co/QQu6Dagm9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- OpenGL / DirectX Graphics Development: 16636BR Software Engineer- OpenGL / DirectX Graphics Development General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of… https://t.co/LoizJk5BYU https://t.co/U8ZDi5F90i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 420049BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : SmallSats are the future!! The Skyfall program is looking for Software Engineers to participate in full lifecycle software development for this SmallSat… https://t.co/cUstSljmT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Safety Engineer (early – mid career): Req ID : 432877BR_1 Job Code/Title : E5403:System Safety Engineer Sr Job Description : If you are seeking a career with tremendous impact on our Nation's defense, we invite you to learn more about the… https://t.co/mZu4H9jfUX https://t.co/GOxaYrd3Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: We are looking for a Junior Front End Developer responsible for implementing a complete user interface in the form of a mobile and desktop web app, with a focus on performance. You will work in a team with the UX/UI designers and… https://t.co/WyVtxxFbwi https://t.co/OC4clRfkA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Only for: Job Summary Required skills: 1) At least one year of JavaScript experience (i.e., Node.js or Angular). 2) At least one year developing RESTful web services (JavaScript preferred, other languages will be considered). 3)… https://t.co/2z9GhxuceG https://t.co/nCT2rLaGOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Specialist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/24/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective… https://t.co/eSu4l6BLLI https://t.co/DalP94QqZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ReactJS Developer: ReactJS Developer in Washington, District of Columbia, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us… https://t.co/IW30hE4Rny https://t.co/SD5k6x0QRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: ENGINEERING Sr. Software Engineer (Code: SSE-MYJ) Dvlp &amp; maint sftwr infrastructure for an image-guided robotic surgery frmwrk. MS+3. Mail resume to Hien Nguyen @ Intuitive Surgical, 1020 Kifer Road, Sunnyvale, CA 94086. Ref… https://t.co/Ncy6xsOxg9 https://t.co/KL1Lvt3hyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Staff Instructor Manager: Staff Instructor Manager (multiple positions) sought by General Electric Company in San Ramon, CA to provide product tech training to internal, partner &amp; customer audiences. Reqs Bachelor’s deg, or foreign degree… https://t.co/wXGApeoXKa https://t.co/gm6iRZqwGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer: Test Engineer : Google LLC, San Francisco, CA 94126 job # below: Network Test Engineer (Mountain View, CA) Design, develop, modify, &amp;/or test network needed for various Google projects. #1615.24145 Exp Incl: networking background; Python;… https://t.co/eDA86RUAJJ https://t.co/d5BEfXhVzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer: Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Product Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer (Req #8EH1919) Develop &amp; execute product qualification plans. Work on the product release of the tools.… https://t.co/gvixLtM8Ux https://t.co/gYkGrXKg4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0518MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies; Manager, Site Reliability (6597.1170) Oversee a team of… https://t.co/ZyQKrlPwZ4 https://t.co/1marol4hb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Photonic Design Engineer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $85k – $140k Posted Today This role is responsible for design and implementation of advanced Si photonics devices, systems and platform development required to intercept the product development… https://t.co/MRiRHYDySy https://t.co/ltW2VGB2ut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer: Principal Developer-&gt;&gt; Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior… https://t.co/GPHXQaFPqE https://t.co/UtbILLz0oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Salesforce Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Verizon Business Markets (VBM) is a newly created strategic business unit within Operations, to serve the wireline communications and networking technology needs of U.S.-based small and… https://t.co/W5xK2zQRrL https://t.co/8hU1Corq11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Finance Implementation Technical Analyst: PEOPLESOFT FINANCE IMPLEMENTATION TECHNICAL ANALYST: Washington State Board for Community and Technical Colleges, 1300 Quince Street SE, Olympia, WA 98504 – Administer impl and enhanc of fin info… https://t.co/7AQRYXSmEw https://t.co/2Q24YgYmGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING VMware, Inc. has multiple openings at various professional levels in Palo Alto, CA. The following software engineering positions develop and/or execute software, testing and validation procedures, programming and documentation:… https://t.co/2J068mxUdV https://t.co/HMb022ZEqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer/It: COMPUTER/IT Customer Solution Adoption Specialist for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) responsible for ensuring the success of customer adoption of SAP Ariba Supply Chain Collaboration from validation to customer deployment. Bachelor’s degree… https://t.co/LSVzcMI1h3 https://t.co/Lxa5wu5cJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Back End Developer: Hello! We are looking for a Senior Back End Developer to join the team at alecia. As a Senior Back End Developer, your primary focus will be the development of the backend databases and infrastructure supporting our video… https://t.co/T1npCt9Qla https://t.co/J6KU86Ht1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Developer: Ntelicor LLC seeks Sr Software Developer in Ft Worth TX w/Bach’s Deg Comp Sci Engrg or a related field &amp; 5 yrs proven exp w/following duties: utilize object oriented develop tools to analyze, model, design, develop &amp; test software… https://t.co/sUoANDah1l https://t.co/vSR1BWh0R0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Accountant: Senior. Tax Accountant Asian Grocery Chain; Provide tax issues resolution &amp; conduct research inclu. sales &amp; use tax, income tax, bus. property tax credit &amp; exemption. Reqs: Bachelor’s in Acct/Taxation/Bus. Admin, or related, plus 2… https://t.co/iexdlcjxIM https://t.co/nuByVnd4KU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposal Developer: Who We Are and What We Do We believe words shouldnt just make you sound better; they should make you BE better. If you believe words have the power to change organizations and make peoples lives better, read on. As a boutique,… https://t.co/6PxYVD7DSX https://t.co/2zrWRyT6P5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Developer: Greetings from Macropace Technologies !! Hope you have great day. We have an opening for below position with our client UST Global (********************** [******************************************************* ), please find… https://t.co/J7cj1sLkHK https://t.co/qKH1r8lemy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET / C# Developer – 6 – 12 month Contract: TITLE: Senior .NET / C# Developer – must interview face to face Location: Manhattan Beach, CA 90266 Duration: 6 – 12 months Contract IMMEDIATE NEED for Sr. .NET / C# Developer who can join an existing… https://t.co/ORAJ1jphIG https://t.co/q1XHyKeNWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Technical Lead: Mainframe Technical Lead Ref No.: 18-20848 Location: Plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Mainframe Technical Lead with the… https://t.co/YFvR78zkjm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>