<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're gonna compare cannabis and alcohol, skunk is to whiskey what hash is to beer simple as.  #drugslive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @piersmorgan: BOOM! We drew the one team worse than us. Perfect. #monaco #afc #cldraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are the women on #roomtoimprove ever happy, 'I want a sandwich making area' go work in centra then, they've lovely sandwich making areas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right I'm off up to Montrose to protest against Tubridy and De Burgh, I hope Murphy will still be there to take no part in it #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy should give Chris De Burgh just as tough a time as he did to Murphy, because De Burgh music is beyond criminal #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck it I'm signing up for the #TheUndateables Ive got a stutter I think that qualifies me I might even take her to Eastbourne if shes lucky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house? Nah too many people live in houses, it's too mainstream lets buy a storage unit and live in that instead #hipsters #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#JosieCunningham that Josie Cunningham one sounds like Bo Selecta's Mel B.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These lads make the Wealdstone Raider look intelligible #youwantsum #angrywhiteandproud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Matthew on the #TheUndateables I have a stammer, unlike Matthew on the #TheUndateables I don't have a truncheon for a knob 😫😪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @phlaimeaux: Thanks robodudes!!!! Also can you please not bankrupt the country again thx http://t.co/DFliq6jxIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyTate_Vines: Who am I?  https://t.co/R97y2d1lCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sad truth is,in war it's always the innocent that suffer and more often than not it's kids that suffer the pain. #childrenofthegazawar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Derekreynolds83 just seem outraged at a subject, take it from a pro it works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Derekreynolds83 I'm sure you're green with envy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Derekreynolds83 😂😂😂😂 this is the pinnacle of life man, ever since I was a boy I wanted to make it onto to the journal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth always comes out in the end and by god it's coming out tonight. This is truly truly shocking #Collusion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash @br_uk @paddypower haha trust Paddy Power to do that, their marketing team is brilliant to be fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GaryLineker: As predictable as it is depressing. All those FIFA members that voted for Blatter have betrayed the game they are supposed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeludedBrendan: When you consider it could be 6 or 7 nil I'd say 5-0 isn't that bad. 

Stoke is a tough place to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianf1 @Richie_c23 @jocsplash @trevm316 I think it's the welsh rugby captain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robthrpe he uses no head just shoulders it's made specially for men in his predicament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what's worse John Waters arguments for a no vote or his hairstyle, either way I'm voting Yes for equality and fab hair #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going on the piss with Louis Van Gaal has now become a life goal, what a man! Some head on him in the morning I'd say #MUFC #mufcpoty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah the Irish lads on the #nightbus we're a sound bunch of feckers us Irish,talk the hind legs of a donkey so we would. Great craic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Derekreynolds83 as I said once you notice it, it's impossible to un-see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Derekreynolds83 he's his doppelgänger he probably gets bullied like him as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronan Mullen looks like Will Mckenzie from the inbetweeners, can't take him seriously I just keep thinking briefcase wanker #VoteYes #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManUtd: #mufc has reached an agreement with PSV Eindhoven &amp; Memphis Depay for the player's transfer, subject to a medical. http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thelatelateshow the whole No campaign's argument for a no vote. Their argument has more holes than Swiss cheese. http://t.co/cbPrgIg0gA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbs_tricks: Utilising Facebook For Small Businesses http://t.co/84PcJmeSQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbs_tricks: Instagram - A Digital Marketing Tool http://t.co/ho6dVry8bS via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbs_tricks: The Use of Social Media in the Premier League http://t.co/qUFrrWxqGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football and Social Media http://t.co/Aew4UV5L18 via @dbs_tricks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Use of Social Media in the Premier League http://t.co/Aew4UV5L18 via @dbs_tricks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianf1 @LABagnall my expectations are very high, if it's near as good as season 1, it'll be absolutely epic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManUtd: Retweet to vote for Ander Herrera as #mufc's Man of the Match vs Aston Villa. http://t.co/TDNrdDYmeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a chocolate expert! &gt;&gt;&gt; Can You Win All This Chocolate? (via @dailyedge) https://t.co/UksEX7oHny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know the weather is gonna be fierce bad when Gerald Fleming pops into 6.1 for a chat with Dobbo about the weather.  #StormDesmond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FM_SarahP: Louisa from #firstdates is probably my favourite person in the ENTIRE WORLD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran last year Evelyn Cusack this year next year the farmer with the hash leaf hat as the #LateLateToyShow special guest. Good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every bloke today should look at the likes of Billy on  #firstdates and see what a proper bloke is. A proper old school gentleman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 well you're just a horrid horrid individual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash well I hate times a double infinity no quitsies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash no you can't do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash I hate you times a million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash that's only the start of my madness you creep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash no you shut up, YOU JERKOFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash still a lot different from walking home from town]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash no I'm not, I'll get the bus home at least I don't have to look at you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash yeah shut up Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Louisa on #firstdates went for a man instead of 'boys' she'll be fine, she's gorgeous and lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @MatchoftheDave fantastic player when I saw he was in the bench I went on Google to remind myself of how good he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paddypower: He's ready and waiting... https://t.co/vKQfi3AiTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChicagoTownIre: We have #DaraO'Briain Tickets to be won for the 21st November! All you have to do is RT to be in with a chance! http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeludedBrendan: After 3 years of solid improvement the time is right to step down as manager of Liverpool

I've outgrown this club and …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight we'll hear what farmers think of abortion,next week we'll hear what fishermen think of people who are gender fluid #Nonsense #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland is the town bike of capitalism,we're getting screwed by many big corporations because we're cheap and won't complain  #wealthdivide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't even escape Kim Kardashian on a David McWilliams programme,  #wealthdivide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 tap them out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 that's ridiculous in all honesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 yeah cool, I've no idea what campus I'm in yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 yeah Tuesday and Thursday evenings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 yes sir, I have registration next Saturday at 11am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash I'll track him down and then I'll send for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash tap him out Richard he deserves it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @BeWarmers @jocsplash actually you should tap him the fuck out if you ever see him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash and then stand there laughing at the puppy while smoking and flick the butt into the skip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @BeWarmers @jocsplash an all round despicable human being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GaryLineker: If Manchester United get David de Gea to agree a new contract it would be the best signing of the summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Joey7Barton: Switching over to watch the GAA. At least it'll be competitive. FIFA need to re-think these mind-numbingly boring games ag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @D_DeGea: Come back to Manchester after a fantastic week!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeludedBrendan: Retweet if you show great character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wall82Jonathan @UPCIreland @SkyIreland tv3 HD is on Sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulsmithie07 @CelticLiam88 @Lampett88 it's not about where he's from we all know he's from Derry, it's the way Parry implied it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paisleybhoy88 he's probably a sevco fan too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YesStevie2014 ah fuck him. The childish prick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YesStevie2014 it's just a cheap dig at McClean. There's no need for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Parry calling James Mcclean the northern Irishman from Londonderry, wonder if he'll call sterling the Jamaican from Kingston.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kkk are just a bunch of tragic inbred ignorant redneck American hicks with bad hair and teeth.  #insidethekkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianf1 Last 10 minutes of #TrueDetective episode 4 season 2 http://t.co/qOW0xfuzZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManUtd: #mufc is also pleased to announce @SchneiderlinMo4 has joined from Southampton. #WelcomeMorgan http://t.co/SqDQXS35Xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManUtd: #mufc is delighted to announce the signing of @BSchweinsteiger from Bayern Munich on a 3-year contract. #WelcomeBasti http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TSBible: When Man Utd fans see their midfield options... 

Schneiderlin
Schweinsteiger
Depay
Herrera
Di Maria
Fellaini
Mata 

https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeludedBrendan: My audition for the next James Bond went well https://t.co/P7GX7tKppZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @doglab: It takes 3.2sec to retweet and help find them #HFT https://t.co/g35ZdRoEwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a person with a stutter that is the truest reflection I've seen of a person with a stutter onscreen well done to all involved #Stutterer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hack of Jack Chambers hairdo it's nearly as outdated as his views on abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joan Burton is a left as my right foot a puppet for Fine Gael.  #leadersdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 @jocsplash @TSBible haha Suk-young fanni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah there's Enda, I thought he'd gone home. Anyway Claire Byrne is hot that's all I've taken from this debate.  #leadersdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kiss can on the #LateLate won't work, purely because we're so frigid as a nation 'what if my mother sees me shifting on tele' she will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironically they're having tripe in leap year considering leap year is a load of tripe. I wished they'd make a movie on the real Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stoners love election time just because all the leaflets they get through the door are used for  roach paper for the next year #GE16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsJOEdotie: Ed Woodward frantically trying to find that letter from Jose Mourinho #MUFC https://t.co/vrtWIAFOMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who'd of thought they'd be found guilty not the ending I was hoping for, that's not how tv works. #Rebellion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23  as I said I'm man enough to talk like that, I can appreciate a proper woman and not afraid to say it. I can teach you if u want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 I'm man enough to say things like that Richard. My balls are firmly attached to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Gus, you patronising twat, Jo is smoking hot and a very nice person. #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's that yellow shit on the posh kinky birds cheeks? #FirstDates]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>