<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Response To Economy: Advice On Altering Your Message, Product, Brand: To what extent should a com.. http://twurl.nl/mq5lsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Baer: Is Twitter Revolutionizing CRM?: The toll-free number.

The email to tech support. 

The Tweet?.. http://twurl.nl/2rs08s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Baer: Is Twitter Revolutionizing CRM?: The toll-free number.

The email to tech support. 

The Tweet?.. http://twurl.nl/oyatrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Guest Post: What Companies Can Learn from the President: by Len Kendall Depending on how you look a.. http://snipurl.com/fyto5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea Learned: 'Targeting' Women Indeed: Satirical Wisdom: Though Jon Stewart reigns eternal as the satire king.. http://twurl.nl/u860az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leigh Duncan-Durst: Twitter UnMarketing Tip #1: Social Marketers beware. Tapping in to highly vocal, critical, l.. http://twurl.nl/ttriyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: The Benefit Of The Benefit: The statement "Sell the benefit, not the feature" may be found within.. http://twurl.nl/d8v7lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Guest Post: How I Got the Job (Or, Optimizing Opportunities in a Stale Economy): by DJ Francis In t.. http://twurl.nl/d7wdfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: Retail in China: Traditional Marketing 4Ps Still Relevant: In Western countries where internet and .. http://twurl.nl/wc4xzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Guest Post: Me 2.0: by Dan Schawbel Personal branding is about unearthing what is true and unique a.. http://twurl.nl/02ntce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allen Weiss: Google and Twitter: What's In It for You: Since I've written about the business models of social me.. http://twurl.nl/wlz3ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Don't Force It: Roam Before You Pave: I have a story for you...

An architect built a cluster o.. http://twurl.nl/1b1uug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Goren: Let the Top Online Content Come to You: I made a fairly big decision about how I consume online cont.. http://twurl.nl/lijs4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: No Joke: Digital Marketing World Is TODAY: After months of anticipation and planning, the uber-cool.. http://twurl.nl/vwvcqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonathan Kranz: A Modest Proposal: The '5 Tweets' Rule: Last week I wrote a post about social media from the rea.. http://twurl.nl/p1xshh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Road Trip Lessons to Grow Your Brand: It's Spring Break season. Road trip season! Did you ever ta.. http://twurl.nl/hpt134]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis Green: Businesses Will Take Social Media to the Bank: There's lots of buzz around social media, but until .. http://twurl.nl/hu2rc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allen Weiss: The End of Internet Advertising?: I typically visit a number of technology sites to learn about new.. http://twurl.nl/7ygeke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Baer: The Customer Chasm. Are You Creating a Social Media Divide? : I understand that social media is the .. http://twurl.nl/x0siv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthew Grant: Matthew T. Grant, SMexpert (TM), Now Accepting Offers: As many of you know, my long-term relation.. http://twurl.nl/7n7ugt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Denny: What's the Definition of 'WE'?: We watch a commercial of a four-year-old take a digital photograp.. http://twurl.nl/x3rhak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: 10 Things I Hate About You: So MarketingProfs is a virtual company, which means that the 25 or so o.. http://twurl.nl/fr2xc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Mininni: Right-Brained or Left-Brained Branding?: A provocative editorial in Brandweek recently, really got .. http://twurl.nl/p3bv8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael E. Rubin: Is the Social Media Expert Going the Way of the Dodo?: Throughout the last 24 hours, word has .. http://twurl.nl/sf6vi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Len Kendall: Innovation Doesn't Have to be Invention: When it comes to innovation we often get hung-up on creati.. http://twurl.nl/vyujm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Chaney: Social Media Is Good for Something... Like, Selling Tampons: Directly on the heels of the Knowledge.. http://twurl.nl/rhfz54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: A Spoon Full Of Surprise Helps The Marketing Go Down: "The only way to please people who expect i.. http://twurl.nl/6a5uzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Guest Post: Recessional Loyalty -- Strengthening Your Business Through Retention, Repurchase and Re.. http://twurl.nl/tkjw3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Lesser: Give Marketing a Quota?: Should marketing carry a quota on revenue?

The answer is yes accordin.. http://twurl.nl/5rx3pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: What Marketers Can Learn from Walt Disney’s EPCOT Project: Walt Disney’s Experimental Prototype Com.. http://twurl.nl/u4oxcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea Learned: Della Disaster: What Makes A Computer 'For Women'?: Is your laptop colorful and a little smaller.. http://twurl.nl/pmzq7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeanne Bliss: Redesigning the Hospital Gown: Why Focus Groups Fail Customers and Companies: The hospital gown ha.. http://twurl.nl/p1y7ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Chaney: Seven Social Media Mindset Markers: Has your company embraced the social media "mindset"? 

I'm t.. http://twurl.nl/4sjbyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C K: Making Sure Your Brands Don't 'Boob': A business can easily charge more when a person super-sizes their mea.. http://twurl.nl/pwgai7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Woodruff: Are You a 'Connection Collector'?: You've seen them. The links to tiresome posts proclaiming tha.. http://twurl.nl/32m6dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Hearing Your Shouting Doesn't Mean They're Listening: "Shouting is not necessarily about making y.. http://twurl.nl/d2fkpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mack Collier: Q&A with IBM's Sandy Carter: What’s the Recipe for Marketing Success with Social Media?: As social.. http://twurl.nl/st7qgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: China: Implications of an Emerging Middle Class: As China slowly transforms its economy from depend.. http://twurl.nl/nf5nju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C K: What Marketers Can Learn from the Frozen Food Aisle: Frozen food is a gamble if ever there was one. Sometim.. http://twurl.nl/70p4uj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beth Harte: The Value of a Marketer: Frankly, it’s just not a fun time to be a marketer. Those who have a job ar.. http://twurl.nl/h0hls4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Guest Post: How I Got Our Web Site from Page 5 to Page 1 Using 'White-Hat' SEO: by Neil Anuskiewicz.. http://twurl.nl/n3ppoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: 100-Day Report Card: Wednesday marked the 100th day President Obama has been in the White House... http://twurl.nl/t1fham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Mininni: Putting the 'No' in Innovation: There’s been so much talk about the need for true innovation in rec.. http://twurl.nl/pozjj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Need Innovation? Set Course for the 'Dragon Gap': In the early days of navigation, when crafting .. http://twurl.nl/ai7fry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: On Mashable: Inside the Minds of Twitter Users: We know plenty about Twitter’s crazy growth rates a.. http://twurl.nl/tgkkhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: The Great Recession: Things Are Different Now: The global financial crisis of 2008 and beyond has s.. http://twurl.nl/6cy78g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Sharpie Is Staying Loyal to Print While Getting Into Social Media - AdAge.com.. http://twit.ac/xDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Growing Number of Moms Using Social Media - MEDIAWEEK.. http://twit.ac/Yv-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindymarcone ✏✏✏ Turn your text articles into fully animated TALKING videos... FREE to try... http://bit.ly/yNSgx  ✏✏✏]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shaunssimpson I have used this to get targeted followers on twitter - it really helped my profile stand out http://bit.ly/VY8l5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shaunssimpson I have used this to get targeted followers on twitter - it really helped my profile stand out bit.ly/VY8l5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ian_del_Carmen gets my highest honors - his new "Rags to Dot Com Riches" will change the game... http://bit.ly/10tFLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: ABCs of Branding: 8 Branding Lessons Through Michael Jackson Song Titles: This week we lost three.. http://twurl.nl/3jjnhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reportlinker Adds Digital Lifestyles: 2009 Outlook (Q2 09) - MarketWatch.. http://twit.ac/Evl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beth Harte: Community Matters : When you joined MarketingProfs did you ever consider yourself to be part of a co.. http://twurl.nl/ljrqu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike O'Toole: Marketers: More Hockey, Less Figure Skating: I first heard the hockey/figure skating analogy from .. http://twurl.nl/qypgmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Len Kendall: Give/Take Ratio: There are countless conversations happening online. We’re beyond the point of bran.. http://twurl.nl/ch71iz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Mininni: Getting Back to Leadership Wins Back the Trust: Nothing gets your attention like a catchy title. A .. http://twurl.nl/a8ddvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[FREE] 15 day Free Trial to The Video Membership - over 400 internet marketing training videos... http://scrnch.me/tvmnew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the best twitter advice I have ever seen for getting more followers and building a relationship with them... http://scrnch.me/ttm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely LOVE these free twitter tools... http://scrnch.me/lovethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$67 for $1000 lead software - Instant Lead Magnet - http://scrnch.me/8654as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New lead software from Calvin Woon http://scrnch.me/8654as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: There Is No Such Thing as 'Being Innovative': If you were to put a few talented musicians or skil.. http://twurl.nl/8du2wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Ivey: Why (Digital) Small Talk Matters. Really. : This week I came across two articles that helped clarify .. http://twurl.nl/z54ab5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christine Whittemore: Creating Community Through Relevant Local Information: How do you learn about local news? Yo.. http://snipurl.com/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: Chinese Brands Are Coming: Chinese brands have come a long way since the days of Mao where coats an.. http://twurl.nl/jr2x6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Mininni: How Much Power Does Brand Equity Really Have?: Harris Interactive’s latest EquiTrend study bears ou.. http://twurl.nl/vt81nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Williams: Eliminate Contradictions and Enhance Your Brand: The meal was delicious, but the service was slow.. http://twurl.nl/fmjq6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Handley: Stephen Berlin Johnson Talks About Twitter: 'An enormous opportunity...': Those of you who attended.. http://twurl.nl/y48eqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephanie Miller: Email and Social Marketing: True Love Always?: Social marketing gives us that giddy combinatio.. http://twurl.nl/7qar6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine Fogel: Are Marketers Ready for the End of Globalization and New Reality of Localization?: Economist Jeff .. http://twurl.nl/wnkrpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Woodruff: Getting Started with Social Networking: It can be a bewildering task for those just getting star.. http://twurl.nl/5set5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erik Bratt: Got 2 Minutes? Take Our Short Social Media Measurement & Monitoring Survey: How important is social .. http://twurl.nl/3yadx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Ivey: The Seven Habits of the 'Just Good Enough' Marketer : Or: Breaking the Curse of the Corporate Perfect.. http://twurl.nl/qjoxdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Woodruff: More is Better. Or Not.: The industry I work most closely with, pharmaceuticals, is being forced.. http://twurl.nl/1hq1l3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: Perishing for Lack of Vision: Marketing executives should have a pulse on shifting consumer prefere.. http://twurl.nl/srh5f1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetRiches Used This To Make Over $5,000 A Month With Just One Tweet! http://tweetriches.com/?e={userid} Please ReTweet This!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mashable Why Teens Don’t Tweet http://bit.ly/FFGzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a wonderful day! We are the cupis of great things for social media - @immasterminds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my twitter account fixed! Looking forward to tweeting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea Learned: Chipotle's Hot Spot: The Vulnerability of Authenticity: The Chipotle restaurant chain just annou.. http://twurl.nl/uibd6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verizon Gives Social Media a TV Spot - TechNewsWorld.. http://twit.ac/tGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Ways to Use Social Media for #FindingTheGood - Mashable.. http://twit.ac/d7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @esapps new FREE resource: How to Attract Anything You Want In Life! http://scrnch.me/attract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media -- getting the word out quickly and sometimes accurately! - Westword.. http://twit.ac/pem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @esapps new FREE resource: How to Attract Anything You Want In Life! http://scrnch.me/attract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Mininni: Coca-Cola's New PlantBottle™: As the principal of a design firm with package design as a core compe.. http://twurl.nl/uoqnf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Len Kendall: 'A company’s corporate homepage is Google.com.': The title of this post is a quote by Dell’s VP of .. http://twurl.nl/qshgrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C K: Sheeple: Everything Old is New (Media) Again.: Seems I’ve spent the past week a split personality. On the o.. http://twurl.nl/8at8oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allen Weiss: The Meaning of Numbers: Does an 'Authority Index' Equal Authority?: Economists and other people who.. http://twurl.nl/3tkm2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacob Morgan: Social Media Translated into the Real World: There is clearly a lot of concern over companies ente.. http://twurl.nl/vh8qwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schedule and send tweets even when you're not in front of your computer.  http://twitRobot.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeanne Bliss: Chips For Humanity: How Frito-Lay Earns Market Share : I am intrigued by Frito-Lay. Having not eat.. http://twurl.nl/r3m3gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&quot;Hire Me&quot; Nation: Using the Web &amp; social media to get a job - Baltimore Sun.. http://twit.ac/aKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DiamondSharp Bumper Sticker: "I'm one bad relationship away from owning 30 cats"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businesspeople learn how to best use social media - Spartanburg Herald Journal.. http://twit.ac/-Ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Barsch: When Strategic Planning Gets Locked in the Basement: Strategic planning helps marketers answer what.. http://twurl.nl/q8uwwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media&#39;s impact: Your mistakes are public -- and they live ... - ATWOnline.. http://twit.ac/zYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booz Allen Hamilton&#39;s Social Media Adventure - CIO Insight.. http://twit.ac/fhR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>