<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Natalie, just be quiet and let GOD show you how.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May we pray for our children and never stop praying for them. Speak love over their lives. Speak greatness over their lives. Speak never-ending hope over their… https://t.co/E6xjzaybRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She lives to empower the world (especially the young generation).  She is an author x 2 and she is a real estate hustler. She shall teach the young people to… https://t.co/CtOFnvLXWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are destined for greatness by way of Gods legacy we can never lose sight of that. We are chosen, they are chosen! EY365 https://t.co/Fqe5uXxTX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people let GOD formulate your legacy ....it’s the best life you could ever live! #EY365 https://t.co/1SzOQDWB61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I can save them from the MANY mistakes I made...they are truly worth all the effort and challenges that “may” come EY365. https://t.co/RebV8O6hYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know the young people don’t always listen to us but that doesn’t mean we stop adding value to their lives #EY365. https://t.co/MJJAJPR4aE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our young people to say “NO” it is a complete sentence and one of the best words to speak depending upon circumstances....#EY365 https://t.co/nGMbIjbS8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last thing don’t EVER STOP PRAYING for our children/teens speak LIFE over them. #EY365 https://t.co/79b4IEoBAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has become the new love of my life! Yes, I see their faces. Yes, I see their parents smiling (and crying). A loving power placed in them! We must guide… https://t.co/2ateI6hAVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, they must have goals, dreams and a plan but it can all be coupled with LEGACY - the scholars will learn the importance of living their legacy!! #EY365 https://t.co/cRGd6axAJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pillars: self-love,… https://t.co/TuRKaovAlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life work. They… https://t.co/kaLahNPfiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people I shall… https://t.co/qsJnfDca7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people use… https://t.co/WtxvT2BjIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams, goals and… https://t.co/zQGQfImFgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d tell young… https://t.co/vonePpfPB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m more excited by… https://t.co/zOX3qPMEev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Live a life you can be proud of. https://t.co/yirSEU31eK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She has a few… https://t.co/OJrJogWajT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living to empower… https://t.co/P5XTnoGCSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young People! You cannot walk in self-hate - it will destroy your mental life and your physical life.  I had a parent mention this to me......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young People! EY365 shall teach you how to serve in your household - that is your responsibility. https://t.co/CCaDR1wyMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people! What is your life work about: GOD and GOD's people. https://t.co/iOfqjA0nK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be my summer for summer writing books 3, 4 and 5 coming....she's so excited about this life she gets to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 4th book - Letters to my Children - will illustrate all my downs and the lessons from within...stay tuned! https://t.co/TV5D8EgOeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The young people (that don't know about it) will learn about the rule of 72 - compound interest will compound their investments. https://t.co/GJqLlhuaWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot help but talk about GOD - so yes young people we will talk about GOD. https://t.co/istc63dju7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people, don't worry about what people think of you - if you care they will always control you! https://t.co/WAd4mzDNA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter has become somewhat of a heart journal for me - I encourage you all to start a gratitude journal (if you haven't) it is life changing! https://t.co/01AsEfUvUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see EY365 growing bigger and bigger through the years....I have much to learn and much to do - and the work shall never end - I shall do this until I DIE. https://t.co/iiNbHOoSMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do know about my other hustles? Books and Buildings...check me out at: https://t.co/utyq8vBulp - I will show the young people what I have done to have other income streams $$$$$$$ - https://t.co/fIEsmHy6R3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the business owners that will come and speak with the young people. https://t.co/Ee9xeGYWeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[December 9, 2021 will be such an epic day......I'm preparing now for that day! https://t.co/SI6KiPAAib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are here to change the world - the question is - how will you change your world? https://t.co/8c6RyrzUCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a vision + GOD's help + the right people around you - WE can do anything! https://t.co/StKrK99efc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its important we are real with our young people - we must teach them through our mistakes as much as our right actions! https://t.co/9C1iT6CftL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EY365 teaches the young people to use love, respect and honor to say what they need to say and do what they need to do! I believe kindness and love are the best ways to change the world. https://t.co/NH4o86e03v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD,
Thank you for waking me up to see another day of life. Thank you for my relationship with you, myself, my family/friends and my legacy. AMEN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must talk to our young people about VISION and DREAMS. Why? It allows them to map out a life-plan with GOD. https://t.co/wLGSE0yDUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude is a great attitude.....we must talk to your youngsters about what they are grateful for and why....#carconversations https://t.co/JmViDyTsBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot explain the passion I have for youngsters - I just know that I've had this passion many many years and it won't leave my soul..... https://t.co/LGaEnN6QJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It summer time - its time for our young people to read more - leaders are readers! We must motivate and encourage our youngsters to read! https://t.co/CN8lEWWwho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its summer time - teach your children how to make $100 per week -- while serving someone else..... https://t.co/I1MSSFKd2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We touch the parents using the KIDS....... https://t.co/iKjiSaH19J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have already imagined all this will become...and don't even know all that GOD will do in the process (all smiles)...... https://t.co/BxWkvaxR4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people I'm so proud of what you will become #collaborationsmatter https://t.co/UhShajaoii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you GOD - I can come to you for perspective because I'm often not on point in my thought process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our children to start a business young...make their own money...doing what they love while serving their community. https://t.co/bcSr3pzKdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People, 
Don't dream - dream BIG. https://t.co/ymXo1lvcZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylewis: discipline is choosing what u want most over what you want now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Ignore the fear and push on. https://t.co/V6Y2xKwsuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
I'm into a few things - and I'm going to teach you to do the same.
Check me out at: https://t.co/utyq8vBulp https://t.co/nzaV4Lvf7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Don't strive to be the best - be the first to ever do it! https://t.co/TTycfdJyJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Everyone can serve someone, somehow each and every day! https://t.co/OUjAg3eZoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People, 
Give your best to the world - and the best will be returned to you..... https://t.co/mCXsda7E9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why be a copy - when you were born to be an original.
Be unique. Be different. Be like no other! https://t.co/umYMtwtcD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephlbryan: Please share https://t.co/9hRLUusuNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Go to college. Learn a trade. Have your own hustle! https://t.co/es3HOOGheN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must never give up on our children - they are our future and they must know and realize their future. https://t.co/QnXzBEye4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
As I work on my curriculum I realize - the lessons that matured me the most are the ones I want to teach to you....... https://t.co/jwLRMoe3mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Great leaders - are readers.....read all the time. https://t.co/PgWCTen4uE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to join forces and collaborate to do what has never been done for our at-risk urban youth...EY365 Explosion https://t.co/nrvnljYi3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Gratitude will change your ATTITUDE. https://t.co/BkT753Vfte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Go to sleep GRATEFUL. Then, wake up GRATEFUL. https://t.co/9Mc3OtLJdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question to parents: What is one thing young people need to understand about life? e-mail me at: empoweredyouth365@gmail.com https://t.co/dpeIyIR5h8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question: what must we teach our young people today? E-mail me at: empoweredyouth365@gmail.com https://t.co/brbqfhMra9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
No it won't be easy - but it will be worth it!! https://t.co/lb8AGKmInk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Don't ask for much, if you are giving so little.  Learn (once age appropriate) to make your own way.  You can own a business while in high school or college! https://t.co/vNNTrRl07W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Your parent is your parent - they are not your friend.
They are preparing you for life as best they know how..... https://t.co/KkhJ4npcbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people chase $$ - I chase young people. https://t.co/nBDLQZKlYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Love others even when they don't love you! Respect others even when they don't respect you! Forgive others even when they don't forgive you! https://t.co/LMWnkBl5lE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Use your gift to serve the world - and you will be enriched in ways you have never imagined. https://t.co/nbUYhK7qtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I empower the kids through the parents - I empower the parents through the kids. https://t.co/Zy3N3TidJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People,
Find someone that is doing what you want to do - serve them (as an unpaid volunteer) - you will learn things $$$ cannot buy..... https://t.co/cT60dQKAt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Young People, 
Your dreams will come true - if you do the work. https://t.co/2dt8mObIkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Children/Teens:
Never stop dreaming! Never stop believing! You can do anything! https://t.co/CrG8UddBin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids are sponges so we must soak them up with good, life-changing, believing power. https://t.co/rJff61i3Gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No dream is easy - but they are so worth it! I know in my bone marrow/my spirit/my heart that GOD gave me a gift to touch the lives of young people..... https://t.co/DaSpIcMmfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its called EY365 because they will obtain daily does of wisdom and prayer to empower them to believe and never stop believing. https://t.co/VaUI33JsG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should teach our children through example and through our mistakes...... https://t.co/q5M1gjKOqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD,

I'm not asking for anything - simply thanking you for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the best way to get out of a slump - remember all that GOD has done for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world becomes better - as we become better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our children that they are brilliant and can do ANYTHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things would get better with Love + the Golden Rule.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you know your purpose - you know fulfillment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD,
I want to do the right thing - in appreciation of all the good things you have done for me and I'm so eternally grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD,
Give me a heart that treasures you always - a mouth that only speaks your words - and feet that move in the direction of your will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleHeadBigH: We either win or we learn. https://t.co/mk8Tf8V0x2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Fight the good fight. https://t.co/LxfeCSfneZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: If you believe enough in the process SUCCESS will come to you. You just have to be willing to see it through to the END.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to ask for you what you want - you just might get it.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: Be strong https://t.co/VpKmA147y2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EntreLeadership: Throw away the titles and get more concerned about impacting others. https://t.co/k5TF6RL29b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: 1) Work your hardest.
2) Dream your biggest.
3) Be your greatest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live for the kids......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you complaining about? 
What are you grateful for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will teach the EY365 from my mistakes and the mistakes of others - in this way - they will be saved the heartache (if they are willing to listen)..... https://t.co/RZB3dFRPSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let GOD lead the way - you are in for a fascinating ride of zero regrets.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>