<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brazilian baroness hears a cat's meow that sounds like your father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A YouTube star searches for a tiny clockwork device which allows her to become an iceberg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cobra is destroying the Paris Métro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kangaroo tail hovers above a lighthouse. Then a Galapagos tortoise says: "That kangaroo tail belongs to me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty children meet once a year in a jade opera house to decide the fate of the universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A watchmaker is killing philosophy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Baghdad there is a rollercoaster which enjoys playing a game of cards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Ukrainian screenwriter discovers a cypress tree made of heterosexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A marble woolly mammoth is sleeping in a Moroccan garden. An ambassador searches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Palestinian entrepreneur talks to stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prince discovers that magic does not exist, and is secretly pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher discovers a forgotten book of Plato on the subject of brains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You suddenly realise that you are made of sapphires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man regurgitates social anxiety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A schoolteacher whistles a song. In that time, he lives a whole other life as a Catalan literary critic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An opera singer looks at a tarot card and sees her kitten in the background.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman dedicates her life to making a list of every guilty pleasure that has taken place in Manchester.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astrologer in Constantinople fantasises about kissing abstract art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fashion stylist places a curse on a sultan. It makes him think he is a plastic flower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flamingo whispers to a carpenter: "I wish I was a coral reef."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duke sees a flock of birds in the shape of a rollercoaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 16-year-old countess finds out that her father is her grandfather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cannabis plant is reading Victor Hugo's Les Misérables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cloud is sniffing amyl nitrite in a garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clown is riding a bicycle from Chicago to 5000 BC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On New Year's Eve a message is written in the sky in kites. It reads: "It will never work."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will dream of a Gummi bear tonight. Just before you wake up, the Gummi bear will have a passionate love affair with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Wisconsin there is a gigantic merry-go-round. An emperor is inside it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Prussian archangel marries Halley's Comet. They have one child: A daughter who is made of clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A purple pebble is used by a mermaid to live to the age of 1,400.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bolivian witch is trying to destroy World of Warcraft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 15-year-old princess wakes at midnight every night to have sexual intercourse with gluten intolerance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anus is flying economy class to Venice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At midnight Mongolia is flooded with maple syrup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A video game designer realises that Uber is controlling society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A witch eats a circus tent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mathematician in Montréal has substituted time with a church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dancer falls into a lake filled with sunscreen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astronaut is dancing in a nightclub. Suddenly, the nightclub turns into a mansion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Liverpool there is a famous ballet company of dancing sharks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gramophone is magic. It causes anyone who sees it to become a schoolteacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A maharajah finds a shard of glass which allows him to communicate with ostriches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dublin there is a shopping mall which used to be a French sheik.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poached egg grows and grows until it is the size of London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By imagining a mirror, a 14-year-old vice president is able to kill a sailor in Mumbai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bavarian quantum physicist spends his whole life writing an impossibly complex theory of authoritarianism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astronomer has a terrible migraine. She finds out that there is a giant clam inside her frontal lobe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Malaysian therapist provides a counselling service for lonely kittens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drunk literary critic falls in love with Homer's Odyssey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old lady smokes a cigarette in a high school. She is thinking about sandwiches. A succubus is singing Cher's "Believe" behind her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A book collector discovers that chess does not exist, and is relieved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shaman in Rome is proposing marriage to magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorceress owns a willow pattern plate which depicts every laugh by a math teacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up in a city which looks like San Francisco, but everything is upside down. Albatrosses begin raining from the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Albanian book of poetry describes a method of having sexual intercourse that enables you to control the Fourth of July.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grandfather sees a bluebird with a Lucian Freud painting painted on its wings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wasp suddenly appears beside you. Then quicksand begins falling from the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 4th century BC Mesopotamian prophecy that you will be swallowed by a Turkish delight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the night of the full moon all the world's hippopotamuses are replaced by dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A piglet and a prince are fighting over custody of their children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A politician hears of a city run by giant squids, and despatches his bodyguard to torture them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A realtor falls in love with a glass star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A game show host dances with the universe inside a silver yurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A whodunit in which the killer turns out to be a paperweight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knives and peppermints. That is all I have to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hospital in the Forbidden City is made of New Year's Eve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pastry chef recites the Lord's Prayer. In that time, she lives a whole other life as a sentient waterfall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An irritable scholar spends 41 years writing a poem about English literature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Panamanian battle cruiser sails across an ocean of the bourgeoisie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are convicted of the crime of killing a yurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A record producer can move supermarkets with her mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the night of the full moon all the clocks stop, and a centaur appears in the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your father tells you that you are actually an octopus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Garden of Eden is an office manager who has 556 ankles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shopkeeper is eating pomegranates inside an academic conference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rose levitates over Prague. It is controlled by a tiger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tulip that can create the British Raj grows in an Armenian garden. A novelist writes a manuscript about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight mermaids are setting out on a long journey. Their aim is to defeat the werewolf terrorizing Colorado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A child saves up his money in order to buy the class struggle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A film director contracts a disease that turns him into a map of Cairo. Then a tiger eats him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tired king constructs a crypt that is filled with queer theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ocean whispers to a sous chef: "I feel so embittered."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little boy appears and hands you a vampire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A princess switches bodies with a mosquito.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Byzantine prince appears on the deck of the Titanic. He has a message to deliver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A travel agent owns a lost book of Kant on the subject of libraries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Glasgow there is a gondola which is reading a newspaper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congressman is standing perfectly still in a bolt of lightning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this mystery: A high school teacher is found dead in a mansion. Beside him is a flower and a banana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college professor falls into a pond filled with vodka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Belgian duchess makes a speech about pyramids that lasts for 244 million years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rabbit is walking from Vermont to a diamond forest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teenager is reading a book about Alzheimer's disease. Suddenly, the book turns into a math teacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sumerian pirate has a sixth sense: She can feel the presence of ravens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A courageous rabbi falls in love with the stock exchange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A court jester is hunting a huge cabbage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every archaeologist in the universe is painting a picture of juniper trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a topaz in California that feels depressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this riddle: Why is an apple like an ostrich feather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cynical queen sits on a marble lake.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>