<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager -IT: 1 Year Contract We are actively seeking an IT Technical Project Manager. The IT Technical Project Manager will be responsible for planning and managing company resources to develop and launch innovative technological solutions. This… https://t.co/UfOzTpXiVm https://t.co/7VUexVhCWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager: Careers that Change Lives * Are you a passionate, dedicated and a motivated Project Manager looking for a new challenge? The goal of the Senior Project Manager is to advance the performance of all MITG/RTG Americas’ clinical, sales,… https://t.co/Po2ULP2bxI https://t.co/DxC3TQ8CrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/3fsUTn1cIu https://t.co/1lOXdckcUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Summit Technologies, Inc. has several full-time positions for Sr. Application Architects with Life Insurance, Annuities and Retirement work experience. You will be part of a team responsible for designing and developing… https://t.co/v2Cjv7YUwX https://t.co/rjakc9Mj5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Summit Technologies, Inc. has an opportunity for a full-time IT Project Manager with Banking and/or Finance background.Thesuccessful candidate will be part of our clients PMO providing project management of various projects.This… https://t.co/zySjLFLNEJ https://t.co/pis6fOu2d5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager: Original Posting Date 26-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization School of Management – Executive Programs STARS Requisition number 48839BR University Job Title Coordinator 4, Prog Mgr Corp Ed Posting Position Title Senior Program… https://t.co/PmBojKH61a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Quality Assurance Engineer: Hologic, Inc. is a leading developer, manufacturer and supplier of premium molecular diagnostic products and services that are used to diagnose human diseases, screen donated human blood and to aid in biomedical… https://t.co/asfnRnaSfW https://t.co/7NQ0W4HBX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Developer: Reports to: Director, Information Systems ChimeData, at Connecticut Hospital Association (CHA), offers data analytic services including innovative information products and solutions. These services help member hospitals gauge their… https://t.co/j6cBDk4GHj https://t.co/ewvob6svAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer -Accuity-Lakeville: NRS, Lakeville, CT – Software Engineer/Web Developer National Regulatory Services (NRS), A division of Reed Business Information, is a leading provider of information, technology and supporting services to the… https://t.co/Qh4IizkWtN https://t.co/7m97Nr414S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Site Reliability Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors,… https://t.co/23lfqPLWBN https://t.co/Pw8YW3tfPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Yale Posting Status CLOSED TO FURTHER APPLICATIONS Original Posting Date 20-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization ITS Support Center – Help Desk STARS Requisition number 48662BR University Job Title IT Support Technician 1 Posting… https://t.co/WdGoDAOEEZ https://t.co/Ivf8rEVfG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience Design Lead (UX), Design System Team: Job posting details. Experience Design Lead (UX), Design System Team The Travelers Companies, Inc. Hartford, CT United States Company Information Solid reputation, passionate people and endless… https://t.co/poCJFITGsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: Position: Support Analyst Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 645 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for a Support Analyst; an integral member of the IT-Applications team in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: – Robust total rewards program… https://t.co/kHvNL2bvdm https://t.co/atBdgmXakd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application System Specialist: Original Posting Date 09-Oct-2017 Supervisory Organization Pathology – Research STARS Requisition number 46446BR University Job Title Applications Systems Specialist Posting Position Title Application System Specialist… https://t.co/lWfjbxGrQI https://t.co/Jk5CZPRinH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services: JOB REQUISITION New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services LOCATION CT NEW HAVEN JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within RHI, combining the best of… https://t.co/7MnWZOn9JD https://t.co/d5KyHGuw8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Associate, Data Programmer/Pre-Doc Intern: Original Posting Date 05-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization School of Management – OB STARS Requisition number 48357BR University Job Title Intern, SOM Posting Position Title Research Associate, Data… https://t.co/uFLendg5VT https://t.co/dh6oYSnCgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Job Title :?Software &amp; Computer EngineerLocation :?Farmington, CTDuration :?9 -12 months contractcandidates must be US Citizens or Green Card holder.?Job Responsibilities:?Evaluate communications and connectivity… https://t.co/finLIurRtT https://t.co/HNBgIqKexb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/nQV4LIgXFe https://t.co/sCYmBHkqEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Original Posting Date 29-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization YSM Cores – YCCI STARS Requisition number 48929BR University Job Title Manager 3 Posting Position Title Senior Project Manager Bargaining Unit None – Not included in the… https://t.co/wv1BcN4lDs https://t.co/6pNAdv4URI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineering Project Manager: NPI: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 2018-03-15 Functional area Manufacturing Background Others – Technical Reference US03508 Introduction ASML brings together… https://t.co/Be2Fx7sk87 https://t.co/3ld4z1GCf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysLSADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/duvVr0wosG https://t.co/uJv6HMkzR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 29888BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Insurance Skillset Data Warehouse Testing , ETL Testing Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location… https://t.co/f1zcF2EA5k https://t.co/nqLE7cKfQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager: Careers that Change Lives * Are you a passionate, dedicated and a motivated Project Manager looking for a new challenge? The goal of the Senior Project Manager is to advance the performance of all MITG/RTG Americas’ clinical, sales,… https://t.co/sKU972zAk8 https://t.co/gyDm5dzXjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Senior Specialist: Cigna Information Management and Analytics (CIMA) offers solutions that provide actionable insights to internal and external business partners and customers to reduce health costs, improve outcomes, and measure… https://t.co/cWvSyNbZwE https://t.co/4jL71dWNUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Application Java Developer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/4PwUJAo3bS https://t.co/Ye3FiIR8NU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Java Architect with Akka Play Framework | Stamford, CT | 6+ months: Title: Java Architect w/ Play Akka Framework Location: Stamford, CT Duration: 6+ Months Years of experience: 10+ years Requirements Java Architect with recent years of experience in… https://t.co/eEx26tZ4am https://t.co/j1xkc3DUzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk / Service Desk Specialist (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/os7k0gkoyC https://t.co/Fh11SSqajD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Analyst: Yale Posting Status CLOSED TO FURTHER APPLICATIONS Original Posting Date 16-Feb-2018 Supervisory Organization Campus Community Technologies – Academic Administration STARS Requisition number 48166BR University Job Title Senior… https://t.co/XA0VFHULWz https://t.co/w7l4iMqkcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Network Engineer: CISCO NETWORK ENGINEER THAT HAS STRONG KNOWLEDGE OF BGP, EIGRP, OR MPLS. A Network Engineer who has experience working with Cisco Routers and Switches. Located in Norwalk, CT, this technology company is looking to hire a talented… https://t.co/bmPC24XYgV https://t.co/CSZUPCQomg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Scientist-Risk Segmentation: The Cigna Information Management &amp; Analytics (CIMA) unit is searching for an energetic and driven data scientist to bring best in class analytics to the Underwriting and Actuarial organizations. The Data Scientist… https://t.co/MClGZ1NpWe https://t.co/ZNlbPgO95B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer/Engineer: Functional Area: IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): Up to 25% Relocation Provided: No American General Life Insurance Company Senior Software Developer/Engineer ReactJS, Polymer, JavaScript,… https://t.co/SNOnf0Ykvz https://t.co/4rGjxq1TuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Scala: We are looking for a versatile, battle-hardened back-end Scala software developer to join our growing team. Here you will focus on building and maintaining enterprise web-based applications. Though we primarily use Play… https://t.co/8zll7SktMV https://t.co/EZUelVIOQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: This is a great opportunity to join a dedicated team of professionals. If you have expertise in ECM than this position is for you. * Assist in development of project architecture, prototypes and proof of concepts. * Accountable for… https://t.co/MgMeSHbONc https://t.co/pjZYP4eaeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Original Posting Date 26-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization Internal Medicine – Cardiology STARS Requisition number 48687BR University Job Title Research Associate 3, HSS Posting Position Title Project Manager Bargaining Unit None – Not… https://t.co/nirSNyrKba https://t.co/IqPuytdhmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys MSWTPU Technology Lead – US SharePoint Application Migration – Berlin, CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for… https://t.co/B0OKeGUpgv https://t.co/s6IzuaGuNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Development Manager, CTO: Original Posting Date 14-Nov-2017 Supervisory Organization Comprehensive Cancer Center – Clinical Trial Operations STARS Requisition number 46813BR University Job Title Training &amp; Development Mgr Clinical Trials Office… https://t.co/nCv5cEabcJ https://t.co/8DpEg355rA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Integration Architect: Responsibilities and Duties: * This position will be a member of the development team who will design, develop, and blog about integrations between client and monitoring products, ticketing systems, automation systems and… https://t.co/A0XmncRbfw https://t.co/idvRs01Bsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: This position is responsible for continuous improvement, implementing, testing and ongoing support of IT NAM infrastructure Services for North America. This includes Network, UC and Workplace, Site Infrastructure, Security and manage… https://t.co/ApwMMvRyPK https://t.co/xLT7YJwdar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grains and Oilseeds Data Analyst: The purpose of this role is to support the global oilseeds and grains research teams to provide timely information and accurate estimates of US and Global supply and demand estimates to the traders. Specifically, it aims… https://t.co/RB6HIHa2V0 https://t.co/jgm52BRlUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Systems Administrator: Careers Center | Junior Systems Administrator Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/o3DtMqyXiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- HCADM Technology Lead – US .Net/SQL – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/eSEqgRWBle https://t.co/SDl0Maba3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Solution Architect: The selected Cisco Solution Architect will be covering Hartford, CT and Danbury, CT so ideally candidates will be somewhat commutable to either location. They won’t be required to go into the office much but they will have to… https://t.co/ZyLKfKXv2S https://t.co/ObXYXZRQlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Project Manager – NPI: Henkel Beauty Care holds leading market positions worldwide and its brand-name product business is continuously expanding. In this fastmoving sector, success depends on constant innovation and high-quality products.… https://t.co/2ozA32TdkO https://t.co/IqjWCKUEtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Mid Level Web Application Java Developer: – Mid Level Web Application Java Developer Job Locations US-CT-Greenwich ID 1741 Department Software Development Company Overview Interactive Brokers LLC, a subsidiary of Interactive Brokers Group, Inc.… https://t.co/l1yGgRDbxU https://t.co/PBdgeck7dS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience (2930): OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who… https://t.co/o7Fjudv9hX https://t.co/oLyjZ6UokK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laboratory Relocation Project Manager: Date Posted: 30/Mar/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: Laboratory Relocation Project Manager Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science,… https://t.co/o8X7ijy99m https://t.co/r8S9a894ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer: TITLE: Associate Developer Global Reinsurance DEPARTMENT: Information Technology LOCATION: Stamford, CT KEY OBJECTIVES With guidance set forth by the IT architect and other senior IT resources, the primary objective is to develop and… https://t.co/hsH0nXQVry https://t.co/CDVCPDIzDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Hardware Engineer: Stratford Solutions is assisting their client with finding aComputer Hardware Engineerto add to their team located in Stamford, CT. This is a full-time, direct hire, W2 position with our client; cannot accept 3rd party… https://t.co/y7cVfwdcsD https://t.co/FQQyBASThP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Engineer: Full Stack Web Engineer – What We Do Featured EPAM Acquires Continuum, Expanding Global Innovation, Design and Physical Product Development Capabilities Press Release – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do… https://t.co/aoi0xzzxi3 https://t.co/DxBXmzuxEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Scholarship Project Manager: Original Posting Date 14-Feb-2018 Supervisory Organization Library – Digital Scholarship STARS Requisition number 48124BR University Job Title Project Manager, Digital Scholarship Posting Position Title Digital… https://t.co/HvtvP3ZuO5 https://t.co/fjwup15O08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Software Engineer: Summit Technologies is looking for a Senior Cloud Software Engineer. The ideal candidate should have experience with hands-on design, development and engineering positions. Candidates should also have experience working with… https://t.co/eEnNpIBIy2 https://t.co/vXryTknB9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/QEcFDXzkYl https://t.co/9uZKB4LmHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Summit Technologies has an available position for a Software Developer. This is an onsite position located in Farmington, CT. JOB SUMMARY: This is a senior level hands-on development position, working with message based integrations,… https://t.co/4g9a9LZGbs https://t.co/JLztszRd5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports users the usage of business… https://t.co/7R2s1U8VW1 https://t.co/wXacHXDcY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/vj6PQRePUT 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/B4LyCeSqeo https://t.co/4Lrf8V4TTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/e3d509pIAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Java Developer Web API: – Java Developer Web API Job Locations US-CT-Greenwich ID 1652 Department Software Development Company Overview IBG LLC, a subsidiary of Interactive Brokers Group, Inc. (NASDAQ: IBKR) is a direct access electronic broker… https://t.co/hSGC71WaIz https://t.co/0NAAp1Rl0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duck Creek Technical Lead/Functional Architect: Stratford Solutions is looking for a Technical Lead/Functional Architect, who has prior experience developing AICS and Duck Creek applications, to add to their product support team located in Hartford, CT.… https://t.co/aD4uk4X587 https://t.co/pLbpLdEgtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer / Engineer: Functional Area: IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): No Travel Relocation Provided: No American General Life Insurance Company Software Developer Location: Farmington CT, Houston, TX or Charlotte,… https://t.co/3DUBSc03iz https://t.co/ARp7tGyotr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/KZt2UDLrMQ https://t.co/YebOtpnMX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Yale Posting Status CLOSED TO FURTHER APPLICATIONS Original Posting Date 20-Mar-2018 Supervisory Organization ITS Support Center – Help Desk STARS Requisition number 48662BR University Job Title IT Support Technician 1 Posting… https://t.co/ex4Zm5jdjM https://t.co/gYVzq3ULe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Programmer for Vision Research Core: Original Posting Date 23-Jan-2018 Supervisory Organization Neuroscience STARS Requisition number 47881BR University Job Title Systems Programmer 1 Posting Position Title Systems Programmer for Vision Research… https://t.co/9HFv4fO11w https://t.co/XGL2NS8Qzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager -IT: 1 Year Contract We are actively seeking an IT Technical Project Manager. The IT Technical Project Manager will be responsible for planning and managing company resources to develop and launch innovative technological solutions. This… https://t.co/ucYxBxjFZW https://t.co/8kOt6xn8em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Title: Agile Coach Location: Hartford, CT ,Jersey City , NJ , Minneapolis, MN, Boston MA &amp; Schaumberg, IL, H Duration: 6+ months H1B also accepted but good comm skill / Tech skills Job Description This role requires and Enterprise Level… https://t.co/BDAxTtc9ie https://t.co/l5gsSS7mKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst 2: Original Posting Date 16-Feb-2018 Supervisory Organization Yale Health – ISS STARS Requisition number 48219BR University Job Title Programmer Analyst 2 Posting Position Title Programmer Analyst 2 Bargaining Unit None – Not included… https://t.co/AK2rbdb1mz https://t.co/ifRVtwfGzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Senior Specialist: Cigna Information Management and Analytics (CIMA) offers solutions that provide actionable insights to internal and external business partners and customers to reduce health costs, improve outcomes, and measure… https://t.co/WCpSUsmCVx https://t.co/vArSM0mmbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network / Systems Administrator: Join one of CTs 2015, 2016, 2017 and 2018 Best Places to Work! We are an expanding IT company that is recognized as one of the Inc 5000s fastest growing companies and the MSPs Top 501. Exceptional Service. Unmatched… https://t.co/eM69v3fR5Q https://t.co/DvCcC615gN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EQ Business Systems Analyst: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62466BR Date posted 03/07/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Using Agile and User Centric methodologies collaborate with others to capture enhancements and efficiency… https://t.co/MagZTTyAOK https://t.co/NJIOlfzrew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Interaction Designer: Senior Interaction Designer at Gartner Skip Navigation Menu – Career Opportunities – Why Gartner – Life at Gartner – Campus Search Keyword CategoryCategoryAccount ExecutiveAdministrativeClient ServiceConsultingEventsExecutive… https://t.co/OmFmklCuLW https://t.co/bfjfOBqUj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: Position: Support Analyst Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 645 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for a Support Analyst; an integral member of the IT-Applications team in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: – Robust total rewards program… https://t.co/T3lCtcU0sk https://t.co/cCMAVN9mq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/aMGd185Db2 https://t.co/9y9APrIByL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET SQL Developer: The Senior SQL Developer creates the overall structure and workflow of a software solution and is responsible for leading and/or handling the development of one to multiple components. The Senior Developer will work with the… https://t.co/oi3m8jIMv4 https://t.co/EROEoVzebs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Scholarship Project Manager: Original Posting Date 14-Feb-2018 Supervisory Organization Library – Digital Scholarship STARS Requisition number 48124BR University Job Title Project Manager, Digital Scholarship Posting Position Title Digital… https://t.co/EpHB9j32F2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Management Program Manager: Yale Posting Status CLOSED TO FURTHER APPLICATIONS Original Posting Date 12-Dec-2017 Supervisory Organization Campus Community Technologies – ITS Service Management STARS Requisition number 47352BR University Job… https://t.co/rknK2C4rH8 https://t.co/F9i7LJp0S8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Primary Responsibilities Wright-Pierce, an award-winning, multi-discipline environmental engineering firm specializing in water, wastewater and civil infrastructure, is seeking aa licensedProject Manager-Wastewater, Water, Civil… https://t.co/LoAaBxk1QB https://t.co/4KGl5QLkTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Job Title :?Software &amp; Computer EngineerLocation :?Farmington, CTDuration :?9 -12 months contractcandidates must be US Citizens or Green Card holder.?Job Responsibilities:?Evaluate communications and connectivity… https://t.co/eF3X5MlynC https://t.co/stQJwUI8K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Technician/CMM Programmer: As part of the Quality Department, a CMM Programmer/QualityTechnician is responsible on the assigned shift for all Quality related activities and tasks required for all plant products and sub-components in close… https://t.co/sxUPoOefmo https://t.co/U3qhMCjw7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Development Manager, CTO: Original Posting Date 14-Nov-2017 Supervisory Organization Comprehensive Cancer Center – Clinical Trial Operations STARS Requisition number 46813BR University Job Title Training &amp; Development Mgr Clinical Trials Office… https://t.co/SQUKlWtuRg https://t.co/Kw55Pg585R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager: Position: SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 554 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for an energetic, hands-on SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: –… https://t.co/e4SMnKdfhx https://t.co/FKUBDevhQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operating Systems Programmer: Original Posting Date 08-Dec-2017 Supervisory Organization Public Computing Services STARS Requisition number 47329BR University Job Title Senior Operating Systems Programmer Posting Position Title Senior Operating… https://t.co/VElFvGlgFU https://t.co/ggEmDYMFpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER Each day, the engineering team is working to meet some of the most unique and exciting global challenges. To maintain our role as a global leader, we continue to seek talented, ambitious individuals to… https://t.co/YKjQdJxkYw https://t.co/uChAuVVixc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/f4K6np8qsR https://t.co/uRGh3vtSRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Engineer: Full Stack Web Engineer – What We Do Featured EPAM Acquires Continuum, Expanding Global Innovation, Design and Physical Product Development Capabilities Press Release – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do… https://t.co/qCdVSvyhbg https://t.co/6c6DqevfXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience (2930): OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who… https://t.co/8kdE3I8Wfg https://t.co/lYxyTdR58Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Careers – Reality Interactive Looking for a great place to work? See our Careers How can we help? ************ – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog Love where you work. Great… https://t.co/HaXOGGZaXp https://t.co/KAonfzomDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Careers – Reality Interactive Looking for a great place to work? See our Careers How can we help? ************ – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog Love where you work. Great jobs… https://t.co/jOxkbvvIJG https://t.co/TJQvjOZyrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Java Architect with Akka Play Framework | Stamford, CT | 6+ months: Title: Java Architect w/ Play Akka Framework Location: Stamford, CT Duration: 6+ Months Years of experience: 10+ years Requirements Java Architect with recent years of experience in… https://t.co/H42fzvog3Z https://t.co/QxQ7LkvSf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware Engineer: Posting Job Title Middleware Engineer Job Group Information Technology EEO Statement Aetna is an Equal Opportunity, Affirmative Action Employer Req# 49654BR Primary Location CT-Hartford Locations CT-Hartford Percent of Travel… https://t.co/XbGMgrjVSL https://t.co/CioJiwRkjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- HCADM Technology Lead – US .Net/SQL – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/2YCOfAIPOt https://t.co/fD9Tayl5rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net tech lead/architect: .Net tech lead/architect Ref No.: 18-12117 Location: Hartford, Connecticut .Net tech lead/architect Hartford CT Long term NO JD Thanks and Regard’s Atul Malviya Sr. Technical Recruiter Enterprise Solutions, Inc. 500 E. Diehl… https://t.co/Z99Rc1Eprv https://t.co/2jMS8G5k6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Hardware Engineer: Sr. Hardware Engineer Design solutions to drive safe living and quality of life Use your advanced knowledge of the hardware engineering discipline, processes and tools to help Honeywell Fire Systems deliver innovative solutions… https://t.co/yxKaksnBBa https://t.co/MGFRFX6RYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: QA Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-00635 Location: Simsbury, Connecticut Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 04/02/2018 Key Responsibilities Design automated test strategies and solutions to support the software… https://t.co/NqFxo8JKrx https://t.co/G53eR83Mqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Site Reliability Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors,… https://t.co/kWHdvDU2k5 https://t.co/HOKr59we7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls and Automation Engineer: Job Description: This position requires an individual with introductory level engineering experience in the manufacturing industry. He or she will provide engineering support for continuous improvement Overall Equipment… https://t.co/qjx52WIXxJ https://t.co/cSKOurkzZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/9Hn01tRfyR https://t.co/m8dWTG702t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Scala: We are looking for a versatile, battle-hardened back-end Scala software developer to join our growing team. Here you will focus on building and maintaining enterprise web-based applications. Though we primarily use Play… https://t.co/7xQ8lZcNkJ https://t.co/WaZ1FB1kzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application System Specialist: Original Posting Date 09-Oct-2017 Supervisory Organization Pathology – Research STARS Requisition number 46446BR University Job Title Applications Systems Specialist Posting Position Title Application System Specialist… https://t.co/nXVQZx1FDk https://t.co/69OqyT4hNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/4vmkjMp8cb https://t.co/zryv38BZu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FileNet Developer – Enterprise Content Managment: Aetna Inc. – Job details Individuals &amp; Families Employers &amp; Organizations Health Care Professionals Producers About Us News &amp; Analysis ? HomeSearch openingsSearch resultsCurrent pageJob details Job… https://t.co/dTIXNQHru8 https://t.co/xcWFFjc0pB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Senior Specialist: Cigna Information Management and Analytics (CIMA) offers solutions that provide actionable insights to internal and external business partners and customers to reduce health costs, improve outcomes, and measure… https://t.co/a6TIPQ1e2i https://t.co/qo8eoc5iLC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>