<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/a41NKKMxih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/WfoHokLZTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/eFurcGATxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/ki36QgMV4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/GRmHp1O2Vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/YrirK62Rzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/ziyIsYEp3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/7JlE78hRNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/QGspZeKZzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/vE1gPS8vW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/RjDE1FQeGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/YfJA9CKTO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/WAl5HR6mZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/TFTMowPS2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/PN6fwNejJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/gxmM6G2wcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/ukd5UHkQgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/5HYzRfFgpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the J. Geils Band  http://t.co/ApgNnn8HwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/j1GHSzeLfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/FsgYrUX8ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/edVhkpv23V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/4pnKX49Fdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affiliate marketing has made businesses millions and ordinary people millionaires. - Bo Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/00fDqfjTDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/zSfWq3FEOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/SQDhPvVJYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/yI9KF4ncgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/4CdgTexFBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/4aynJtoyYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/j1tIlrqyWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/kKDT5E2BNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/ifaq6KV6fL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't satisfied just to earn a good living. I was looking to make a statement. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/Dqfn292SBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/ECQvFL33GF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/BbebRt1HpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/LWCBARMhPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/Yn7ZdqGoyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/9fI3mzQZwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/lXrmP53mL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/QXnulhsJIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/D5hrBL5VnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/2DhsiQzV2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/WuxtJxL6L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/acTPAOYDvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/ogpRpOkvfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/oWPB0XMOD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/fwxXilZ7rM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/SG8IdukreM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/yWfKdy9q9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/JFhDpu2pFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/L4XVS3POhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/xW1QyswoFN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>