<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If it feels like time is moving at the wrong speed, cancel a few meetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't negotiate absurd schedules with engineers. Encourage truth telling and reasonable time estimates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Suppress your inner alarm. Be the calmest person in the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: You're going to meet some buffoons and scoundrels. Try to be the better person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Shakespeare tip: Our doubts are traitors and make us lose the good we oft might win by fearing to attempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard economic tip: The risks of confinement to a single planet exceed the costs of interstellar travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you want your lieutenants to become leaders, send them on away missions without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard cosmology tip: Six sevenths of all matter is undetectable, so stop thinking you know so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The respect you show your crew is a major factor in determining how they feel about their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: Every choice we make allows us to manipulate the future. Living is making choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It is not necessary to agree with the majority. Part of leadership is individuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When leaving to go to the bathroom, there's no point in being specific. Just say you'll be in your "ready room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: The Big Bang is still happening, and you're part of a small, swirling eddy in the explosion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you succeed too much and become cocky, recognize it, admit it, and stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard negotiation tip: Invent new Starfleet regulations as needed. They won't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Videoconference with your mortal enemies. The results may surprise you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Shakespeare tip: The fool doth think he is wise, but the wise man knows himself to be a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard ethics tip: Respect the unusual customs of alien cultures, except when they're simply doing it wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Pick your battles. Fight injustices before annoyances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard artistry tip: Lacking innate talent at a skill doesn't mean you should stop. On the contrary, it means you need to practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be patient with crew members' idiosyncrasies. They aren't machines. Well, most of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Polite crew members solve problems together. Rude crew members escalate problems all by themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it sound like you know what you're doing, even if you're just picking a direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard individuality tip: Do something, anything, that no one else in your collective would ever do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard career tip: Stand out in a crowd. When there is a power vacuum, take command.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your orders do not dictate your ideals. Your ideals determine how you interpret your orders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Avoid euphemisms. Call a thing what it really is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you hear yourself start to raise your voice, stop, take a breath, smile, then speak politely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard ethics tip: A man cannot be held accountable for his dreams; only for his actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard entrepreneur tip: Your enterprise's first year might be disappointing, but things are likely to work better by year three.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There are times when men of good conscience cannot blindly follow orders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Stirring up competition between crew members is the opposite of your job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard style tip: If you're balding, don't hide it. Own it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Develop a catchphrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard technology tip: An advanced system isn't always easy to use. Improve the interface, or try pushing buttons at random.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: For each command, assign it to one person, or ask for a volunteer. Don't ask a crowd to take an action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If people accuse your organization of endangering people who wear red shirts, put on a damn red shirt every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't waste time using social media. Pretend it was never invented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Ignore rules that make no sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tolerate failure, not incompetence. Learn the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard programming tip: The first version of any software will be buggy. That's why so many holodeck programs try to kill you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you stand up, straighten your shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're not sure what to say, take a deep breath and a dramatic pause. Maybe somebody else will talk first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Hire aliens. It's no big deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard culinary tip: Tea. Earl grey. Hot. http://t.co/bAqKSKDQDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's okay not to know things. Practice saying "I don't know." Go ahead. Say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Give your crew the best technology available and you'll be amazed what they can do for your enterprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't assume anything is possible or impossible until you've asked the people who will be doing the work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you lose one crew member, mourn appropriately. If the whole ship explodes, don't worry; time travel will fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard confrontation tip: Grant yourself more patience and persistence than your adversary can afford. https://t.co/KKdMPU2xO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you never fail, you aren't going boldly enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: Antimatter is not a toy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When a middle manager says one of his crew isn't fitting in, tell him to befriend the crewman and fix the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Encourage extracurricular activities with your crew, especially if it involves wearing costumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It takes hard work to become a master at single-tasking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you've gotten enough sleep, an impossible task becomes an interesting challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Every officer needs to be in charge of something they understand, even if it's just radishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: "That's the way it's always been" is never an adequate reason to continue doing something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Put your experts in a conference room, tell them the problem, then shut up and watch the magic happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Ensure chocolate is available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Say yes whenever possible, except when your tactical officer recommends attacking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Admit ignorance and ask a question rather than blunder forward out of pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tell your employees when they do well, even if you believe they are empathic and can read your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If it feels like time is moving at the wrong speed, cancel a few meetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it so that people feel they can come to you with any issue without fear of reprimand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard programming tip: When the holodeck malfunctions, stay in character. Don't piss off the computer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Speak candidly, and encourage others to do likewise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Data is easier to manage than humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Work should be useful, stimulating, and challenging, not wasteful, tedious, nor impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know your audience. Display strength to Klingons, logic to Vulcans, and opportunity to Ferengi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Used sparingly, some light swearing can help emphasize your damn point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let upper management dismantle your team, nor your team members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep up with new technologies. Today you get a holodeck, but tomorrow could bring a holographic doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In a strange new environment, be wary of making changes until you understand more about what's going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard beauty tip: Traveling for years at superluminal speeds greatly slows down the aging process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard investigation tip: Magnify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Don't assume your opponent will behave rationally. Plan for their emotional response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Admitting one's failures is a sign of confidence and strength. It reassures others that failing is okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Even if computers can talk now, remember how deeply stupid they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a realistic understanding of what your ship can and cannot do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard exploration tip: Our galaxy has over eight billion habitable planets. Get to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Do not assume there is an ulterior motive for a gift. Accept it with gratitude and be done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The least you can do is to make everyone onboard feel acknowledged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Try to understand more than half of the technobabble. Ask for metaphors to explain the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Decide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: If your organization won't install fuses, don't touch any consoles while your ship is under attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: No kissing until after you've faced mortal peril together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Intuition is valuable, but it's not a substitute for facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Give orders that make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Results are more important than protocol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Do your best to learn about and comprehend the experiences of people who look very different from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Once all their basic needs are taken care of, crew members are motivated by the meaningfulness of their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Defend your crew members, even against each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Hone your inner bullshit detector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: The greatest threat to lasting mutual respect is egocentrism. It may never leave you, but resist it at every turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard #TableTopDay tip: Overcome your hesitation and join a game with people who make you smile. https://t.co/UVe1XQyswH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Put your experts in a conference room, tell them the problem, then shut up and watch the magic happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Develop a catchphrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you never fail, you aren't going boldly enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be willing to laugh at yourself, but unwilling to laugh at your coworkers.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>