<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/LjHoC4sidT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/k4ucUzTbG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/Cqkq2Qa06l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/HWiOmJPGtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/ElpLU1eom1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/SV5sEmARAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/KdV64XQJV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/3PAln1CXT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/v9a5czqPJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/pq8VSVgDg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/81eRldYImC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/iA042sE0cu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/k0Po8Ff0JB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/QaJySAmuBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/58vzv7RgyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/57QgKyNUvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Tv1c8FYbwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/NnfBDi41b5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/TcmsXp6gay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/g4A4M6JnwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/9Gfsc2IUJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/b4x2R2HRqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/RJvThyJAXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/iBB08hQ1hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/sLqsPBDjaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/gJvBoiBWHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/q3XHplyqLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/s475c64BlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/8myIDiNn7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/MEqXXPr6E5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/Gmkygp3LaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/26716S5z04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/jepXsLyDJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/8PagtGOPWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/j8vPesh68a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/WVTfISrtW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/yrAhwojgXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/hiwz2eqLPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/MtnBL3Yycg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/vjuKryTxTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/aCDS8cks4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/PVn0eIFFJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/HpBZF6KawM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/riOlHFvXFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/REUtnWSRMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/Je6XP86HYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/7EMCxWgWz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/QYgHTNbMPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/k9HRrwzhDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>