<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Button Giving Millions of Americans Better Handle on Energy Costs: 
	This afternoon President Obama is vis... http://t.co/RhEvutCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses Solar Power in Nevada: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks on energy af... http://t.co/w883lBPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making America a Top Tourist Destination: Commerce and Interior Keep Up Efforts to Increase Visitation: 
	Ed not... http://t.co/UW86SlkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasing Access to Locally Grown and Healthy Food: 
	Three years ago, I was asked to participate in the White ... http://t.co/A8MhoxRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Reform in Action: A Mother's Story: 

	Tracy Muñoz realized our health care system needed to change the... http://t.co/iKtXi0Nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: The Budget: 
	In response to the Ryan Republican Budget, Jeff Zients, Acting Director ... http://t.co/7g7BWZtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ryan-Republican Budget: The Consequences of Imbalance: 
	Yesterday, House Republicans released their budget ... http://t.co/Mi6gKZTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking it Down: The Health Law &amp; Young Adults: 
	Ed note: This was originally posted on http://t.co/hoUn6Y6I

	... http://t.co/SJPgjREw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steven-Care: Insurance for Young Adults Under Age 26: 
	The health care law, the Affordable Care Act, is giving ... http://t.co/lPzFxXx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 2.5 Million: 

	Under the Affordable Care Act, parents can now add or keep their children on t... http://t.co/DLWzxRis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Tweetup: United Kingdom Arrival Ceremony Engages Online and In-Person: 
	The White House reached out... http://t.co/3PuAAl8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama meets with Irish Prime Minister Enda Kenny: 
	Today, President Obama welcomed Enda Kenny, the Ta... http://t.co/hALGyyT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facilitating Internet Freedom in Iran: 

	This morning, in a statement marking Nowruz, President Barack Obama... http://t.co/ikeggrs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smarter Regulation: New Guidance on Reducing Cumulative Burdens: 
	Ed note: This post originally appeared on the... http://t.co/bPmI5VV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking it Down: The Health Care Law and Women: 
	Ed note: This post originally appeared on http://t.co/hoUn6Y6I... http://t.co/IkDEIKDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VanessaCare: Health Coverage Without Lifetime Limits: 
	Vanessa Mishkit, a nurse in Tampa, knows firsthand what ... http://t.co/GE0IY5Rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Nowruz, President Obama Speaks to the Iranian People: 
	In a video message earlier today, President Obama sen... http://t.co/y6saGVN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 20.4: 

	President Obama’s health reform law requires that new health insurance plans cover pr... http://t.co/URdyqDfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: White House LGBT Conference on Safe Schools &amp; Communities: 
	Today, the White House will partner wit... http://t.co/mUYdCSO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Question 3/19/12: Jay Carney Answers Your Questions on Energy and the Affordable Care Act: 
	Today, White ... http://t.co/GCVDUNW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Technology to Help Homeless Veterans: 
	More than 67,000 veterans spent one night homeless, living in emer... http://t.co/QBC0TMZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Joins Campaign to Encourage the Next Generation of American Engineers and Innovators: 
	Last week I was in ... http://t.co/n9MvOAg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $4,200: 

	The average senior on Medicare will save $4,200 on their health care by 2021 becaus... http://t.co/JTkTvhYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementing Section 508: Improving Access to Government Information and Data for Persons with Disabilities: 
	T... http://t.co/j8ydrr1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helen-Care: Giving Seniors Peace of Mind and More Money in Their Pockets: 
	Ed Note:  This was originally posted... http://t.co/FBShNhyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking It Down: The Health Care Law &amp; Seniors: 
	Ed Note:  This was originally posted on http://t.co/oUu2ssYN, ... http://t.co/9sTv1Zsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Question: What do you want to ask the White House Press Secretary?: 
	Today, we’re pleased to bring back “... http://t.co/5L8lNHzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Call to Action: Let's Move!: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama delivers remarks during an event at American... http://t.co/jBXd88Xe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama at the Dubliner on St. Patrick's Day: 
	President Obama left the White House this afternoon to c... http://t.co/EvXTL4yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Ending Subsidies for Big Oil Companies: 
	President Obama says that America needs an all-of-the-... http://t.co/rPX2jow8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gulf War Veteran Serves Again Through AmeriCorps: 
	Ed. note: The Office of Social Innovation and Civic Particip... http://t.co/QvWUiaJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Standing Together and Working Together: 

	A quick look at what happened this week at WhiteHouse... http://t.co/l6QI9IiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community College Key to a Better Future: 
	Ed note: Dr. Jill Biden wrote this op-ed for USA Today.

	Danny Ande... http://t.co/LJxj9LQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Health Care: 
	Two years ago, President Obama signed the Affordable Care Act – legisla... http://t.co/8lS5dbjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama’s Picks for the 2012 NCAA Women’s Basketball Tournament: 
	Earlier this week, when he met with E... http://t.co/EbW6ymOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/16/2012 or "Leveling The Playing Field": 
	This week, the President pressed for support of adv... http://t.co/mKX2BzA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/16/12 or "Leveling the Playing Field": 

	West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's happ... http://t.co/7q35dBGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USAID and OIC: Working Together to Save Lives: 

    USAID Administrator Rajiv Shah and Professor Ekmeleddi... http://t.co/19tjgOUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Energy: The Facts: 
	Any American who has filled up recently knows that prices at the pump, driven by i... http://t.co/oLW9Svbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the Path from Prison to Service with AmeriCorps: 
	Ed. note: The Office of Social Innovation and Civic Pa... http://t.co/lcwc5e5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Your Question: National Equal Pay Task Force: 
	Since his first days in office, President Obama has pushed f... http://t.co/dKrZnqxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend This Fall at the White House: Internship Applications Are Now Being Accepted: 
	For college and university... http://t.co/b1u8l4SI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting to Know More About http://t.co/Ms4Fpjzv: 
	Last week, right before we launched http://t.co/Ms4Fpjzv -- whi... http://t.co/6vKdDJ3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toasting the Alliance between America and Britain: 

    President Barack Obama and First Lady Michelle Oba... http://t.co/DEES5FuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobs On The Way: U.S.-Korea Trade Agreement Takes Effect Today: 

    President Barack Obama signs the “Uni... http://t.co/Tk20oRzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK State Dinner: What's On The Menu?: 
	Guests at tonight's State Dinner honoring David Cameron, the Prime Minis... http://t.co/8IMjKJZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bridging the Pond: President Obama and Prime Minister Cameron Hold a Joint Press Conference: 

    Presiden... http://t.co/9fGFxKfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AmeriCorps: Developing the Next Generation of Public Servants: 
	My journey to this moment began almost twenty y... http://t.co/irISJIQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Prime Minister David Cameron Arrives at the White House: 
	In a ceremony steeped in tradition, President Obam... http://t.co/xDx2gUh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Alliance for Global Development: 
	When Prime Minister Cameron meets President Obama in Washington today it w... http://t.co/EnaJJ5JN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Corps and VSO:  A Partnership on Volunteerism to Promote Global Development: 
	In May 2011, President Obam... http://t.co/LZ4L2C0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's 2011 NCAA Tournament Bracket: 
	Yesterday, President Obama took some time to fill out his brac... http://t.co/9Jo3zdKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBO Update Shows Lower Costs for the New Health Care Law: 
	Yesterday, the Congressional Budget Office released ... http://t.co/0A20iVxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Notable British Visitors to the White House Since World War II: 

		This morning, President O... http://t.co/1FTTsJDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for an Official Visit From the United Kingdom: 
	Outside the White House, the Union Jack is flying alo... http://t.co/eBOEp7CU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. Will Bring a New Trade Case Against China: 

    President Barack Obama, flanked by Commerce Secre... http://t.co/tr2giLHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Announcement From FEMA and AmeriCorps: 
	Later today, Secretary of Homeland Security Janet Napolitano, Federa... http://t.co/FjLBneav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $7,610: 

	As gas prices rise, oil companies jus... http://t.co/5LUi5PFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Facts on Gas Prices: Infographic: 
	Here are the facts: The United States produced more than 2 billion barre... http://t.co/Jn5YBFp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revamping Job Training with the American Job Center: 
	In his State of the Union Address, President Obama talked... http://t.co/o5aXTNIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Blueprint for a Secure Energy Future: One-Year Progress Report: 
	One year ago, the President put forward a ... http://t.co/DYh3m1av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call with President Karzai Following the Report of Afghan Civilian Casualties: 
	Sunday afternoon, President Oba... http://t.co/pvPn4UY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Tsunami in Japan: 
	One year ago today, one of the most powerful earthquakes ever recorded st... http://t.co/Z5Xpo3g8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 1 in 3: 

	While 1 in 3 women in the United States have experienced rape, physical violence an... http://t.co/MKn9kZWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House White Board: President Obama's Plan for Refinancing: 

	The financial crisis and the recession bot... http://t.co/BpOSdSBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Dr. Jill Biden's Community College to Career Tour: 
	Today, Dr. Jill Biden will visit Reading Area Communi... http://t.co/ziUkG5ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Health Care Law is Helping Small Businesses: 
	Small businesses are the engine of the American economy.  Ove... http://t.co/24lwPUCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Shuttle Discovery Flies Above Washington DC: 
	All eyes were on the sky above the White House this morning... http://t.co/oyCRsxM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes NASCAR Champ Tony Stewart to the White House: 

	President Obama today congratulated ... http://t.co/FbW7AvqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking Down on Oil Market Manipulation: 

    President Barack Obama announces a plan to increase oversig... http://t.co/PwPNXdUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Benefits of Civic Engagement for Tomorrow's Leaders: 
	Ed. note: The Office of Social Innovation and Civic P... http://t.co/kCJX3G6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Announces First Google+ Photowalk: Spring Garden Tour: 
	Today, we’re excited to announce our first ... http://t.co/DTbaAlZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning Apps to Close the Pay Gap: 

		Ed. Note: This was cross-posted from the Department of Labor's Work in Pr... http://t.co/flxDeMCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Your 2011 Federal Taxpayer Receipt Now: 

	Today is Tax Day,... http://t.co/P0pwsB08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Securing Equal Pay: 
	Today – Tuesday, April 17 – is Equal Pay Day, which marks the fact that, nearly 50 years s... http://t.co/aaK7GYtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Drug Policy for the 21st Century: 
	Illegal drugs not only harm a user’s mind and body, they devastate familie... http://t.co/6ZZUnIJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More from the Summit of the Americas: 

    President Barack Obama arrives at the Julio Cesar Turbay Ayala ... http://t.co/YCzkoobQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Buffett Rule Would Make Sure Everyone Plays by the Same Rules: 
	The share of national income earned by the ... http://t.co/86afQy47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating America's Greatest Asset: Our Volunteers: 

    Volunteers help build homes on the fourth anniv... http://t.co/HQW76ix5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2012 Citizens Medal: Open for Nominations: 
	For more 40 years, the Presidential Citizens Medal has recognized A... http://t.co/XtlOA8Na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama at the Summit of the Americas: 

    President Barack Obama participates in the CEO Summit ... http://t.co/E2Sqj1go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: It’s Time for Congress to Pass the Buffett Rule: 
	President Obama urges Congress to pass the Bu... http://t.co/aTsAsEFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: "You Guys Were Excellent Wild Things": 

	A quick look at what happened this week on WhiteHouse.... http://t.co/uEAASeZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60,000 Veterans and Military Spouses Have Been Hired Through Joining Forces Employment Initiatives: 

    F... http://t.co/bSLX1JSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facilitating Safe and Responsible Expansion of Natural Gas Production: 
	A key part of President Obama’s all-of-... http://t.co/Blm8cwiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama and Vice President Biden’s 2011 Tax Returns: 
	Today, the President released his 2011 federal in... http://t.co/nJVbpkCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report from USDA: Supporting Cutting-Edge Efforts to Reduce America’s Reliance on Fossil Fuel: 
	Since taking of... http://t.co/3QXR0ZPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 4/13/12 or "You're Proof of Change": 

	This week, the President hosted a forum on Women and the... http://t.co/bCA6sWIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hangout with White House Chef Cris Comerford and Gail Simmons: 
	This is cross-posted from the Let's Move! blog.... http://t.co/U7ZYH1LE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raising the Bar: The One Year Anniversary of Joining Forces: 
	Over the past 12 months First Lady Michelle Obama... http://t.co/f56dw7q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Your Buffett Number?: 
	For half a century, the average tax rate paid by the richest people in America ha... http://t.co/coAew7jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sidewinder Performs at the White House: 
	Sidewinder, the Missouri Air National Guard rock band, was at the Whit... http://t.co/YvuEiOMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Hangout: The Buffett Rule: 
	Today at 4:00 p.m. EST, the WHite House is hosting a Hangout on Google+... http://t.co/n9FEC3x5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Connecting the Americas: 
	Tomorrow, the White House, in partnership with the U.S. Dep... http://t.co/VmuNwM4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing in America’s Health Care Workforce: 
	In too many communities across America, residents do not have ea... http://t.co/NiFhwHEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Buffett Rule (aka The Reagan Rule): 
	The President believes we should build an economy where everyone does ... http://t.co/w1aSbY0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy-Care: Making Insurance More Affordable for Small Businesses: 
	Nancy Clark is the owner of Glen Group, a s... http://t.co/LeqT0qQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama's Message to Military Families: You Do Live in a Grateful Nation: 

	First Lady Michelle Obama ... http://t.co/bDqYjkwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Board: Brian Deese on the Buffett Rule: 
	In this new White House White Board, Brian Deese, the Deputy Dir... http://t.co/AUAWrIBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2012 #EasterEggRoll in Tweets: 
	"Let's Go, Let's Play, Let's Move!" was the theme of this year's Easter Egg... http://t.co/DfjL2Br4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>