<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna slag kazim Richards more often...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gazq87 it's when it's really obviously onside it's annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else look forward to seeing the Celtic team...just to be disappointed every week? Kazim Richards, again, really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamPaisley me as well, even if theyd been playing Celtic I'd have been happy if hibs won, hearts would just say 5-1,like thats relevant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly Sunday was a fluke...Celtic obviously just wanted hibs to have an easy game in the final!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaxtersSoup @richard0188 I think they can sack him...not like they could get worse if he leaves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the end of the day it's an upset against an organised Rangers. If they win the league next season I'll be concerned. New manager please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vCrooky loads of people seem unhappy with moyes, I'd take him in a minute!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you get rid of Ronny now? Or wait until the end of the season? Who takes charge if he goes now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 @Great_Run did you enjoy it though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 @Great_Run was it the half marathon? Good effort mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 @Great_Run are you wearing a bum bag?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was rubbish. Shocking display from Brown...I'd say McGregor and brown had least pressure in that shootout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticfc Neil McCann going on about how bad Celtics defence are. They've conceded less than Rangers. In the league above!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leighgriff09 let's make sure you don't hit any penalties! Feel free to score as many as you like from open play! Hail Hail!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is David Tanner saying it's an old firm game tomorrow?Is he jumping in his Delorean and going back to 2011,before the zombie apocalypse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaxtersSoup  have you dyed your hair and gone in goals for hibs mate? #fillsthegoals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Cummings that's just unforgivable. Total joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new jungle book film looks amazing! Might need to go to the cinema for the first time in about 3 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R__Ha what a penalty to win it. Horror penalty lost it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R__Ha best penalty takes just injured himself. Bilbao all the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R__Ha Bilbao v sevilla in extra time on bt sport red button mate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard0188 @michaelmain @ScotRail I don't want you to go on the train. I'm really worried about you. Where are you, I'll pay for a taxi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail that's nothing to do with poor use of language. Your family or anyone could be looking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail no need for swearing on social media. Shows a lack of vocabulary...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail I got it at commuter time 2 weeks ago. I enjoyed the hustle bustle of it all. Made me feel part of something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail I'm actually a regular on trains. That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard. Sorry I'm not a train expert it seems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail I'm sure getting alive was a success. It sounded like there must've been numerous casualties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail you're clearly one of they folk who stands and moans...if I'm on the train I don't expect a reclining chair...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail I think so mate...I quite like standing, it's good for my posture. Did you make it to work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmain @ScotRail absolutely shocking, more people should cycle to work...what weirdo is taking photos on the train?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @R__Ha: 11-4-11 Dad died 5 years ago today. Glad he didn't have to see this Aston Villa side, would have killed him. Miss ya https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 seriously though mate, was it a proper game couldn't see anything on TV...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep seeing posts about the Rangers...did they win something today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewB19601057 @hoopsjaz08 it's not really, if he could take penalties we'd be on for a treble...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Leigh Griffiths the penalty taker? He's awful at them. Everything about his run up tells you he's about to miss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Sport - Masters 2016: Ernie Els cards nine on first hole https://t.co/bM4UhdrK5B @Nakanickete told you he would do well!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard0188 @Sconway89 rab wanted to play on, then I shouted it was a foul. So rab then stopped the game like he was paolo Di canio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sconway89 and everyone just played on after it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sconway89 it's great when a guy just munches you in a wee friendly game of 7's eh...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard0188  https://t.co/tHwdRI8M9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Chris Sutton just like slagging off any manager? I'm sure he was a manager for 5 minutes and was awful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leicester's tartan pitch is giving me a sore head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 Hadouken!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard0188 @simmy1874 that's because there's nobody there. Wait until to juwon oshaniwa shows up shouting 'hadouken'...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 @richard0188 it wouldn't have been out of place outside club earth...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 @richard0188 I think it was GBH. A late one on the ground would be a booking, so a flying missile in the air should be...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaleysBhoys Chris commons...easy. was watching him on football gold against yeovil today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England were gonna win the Euro's 20 minutes ago...now they're getting beat of Holland who are about as good as Macedonia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is bridcutt doing, not only with that tackle, but just in general. He's like the anti vardy, he's somehow made it even though he's shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theawayfans @craigherkes I wonder why everyone hates England fans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and @AHbeanie are off for 2 weeks; anyone else fancy it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigBishop86 I probably wouldn't be able to commit with the wee man. Whose it for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigBishop86 not been playing mate, just sevens a couple of times a week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think #SoccerAid should be decided by a player who is still playing in the premiership. Surely that's a bit off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrcWanoddm she's obviously just trying to annoy her opponent or something! Wouldn't like to see her at a fire drill...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena Williams slow walking is one of the most annoying things in the world. Just hurry up, nobody actually walks like that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmy1874 why have you just wasted time tweeting about it then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Napoleon_Celtic: #SuperDuperGaryHooper https://t.co/ULa9sFHe6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @photosofootball: Toulouse had to win their last match to avoid relegation. This was manager's speech that moved his players to tears!
h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arcticmacky Dean shiells really better keep away from him on a night out. That could be problematic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think with Rangers being so upset about their players being assaulted, they wouldn't go sign a guy who assaults his team mates!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The commentators are talking about Harry Kane's penalty being a good positive penalty. He missed guys. Like didn't even hit the target.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arcticmacky that's OK mate, try not to get disheartened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arcticmacky that was about kilmarnock, Lee Clark is their manager...just mentioned the Rangers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Lee Clark had done that at hampden I'm pretty sure he would've been accused by Rangers of assaulting a police officer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamPaisley I think it was because the ball was moving so slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamPaisley I was just thinking that mate. Bayern's missed penalty made me properly laugh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R__Ha Bayern v Dortmund...penalties about to start on BT sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a finish that is! Wanted penalties, might still see them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebovril I've already said that the hibs fans who were violent should be dealt with...so your point is irrelevant to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebovril what about sectarian words? Is that OK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have Rangers not mentioned any smokebombs or very dodgy singing in their club statement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports hibs fans hitting Rangers players with belts. Get them life bans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like trying to run towards a forest; without running towards a tree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hibs fans ran towards Rangers fans' if you run on to celebrate from the hibs end is it not virtually impossible to not run towards them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton @SebGarcia88 @RangersFC have any team ran on to celebrate losing before? Just stay in your seat or go home surely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AHbeanie did you come second in the rugby? Your medal will be very similar to that of the Rangers! #HibsedIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordNelson88 you obviously are not aware that a Tony Stokes hair transplant trumps a magic hat every time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carra23: 3-2 Hibs best game I've seen this season. #ScottishCupFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibs had to wait 114 years! The Rangers have still never won it! Stokes and Henderson, your mission is complete, return to paradise bhoys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henderson on the bench, but fyvie starts... are hibs just thinking they'll lose so not playing their best player?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomCheese8 supposedly you can't actually get liquidated if you just pretend it didn't happen. So they wouldn't mind...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Besty_D: @PE_TotD 'Century Club' - Y9 Fitness Lesson. My take on the 300 routine. Students complete as many challenges as.. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously Griffiths has been great this season. But it's a good watch when there's someone who actually passes playing up top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, Celtic are so lucky that this striker situation hasn't happened earlier in the season. Poor management to have no back up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Ambrose starting again, play an under 20 player! Also no strikers, aitchison on the bench might really benefit from a start!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I say to Eli every time he falls over... it's an important life lesson https://t.co/JJi6q1h9ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton maybe signing for the Rangers. That's a perfect fit...thank god he's never been anywhere near Celtic...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure I wrote that new Stone Roses song in primary 3 during my musketeers project. It's murder. But everyone pretends it's groundbreaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm delighted Newcastle are away down...always try to pretend they're a big club. I'd say now they're where they should be. Byeeee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep hearing about how good graeme shinnie is for Aberdeen. They should bring him on to mark Patrick Roberts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clarkstermbe if we can keep it to 11 I think the league's ours...that's why we're just going with 1 up front...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottyarf, well done getting back up to the EPL pal, still not good enough for Pete Lyons' county team though... @jamieandniamh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today @celticfc have one striker in the squad, if Aberdeen decide to nail Griffiths early we'll be phoning Craig Levein for advice on a 4-6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get in there! C'Mon livi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a win for @SunderlandAFC ! I wonder if @NUFC will manage to scrape a draw at villa park next season too! @leighmacd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to @beramangela today, would love to see him in the EPL #onceatimalwaysatim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have The Rangers given themselves a target of 55 points? Nae chance that'll be enough to win a first spfl title! https://t.co/pik0RVgbDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I reading tweets about a wonderful chip by bale? It was a deflected cross!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>