<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/ezROgvbOHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/UunR6EmDne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/MIPAlsZTWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/M2fgaB5Gms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/jPNdbEUevY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/3H4KikYCxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/sQPMI3urpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/0xCrldZZkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/0eSlLoMl9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/CBVp8fQVr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/JlChPmCes6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/F415BH9GPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/SUiEfODkDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/VlMy1L3EpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/Wg9zzet4zH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/AzogdKwOUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/otIRniWRuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/tZbrUwbAoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/7zWPjDZuG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/TO6mgTKrtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work is the presentation of our capabilities. - Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/YRsBwAQsq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/ldksDWBS5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/R8dLMrGjJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/Avo3tpnsQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/zUkH4PJjPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/zyAqKiEuYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/WbmYJY6BBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/UzBdmgPL4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/vWYrhUepuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Lg1SAkel88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/15txNzZ1e6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/quWvQUNN1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/r3RkOwNEzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/bHnuizaSzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/vIJpVaLB0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/qn7EjUM5Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/9qa86fsc0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/yEoW3oOapT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/OcJngeVeFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/GrSLgwgWUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/RdYl7V3gAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/0fx1s7c9uE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/Ed1MwkxHqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>