<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bellesxxoo lol haven't thought about him in a long time but that movie made me remember]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listened to @taylorswift13 #Reputation on the way to work.. Listening to @rqui #Divas on the way home. Swift better step up her game. @sternshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValIeriee I tweeted it earlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValIeriee Did you watch the Deadpool 2 Bob Ross trailer yet? It's only 2 minutes but it will entertain you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN NOT WAIT! https://t.co/PnesqyxxRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioMoBounce I always had a feeling they would get back together ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For real why isn't @taylorswift13 performing at the #AMAs? She just released an album... Shouldn't she be there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funniest thing you will see all day. @deadpoolmovie #Deadpool2 #BobRoss trailer. @VancityReynolds https://t.co/8E74GUUGqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duchessangela @Pink @kelly_clarkson @xtina Yes @NiallOfficial was my fave in @onedirection and he's super nice. I met him a few months ago. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duchessangela I'm sure they are talented but I am more pumped about @pink and @kelly_clarkson duet and @xtina tribute to Whitney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duchessangela They have quite the Twitter warrior force... I better watch out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inpaperdreamss @NJHNEWS @Pink @kelly_clarkson @ShawnMendes @selenagomez @xtina @ladygaga @NiallOfficial @Imaginedragons @ddlovato @nickjonas @BTS_twt Not to 40-year-old women like myself ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inpaperdreamss @NJHNEWS @Pink @kelly_clarkson @ShawnMendes @selenagomez @xtina @ladygaga @NiallOfficial @Imaginedragons @ddlovato @nickjonas @BTS_twt They are.. I named my favorites from the list. The ones I think are ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inpaperdreamss @NJHNEWS @Pink @kelly_clarkson @ShawnMendes @selenagomez @xtina @ladygaga @NiallOfficial @Imaginedragons @ddlovato @nickjonas @BTS_twt What about them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AMAs lineup is ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ @Pink &amp; @kelly_clarkson, @ShawnMendes @selenagomez @xtina @ladygaga @NiallOfficial @Imaginedragons @ddlovato @nickjonas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for them... Hopefully it works out this time. #Jelena https://t.co/HzFPkAF5QJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @maroon5 song of the day will play at noon on @947FreshFM ... Keep track all week to win a trip to see them in Denver! #Maroon5 #FreshAmericanTour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bellesxxoo I was 20. Went w my boyfriend right before he broke my â¤. Our love sank with the ship. ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titanic is returning to theaters for one week only next month... It's 20 years old and they just remastered it. How is Titanic TWENTY years old???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chatteyone Just fabulous, how are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsadoraBSer @blakeshelton @people I thought @people would announce today but haven't seen anything yet. @GossipCop says it's him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read that 12% of @Netflix subscribers admit to watching on the toilet in public bathrooms. Who does that????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the fans take over the poll... or maybe he's just that sexy? https://t.co/JsGBFiw2eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/8yS3yU4McC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rumor has it @blakeshelton will be named @people's Sexiest Man Alive. Do you agree with this choice? #SexiestManAlive #BlakeShelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love shopping at @GiantFood and my son loves pushing the little shopper-in-training cart around the store. Listen to me to win a $75 gift card at 11:30am all week! https://t.co/6N53oxzkBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do cable companies charge so much money for monthly service while at the same time assuming their customers don't have jobs? Sure we can sit at home for 3 hours in the middle of the day waiting for you to show up late..............]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cute https://t.co/Fo6yD0lwml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooooh don't tell my 13yo daughter she will lose it! @ShawnMendes and @haileybaldwin getting cozy... https://t.co/l1SO6SI8F3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article questions whether or not Angelina Jolie is having financial trouble because she's "discount... https://t.co/KyKWRWkQ4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @TommyMcFLY @cityshopgirl @JenRicher @darikforeal @ItsBrittWaters @scottstraffic @947FreshFM @theandreasmoss @dccelebrity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Matt Damon get the boot from #Oceans8? A LOT of people think so! https://t.co/3jrKHturM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could not find my Visa card... Hadn't used it since Oct. My husband SWORE he did not have it. I've been looking for a week. Guess where it was... IN HIS CAR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK where are all the gross people who watch all of the pimple popping videos? I keep hiding them on Facebook, but they obviously have a big nasty following if people keep posting them... Show yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would have been awesome if @Gap had ANYTHING left on sale in my husband's size!! Not in stores... not online... Guess I need to shop sooner next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skylar_l_19 Definitely lame, but my kids get them anyway... They get candy and cookies so it's only right to include a toothbrush too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you actually watch Facebook stories and Instagram stories? I usually don't. I like to just scroll through but... https://t.co/OXMQMId39n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darikforeal Whoever smelt it dealt it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uranium One is either a massive scandal or a big fat nothing burger depending on which political party you affiliate with. #politics #America #FactsMatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Disney World for a day when we're in FL... Which park has new stuff? Animal Kingtom, Magic Kingdom, or Epcot??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #ReGiftingDay... Have you ever been regifted and it was obvious? I have.. It was so bad. So, so bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WQYKGeno It's not StubHub, I am pretty sure it's directly through Nats Park where the concert is! I can walk over there and get them myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I am just spoiled because I get to go to a lot of shows for free and I usually get good seats too... But... https://t.co/ZjqU7UWJjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is a $69.50 "convenience fee" to buy tickets online?? Just when I thought I was going to splurge on something that is already way overpriced??? Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adrianlui: "Nobody puts Baby Jesus in the corner" #MakeMoviePlotsChristmassy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbcwashington Sunday is the 24th.. Sat is the 23rd :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy mom fail! How one #elfontheshelf was tragically burned in the oven! https://t.co/mtke8mscH6 Was his name Hansel? Ouch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #SangriaDay! What restaurant has the best sangria? My husband always gets the big pitcher when we go to @bucadibeppo and then I have to drive home! https://t.co/Qq73icEBSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Luke at the Daily Caller the only reporter in DC covering this MASSIVE story? https://t.co/OWtwLVgTeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukerosiak I know... been following for several months. Even people I know who do news roll their eyes when I bring it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukerosiak Why are you the only one reporting this massive story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I am... see what you're missing if you're not following me on Instagram @danasdirt!! https://t.co/HcKC7e0TWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG I love #funfetti cookies so much @Pillsbury #baking #Christmas #Christmascookies https://t.co/R7tavFM1Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocco just asked the question we've been dreading at Christmas for the last few years: "Mom, what's the elf on the shelf?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK... which is it? Pink &amp; white or blue &amp; gray? https://t.co/9MaWaEPs3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boltsfan850 Yes that one is bad... "touch base" also drives me insane but I don't think it's as widely used as "whatever" and "literally" at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WQYKGeno I use SO way too much... or even just starting a break or a sentence with "so"... someone pointed it out in Radio Peeps group a while ago and now I catch myself doing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the most annoying words/phrases of 2017... Which one drives you nuts? Would you add anything? #ThatsItImDoneWith all of them. https://t.co/zfkWnCzNsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a super sweet deal on some @BestBuy gifts and am now hoping that I actually get them because now the item says "sold out"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be the only one who received early Christmas gifts - gift cards - that I am now using to buy gifts for others... right? #TuesdayThoughts #shopping #Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you feel about people using the f word and the sh word on social media? In memes or otherwise? It bugs... https://t.co/u9obTRUzkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darikforeal I'll be in Florida where it will be 81 and sunny. ðŸŒžðŸŒ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will have one of each please. And 2 of Maine's molasses cookies that my mom always made. https://t.co/jusBhjrivt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinOnTV @SouthwestAir Only airline we ever trusted with our daughter flying solo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awwww... @SouthwestAir always the best!! #SouthwestAirlines #Southwest https://t.co/5wgPmucW7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocco did not like Santa in 2013. https://t.co/GsXSd3M0iM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of big celebs celebrating birthdays today... Brad Pitt @KatieHolmes212 @Sia @xtina Steven Spielberg, Ray Liotta, Stone Cold Steve Austin and Keith Richards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskTarget Thanks! I shopped some more and it died down pretty quickly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you do this too
@Target #TargetRun #TARGET https://t.co/zXitbPCapS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tis the season for this long long long line at @Target! #TARGET #shopping #christmas #tistheseason https://t.co/eDbuItr7c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally ordering @LedoPizza on this snowy night... now to get thru the awful worse than usual #dctraffic #pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avatarget Gift Card #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oceans Eleven Pipers Piping #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Gonna Gift You Sucka  #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand and Deliver With 2 Day Shipping #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorillas In The Mistletoe #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Framed A Picture Of The Grandkids #GiveAGiftToAFilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romancing the iPhone #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Little Workshop In Texas #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas The Toy Trainwreck #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch Me If You Candy Cane  #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Men and a Baby Doll #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clear &amp; Wrapping Presents Danger #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gloves Actually #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brokebackscratcher Mountain #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Toy Story #giveagifttoafilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good times... https://t.co/hBF7pJBx9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's gonna snow this afternoon and it might stick and get slippery which means #FML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonaLisa85AAR @947FreshFM @1067theFan @tysonritter Yup those are fun songs to belt out! How are you feeling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only there were more hours in the day... https://t.co/fJwRJDNKyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are getting married on May 19 so I hope that's not your wedding date....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who just thinks #CheetosPopcorn = orange powder all over the seats and my lap and my kid's face at the movies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is talking about #LastJedi so we're giving you a chance to win @Fandango vouchers to check it out all weekend on @947FreshFM #StarWars #StarWarsTheLasJedi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I freaking â¤ï¸ @nickjonas https://t.co/kD3nNTSLoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #I66 toll went up to $44 this morning... There goes your Christmas gift...  #HighwayRobbery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @TommyMcFLY for sharing some of the @Lindt_Chocolate truffles from @CandyUSA! https://t.co/yAUYAOA1Ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did karaoke last night at our @947FreshFM holiday party... What's your favorite song to sing when you do #Karaoke? I sang "Summer Nights" with Jackie from @1067theFan #holidayparty #wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is ðŸ˜‚#ByeFelicia #Omarosa #OmarosaGotFiredParty #RobinRoberts https://t.co/IQWLBmD43c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCCelebrity @947FreshFM @Wawa Haha maybe when the hype wears off... I'm not waiting in that line!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carters Eggs &amp; taters!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>