<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chronicle: Women value #highered more highly than men do: http://t.co/JlIQhp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day two of Hatter Productions retreat!! #leggo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though Im exhausted, I had an absolutley amazing first day at Stetson! #HatterProductionsRulez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glee 3D makes me want to go sing karaoke tonight, anyone down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artibagga tell me about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thatawkwardmomentwhen its your last day working somewhere and the entire office goes out to lunch without inviting you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry Im late to the congratulations party but congrats @johnzajicekjr !!!!!! #cohortlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneReigns perfect!! So epic!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xoflowers OMG, Im literally watching it right now!! Its for sure making the list!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need motivational and pumping up youtube clips for my programming board retreat, whats your fave motivational speech from tv show/movie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the youngest person on this casino boat by at least 20 years #newportwrinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the rays game with the 'rents #gorays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stoked @CollegeGameDay will be at the  FSU v Oklahoma game! #gonoles #corsobetterweartheheadress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently Im officially irrelevant since Im not even being introduced to new GAs #awkward #Istillhave3daysleft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last day at ucf osi was capped off with some great fsu news and a nature movie for the ride home #winning #gonoles #gosealions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading professional development books for work makes me feel so important and sophisticated #sagrad #prodevo #beatsreadingforretention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had an absolutely perfect day, but im sooo excited to crawl into bed! #beacheswearmeout #sodofabdragqueens #cohortlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These past two days have been one of the most refreshing and fantastic experiences I have had so far in grad school #StetsonLove #OSILove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo tonights staff teambuilding activty is karaoke #awesome #obvssingingsometswift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was a complete affirmation that I am exactly where I am supposed to be #GREATday #ILoveStetson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just heard a freshman describe daniel tosh as his idol #smh #chooseabetterrolemodel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week is going to be bananas, but its totally worth it so that I can attend a two and a half day retreat with my new Stetson fam...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo after several hours of watching My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding, I still dont get Gypsy culture... #confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZOMG!! MR SHUE IS SINGING SWAY #SWOON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok "midnight red" aka laaaammmee opening opening act, no one cares #givememrshue #nkotbsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently every nkotbsb member has a solo career... #relivingthe90s #sostoked #nkotbsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artibagga thanks, but we just headed straight inside lol, we should hang afterwords!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo stoked for nkotbsb!! Ps we are probably going to go somewhere after let me know if you want to join!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be hangin tough with @misst7 and #stephanieneedsatwitter at 
#NKOTBSB tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laura_Cosenzo @artibagga what time/where do you lovely ladies want to do dinner? PS anyone else is welcome to join!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New bloggy blog up! http://t.co/UUWXcoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jana_heath thanks! #cohortlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xoflowers thanks! #cohortlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artibagga @johnzajicekjr @jimmy3_k thanks #cohortlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnzajicekjr programming board :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just accepted my dream graduate assistant position, couldnt be more excited!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xojazi I think this website just became your new bff http://t.co/304Yftd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im all about free speech, but having your 5 and 6 year olds pass out pamphlets in front of abortion pictures is rather disgusting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for #NASPAFLDriveIn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am completely blown away by this #StetsonValuesDay discussion! #sagrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to jump out of a plane with my programming boad students, nbd #stuact #sagrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just finished my last group presentation of grad school! #beginningoftheend #sachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ThatAwkwardMomentWhen you wan to go to the gym and your roomate and her boyfriend are having a huge fight in the living room...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cponder7: Tough loss but ALWAYS a Nole fan #ProudTweet keep your heads up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poll 92636]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win or lose, I still love my #Noles!  We totes still have the #ACCChampionship and #OrangeBowl to look forward to! #CharlotteBoundFoSho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying in DeLand until halftime so I miss as little #FSU football as possible? Thats #dedication #GONOLES #BeatOkaCHOKEma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love seeing the boys of @collegegameday at langford green!! #gonoles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wif76283 What do you want to see at Stetson?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got an amazing text message from a student! Its awesome to know you made a positive impact on someone's day! #SAgrad #LoveUHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CollegeGameDay: Reminder, we're going to Tallahassee next Saturday for a Top 5 showdown between the #Sooners and #Seminoles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tailgating with the cohort #gameday #goknights #gonoles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI, NEVER EVER use @geeksquad to fix your computer! A week and a half later and I STILL dont have my computer back #terriblecustomerservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm you might have won Auburn, but you should have killed Utah State #embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My definition of a perfect Saturday morning: pancakes, family and @CollegeGameDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this class real life? #poems #dancing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging with my wolfpack @hatterproductns tonight and watching Hangover 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ragefest day two with @hatterproductns #lovetheseguys #legit #focus2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ragefest with @hatterproductns #legit #focus2011 #glowstickseverywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had an absolutely amazing week with @HatterProductns!! Sooo excited to see what these awesome kids do this year!! #legit #presh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nacaboardchair So many great ideas!! Awesome chat!! #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nacaboardchair for advertising we use facebook & twitter as staples,but we also use poll everwhere,a polling service through txt #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who have done bingo before, how do you generate the bingo cards? #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecraske its basically like speed dating, but with more of "making friends" then dating twist to it  #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nacaboardchair it isnt targeted for first year students,we held it this year in September and we had a variety of students attend #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fr33nAcc3ptd11 we do a speed friending event as well for the beginning of the semester and it works great! #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Sorry Im late, my name is Katie and I am a graduate assistant at @StetsonU working with w/ @HatterProductns #nacachat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In and out of Florida Mall in under an hour and a half #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come it took me this long to see how sexy Zach Gilford is? #cleareyesfullheartslovemattsaracen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So pumped to see what 2012 brings #timefoforarealjob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Defense, just so you know, we started the game now, so if you could show up, that would be great...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my fellow GA brought in her lil bro to work and my day has been filled with Disney movies, Dora, and Backyardigans #yaychildhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do yourself a flavor and get sugar cookie sleigh ride herbal tea #soamazing #iseewhatyoudidthere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be heading to GA for #Thanksgiving!  Now if only Apple could invent a self packing suitcase....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging with two of my fave students at islands of adventure #chaperoningisawesome #sagrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know of a poem or story that is inspiring that involves an object that can be given to students as a takeaway? #stuact #sagrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True Life: My Apartment Is Incredibly Awkward and Uncomfortable Because of a Terrible Roomate #roomateproblems #cantwaittogotoworktomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using my conflict resolution skills like a boss #roomateproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-12 hours, we are going to rock it! @misst7 @artibagga @johnzajicekjr @jana_heath @xojazi @xoflowers @jimmy3_k @Laura_Cosenzo @erinrenee88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officially have gone off the deep end, tonight's study break was spent making a My Little Pony cover for my colorful Comps binder...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan of attack for comps in case I completely blank: relate everything back to Chickering #ChickeringRulez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nom nomz at urban flats then catching a sac comedy show with some of my Stetson faves! #grownupfun #lovedowntown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roadtrips just aren't complete until you stop at a Cracker Barrel #nacasou #truetalk #tylersfirsttime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the literally the 5th "Moves Like Jagger" cover ive heard this weekend #nacasou #switchitup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Carol from Everything But The Mime remembers me from undergrad #totesawesome #nacasou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hai ryan cabrera #nacasou #boyshairhascrazyvolume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free diet coke and pamphlets from the advior resource room #nacasou #offish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaTMZRadke Thanks dear, we love Boston!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaTMZRadke You missed my look of sheer terror/excitement from the large amount of fire #HPMemories #GetOnOurLevel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love if the #budgetfairy could come by the CUB tonight and make everything make sense tomorrow. #budgetpartycontinuestomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#budgetparty with @kkeellyyooo #weloveit #sopumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just submitted my last school assignment probably ever #OMG #Graduationin10days #SAGrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today started out on an awesome foot because my @birchbox account has now gotten active!! #excited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just might faceplant into my desk #budgetproposal2012 #StuAct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's budget work is powered by @vampireweekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing HW in Starbucks because internets are down #FeelsLikeImBackInHS #GradLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drove half an hour just to find out that #cinnebistro is 21+ and my sister is 20, #nohungergames #luckisnotinourfavor #cobbtheatersssuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling that my adventures in lucid dreaming and reading the Hunger Games will create some pretty awesome dreams.  #nerdstatus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my internship but I just want this day to fly by so I can go home and keep reading #hungergames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading home after an awesome experience at #tpe12! Thanks @TPEcanserv for all the support and words of encouragement! #sagrad #sasearch]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>