<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet, Intel, FedEx, AT&amp;T among drone pilot winners: universities: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The Federal Aviation Administration on Wednesday is unveiling 10 pilot projects from counties, cities, states and universities that have been selected to help… https://t.co/hIHcs2nM4f https://t.co/bqnUKTmndi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead – Java – US: We are The Mobile Bank. Our vision is to build a bank the world loves to use. Technology and design empower everything we do. N26 is Europes first Mobile Bank with a full European banking license. We redesigned the banking… https://t.co/Xj6G4AOWAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's ZTE Corp says main business operations have ceased due to U.S. ban: HONG KONG (Reuters) - ZTE Corp's main business operations have ceased due to a ban imposed by the U.S. government, but the Chinese firm is trying to have the ban modified or… https://t.co/DVuptkiBLh https://t.co/gHoObeu9OE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/oYVLcDMIMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/zojBLgPAjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital Markets Inst. Ops. Support Analyst 3 – Tax Operations SME: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/85qECEc1x9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vodafone to pay $21.8 billion for Liberty assets to strengthen European presence: LONDON (Reuters) - Vodafone has agreed to pay $21.8 billion to buy Liberty Global's assets in Germany, the Czech Republic, Hungary and Romania to take on rivals with a… https://t.co/luofq8tuAn https://t.co/NfUjLon1yB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/eAAVuy51cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN-Graduate: Job ID: 238699 RN-Graduate Murfreesboro, Tennessee Regular / Rotating Additional Job Information Title: RN-Graduate City, State:  Murfreesboro,TN Location:  Saint Thomas Rutherford Hospital Department:   Nurse Education 001 Additional Job… https://t.co/hE5WsK96dc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/DQTqJgefwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook shakes up management, launches blockchain division: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook Inc Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg on Tuesday ordered one of the biggest management shakeups in the history of the social network, giving more responsibility… https://t.co/ATn7dJG17H https://t.co/f3sH0AHShC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/8bzvZwyQ6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Analyst 5 – Senior Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) Analyst: Job Description It starts with you. Our goal is to attract, develop, retain, and motivate the most talented people – those who care and who work together as partners across… https://t.co/nYEZl8q79P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4 – Enterprise PM Tools and Automation Business Analyst: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/cTnN7pDycV https://t.co/9SbrAM6bXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Data Engineering/Query Engine (Mid-level, Senior, and Principal level openings): Join our team and experience Workday! It’s fun to work in a company where people truly believe in what they’re doing. At Workday, we’re committed to… https://t.co/rrzCU5GugO https://t.co/r6bi4Ca7Be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Build &amp; Release Engineer: Senior Build &amp; Release Engineer This role will contribute to the continuous improvement and standards definition of common processes that will be implemented to ensure consistent, high-quality delivery of software in our… https://t.co/o6MR6Y8FPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's updated virtual assistant can book appointments: MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif.(Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's Google on Tuesday showed off an updated virtual assistant that can call restaurants, hair salons and other businesses to check hours and make… https://t.co/gzaeVCqBa5 https://t.co/IV9uJ3BIYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Specialist: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Business Analytics… https://t.co/RUA7taRrAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook to block foreign ads in Irish abortion referendum: DUBLIN (Reuters) - Facebook will no longer accept advertisements from outside Ireland related to the country's May 25 abortion referendum, the U.S. firm said on Tuesday, in its latest move to… https://t.co/XUsKAMF2hx https://t.co/2XVN7Lz6Kt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSA Capture Manager: Req ID 98043BR Business Title NSA Capture Manager Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Hanover Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Marketing, Sales &amp; Business Development Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is currently seeking a… https://t.co/YCnvCeJX2P https://t.co/JCQDtO1SLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Full-Stack Developer The Motley Fool is looking to hire a software developer that has a knack for implementing deployment and automation tools for web applications. Does this sound like you? Great – you sound like a good fit for our… https://t.co/nqWj1BOeIA https://t.co/4mg2KENFlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Data Engineer within PNC’s Enterprise Data… https://t.co/swtY4sXsLz https://t.co/REdw4W1HX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber hires former NTSB chair to advise on safety culture after fatal crash: (Reuters) - Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] said Monday it has hired a former National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) chairman to advise the company on its safety culture… https://t.co/wseabCON5G https://t.co/aV2sWfElGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Lead: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Application Developer Lead… https://t.co/2OdPQ4Sd8i https://t.co/sVHm2gObqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffett bashes bitcoin as nonproductive, thriving on mystique: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Billionaire investor Warren Buffett on Monday said buyers of bitcoin, which he characterizes as "rat poison squared", thrive on the hope they'll find someone else who… https://t.co/8EmIzKTmIw https://t.co/nKs6m3bjaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Business Process Engineer (Prospect-to-Customer) (P-Mod): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely… https://t.co/U8ruGSuUrm https://t.co/dE0KiUOzgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Technical Support – Incident Response (Sucuri): About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under… https://t.co/Tin2S6jiBV https://t.co/4nsXwio8tU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire Alarm Project Manager: Job Description Fire Alarm Project Manager (WD***********) What you will do: As a Field Project Manager, you are responsible for profitable execution of assigned projects, including project delivery, estimating, and financial… https://t.co/HZbBWqQ1P8 https://t.co/Jdxen26eSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appian Developer: Appian Developer Ref No.: 18-18406 Location: Boston, Massachusetts Title:- Appian BPM Developer Location:- Boston MA Contract W2 Role Must-Have 1. Minimum 4 yrs of Appian BPM experience. 2. Appian Workflow implementation experience. 3.… https://t.co/APH00Zruxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Lead: We are looking for an experienced Software Quality Assurance Lead to join our team. You will make a significant contribution to our existing software development department here at Christopherson Business Travel. The… https://t.co/T0vD2wxMzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chip designer Mediatek gets Taiwan nod to export goods to ZTE: TAIPEI (Reuters) - Taiwanese chip designer Mediatek Inc has received an export permit from the government to sell components to ZTE Corp, a Chinese telecoms equipment maker subjected to… https://t.co/HgEq5TOXHa https://t.co/Czfii7ADPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Engineer: TriNet is a leading provider of comprehensive human resources solutions for small to midsize businesses (SMBs). We enhance business productivity by enabling our clients to outsource their HR function to one strategic partner and… https://t.co/84op6oDHbd https://t.co/2rvyR6ffYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three-quarters Facebook users as active or more since privacy scandal: Reuters/Ipsos poll: NEW YORK/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Most of Facebook's U.S. users have remained loyal to the social network despite revelations that a political consultancy… https://t.co/iEDSfpZ1mW https://t.co/fidbE9wsNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Solutions Architect: What You’ll Do A Customer Solutions Architect (CSA) is a senior technical salesperson that works with customers, account executives and sales engineering leadership to develop strategies that deliver business outcomes based… https://t.co/GobFkW5Ncc https://t.co/pBiSwGYKUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst: Job ID: ****** Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst , Missouri Regular ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst CITY, STATE: MO LOCATION: MOSTL Virtual – MO DEPARTMENT: Budgeting… https://t.co/9js5XVNkot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Integration Engineer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.       We are… https://t.co/mvPMHb0Fix https://t.co/K924JfJBeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffett owns 5 percent of Apple. He'd like to own more: OMAHA, Neb. (Reuters) - Warren Buffett said he would be happy if his conglomerate Berkshire Hathaway Inc owned more than 5 percent of Apple Inc's stock, including if the iPhone maker bought back… https://t.co/QxRPtafwGI https://t.co/pWPzMN7M5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inventory Control/Quality Assurance Manage – Relo offered for laterals: Position Description * Communicate with (or to) individuals or groups verbally and/or in writing (e.g. customers, suppliers, associates). * Identify associate, customer, and/or… https://t.co/MsfzZyvO9G https://t.co/Y4kIUHoIf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II: Overview Business Analyst II (BA) will be assigned items from our road map and will be tasked with creating requirements/user stories &amp; acceptance criteria by eliciting feedback from internal and external stakeholders.  The BSA works… https://t.co/T78EqEVzNP https://t.co/9Az9p2i4hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Services SalesForce (SFDC) Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/50VtjSaJ4W https://t.co/v01VtYinBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facilities Project Manager: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Tyndall Air Force Base, FL Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy… https://t.co/6bm1uzwlKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.:18-06700 Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 04/12/2018 Job Title – .NET Developer Job Location – Minneapolis, MN Duration- Fulltime Required Skills – – Primary .Net, MS SQL,… https://t.co/7jOTtlwOF5 https://t.co/hqAAZukKYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and… https://t.co/JQUxcrnuLt https://t.co/lfPHrJ9nUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D Software Developer (#3685DP042618): COMPANY DESCRIPTION * Company has over 50 years of industry experience * Company is employee owned (ESOP member) * Creates software for use in the medical and healthcare industries JOB DESCRIPTION * Responsible for… https://t.co/dkVf2cs9sY https://t.co/nLnrgZqJbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW UX Architect: CW UX Architect (******) Plano, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 04/30/18, Posted Date – 04/30/18 Primary SkillsUX UITax TermsW-2Overview * Description: Design and user experience (UX) are at the forefront of everything we do. The… https://t.co/ABwDZX7jAB https://t.co/oSCGVuUBFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk/Technical Support Specialist: FHLBank Topeka’s products, services and programs help our member financial institutions provide affordable credit and support housing and community development efforts. We are accepting resumes for the position… https://t.co/TK93a0zLhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Application Architect II or III: Basin Electric Power Cooperative Dakota Gasification Company Enterprise Application Architect II or Enterprise Application Architect III • Responsible for the conceptualizing, designing, development,… https://t.co/DTFw2z6KxU https://t.co/81Bcdf3It3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China asks U.S. to amend ZTE business ban - sources: BEIJING (Reuters) - China has asked the United States to amend a seven-year ban on American companies selling components and software to Chinese telecom equipment firm ZTE Corp, two sources with… https://t.co/J5o6ZFCOgZ https://t.co/4JdgvUoMhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java/Scala Engineer: TAISTech Catalogue Team is in need of a Sr. Java engineer with experience in Scala. For our Catalog team, we are looking for Strong Java developers who know Scala. The bulk of their Spark Streaming jobs are written in Scala which… https://t.co/e8EpENvhaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer – OpenShift: Red Hat Jobs – Explore Open Source Career Opportunities &amp; Online Skip to content – – Find a job – Job categories – Technology – Sales + Services – Marketing – Corporate – Internships – Locations – Asia Pacific –… https://t.co/Zt7ra1JZ8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (C++): Jobs PRENAV: Precision Navigation for Drones – Home – About Us – Jobs – Blog – Contact Us – Home – About Us – Jobs – Blog – Contact Us Jobs WORKING AT PRENAV Robotics is one of the most challenging disciplines to work in… https://t.co/TW1Rbk4mtA https://t.co/YfFaNaA4vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway bought 75 million more Apple shares in first quarter: CNBC: (Reuters) - Berkshire Hathaway Inc bought 75 million additional Apple Inc shares in the first three months of the year, CEO Warren Buffett told CNBC on Thursday,… https://t.co/7eh6Bv4GZl https://t.co/QeMw9oIYqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoPro sells more cameras on ad push, driving revenue beat: (Reuters) - Action-camera maker GoPro Inc's first-quarter revenue beat expectations and it reported a smaller-than-expected loss on Thursday, benefiting from aggressive marketing of its cameras… https://t.co/JHhDnPgPXs https://t.co/LZT9nteddq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Engineering -Information Technology Opening for degree and/or experienced applicants for Business Systems Analyst in Arlington Heights, Illinois and other multiple undetermined work sites throughout the United States. recblid… https://t.co/73nNs5mapD https://t.co/neTuh1EokL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Engineer: Database Engineer Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Hardware Development Engineer (Req#AHPPLW) Dsgn, dev, test, &amp; mnitor the manufctring of high-perf camera lenses for mbile dvices. Travel req. 20%. Software… https://t.co/xZm7ZdwQzN https://t.co/yz9Iv7d4ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robots help artist bring fine bison hair to pricey paintings: NEW YORK (Reuters) - American artist Barnaby Furnas has turned to a custom-made robot to help him with paintings that can sell for more than $100,000 at New York galleries. https://t.co/BtRG8Bcexa https://t.co/rnZOFA1P4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Product Manager: TECHNOLOGY Associate Product Manager professional needed at Wal-Mart in Sunnyvale, CA. Master’s or equiv in CS, Eng’g (Any), or rel. field. Walmart will accept any amount of prof’l exp w/req’d skills. For specific job duties,… https://t.co/SOmgWTCfOM https://t.co/wR6RbfWNGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join our… https://t.co/9WFzyGSovM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Help Desk Technician: Help Desk Technician Irvine, CA Temp-to-perm (6 months) $25-$30 per hour A nation-wide Home Builder has an immediate need for a Level 1/ Level 2 Help Desk Technician in Irvine. This position will be a 6 month contract position,… https://t.co/vFPB8cYTJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In U.S. Gulf, robots, drones take on dangerous offshore oil work: HOUSTON (Reuters) - At BP's massive Thunder Horse oil platform in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico, a dog-sized robot called Maggie uses magnetic tracks to creep along pipes connecting the giant… https://t.co/JxXcQPfiSF https://t.co/ADtkGvsYum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management 4 (San Diego, CA):   Job Description – Project Management 4 (San Diego, CA) (18004373) Project Management 4 (San Diego, CA) Requisition ID : 18004373 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/flnMzHoNbD https://t.co/8Yh5gb4GaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Programs 3 (Maintenance Manager):   Job Description – Manager, Programs 3 (Maintenance Manager) (18004692) Manager, Programs 3 (Maintenance Manager) Requisition ID : 18004692 Location : United States-California-Palmdale US Citizenship Required… https://t.co/aTFhimSdVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Analyst: The Team: Fueling the technologies that drive our products and support our company s infrastructure, the Technology team consists of talented developers, network architects, and IT experts who help make technology one of… https://t.co/6HmXkbBrkZ https://t.co/wQEWRlalQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Programmer III: Job Title CNC Programmer III Job ID(Requisition ID): 3535 Job Summary Precision Technologies Tempe, a division of Benchmark Electronics, Inc. has an extensive capability in mechanical manufacturing. Our customers are leading Original… https://t.co/cClnW9RNKa https://t.co/JSsuYDdQr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM bets on 3D printers for cheaper and lighter car parts: DETROIT (Reuters) - General Motors Co said on Thursday it was working with design software company Autodesk Inc to manufacture new, lightweight 3D-printed parts that could help the automaker meet… https://t.co/JT4bdhqAyg https://t.co/3lSlapckxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poorest U.S. consumers seen hit hard by T-Mobile, Sprint merger: (Reuters) - The poorest U.S. consumers would lose most from the proposed tie-up of wireless carriers T-Mobile US Inc and Sprint Corp, according to consumer advocates who warned the combined… https://t.co/j6lDYfa4vR https://t.co/Pr1W21hFXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Factor Engineer: Engineering: Human Factor Engineer (Irvine, CA) Eyefinity, Inc.: Develop user interface designs for web, tablet, mobile, &amp; desktop user applications; lead/improve process of defining user interface application design &amp; behavior.  … https://t.co/tE1kn691HH https://t.co/NLioVjawa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Data Architect Senior Associate – Consumer Market: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/ZkQyYs5fWk https://t.co/nVuOdr7Tu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSB chief executive to lose bonus linked to computer system migration: LONDON (Reuters) - The Chief Executive of British lender TSB, Paul Pester, will not receive a bonus that he was due and which was linked to the bank's botched computer system… https://t.co/jTbsWu6DJ1 https://t.co/qB0RvPOzSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Test: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/eRR5tpmhpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Managers: Richmond based Manufacturer looking for Project Managers / Coordinators to work closely with Engineering, Manufacturing, &amp; Customers to process orders through the factory and transition them to Field Service Complete resume required… https://t.co/miDKvY0fsn https://t.co/HcwL2S19Pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon offers to buy 60 percent stake in India's Flipkart: CNBC-TV18: (Reuters) - https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc has made a formal offer to buy a 60 percent stake in Indian online retailer Flipkart, CNBC-TV18 reported on Wednesday, citing sources. https://t.co/NZ9LCCMCBJ https://t.co/5zNNCaNeOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Job details Job title Senior Software Developer Job reference FXP00400 Application closing date Location Penryn, Cornwall Salary 34,203 per annum Contract type Permanent, Full time, 37.5 hours per week, 52 weeks per year. Job… https://t.co/S2lYWKjAkH https://t.co/mJvBgu9zW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Technical Consultant – Cisco Solutions- Central Region IL, MN, MI, MO, KS, OK: Looking for the next step in your career? Enjoy a challenge? Do you have an ambition for innovation? Want to make a difference? If you join our growing global team,… https://t.co/FEcwb98eRR https://t.co/xQ2aPvGrhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer with microservices: Java developer with microservices Ref No.: 18-18101 Location: Seattle, Washington Role: Java developer with Microservices Position: W2 preferred Duration: 12 months location: Seattle WA Skills: Javascript, html, xml… https://t.co/zt6yraYcjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Solutions Architect St. Louis, MO: Sr Solutions Architect Client: CMMi Level 5 Company St. Louis, MO Full Time Position Summary: As a hands-on Senior Solutions Architect, the candidate must possess the necessary IT consulting experience to be fully… https://t.co/sj2vRk2avs https://t.co/ZpkbpjCwd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyberwarfare, populism top 'black swan' events at Milken conference: BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (Reuters) - Cyberwarfare and populism are some of the top risks that could threaten global stability and financial markets in the years ahead, investors and… https://t.co/UstIJZ4tuw https://t.co/663vzGk9mU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Sigma Infosolutions Inc. S/W dev. &amp; Services CO. in Irvine, CA has openings for S/W Dev. Resp. Understand &amp; translate user req. into well engineered &amp; integrated tech. solutions &amp; reusable components. Design &amp; program… https://t.co/ZTDCJRuQsz https://t.co/zXBQ9GHNTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap's user growth misses analyst forecasts, shares plunge: (Reuters) - Snap Inc's user and revenue growth fell short of analysts' expectations for the first quarter after a widely panned redesign of its Snapchat messaging app, sending its shares… https://t.co/eS2FyDfyY1 https://t.co/QvVcaGQhzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK lawmakers prepared to summon Facebook boss Zuckerberg over data scandal: LONDON (Reuters) - British parliamentarians said they were prepared to issue a formal summons for Facebook Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg to appear before them and answer… https://t.co/M1hmnmRRBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – SailPoint Developer – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/q7Lo7tmO9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operation Product Manager – Eden Prairie, MN: Primary Responsibilities: * Day-to-day Program Management including resolving member benefit access issues * Support benefit development and execution * Support short and long-term goals for Program *… https://t.co/9R889sbHjG https://t.co/DXDq9YGQHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: We’re looking for a IT professional who will thrive supporting a variety corporate clients and their users. This position is in our Durham-based support center, and will provide support to our clients remotely (over the… https://t.co/lcuy0kxLDx https://t.co/g4isXIuKJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Web Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Front-End Web Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Senior Front-End Developer that can create engaging web applications that… https://t.co/ZFes1WSPqB https://t.co/vLGSTn3nZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore airport may use facial recognition systems to find late passengers: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Ever been delayed on a flight because of straggling fellow passengers? https://t.co/J7k8iK1kXb https://t.co/P0U0LrfG3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Description What is the opportunity? – Work as a front office software developer to implement software platforms/micro services within Client Enablement and Banking. – This position requires the ability to work effectively within… https://t.co/eVD3cgnMib https://t.co/tyGMguzNG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator, Senior: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and… https://t.co/hNGllLxast https://t.co/kYf6KT28CX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: SOFTWARE ENGINEER w/ Red Hat Inc. in Raleigh, NC. Senior Systems Engineer on our Infrastructure Services Measurement &amp; Metrics team. Support &amp; evolve our measurement &amp; metrics service portfolio, specifically w/ our Site Reliability… https://t.co/dM3sPwqAOU https://t.co/KeK6FDOnUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: PayPal, Inc. has the following job opportunities in San Jose, CA: Global Pricing SOX Operations (Req.#16-3596): Work w/ SOX (Sarbanes-Oxley) Internal Controls program planning activities for Pricing process, including materiality,… https://t.co/i9eEu6zqwi https://t.co/5kPJbUY25w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Analyst: IT Security Analyst ABC58558361 *Richmond, VA* A lead security analyst role in a information security policy development project.  Requires ability to quickly process and organize information, in both written and oral formats.  Must… https://t.co/9cEDjfdr8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian telecom stocks face minimal 5G risks - JP Morgan: (Reuters) - Shares of Asian telecom players have already priced in the impact of investments for setting up fifth generation (5G) mobile networks and potential monetization uncertainty, J.P. Morgan… https://t.co/XjKEEal5WV https://t.co/X5qX2yLaqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required:   Job Description – Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required (17027927) Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required Requisition ID : 17027927… https://t.co/8mMFcXiJpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Multi-Disciplined Eng II: 109657BR Sr Multi-Disciplined Eng II CO – Aurora 109657BR Raytheon IIS/GIS provides Operations and Maintenance support for the Intelligence Community Job Description: This Sr. Multi-Disciplined Engineer II will work within… https://t.co/xKrgbbQFJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering UNIX/Linux Technician (Consultant): Engineering UNIX/Linux Technician (Consultant) Orangeburg Posted Feb 2, 2018 – Requisition No. 64957 An exciting opportunity exists for a UNIX/Linux technician within a world-class Operations center. You… https://t.co/aYTDde9aoy https://t.co/TnmT57HqmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Engineer Asc: Req ID : 430237BR Job Code/Title : E2541:Info Assurance Engineer Asc Job Description : This position is for an Information Assurance Engineer Asc working for Lockheed Martin Enterprise Business Systems (EBS). The primary… https://t.co/0GqO18kTqW https://t.co/kXji62n12w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist (4/18): Overview Utilizes basic computer technology skills as entry level technician to investigate and resolve software and hardware issues experienced by students using our products and offerings. Essential duties and… https://t.co/XLcE2Zu2zo https://t.co/3sV0sDtD9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Admin and Systems Architect: JumpCrew is building a team to support our new headquarters in Nashville. Were entrepreneurs with a track record of building and managing successful businesses. Were passionate about our serving our clients well… https://t.co/q8hei03JFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft End User Computing Developer: Microsoft End User Computing Developer McLean, VA or Carrollton, TX The position is a Developer Professional who will be supporting the EUC Program Office within Information Technology division. The candidate will… https://t.co/g5Ktw1yasZ https://t.co/6goTuTDFJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Baidu to sell majority of financial services unit for $1.9 billion: (Reuters) - China's Baidu Inc said it will sell a majority stake in its financial services business for about $1.9 billion to a consortium led by TPG Capital Management LP… https://t.co/qZsKIzhcDY https://t.co/tqF9Fubriw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Researcher: User Experience Researcher ========================== Cortina Productions is seeking a passionate, experienced User Experience Researcher to be part of the creative team for the design and development of innovative interactive… https://t.co/stmj3YLLQu https://t.co/ABkHV4oAdC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>