<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/sdZgBI8uTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/SHvQh7mzsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/bXqWUQwIu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/FyuybvO5yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/2kwq6gK0m2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/Jsq4DPcJRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/PzA78NMIII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/QCbjiUPLVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/PKYsKHDeE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/3SEZPqYrcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/I2kSEsyVUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/rA3mW1KWJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/FnoTnFjEBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/PX4SBPUPo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/QebPsokomL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/FSAEOA13S4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/exPzrukWgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/hnEWLctmlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/7LkTIXRoej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/f6YSyE0PB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/udMbAnIu0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/IGEZlDPSEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/HYb4rZk53p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/gUgWVgJXm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/T1YjqQRtEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/6wryQFEVNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/7QGQc5kKFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/NT0LayQOaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/vGGwLTf6WU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/WUM8DNnLZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/t1r2OPZFE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/K58lkOH9ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/SDEqVlt6CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/iRRvnWKjQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/0H673IMb7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/6iM7PTEmHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/nGAlw609cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/yr2IzFAWt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/miHIdD6pI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/wkalhPpV4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/beHGmkMRXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/uFLUZHxXEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/3SEZPqYrcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/zpst98D2Lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/vQczSDMdri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/4vqMUtAGFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/wIXEAJsyeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/ILjbznkhxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your time...don't live too fast, troubles will come and they will pass. - Simple Man - Lynyrd Skynyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/SGs9ZEYVIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/ayNzbMGhU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/6shrOXniov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>