<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/07EOLallnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/K98Iuq93M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/9ZPpcOAjN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/cwVONyE2wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/IeLKXe0vJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/SrxAwMJ4hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/AEuooRZtSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/tqzAZkeQa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/eH6ZYp4vc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All My Friends Are Dead - Kids Book - Darkly Hilarious!  http://t.co/GDQZPNJvUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/sYrxp23Zya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/UTUw7nYrWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/qWIx7iOznD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/uJwi2iABv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine is God's way of saying you're making too much money. - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/n8sXfYl2yf]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/7F1kjArhGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/EE8u7pLjcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/0sL3qBgiFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/wrZRukhAuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/KF9WfAvk4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/dMGM1uB0On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/f0smwX8Mby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/Wmk9goUAWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget how fast you did a job - but they remember how well you did it. - Howard Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/QGp8WC6tRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/92CgeIVtXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/X09cncNuYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/m9KqEJjiK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/lhQSmO1UWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/NFoBfMWiFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/98fD6wDSMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/62mHZofam9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/e9qnur2PIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/SjHSZPaBMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your time...don't live too fast, troubles will come and they will pass. - Simple Man - Lynyrd Skynyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/twezwEDX9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/US9sOnXtjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/XoCRG6aZch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/hX1S8W4KJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/ZLavA9dVDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>