<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattwhouse: Yes. We're just waiting for some well-qualified Cabinet nominees.

We got billionaires and bankers instead. #SwampCabinet h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Heitkamp, who has said she's voting to confirm, also voted to extend debate. https://t.co/CBkW80VcHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the same point Sen. McConnell made to stop @SenWarren from speaking. @SenFranken was denied. https://t.co/vOSMW4VMCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing - @SenFranken points out Barrasso is accusing those against #pollutingPruitt of conduct unbecoming of a senator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barrasso's back on the floor. Last night after defending #pollutingPruitt he went to a polluter lobbyist fundraiser. https://t.co/mQ7A8asS3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley appealing to Hamilton's intent that the Senate stops nominees of "unfit" character, like #pollutingPruitt. 

@Lin_Manuel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCFedGov: HUGE thanks to @SenDuckworth for covering the graveyard shift (1-2am) to oppose #pollutingPruitt as EPA nominee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @grist: Scott Pruitt is just as bad as Betsy Devos https://t.co/27N78vBQ5M https://t.co/9P8IA63lcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Senate dems managed to #holdthefloor all night, @SenJeffMerkley calling for delay in vote on #pollutingPruitt until we see the emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: Confirmation vote must be postponed! Call your senators and urge them to VOTE NO on #Pruitt #Resist #RejectPruitt https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: The Senate should not vote on Scott Pruitt’s nomination until the public can see what’s in these emails. https://t.co/8vf9UeFkRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone was wondering, this is exactly what's happening. Get angry. #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/yKPOa1Juem https://t.co/3VH2SsdkJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And when he wanted to see #pollutingPruitt's emails with polluting industries, @SenMarkey says the answer was "go FOIA yourself." https://t.co/ezUDP02ogv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey points out as EPA admin, #pollutingPruitt would be plaintiff, defendant, judge and jury on cases where he has been suing EPA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to tune in overnight to see what gov't leadership looks like. Thanks @SenMarkey for speaking out against #pollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sad state when the only comparisons for a historically bad cabinet nominee are other cabinet nominees. But here we are. 
#pollutingPruitt https://t.co/RcTpByxrAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pollutingPruitt is as unqualified as Betsy DeVos and as morally outrageous as Jeff Sessions. 
https://t.co/yKPOa1Juem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True leaders going strong in the Senate: @CoryBooker working to #holdthefloor, showing #pollutingPruitt put polluters before children as AG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CoryBooker: Speaking on Senate floor ~10pm ET against Scott Pruitt nomination for @EPA Admin. Watch LIVE on @CSPAN or here: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @womensmarch: .@NRDC says Trump's nominee for EPA administrator, Scott Pruitt, is the worst choice to head the EPA. We stand with the NR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emilyhholden: Okla. judge orders release of #ScottPruitt emails...Tuesday after he's likely already confirmed. By @MikeLeeFW https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Congress actually going after clean water, endangered species, and baby bears all at once? Yep. Samantha Bee: https://t.co/xjr53JIG3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DefendOurFuture: A3: We have made great progress in protecting our air, water and land. We cannot go back. Lives are at stake. #RejectP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @womensmarch: Q3: Why should young people care about who heads the #EPA, and how will it affect this generation? #RejectPruitt #Pollutin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator @KamalaHarris is rocking it during the #pollutingPruitt floor debate, stepping back for the big picture on American ideals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenFranken: I’m voting no on @AGScottPruitt for @EPA Admin, but 1st I’ll be speaking on Senate floor around 3:30 PM CT urging colleague…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRyanParker @AaronCouch there's going to be a big, beautiful 2-meter exhaust port in that wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress' first law signed by @realDonaldTrump makes easier for oil/gas/coal companies to bribe foreign governments. https://t.co/puy78hvhn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCantwell: Scott #Pruitt described himself as “a leading advocate AGAINST the EPA’s activist agenda” in 2016 on his LinkedIn page…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndivisibleTeam: Wait. So, my member of Congress only represents me if I agree with him? No, sorry, try again. https://t.co/Mgm6ud9AIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is happening https://t.co/Rfo9VLMt61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCFedGov: Vote NO on @repdonyoung’s inhumane bill, H.J.Res.69, to allow shooting bear cubs from helicopters and gassing wolves in the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. #Pruitt's record tells me... he's going to take the option most beneficial to polluters, not the one best for public health." @timkaine https://t.co/TWMVz9ceVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt sued against protections for clean water in Chesapeake Bay... as AG of Oklahoma. @timkaine speaking on it now. #pollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: Trump picked the worst group of cabinet nominees in the modern history of America. But EPA nominee Scott Pruitt is the wors…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is also on C-Span now: https://t.co/JRWxio6szv https://t.co/WG1IUCveIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EPWDems: EPW Members call on Republican leadership to postpone Pruitt vote https://t.co/ZP3845hKKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenJeffMerkley: What else is #PollutingPruitt hiding in his thousands of emails with Big Oil? We already know he takes oil industry wor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mulvaney confirmed.

#pollutingPruitt at bat. 

@SenatorCarper demands delay til an OK court requires that he releases emails w/ polluters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where was #pollutingPruitt for Oklahomans' health and safety as AG?  https://t.co/RHIj711h4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOON: Senate finishes voting on Mulvaney, after which, #PollutingPruitt's floor debate will begin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeoDiCaprio: Thank you @SenatorCollins for voting NO on #PollutingPruitt. Call your senators and encourage them to do the same: 866-347…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may start with Allagash or Maine Beer Co. to properly toast @SenatorCollins for her commitment to vote against #pollutingPruitt. https://t.co/HU7FtOmdoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite action yet. #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/HU7FtOmdoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NateSilver538: It can be "fake news" or illegal leaks of classified information but it can't really be both. https://t.co/Ysdokh2l7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to @SenWhitehouse for speaking up against #pollutingPruitt tonight! https://t.co/AtJ84AOo1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCVoters: "I have one simple thing to say: climate change is real and climate change is costly." -@USRepRickNolan https://t.co/orCi1cCV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our own government will be going after our national monuments,  as of this morning. https://t.co/ZDraMFCOEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: All National Monuments Designated Under the Antiquities Act https://t.co/8x8qHZKuPc via @nrdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And by nerds I mean @AaronCouch https://t.co/BdkxTOFjnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female scientist seeking office is named PHOENIX, studies VOLCANOES, has red hair. Help me out here, fellow nerds.

https://t.co/SoxkjPk1qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out for each other this weekend, #climatemarch -ers. https://t.co/6awMxjlEMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Coupled w other rhetoric, clear Trump officials view job as 'drill, Baby, drill,' yielding independence &amp; magically improve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: I've asked @EPA &amp; @EPAScottPruitt repeatedly to ID actions they've taken to reduce air &amp; water pollution more than status q…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Revealingly, Trump officials' #EarthDay op-ed opens w a falsehood. They know they need to address environment, but claim be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Observations to follow, on #EarthDay op-ed by @EPAScottPruitt, @SecretaryZinke &amp; @SecretaryPerry. https://t.co/NPP1KaFcrE v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring back Google Wave!... No? Anyone? https://t.co/JNQhWLyJrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a week of public comment on repealing @EPA rules, #pollutingPruitt has received 2 in favor. 938 against. https://t.co/IH2hOerPW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billyeichner: Looks like the only job Bill O'Reilly will be able to get now is PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question is, can R's consolidate voter support better than D's can capitalize on this crazy upswing. But either way, crazy upswing. https://t.co/8tMYLlSxE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Redistrict: PROJECTION: #GA06 is headed to a 6/20 runoff between Jon Ossoff (D) &amp; Karen Handel (R). @CookPolitical still rates race a T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adriannaq: "The skinny budget is a threat to every community...Trump doesn't get to dictate what happens to our communities --we do!" @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColinACurtis: You know you've got a strong Exec Order when even your own Senior Advisor thinks it's a good idea! 

Wait. https://t.co/M…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: A hundred days into Trump’s presidency, we’ve already seen more than enough. It's time to gather and speak out. https://t.co/W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting interesting. https://t.co/6H7GGe0jvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: .@EPA Not to mention, the owners of the coal mine have been trying to get out of the coal business for years.
https://t.co/rYqPHX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Today, Pruitt delivered his vision for the @EPA from a coal mine.

A mine that was fined $3M for Clean Water Act violations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMConstible: #Climate action is stalled with the feds, but Northeast &amp; Mid-Atlantic states are pushing for a healthier future. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently, government shouldn't protect the environment from polluters--it should just protect Scott Pruitt.  https://t.co/S56VF4zso7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tlongpine: Early #ks04 post-mortem: https://t.co/NY0UEAAwn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidaxelrod: If America's worst polluters could write the federal budget, it would not look any different than this. https://t.co/kfhs…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's one of those days where "Six Meetings Before Lunch" sounds like a cakewalk. But also, now I'm eating cake. @WestWingWeekly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesThompsonKS: We are Democrats, the party of working people, and we must fight. Fight every battle, no matter the odds. Fight for ou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tlongpine: Politicos &amp; press new to KS Elections: Sedgwick Co. Election Commissioner is going to take her time and still make mistakes.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Taniel: 2 points relevant to tonight: 
—#KS04 significantly redder than either #GA06 &amp; #MTAL.
—All 3 significantly redder than the medi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That this is a nail biter is amazing. Congrats to @ColinACurtis @JamesThompsonKS and @KansasDems for fighting the good fight either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryanstruyk: In Mulvane, one of those crucial small towns near Wichita for Estes. Trump won 65-25% in November. Estes is BEHIND 64-36% i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does this keep getting worse? https://t.co/FROjUxWxGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ericgeller: "These people spoke on the condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to describe the plans for the Easter Egg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @imdanielsalazar: (1/16) Good morning. You might have heard we have a little vote today. Here's a nearly-complete rundown of @kansasdotc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WeatherKait: You're paying for climate change even if you don't live near a beach and even if you don't believe it is real.
https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnDingell: Know anyone in the Wichita, KS area? Remind them to vote tomorrow. Dem candidate @JamesThompsonKS is an Army vet &amp; civil r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @patricey: 2 days left! #KS04 special election is tomorrow. @JamesThompsonKS https://t.co/WL9Yl6YT43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnJHarwood: Trump, w/newly sworn-in Justice Gorsuch in Rose Garden : "I want to thank Mitch McConnell for all he did to make this ach…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KY coal mining museum converts to solar power - "It's a little ironic."
 https://t.co/NyBaV4S6pT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eerie, or a stroke of marketing genius? Ads for going to Canada are showing up all over @washingtonpost as I read up on today's news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bradplumer: It's hard to get US elites enthused about humanitarian intervention unless it entails blowing stuff up https://t.co/W7Vv8Nq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepAdamSchiff: When McConnell  deprived President Obama of a vote on Garland, it was a nuclear option. The rest is fallout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: .@SenJeffMerkley just completed 15 hours of speech on the Senate floor against Gorsuch comination  https://t.co/JK6EFdBz3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: The Trump Administration broke the law by arbitrarily approving the #KeystoneXL pipeline. Here’s how. https://t.co/W1KFL0qjOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's @EPA ramming through approvals of dangerous pesticide while buddying up to Dow Chemical's CEO: https://t.co/wCZGhFWatA @maddow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cleanaircouncil: .@GovernorTomWolf what is your plan to #CutMethane from existing #natgas facilities that are already polluting our air?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch That is some Khal-Drogo-level boasting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WRIClimate: EPA + Defense both protect Americans, but Trump wants to shrink EPA's teeny tiny budget. @TheDailyShow explains: https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: By the numbers: more clean energy jobs than coal, oil, &amp; gas jobs combined. And clean energy jobs are growing fast. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: These are more than statistics, they’re American lives at risk because this administration willfully ignores the scienc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all of that sun we're importing from outer space. https://t.co/VLsEJ0wY7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katie_at_sea good to see you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: Suds, not duds. On the same day President Trump rolls back climate efforts; Budweiser is going 100% clean energy https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Science saves lives. Science is the key to protecting the planet." Thanks @SenMarkey for speaking out against Trump's EO! #DefendClimate https://t.co/4Jr3vc5HIS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>