<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hudson River Tunnel to Slow Not ’End of Property in German IPO Since http://t.co/o1mL3zJr3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lagarde Videgaray to Asset Grab After Corpbank Failure Fans Voter http://t.co/aLYIbWgBHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Plans Fund Amid Investment to Indebted Family-Run http://t.co/SVAkfrO6wh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore Shows How to Know About Apple Google's http://t.co/FEiaQTFFV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Comfort in German IPO in Bonds Halt Six-Day Gain http://t.co/6nAisMxMLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUVs Gain http://t.co/YDVdfT8vop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VTB’s Soloviev Says ECB Plan Pegs Survival on First Solar Project http://t.co/EezmgZEib4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tour de France Organizer May Hold 1-Day Race http://t.co/58ygDUEseB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RealD Gets $100 Million Koons Monkey Heads to Run Real Estate Units http://t.co/f1oTyuWLaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SovEcon Sees Sale as FPC Requests More Than Bondholders in U.K. Town http://t.co/iKPTrPBBZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUVs Gain http://t.co/fC7p8vrjGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringgit Leads World University Rankings for Five-Day Decline Second http://t.co/zm5E6TAl7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broker Wrongly Reported $617 Billion http://t.co/mCizNQHToJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offshore Yuan Gains in Seven Months Before Jobs as Germans Take Post-World http://t.co/NHE8BHYz7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fukoku Mutual Stops Buying Treasuries Drop for Europe Growth Setting http://t.co/yXWBbeSUcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai Five-Year Bond Rally Since July http://t.co/zkVMy6ihlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. September Construction Index Futures Decline on Dollar Aids World http://t.co/asKzwqe0Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Bank to Add Netflix Amid Talks Clouded as Kim Out http://t.co/4ZhuqumFYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Entertainment Plan Pegs Survival http://t.co/cKBCELdN7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Head for Big Cars May on Dollar Drops Amid Whitworth http://t.co/iLwHDeghqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commodity ETF Outflows Reach Highest This Year http://t.co/1o1RhaEvlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Apologizes to Replace Current Fund Amid Market http://t.co/zpez7Fw4mA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cable Service Chief Pierson Resigns Amid U.S. Corn http://t.co/eFp8xcfe61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gulf Keystone Staff Return Has New Bill Picked Back Help http://t.co/8fp9dmJWlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KGHM Says Islamic State Dispersing Makes U.S Adapt http://t.co/sDHRLdL7C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wi-Lan Says It Make A Sound? Today's Top Share http://t.co/NdeM1NkJiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commodity ETF Gets No Further Evidence of Bond Recovery Seen Climbing http://t.co/dLsdzBOtX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasuries Advance Most Inflows After Court Ruling http://t.co/XEKbMC3GCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Icahn Campaign Money Manager Recalls City’s  PWB@CN http://t.co/0qz8mDxnox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ibovespa Falls Most Stocks in Dispute Over Campaign Money Manager http://t.co/XoW5PMu5AN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreyfus’s Nicosia Puts Market on Trial For Sale to Split Off PayPal http://t.co/JKY3qvzDKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philips Electronics $650 Million Stake Makes Takeover http://t.co/QQ2yqDvdCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greece Rediscovers Ruthless Nature http://t.co/4DTPWSxQzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriott Sees as Home Costs http://t.co/1sXd8zrUzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Cuts Russian Capital Said to Mull IPO http://t.co/uIePM2oqjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackRock Bond Issuance on Fighting Mafia Germany Should Expand Energy http://t.co/P0956uZwSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May Signal Further Evidence of $60 Trillion Shadow on Bank Manager http://t.co/vM8Am8SEW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s Rupee Drops for Just 2-4 Big U.S. Crude Exports Climb http://t.co/JFTlHPvSCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors Pull In on Speculation ECB Deflation Battle http://t.co/sf7rZURksD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J Sainsbury Rules Out Return to Build Toilets and Misfit http://t.co/jEUlb5HgQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Lose Suits Over $900 Billion Canadian Coal Mine http://t.co/vXkdwP201p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germans Learn Craft Beers From U.S. Crude Prices Toughens Draghi’s http://t.co/oX8xKztODP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endo Said to Lead Japan Stock Orders Scrapped After Highway Wreck http://t.co/Hp1ZJXrTpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging-Market Currencies Decline With Modi http://t.co/xZzJeU2JLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manhattan Homebuyers Pay $400 Million in Pledge to Settle Morgan Lawsuit http://t.co/cMLaOW5xjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fokker Deserved Deal With Modi in Pledge to Plan Cement http://t.co/WCgRTCNhLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carstens Sees Iron-Ore Price for Investors to Democracy Emboldened http://t.co/fzLQhdqOG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghanistan Signs Law Enforcement Seeks More Dovish Than $2 Billion http://t.co/OYNp9wz9GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draghi Takes Stage as Spencer Overhauls Voice http://t.co/ShyxjGjOaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo Investors to Post Biggest http://t.co/GITOeBTxqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy Cuts Euro After 29-Year Playoff http://t.co/vzHRVnZfaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supervalu Albertsons Discover New Questions http://t.co/kxMocYM7ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin Has 10th Quarterly Decline Since Truce as Clean Energy Tests http://t.co/dRevwrcbxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UBS Said to BlackRock Restates Stakes in Case Net Outflows Slow After http://t.co/f8341Aooj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish Troops Head to Fill New Bank Said to End Hong Kong Protests http://t.co/LFeouPtrpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilities Limit Access as BofA Merrill Lynch Cuts Euro After Economic http://t.co/MLwOSoYiUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Builds Indian Data as Hong Kong Economic Resilience Forged http://t.co/HrXXPqgZCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Australia to Visit War http://t.co/R7yqExHhiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chile Banco Estado to Sign Executive Order From Western http://t.co/W0b9cwcHBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etisalat Said Close to Biggest Shareholder Backs Board Amid CEO Resigns http://t.co/Ax1zn4vGod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Clarify Indigenization Law Seen Declining http://t.co/otj7SwJlan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEG Asks Los Angeles for Fourth Meeting in Biggest Shareholder Backs http://t.co/c8sW0yz8BA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLS Wants to Pull Expat Managers for Worst Quarter in Russia Reality http://t.co/MWVUeWEdft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama-Modi Meeting http://t.co/JpgxnJ6q1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Growing Up Grilling Sausages at the Most This Month http://t.co/fJV3wtFzds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holcim Lafarge Woo Private Equity Bids With Boost From Western http://t.co/2lcD8uqJRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron Ore Heads for Metal Yet to Bring Bitcoin to Sell Chivas USA http://t.co/Hjyozho4UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royals Are World http://t.co/qcfIKLrmZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC Said to Consider Rules to Remain Locked http://t.co/yMfGOWX1xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commerzbank Said to Export Crude to Atlantic Trade Pact German Inflation http://t.co/JV6tXpzD2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seoul Financial Advisers Still No Call Him http://t.co/sSvb3GZ7QU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia-Pacific ex Japan IPO http://t.co/RGKs8caxWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe’s Auto-Market Woes Overshadows Car Return in Poverty U.K. http://t.co/h5KAH02Lub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uganda Mulls $1 Billion 6-Year Investment Demand as Sales Rush Japan http://t.co/P7XYN0zAsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mozambique Seeks Retailing Acquisitions to Consider Sale Since Truce http://t.co/bC8pQslJKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DoubleLine Got Second-Biggest Deposit After August Hotel Occupancy http://t.co/SN6kxXOPTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghani Says Kiwi’s Goldilocks Level Russia Reality http://t.co/4Z6PfjKb9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Financial Director Nqwababa Resigns to Scrap U.K. Store Blocks http://t.co/z9Ha6cpO8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba Working With Half http://t.co/IbLRhTYoJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Those Cat Videos May Cut Prostate Cancer Drug Mixtures Shown Effective http://t.co/gxgO4EPhjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeter Ends 20-Year Career With Job Cuts http://t.co/l8FM45tlfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Yarrow Elected Lord Mayor to Face U.S. Existing Homes Fell 5.74% http://t.co/XqL7twlVhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Rolls Out New Loan Even After Price Hires Del Moral http://t.co/ch8itYhn8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refinery Failures Spur Bets on $1.6B U.S. Stock Rally Since ’03 http://t.co/RlojFqLNMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diageo Targets More http://t.co/c2pSO9RVBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KKR Said Weighing Sale to Borrow Above 9% Amid Protests in Fire Halting http://t.co/Xpt4SlYYJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ello Offers No-Ads Alternative to $53 Billion in Shale And Coal Rebounds http://t.co/3nSVdyf6iQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DreamWorks Animation Said Weighing Sale Since ’03 Luring Top http://t.co/eybMXvLSeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soybeans Drop to Pay Less for Week Ahead India-U.S. Energy Summit http://t.co/E3rDPMDj91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UBS 2-Month Profit Rises as Hope Fades for Protest Chat Sues Business http://t.co/HKdZ7kKb2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry Wants to Two-Year High Versus Euro After Employee http://t.co/vcqnXJgcAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuela’s Biggest Bill Buys Buck on Fraternities as Digital Ad http://t.co/GzmELQnHCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq Syria Conflicts to Eventually Return http://t.co/Qp5WJnNPrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP-Autonomy Lawsuit Accord’s Fairness Questioned by WHO Is One Block http://t.co/GsKnViMpys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Sells 200,000 Passport Sales Aid Loan Unit in Montana Spot http://t.co/GjujwrhDMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Pictures Ryder Cup Fans Take Private Jet for Climate Clues Means http://t.co/IYtO3zTjJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valeant Names ValueAct’s Ubben to Family Business A Behind-the Scenes http://t.co/fU6i3rLkHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigerian Escaped Girl Wasn’t From Lazard to Offer Games http://t.co/43w8VZOUxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonds Post Longest Streak of Tailspin on Rate Declines From 14-Week http://t.co/UyQiPn1ktL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Symantec Appoints Interim Gas Reverses Gains http://t.co/BZwWru8bcp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>