<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["You have brains in your head. Your feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself in any direction you choose." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our aspirations are our possibilities." - Robert Browning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be not simply good; be good for something." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't wish it were easier. Wish you were better." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My interest is in the future because I am going to spend the rest of my life there." - Charles Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Discontent is the first step in the progress of a man or a nation." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To lose patience is to lose the battle." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any fool can criticise, complain, condemn, and most fools do." - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pull the string, and it will follow wherever you wish. Push it, and it will go nowhere at all." - Dwight Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Unless you try to do something beyond what you have already mastered, you will never grow." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't know why we are here, but I'm pretty sure that it is not in order to enjoy ourselves." - Ludwig Wittgenstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make each day your masterpiece." - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not failure, but low aim, is a crime." - James Russell Lowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At the centre of your being you have the answer; you know who you are and you know what you want." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Create your future from your future, not from your past." - Werner Erhard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think of life as a good book. The further you get into it, the more it begins to make sense." - Harold S. Kushner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The teacher is like the candle which lights others in consuming itself." - Giovanni Ruffini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over. Smile because it happened." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let someone else's opinion of you become your reality." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our doubts are traitors, and make us lose the good we oft might win, by fearing to attempt."  - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Conquer your bad habits or they will conquer you." -  Rob Gilbert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is nothing impossible to him who will try." - Alexander the Great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is never a better measure of what a person is than what he does when he's absolutely free to choose." - William M. Bulger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A leader has the vision and conviction that a dream can be achieved. He inspires the power and energy to get it done." - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Early to bed and early to rise makes a man healthy, wealthy, and wise." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I always like to look on the optimistic side of life, but I am realistic enough to know that life is a complex matter." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only time you mustn't fail is the last time you try." - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The journey is the reward." - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone who angers you conquers you." - Elizabeth Kenny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must do the thing you think you cannot do." - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A person is a success if they get up in the morning and gets to bed at night and in between does what he wants to do." - Bob Dylan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can do it if you believe you can!" - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time." - Barack Obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life has no limitations, except e ones you make." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone who keeps the ability to see beauty never grows old." - Franz Kafka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Strong, deeply rooted desire is the starting point of all achievement." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Problems are only opportunities with thorns on them." - Hugh Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even a mistake may turn out to be the one thing necessary to a worthwhile achievement." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be as smart as you can, but remember that it is always better to be wise than to be smart." - Alan Alda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every exit is an entry somewhere else." -Tom Stoppard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forget the times of your distress, but never forget what they taught you." - Herbert Gesser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An ant on the move does more than a dozing ox." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all possible objections must first be overcome." - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our life is frittered away by detail. Simplify, simplify." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't wait. The time will never be just right." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of success in life is for a man to be ready for his opportunity when it comes." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let yourself be silently drawn by the stronger pull of what you really love." - Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is unwise to be too sure of one's own wisdom." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To be wronged is nothing unless you continue to remember it." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Circumstances do not make the man, they reveal him." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I began learning long ago that those who are happiest are those who do the most for others." - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The measure of a man is the way he bears up under misfortune." -  Plutarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away." - Antoine de Saint Exupery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The future depends on what we do in the present." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Need and struggle are what excite and inspire us." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A fool despises good counsel, but a wise man takes it to heart." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can stand tall without standing on someone. You can be a victor without having victims." - Harriet Woods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The man with insight enough to admit his limitations comes nearest to perfection." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If people believe in themselves, it's amazing what they can accomplish." - Sam Walton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What do we live for, if it is not to make life less difficult for each other?" - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is either daring adventure or nothing." - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must travel in the direction of our fear." - John Berryman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit." - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Desire is the starting point of all achievement." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anything's possible if you've got enough nerve." - J.K. Rowling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out." - Robert Collier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Like what you do. If you don't like it, do something else." - Paul Harvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we accept tough jobs as a challenge and wade into them with joy and enthusiasm, miracles can happen." - Arland Gilbert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better." - Samuel Beckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterwards." - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. It is the source of all true art and science." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It does not matter how slowly you go so long as you do not stop." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is neither magical nor mysterious. Success is the natural consequence of consistently applying the basic fundamentals." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you are content to be simply yourself and don't compare or compete, everybody will respect you." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Discontent is the first necessity of progress." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is important is not what happens to us, but how we respond to what happens to us." - Jean-Paul Sartre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ultimate reason for setting goals is to entice you to become the person it takes to achieve them." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest compliment that was ever paid me was when someone asked me what I thought, and attended to my answer." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who talks more is sooner exhausted."- Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you want something, you have to be willing to pay your dues." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Think and wonder, wonder and think." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The significant problems of our time cannot be solved by the same level of thinking that created them." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love what you do. Do what you love." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your worth consists in what you are and not in what you have." - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The challenge is not to manage time, but to manage ourselves." - Steven Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we seek to discover the best in others, we somehow bring out the best in ourselves." - William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not all of us can do great things. But we can do small things with great love." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Common sense is the collection of prejudices acquired by age eighteen." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One machine can do the work of fifty ordinary men. No machine can do the work of one extraordinary man." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our duty as men is to proceed as if limits to our ability did not exist." - Teilhard de Chardin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keeping score of old scores and scars, getting even and one-upping, always makes you less than you are." - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Patience is the companion of wisdom." - St. Augustine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be the change that you want to see in the world." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deal with the world the way it is, not the way you wish it was." - John Chambers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>