<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems/Software Requirements Analyst, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/31/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/j6WF4IBY1R https://t.co/3Fz7Ow07ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Enterprise Software Engineer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Senior Enterprise Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/vaog0hiWE1 https://t.co/4sWiRWnWB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDP Developers (Python Development): EDP Developers (Python Development) Ref No.: 18-26274 Location: Sunnyvale, California EDP Developer(s) Strong SDLC experience with the ability to excel in a RAD DevOps model with biweekly releases Hands on expertise… https://t.co/lTrEjtIg8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Specialist: Cyber Security Specialist Location: Quantico, VA Job Code: 3448 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products… https://t.co/N10kEwWxjd https://t.co/Dhq7TNzMa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title Cloud Architecture Software Engineer: Job Location US-VA-Reston Posted Date 2 months ago(4/18/2018 3:11 PM) Requisition ID 2018-3280 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development company headquartered in… https://t.co/Arq796ZoGl https://t.co/xrMRgLnrwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Quality Systems Specialist: Closing On: 23/07/2018 Principal Quality Systems Specialist Location Americas, USA, Minnesota, Minneapolis Job Reference SMNA00719 Schedule Type Full Time Duties and Responsibilities Provides leadership for and… https://t.co/cvptDClyBC https://t.co/5iCvQLmABI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Project Manager.: SharePoint Project Manager. SharePoint Project Manager. IRG is looking for a dedicated and meticulous SharePoint Project Manager to join our growing team associates. In the role, you will operate independently and as part of… https://t.co/m7vrGisp0k https://t.co/37HR1KDLf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Architect: Irvine co. seeks a full time System Architect. Requires: Master of Science in Software Engineering with 48 months prior experience as software developer. No travel. Jobsite: Irvine, CA.  recblid szccwv2en6itoeu9evmgx3ru9d9m3b https://t.co/CBmKK1hblm https://t.co/S3sq42awfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III #58808: Software Engineer III sought by Accolade, Inc. in Plymouth Meeting, PA. Job # 58808. Resolve complex technical issues and deliver innovative solutions that improve user engagement, system availability, resiliency, and… https://t.co/LQFph35qOM https://t.co/fdIJA6vlD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: IT Project Manager $73,924 – $103,494 DOE   The Project Manager will serve in the implementation of short- and long-range public transportation technology projects within budget constraints, oversight of scope, and technical… https://t.co/02HItDSX5p https://t.co/Y8KBXiLToa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin skids below $6,000, hits lowest level since November: LONDON (Reuters) - Bitcoin's value slid to its lowest level since November on Friday, as waning investor interest and recent negative headlines from global regulators weakened demand for the… https://t.co/A5hGv0i5gG https://t.co/DnE26oHI3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer / Customer Success: ENGINEER/Customer Success at Palo Alto, CA: Engage w/co’s new customers &amp; help them implement co’s products; drive end-to-end implementation execution; Frequent travel to customer sites req as assigned by employer (70% travel… https://t.co/WCLA6CxxDd https://t.co/6LYkY0RySu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Sr. Software Engineer Sr. Software Engineer Company ****************** LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need A Senior Software Engineer will mentor Associate Software Engineers, lead small development… https://t.co/rHPJspZSgn https://t.co/Dz4MUxMYLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Programmer 4: Participate in the requirements, definition, design, development, testing, and documentation of database systems. Analyze web application requirements, code, and documentation for database support and provide recommendations for… https://t.co/gHWlSNVsJW https://t.co/ZzXJojZjJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theater Security Cooperation Analysis and Management Support 16734: Career Opportunities Theater Security Cooperation Analysis and Management Support 16734 Position Location: Shaw AFB, SC Requisition #: 16734 # of openings: 2 Description Description :… https://t.co/n7MylmMWFJ https://t.co/rvpiea8ad6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology will provide software development and maintenance in services support of the Naval Undersea Warfare Center Division Keyport. The Software Engineer position supports the maintenance and… https://t.co/Epgjqycxbb https://t.co/4AcqDeFVM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Research Analyst: Market Research Analyst to research market conditions/determine potential sales. Mon-Fri. 40 hrs/wk. 12 months exp. req’d. Mail Resume to Balloonzilla, LLC 18021 Sky Park Circle Suite K Irvine, CA 92614 recblid… https://t.co/MEFLB6lmA7 https://t.co/rVmcryHYYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: Synaptics, Inc. has multiple openings in San Jose, CA. Software Engineer: build up chained secure flash boot flow on ARM v7/v8 architecture SOC Senior Software Engineer: design multimedia framework incl. AVIN, VPP, VDEC… https://t.co/jSDmLqtDsM https://t.co/etj6eUQ0Yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML: Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML Tracking Code ******* Job Description Do you have great ideas about how to create user interfaces (UIs) that are intuitive… https://t.co/xpOFFJGncZ https://t.co/XFQYCTLliV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Tech Lead: Position: Production Tech Lead Job Description: Principal Accountabilities The Production Technician Lead provides work instruction and prioritizes work of their team to ensure integration quality, production objectives and… https://t.co/CUjrzh3cHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst/Assistant Project Manager – Maher Maher, an IMPAQ Company: Careers Center | Analyst/Assistant Project Manager – Maher &amp; Maher, an IMPAQ Company Welcome page Returning Candidate? Log back in! – Analyst/Assistant Project Manager – Maher &amp; Maher, an… https://t.co/kHxGAUTJSL https://t.co/hXRrwMFzZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new… https://t.co/eqkdFVJ4qU https://t.co/4wDKwMtgkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Saint Inigoes, MD Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/27/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/b0cjFXej69 https://t.co/PYFMwreypw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail Salaried/ASP Positions for District 1 (Staunton, VA) Assistant Store Manager: Apply now Retail Salaried/ASP Positions for District 1 (Staunton, VA) Assistant Store Manager =====================================================================… https://t.co/URUB02LnO7 https://t.co/BNlZvCzedU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Security and Data Compliance: at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Because you belong at Twilio The Who, What, Where and Why Who? Twilio Security is looking for an experienced Security and Data Compliance leader who has… https://t.co/anZkhsoXuP https://t.co/Jskr2RSFEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Director – Packaging / Coated Products: Title: Technical Director – Packaging / Coated Products Location: Green Bay, WI Job ID: 41176 col-wide Job Description: Technical Director – Packaging / Coated Products Due to an upcoming retirement (late… https://t.co/oNu2K1qZdp https://t.co/dORwJyJqA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Softw Dvlpr: COMPUTER/IT Softw Dvlpr, IBM Corporation, San Jose, CA: Support robust cloud apps as well as srvc dvlpmt, whether running in a public cloud, priv cloud or in a hybrid environ w/ connectivity betw the two. Deliver softw solutions for Cloud… https://t.co/ItvYT5ALbq https://t.co/y1NsR4yOe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Senior Developer for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) to provide maintenance and support for SAP GRC. Analyze customer problems, design and implement corrections, and deliver them as customer specific or standard corrections in the… https://t.co/qGGuPEG8qJ https://t.co/2AwdKutuCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Senior Software Engineer (Design, develop &amp; implement J2EE based application components using Java, J2ee, WebServices, Hibernate,… https://t.co/jXJ4oonMnR https://t.co/Bs4ubwh8jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer w/ Active Secret Clearance: Job Opening | Columbus – Facebook – Twitter – Linkedin – Home – Home – Default – Home – Corporate hot – Home – Color – Home – Light – Home – Video – Home – Video – Light – One Page Website – Sliders… https://t.co/U55qym4SjP https://t.co/HN9fEOb9J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Operations Analyst/Research Analyst – Web Design – TS/SCI – Quantico, VA: Requisition ID 2018-42071 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides… https://t.co/mPPZkT2cHr https://t.co/Fs1xa7POBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer II: Java Software Engineer II Amherst, NY Opportunity JAVA developer with knowledge of Web Sphere. Linux and Oracle to assist with the implementation of CGI’s CACS 9.2 system. This resource will be responsible for writing Web… https://t.co/vnLh6SBT0k https://t.co/lR5E94tH6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Logistics Support (ILS) Manager: 17775BR Integrated Logistics Support (ILS) Manager General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world… https://t.co/HKmu7ZPY8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Under Armour is all about performance. Because what we make empowers athletes in every form to push themselves, to turn good into great, and to stay hungry for whatever comes next. And this is exactly what we expect from each other.… https://t.co/abd1XvFBtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Do you get excited about creating effective landing pages that leave a lasting impression? Are you a Javascript / WordPress guru? If youre looking for an exciting career opportunity in digital advertising and marketing, working with a… https://t.co/zJezZ80MmD https://t.co/t50fKqdUYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, systems integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial sectors. Design Group… https://t.co/EHdlL2QIBi https://t.co/LVHENjV3Pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/3FOyM7lIzy https://t.co/bpAjPmQg82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OEM Software Engineer: OEM Software Engineer sought by Masimo Corporation, Irvine, CA: Design, develop, and implement medical device firmware and software applications. recblid regtk2kzbd5y0ylggq0oxslpk425y9 https://t.co/kbiNCMLJu1 https://t.co/XrwnBDa7op]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst Evaluate business, function &amp; technical requirements. Component design documents. Design, develop &amp; code modules based on TIBCO, Java standards. Enhance technical document &amp; implement changes. Module &amp; integration… https://t.co/2TW0IgVY6z https://t.co/JP5L2EOXL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Are you ready to grow your dream career while making others’ vacation dreams come true? Marriott Vacations Worldwide is a world premier organization for Vacation Ownership with resorts at destinations around the globe. Join our team and… https://t.co/owUNMYZKMR https://t.co/AxcM5uT8aX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Developer: Company Summary =============== Data Trace LLC is the nation s largest provider of automated title plant and tax information services for title companies nationwide. Our leading technology allows quick access to title history… https://t.co/KBhA6np54l https://t.co/7UHOh9bnLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/wQWwCv3WTw https://t.co/VTKdgnZs1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROGRAM OPERATIONS ANALYST: University of Washington Location Seattle, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category Administrative / Office,Customer Service,Health Care,Management / Executive Job status N/A Posted on Jun 12,… https://t.co/MAaaahR19W https://t.co/XIe04KHrIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer Provo, UT: DevOps Engineer – Provo, UT Tracking Code ******* Job Description Micro Focus is seeking a talented and motivated individual to assume the role of DevOps engineer in the Identity and Access Management Engineering Department. We… https://t.co/CAGAd4JCJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: QA Engineer Richfield, Minnesota – United States Job Start Date – 06/27/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: Developer (Specialty) II Duration: through 12/27 Work Location: Richfield, MN Position Overview:… https://t.co/zh6sdMKVo6 https://t.co/jiQGdNXbhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT ServiceNow System Administrator: ServiceNow Systems Administrator **DIRECT APPLICANTS ONLY – NO THIRD PARTIES, PLEASE ** 3 months contract to hire Oakland, Ca Minimum requirements for this position are: – 3+ years of ServiceNow development,… https://t.co/HYouRgiaY1 https://t.co/iP1oJFN60a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Cloud Software Engineer(s) (Job #461) &amp; Software Engineer(s) (#457): Dsgn, dvlp &amp; build sw for ntwk security firewall prods.… https://t.co/0WzJ3pyeAr https://t.co/9yf26luovX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: O2 Technologies, Inc. in Irvine, CA is seeking Software QA Engineers to monitor, analyze &amp; test sftwr during dvlpmnt in order to ensure quality. No trvl; no telecomm. Job duties are proj-based &amp; performed @ unanticipated sites w/in… https://t.co/5QWj0IHhVX https://t.co/mCPQqU2jvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-00670 Location: St. Paul, Minnesota Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional offices… https://t.co/NGBxT1FxPD https://t.co/6exTjxbFk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Company Description Senior SW Engineer – Fraud and Authentication Applications You may have noticed that payment has become a very hot area in the last couple of years. Given the strong demands and rapid innovation, this will be a… https://t.co/Xy1r3laPUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: L3 and its divisions are committed to expanding access to employment for people with disabilities and disabled veterans. If you are a qualified individual with a disability or a disabled veteran, and your disability prevents you from… https://t.co/XWV0aLRNJS https://t.co/PjDZphNLgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Epic Ambulatory Systems Analyst II: Job ID 2017-25104 Department EPIC AMB Site CORPORATE Job Location US-NJ-Eatontown Position Type Full Time with Benefits Standard Hours Per Week 40 Shift Day Shift Hours 8:30 a.m. – 5 p.m. Weekend Work No… https://t.co/GploWLfHHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Department Ops Mgmt Employment Type Full time Minimum Experience Mid-level Environmental Management Specialists, Inc. (EMS) is a professional environmental contractor specializing in environmental cleanup and site remediation, emergency… https://t.co/PAdOwiCO8Z https://t.co/qFY44d1NVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer: Req ID 96679BR Business Title CNO Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Performs as the technical subject matter expert.Designs new capabilities… https://t.co/iuhCeOAImB https://t.co/8jnhm2HEwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator- Underground Utility: Oxnard, CA Full-time $80k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Estimator with experience, please read on! ***MUST FILL OUT QUESTIONS &amp; SKILLS TO BE CONSIDERED FOR POSITION*** Top Reasons to Work with Us – Supportive… https://t.co/6LSo2ZIRCT https://t.co/EoKJSfAgzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Engineer: Machine Learning Engineer Palo Alto, California Data Science Full Time One Concern is a startup which specializes in Artificial Intelligence for Natural Disasters. With our team of global disaster scientists and engineers, we… https://t.co/ztSJJXZpNT https://t.co/zlSf1wnRp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Alignment Technical Analyst: – Business Alignment Technical Analyst Req No. 2018-3380 Location : Location US-IL-Elwood Category Information Technology Overview Clearwater Paper manufactures quality consumer tissue, away-from-home tissue, hard… https://t.co/Nj6IAKnfS1 https://t.co/q0oKJiam39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Developer (LOCALS ONLY): ETL Data Developer (LOCALS ONLY) 6 months Contract To Hire Reston, VA Job Description:* This Senior Software Engineer will have a range of skills and experience to manage existing ETL jobs in the legacy Informatica and… https://t.co/JFimsNzi2M https://t.co/TBQ8eUPsq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Tester: Job Description Quality Assurance Tester – Tysons, VA, USA – Full-time Company Description Leading Products – Innovative Ideas – Exceptional People ….MicroStrategy, A Dynamic Place to Work! At MicroStrategy, we are passionate… https://t.co/oi2QypiECU https://t.co/dHWoo5K7IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title US Government Project Manager: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/b85hK2RHGN https://t.co/3a1vrwGNWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: What does it take to protect and maintain the most sensitive data for over 220 million people and 25 million businesses? What does it take to meet daunting challenges and shape solutions that pioneer industries and improve… https://t.co/Bc2LNricJc https://t.co/3KOhiy5MoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer C++ Java: For Siemens Software Engineer – C++ Java – Shoreview, MN job – Research &amp; Development – Shoreview, Minnesota Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/7aDergveio https://t.co/eCeX95paVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Project Manager: Environmental Project Manager – Seattle, WA TRC Solutions, Inc. is an engineering, environmental, and construction management consulting firm that provides integrated services to the environmental, energy, oil and gas, ,… https://t.co/hKB86Uhozd https://t.co/txAjxkb3BX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Group Implementation Consultant / Project Manager: Functional Area:SM – Sales &amp; Marketing Estimated Travel Percentage (%): Relocation Provided: American General Life Insurance Company Your future team VALIC specializes in retirement savings and… https://t.co/CeyM1V6Fm8 https://t.co/ndSus4fThm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richmond Project Manager / Sales: We are looking for a loyal, driven and self-motivated individual who wants to help homeowners, move up on their own, and increase earning potential. Our company is a national leader in our field. Our commission Project… https://t.co/4iYBqAEdJe https://t.co/UjD6nppZEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Job TitleSystems Administrator – ID:30350 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsWindows, AD, Networking, Virtualization LocationSandy, UT Date Posted03/13/2018 The System Administrator deploys, maintains and supports… https://t.co/GddxdYHCqT https://t.co/0obLgxgsq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Engineer: USfalcon – Careers USfalcon, Inc – Benefits – Employees &amp; Returning Candidates – New Candidate Information Assurance Engineer LocationOhio Job Description and Requirements: USfalcon, Inc., recognized as one of the fastest… https://t.co/3ayyUrHbwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java IVR Developer: What you’ll be doing. If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and find ways… https://t.co/0wrVM6fODW https://t.co/McpSwTVwGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer – Client Account Info: Are you a master of Java interested in the coming frameworks, tools and techniques? Do you know how to solve challenging problems in elegant ways? We re looking for someone like that who can: develop… https://t.co/gbdjwnjgFs https://t.co/HX7EARMF3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Supply Chain Specialist: Senior Supply Chain Specialist Posted Date 1 month ago(5/10/2018 9:59 PM) ID 2018-31191 Job Location USA-VA-Fairfax | USA-MA-Taunton | USA-AZ-Scottsdale Category Procurement Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company General… https://t.co/37zGORsZQN https://t.co/EcY43hDroL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pega Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You’ll support development on Pega platform across multiple business channels including Customer Care, Retail and Mobile. You will design and develop functional and framework components of the… https://t.co/xNavaIYGQn https://t.co/q6VYiWPC3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OCS Inspector Rail: Careers Center | OCS Inspector – Rail Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/7dR11dPBr8 https://t.co/jVrxpkSqct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager ITS Applications: Snohomish County Public Utility District No. 1 Employment Opportunity An Equal Opportunity Employer Of Minorities, Women, Disabled, And Veterans. We are the Nation’s 12th largest public utility, serving over 341,000 electric… https://t.co/GUELgHmYYo https://t.co/tlJPdi2qFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Req ID : 407091BR Job Code/Title : E1993:Systems Administrator Sr Job Description : This Enterprise Business Services (EBS) position supports the Space Systems Company (SSC) located at the Lockheed Martin Sunnyvale, CA facility.… https://t.co/qJAYFwlnJ4 https://t.co/cUmSA8rWiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Project Manager: Brea, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with commercial construction experience, please read on! Based in beautiful Brea, CA we are an exciting, fast-paced and innovative electrical… https://t.co/eJdidt2ANg https://t.co/Phn7Hx7ds8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: About Meduit Meduit, a growing national healthcare revenue cycle management firm has an opportunity for an Office 365 Systems Administrator located in its Charlotte NC corporate headquarters. Job Responsibilities Working in… https://t.co/dnX7aLOf9w https://t.co/jPT34SuyfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Developer: Developer for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to develop, maintain, and improve our automated functional test, integration test suite, and performance test suite. Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, or a… https://t.co/vgfYNNZioV https://t.co/wmxLpgTu7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced JAVA Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right… https://t.co/MSZpDeV1eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal / PHP Developer: Drupal / PHP Developer Ref No.:18-09901 Location: Raritan, New Jersey Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/01/2018 DRUPAL / PHP DEVELOPER Diverse Lynx LLC is an Equal Employment Opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will… https://t.co/RcAJTs80vg https://t.co/ltQ5dR21Ts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst Clarity ETL BI Administrator: Senior Analyst – Clarity ETL &amp; BI Administrator (43886) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 43886 Job Description Job Summary The Senior… https://t.co/iLRtmkOhHr https://t.co/CVVabyxobt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager (Pharmaceutical): Redwood City, CA Full-time $60k – $75k Posted Today Title: Product Manager Salary: $120K – $130K + bonus + 401K match Location: Redwood City, CA Specialties needed: Product Management, Pharmaceutical products, dietary… https://t.co/h8r2YjObMX https://t.co/Ekp6hhMiFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: https://t.co/YrEWvtteet Services – Irvine, California Software Development Engineer II – Design, dev., implement, test, &amp; doc. SW apps, tools, systs &amp; services.  EOE. recblid q7repj8nqxm9allzdpt31mn4o799kb https://t.co/v67xQ7hQkO https://t.co/DnHkovGQ8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist – Neural Networks: Does business and technology consulting excite you? Do you want to operate at the frontier of the rapid disruption from Big Data / Analytics / Machine Learning? Neal Analytics is Microsofts premier Advanced… https://t.co/GJ3nCQeGnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer: Sr Software Engineer Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show… https://t.co/o26HbO5WjB https://t.co/AuMtg79J76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Warehouse Developer: Brief Description: This role is on the Enterprise Information Management (EIM) team, which is responsible for supporting Huntington’s (HNB) Enterprise Data Warehouse, ETL and Business Intelligence tools. The role will ensure… https://t.co/SYcV4f37xX https://t.co/AYP9eDub0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Solution Architect / Rockville, MD: Req ID : 431901BR Job Code/Title : E1804:Comp Systems Architect Stf Job Description : Lockheed Martin Corporation is currently seeking a Solutions Architect with a strong system architecture and technical leadership… https://t.co/dkNob5Gznm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Developer: HomeAdvisor is looking for a senior-level JavaScript Developer to join our Software Development team. In general, we are looking for someone who has experience working on public-facing web properties, and being part of a… https://t.co/5RsaJB3pBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Norfolk, VA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/vi6x593xb7 https://t.co/4JX6bT2nHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Software Developer: Hollywood, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted 01/25/2018 Do want to work for the #1 up and coming start-up in LA? Do you enjoy being on the cutting edge of technology? Are you an active contributor or have published libraries or… https://t.co/iH4OSdz0X4 https://t.co/gro9yeuqTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer  We are looking for engineers who: Are customer-focused, driven and passionate in creating premier experiences through well designed, tested and maintainable code-bases. Are always looking to learn and improve –… https://t.co/bCxcOFJnp7 https://t.co/gohJXj0HLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Designer/ Marketing Support: Website Designer/ Marketing Support Commercial Roofing/ Construction 1 year experience.  recblid q4tywbwzpntfqabg8qowz22px3m1km https://t.co/COmaMqNXJU https://t.co/I8yDGP0czB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Sr. Full Stack Software Engineer: – Sr. Full Stack Software Engineer Company Nexsys Technologies LLC Location US-Remote Who We Are Nexsys Technologies is a financial technology company founded by mortgage IT experts to create and deliver innovative… https://t.co/U09YGR0msK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Principal Architects serve as the technical design authority and architectural expert for sales opportunities across multiple vertical and geographic regions, in support of the… https://t.co/byDFP0h9XX https://t.co/sBgi1bxBwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst III: IT Business Analyst III at C.H. Robinson Skip Navigation menu – Corporate – Offices – Student – Contact – Create a Profile – Log In Keyword Search City, State, or ZIP Search radiusRadius5 miles15 miles25 miles35 miles50… https://t.co/K4P0JoIRh2 https://t.co/3r1OZAQVpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer Program Manager: Senior Developer Program Manager – Job ID #: 13229 – Job Category: Software Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Ecosystem – Primary Country: USA –… https://t.co/v8y8ted31K https://t.co/2yQcxExk7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer Principal: Req ID 95615BR Business Title CNO Developer Principal Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Hanover Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a diverseteam that leads the… https://t.co/kquMYxMAk6 https://t.co/8arGXPWjLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integration and Test Readiness Engineer (mid-career): Req ID : 428469BR Job Code/Title : E1463:Systems Engineer Sr Job Description : System Integration and Test Readiness Engineer for Military Support Programs Block 3 program to assist ATLO in… https://t.co/FE38Ij8G4a https://t.co/jdxVGyhgSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead Engineer: SilverRail Technologies is looking for a Technical Lead Engineer to join us in our mission to open-up rail travel around the world. As a Technical Lead, you provide a blend of hands-on and technical leadership within a team of… https://t.co/T9ljwauO5W https://t.co/aiWhEmAcAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Development Lead (Java/Grails): We are looking for a Java/Grails Development Lead to steer the development of the APIs powering our successful own-brand and grey-labeled products. The position involves about 30% leadership and 70% hands-on technical… https://t.co/HVoslM0a7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Developer: Automation Test Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position 2+ Yrs Job Description: Candidate must have at least 2 years of experience developing C++ test framework and test cases OR C++ application development experience… https://t.co/IRTVyxLcQ4 https://t.co/floz1ubYOb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>