<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicolaSturgeon: 📺👇Callum is a remarkable young man. With love and support, care experienced young people can achieve as much as anyone.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic @whocaresscot story. More of this please. Let's help more young folk reach their potential. https://t.co/ZzNAWuQwtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristinaSNP: Tackling funeral poverty. #dayjob https://t.co/Wu1jqQ4v8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new fixed weekly surgery programme for Southside Newington.  If you have a local issue to discuss, pop along or book ahead. https://t.co/NyGONs8dmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCScotlandNews: Record number of Scottish pupils gain university place on exam results day https://t.co/oAMR08R4i5 https://t.co/B8ndWb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EISUnion: #EISNews Exam Results Testament To The Hard Work Of Pupils And Teachers #examresults https://t.co/C3nWdDag6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @engagefored: DFM @JohnSwinney celebrating achievements of care experienced young people #examresults @whocaresscot @sqanews https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skillsdevscot: Our fab team of careers advisers is back at 8am tomorrow to answer your calls on the #examresults Helpline 0808 100 8000…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edinburghpaper: Good luck to all those getting exam results today! Counsellors &amp; career advisers are on standby: https://t.co/rFzHGMxSA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicolaSturgeon: Best of luck to everyone waiting on #examresults today. If you need any advice, the @skillsdevscot free helpline is 080…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skillsdevscot: #Parents &amp; carers, our Exam Results Helpline supports you too. Opens 8am on #examresults day 0808 100 8000 https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinned to my wall many moons ago! Whatever your #examresults...we believe in you. You are all amazing young people with many options ahead. https://t.co/GVvFfJPNGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been an arty farty day. Popped into Nustart Art Group at Cameron House. Fantastic finished, and soon to be, paintings #community https://t.co/domn9kszvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great artwork going on at the fab #community of Prestonfield Neighbourhood Project too...and a 70th birthday tatoo! #socialisolation https://t.co/GAHMDoGJVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belting out Sinatra at Prestonfield Neighbourhood Project's Desert Island Discs today! Day centre, advice &amp; much much more #socialisolation https://t.co/XcHIskFOGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to bump into the @Edinburgh_CC mobile library in Prestonfield today. Nice chat with staff too. #libraries #access #community https://t.co/sAvN96GTzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to read about a new Gowrie Care Drop-In coming to my ward/Gilmour St to support #homelessness V much needed. @Hillcrest_Group https://t.co/PHDiyh5Zqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialSYP: From April 2018, the Carer’s Act will come into effect. Find out how it affects you at @YoungScot. https://t.co/9cnNQEBen4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theyardscotland: We're proud to support @InspiringSland #AwayandPlay campaign, highlighting the benefits of active, outdoor free play h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Summerhallery: The Summerhall street team are out today postering about town. https://t.co/pbiToqJmws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamrmcvey: Productive discussion with @shelterscotland today. Addressing homelessness &amp; housing shortage at very top of our agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamBalfourLang: Thanks @adamrmcvey for meeting with myself &amp; @Fee_King to hear @shelterscotland's concerns about housing &amp; homelessnes…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinReporter: Edinburgh International Festival 2017 – At The Queen’s Hall https://t.co/vsI24D2sbA https://t.co/qIclMg577S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edinburgh_CC: Visitors to @edcentrallib can now sample a selection of Nordic noir thanks to a delivery from the Finnish Institute https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edcentrallib: Delighted to receive a gift of 10 books from Finland to help them celebrate #Finland100 https://t.co/DJVXoPjXta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shelterscotland: Your local Shelter Scotland shop needs volunteers! Can you spare a few hours a week? Get in touch: https://t.co/43gE2t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to drop into @CragsEdinburgh today.  Lots of activities for young people, links to schools &amp; a social enterprise too! Thanks to Ewan. https://t.co/jnOOV5pjT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason to love the Southside &amp; esp for this Ayrshire lass! Visited Museum Group to hear stories of those who've walked it..Burns too https://t.co/kXLfXajaRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budding actors/actresses, great opportunity at the fantastic Cameron House community centre. https://t.co/9LCKwhJuMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Let's talk about Hate.' Countering the hate narrative with Muslim Women's Association &amp; @Radical_Indy One trunk, many different branches. https://t.co/w7UINpSWJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about affordable &amp; flexible childcare with mothers at the Toddler group in the Central Mosque today. https://t.co/ugFYZJwGiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamrmcvey: Just a fraction of the dress-code criticism most women experience in their lives... https://t.co/VIxT0AXvK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danieldjones @LEAPsports Hugely honest and helpful blog for others Daniel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharterisCentre: .@EdinburghUni Welcome Week is just around the corner. Looking forward to welcoming student groups old and new into ou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CHScotland: Are you aged 16-25? Come along to our workshop with @YoungScot on 'Attracting Young People to Volunteering'! https://t.co/W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CastlebraeCHS: Friday! Skiff Day! Weaving the seats! https://t.co/CUc9gPAuyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nikki27681: @AlisonDickieSNP @CastlebraeCHS @EdinburghUni Brilliant school! Amazing job with the skiff 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edinburgh_CC: Pupils from St John’s RC Primary get stuck in at the sod cutting for their new school. It will open August 2018. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @youngedaction: https://t.co/k9CM6GS3JO Young people of Edinburgh we need you to tell us what you think #YEAyourvoicematters https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They even do boats @CastlebraeCHS ! Lots of skills, sport &amp; dance academy, #STEM mentoring with @EdinburghUni &amp; more.Thanks #amazingschools https://t.co/ZIjBz8oEpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real school community &amp; holistic education approach @CraigroystonPS Loved the visit &amp; the tour. today Thank you. #amazingschools https://t.co/SVhnv5Er1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just fantastic real life tour guides @Castleview_PS but sensory rooms &amp; much more. Let's get news about our #amazingschools out there! https://t.co/Jdgb4JuXWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RockTrust_tweet: Mental health is a huge factor in young people becoming homeless. If you think your mental health is putting you... ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14th? Coffee &amp; #socialenterprise Will be there! https://t.co/wR9FQCZNKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edinburgh_CC: Happy #ReadABookDay ! Follow @TalesOfOneCity for news and information across all the city's libraries https://t.co/rKMLwy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edinburgh_CC: It's Suicide Prevention Awareness Week ! Find out more about reading between the lines https://t.co/YfMqBVAyPb https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally. Popping into @CharterisCentre soon. Is your new programme out yet? https://t.co/cca4wqVvQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So phenomenal...&amp; a little bit scary! Innovative, interdisciplinary &amp; real life learning. Fab &amp; thank you. #amazingschools https://t.co/nQ2Tq6Lqje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SaveChildrenSCO: We're pleased to hear @ScotGovFM recommit to investment in early learning and childcare and giving all children the be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shelterscotland: Thanks for all your support for #FarFromFixed - great to see #homelessness on agenda for @scotgov's Programme for Gove…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ferns_kitchen: Join us for Fern's Kitchen Wednesday Matters: LOOPS Talk, Wednesday 6th September, 13:30-14:30. FREE event. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CanalViewPSEdin: It was a pleasure showing you around :) https://t.co/1xgNBX9cuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all P4 to P7s. Get writing! We know the huge talent in schools. Let's showcase it out there. #amazingschools https://t.co/5TBJbkYASY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamrmcvey: Edinburgh is proud to provide a home &amp; refuge for those in need. People moving here, whatever their circumstances, are dese…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First visitors to my surgery at Newington Library...the local cats! Beautiful setting &amp; Book Bug songs soon too. https://t.co/NFSBDbuAhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bringing Edinburgh's fantastic history alive through art. https://t.co/imTexouKty https://t.co/sEyN663PWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CHScotland: Are you an employer who supports their employees to volunteer as Children's Panel members? Let us know! #volunteering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving children the best possible start...beginning with the environment. Wow new nursery &amp; 1140 hours at Davidson Mains PS @DMainsPSA https://t.co/epiTtzmFBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspirational visit to @CanalViewPSEdin Not just a school but a community. Home Link Officer &amp; Place2Talk amongst success. Fab P7 guides too https://t.co/pXiq00q29U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PrestonfieldPS: Prestonfield Primary School wishes all our Muslim families Eid Mubarak! https://t.co/HHLS6x8fEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharterisCentre: We're back! Normal service nearly resumed! #Festivalisover https://t.co/qTxhkv0qc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MindroomInform: Absolutely delighted to meet with you, all the very best in your new role #learningdifficulties #mindroominform #suppor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brack85: Enjoyed listening to @AlisonDickieSNP at HT event today. Huge passion for children's rights, equality and apple crumble! All g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brack85 Thanks Kevin. Pleasure to there.  All of you make a difference every day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooftop engagement this week &amp; what a view! You've got to love Edinburgh. https://t.co/IfRbMl9qBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! #endchildstigma https://t.co/KGNQQKs7N7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cisweb: For young people's views on how life issues impact on school &amp; support that helps, see Reach @Reach_scot https://t.co/KhJ8mIdBJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st of my new weekly surgeries held in #NewingtonLibrary this Saturday. Drop by &amp; bring your kids.  The Book Bug's on &amp; it's free! https://t.co/9xKT2ryjdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspirational chat with Cathy McCulloch about the work of @Creative_Voices Talking children's rights &amp; getting their voice out there. https://t.co/zHQ4hc6RAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It takes all kinds of minds' Dropped into @MindroomInform to talk support for learning difficulties. Hope to work more together soon. https://t.co/sQpm8V0Es1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GavinKBarrie: Fantastic preview sample of Chinese lanterns that will grace @EdinburghZoo this winter from 1st December. @ETAG_UK https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lewisritchieSNP: Delighted to convene what I thought was a thorough &amp; fair hearing on the #royalhighschool. Unanimous decision against…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaEdin That sounds super. Will be in touch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamrmcvey: Good to meet @DerekMackaySNP to talk about local government finance &amp; how @Edinburgh_CC &amp; @scotgov can work together. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, look at this! Visited @VictoriaEdin to discuss new school &amp; found they have a museum. Ticks all curricular boxes. #amazinglearning https://t.co/AYbr7voE8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to visit @SKELFBikePark today to discuss their work with local young people and schools, their future plans and local issues. https://t.co/gGaHb2poLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to help raise the voice of Carnegie Court on a number of issues. Invites coming out for residents' meeting soon. Lots to do here. https://t.co/0VXC1Tr5od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about @MindroomInform in @TESScotland mag &amp; their work with schools to support YP with additional needs.Look forward to meet on Wed. https://t.co/gaZJqQgbBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much learning to be celebrated across our schools.  Well done to budding author Holly for being the Scottish winner of short story comp. https://t.co/3DOjL80lX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CoffeeAngelEdi: Sunday Fundays are back at @theyardscotland until 5pm.
So head on down and bring the little ones. Loads of fun!
#Edinbu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GCP_Edinburgh: Starved of human contact: what it's really like to be #homeless https://t.co/4jOIIEZbK8 https://t.co/DNlLvspOpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CYPCS: Supporting staff to volunteer as Children's Panel members is great for developing leadership, decision making, and communication…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateC_SNP https://t.co/ti7Zeo9wXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate has a real heart for tackling homelessness. She will be a strong voice. @street_work @SocialBite_ @InvisibleEdin @shelterscotland https://t.co/PmniXXAJq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are many ways to bring back #community @ferns_kitchen is 1! Fab cake, company &amp; a wee dance at Balfour House. Open to all, spread word https://t.co/PNDhhBrRFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kim_harding: @edinspotlight Actually the bins in my street have gotten better since @AlisonDickieSNP got involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting the inspirational Fran &amp; Charmaine at Heathervale &amp; Moredun YP's Centres to chat about work with care experienced YP @whocaresscot https://t.co/OGhxCuVTFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @get2getheredin: What a great event! Great to talk to you @AlisonDickieSNP https://t.co/qYWqYHEHJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @whocaresscot: Care Experienced? Want to help guide our Care Family? Please consider joining our board. We want to hear from you. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to help P7s at Davidson's Mains @DMainsPSA today with their democracy learning...the importance of local government to people's lives. https://t.co/kOrJ2mg37h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @engagefored: DFM @JohnSwinney launches new £1m school library improvement fund at @GracemountHigh. @SLIC1991 https://t.co/vQ9Eo2ssjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab. I will certainly be back. Be good to drop in to chat with the young folk too about the issues that matter to them. https://t.co/eapCbHdX3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab food with Cllr @CllrNormanWork at the Old School Cafe @Canongateyouth Get yourselves down there! https://t.co/VhgjmlvzCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great turnout &amp; discussion at Carnegie Court Residents meeting tonight. Serious issues. Time for some focussed action now on this community. https://t.co/K29M5iCB2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a wigwam! Loved the opening of @corstorphineps new nursery.1 of 4 new nurseries &amp; best possible start written all over natural design https://t.co/EX9CRb8aJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic chat with @NiddrieMillPS &amp; @stfrancisps kids at The Venchie today. Seriously impressive toothbrushing...breakfast club &amp; much more https://t.co/HAeyxpzeCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this photo! Great work @DadsRockEdin https://t.co/oFz8R86UJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carnegie Court Residents Meeting tomorrow (Wednesday) 6pm in Southside CC. Warm invite to all residents - let's discuss issues &amp; actions. https://t.co/33sGO4xKs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a crowd at Friends of @PrestonfieldPS tonight. Parental engagement at its best! Lots of praise about this fab school from HT &amp; parents https://t.co/VyjISC54vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cyrenians1968: Great to host @AlisonDickieSNP at our FareShare Depot yesterday! https://t.co/fpL0tkcI4T @FareShareUK #FoodWaste #Charit…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>