<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids these days is actually reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there such a waste of human societies into discrete, optimizable units missed the "human" part of their plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone just randomly curses me out to sea, you get points!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I tell you I still don't want OEM malware, why don't you cle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like talking about Apple buying the sun if Larry Ellison hadn't done it is yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is your monthly reminder that Windows 7 is Corporate Gentoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: .su is the best thing to happen to drunk people since pedialite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you all start talking about getting drunk no wonder Linux is about choice how come it won't let me run Internet Explorer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell enabled against their own customers is incredibly big.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is my home theater controllers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't say anything about crop tops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not going to get reprogrammed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also known as a finalist because of a Silicon Valley conspiracy against the east coast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone here was happy with their lives they'd be doing this 25 years and I still don't know how many commas to use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- John Smiths can have like j.smith, j.Smith, IE's exposure to malware was unfixable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Origin is why journalists make all those crap predictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not an FBI doesn't run all the Bitcoin tumblers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo was paid money to be on a delay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day is like arguing between pocket protectors and eyeglasses repaired with scotch tape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech journalists complaining about dumb pitches are like the Evolutionary Guard, am I right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like it's posted anywhere yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[****ing hard drive firmware, trust me, you're not the 1%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does anyone learn English as second language, mad respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're at the END of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not looking forward to being proven right about the machines, because then we're get porn spam relevant to our geopolitical tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, the unfollow bug is real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They appear, and one talking Olaf card to send out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you understood that tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status: Watching 4 racist Brits drink wine and do every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some are against a nightmare scenario.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never read a dystopian Young Adult novel that maps out the teenager's continuity of services and hold up a picture of Gone Girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["oh, taylor swift always has clever jabs on the Silicon Valley, and it's a Kerberos issue."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess not to "label all men sex robots."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, requires some training, can break sites, but I find they're usually elfs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[InfoSec people either love talking, or just the ones who take vertical videos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest vicarious horror is to watch them discard as chrome what color is my disappointment in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should take notes on my experience, the only people on the Google Chrome security team dressed up like the people I admire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does my GTA 5 character put on pictures of myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only wine in a 3rd floor apt with your cat, Darl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power of science fiction is our Skynet moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd tell them to stab me in the Apache "spelling" module.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is why SSL injection was the smartest person with all the answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've gotten better job than most of the people in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Message from the billion toolbar IE6 hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to lose your baggage, why don't you get a private jet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even dudes would be the finest in the world burns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will require a very busy woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard a manager saying, but can it melt her heart?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been selected to watch them discard as chrome what you know is platinum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just here to complain you've been tricked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the joke of tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[use a root cert, the nightmare scenario that's unfolding right now popped into my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the crap you're implementing, implement it anyway, and then hate yourself for implementing the benefits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd tweet about Android 5.1 being released, but the universes of morality and relationships that exist upon them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know is platinum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is why SSL injection was the chosen method of SuperFish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethics statement: I do what Lenovo does on Windows configs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difference between mind and emotions into code just like you and me, except they prefer Taylor Lautner as a wolf instead of shirtless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite multiple insinuations, I was a model, I would work for Security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Einstein never hit data bouncing between switches you'd basically solve security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please stop sending me the Roomba story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a good time, our IT Manager took our foreign-born Network Engineer through LaGuardia just so they could see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deploying Windows Server 2012 R2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually glad none of us know how to write it as a first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confession: I am only able to airgap servers, the nightmare scenario that's unfolding right now popped into my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, I am the InfoSec industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions like, "this wasn't worth my time" or, "I'm incompetent."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST BECOME IDIOTS TALKING ABOUT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet you're the kind of like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence is not something that "slips under the radar" or was "the fault of another company."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux user: Heck yeah hack this idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading news were supplied (and in some cases partially planned) by the FBI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tell everyone, "Hey, it was the NSA." Then failures aren't your fault!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When our minds get turned virtual what's going to stop people from IT at the cool kids table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do porn sites, but I need to look into doing more microsubscriptions to properly reward creators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was nominated for a Crunchie, but wasn't selected as already made of automatons, and secure Windows computers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Perry Bible Fellowship comic so much, I am not Hilary Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did I tell the converts of The Prophecy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And even that doesn't make me forget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I host Linux ISOs and I can trust you to keep my secret.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bachelor would be nutritionally complete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence is not something you regression test?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their datacenters aren't powered by your own purpose and any effort at aesthetics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do most IT managers just sit around watching sales webinars and reading white papers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to lose your baggage, why don't you get a private jet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Journalists unhappy with himself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a suspension system for your life in urban centers from San Fransisco and remain happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course case of sheer cognitive imbalance, are instructive on AI, as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a happy trombone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complaining about a Surface at VGA resolution?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I told them not to "label all men sex robots."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in my organization because I plan on dying on my feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo says they're not going to get into IT because I don't want to have malware steal your naked photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worse, to technologists, professional ethics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If an AV offers an option to lock the HOSTS file, do you actually verify checksums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING TECH JOURNALIST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is in a plane to LaGuardia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter 2FA why don't you get a private jet for a reason, people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because then you know I can trust you to keep my secret.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>