<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 yeah it was. Just back, wasn't that great to be honest, I'll fill you in later over pints. When are you free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae I've been enjoying the most recent Bombay bicycle club album, it's a good 'un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 yes could be mate. Am going through to Glasgow today for a careers thing. What time are you done with uni?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunnyleither aye I know. He's a gem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got two tickets for sale for #boniver on the 22nd October in Edinburgh. £15 each. Who wants 'em?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Grim news for Lucas and Liverpool. He's out for season confirm @LFC. Cruciate. Big loss. Lucas has been playing brillia ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 This aint like dusting crops ender! #thingshansolowouldsayinendersgamemovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 ken pal. Got exams all next week though so going to have say no. Keeping the nose to the grindstone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Peston: Most signif Bank of Eng announcement today - in long-term sense - is telling banks must state ratio of gross loans to capita ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GARYTANK: STV/.STV/PLAYER STV/DOT PLAYER - GET OOT MA LIFE!, GET OAF MA TELLEH! MAKES ME SAE RAGIN UV GOAT STEAM COMIN OOT MA FACE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@BBCBreaking: Rob Andrew is appointed professional director for the England Rugby Union- because he's done a great job so far??? @aspy87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/XXzynkDe @rustyboy2310 OMG cat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@rossmcnairn: Scotland is first UK nation to make forced marriage a crime #law #scotland” bloody excellent. Back off ladies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 Yeah prob going to have to miss next week as well! got an exam next wed. All good up here. Have you had interviews yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Azeda Booth on @Spotify
http://t.co/L2uLoxCO
Great revision tunes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 ZOMG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah yeah that's fine. Keen for one soon though. You been sending out job applications mate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody should watch 'riding giants on bbc4 right now. It's amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@domdunnett: #Hanging. Well played @EdinburghYP @williamrjyates” / quite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @k44rve: Today's service was heartbreaking. Massive turn out of Scottish skiers and a brilliant tribute to a genuinely awesome lad. A ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMannah: Hail Hail the Hibs are here (on Twitter) @HibernianFCClub #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah Monday would be perfecto if you can manage it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Hats off to The Scotsman: story about J K Rowling's hassles with media illustrated by pic of her and husband snapped thro ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 do you want to come here for dinner? I'm going to johns after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah potentially- got a shiteload of work on and exams soon so sooner rather than later would be better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 are you staying at home or at Islas? ...Need to sort heating if you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 sorry mate going to be baw deep in an essay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 Ho fo sho! however all they would need to do is look at my tweet history and think hmmmmmm.... #no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... And the bastard just responded to that comment by freezing and losing a couple of hundred words #drat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody kick me in the head before I buy a Dell laptop again. #whenwillilearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sethmorrison1: Asked a teenager today why he wasn't skiing with poles, he says "I'm not old enough yet!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBig_Sam: Bit wet to train today, so let the lads watch some of my 'Sabrina, the Teenage Witch' videos in the office. That cat is  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 teehee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Ski champion Craig Macfie killed by drunk-driver http://t.co/LYqtfsjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep. Think I know why #gutted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe the  #muppets movie doesn't come out til February for the UK. It sounds and looks incredible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EliBraden: Just poured a packet of Jello powder in the fishbowl while my fish was asleep. PUNK'D!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mcbride, what an absolute clown http://t.co/hGIt6NBZ @officialmannah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: Rhodes looks a bit tired tonight for the U21s. Almost as if he recently travelled across all of Europe to only play for ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeremyjones: A free thinker, Lived by his own rules. Touched many. RIP brother. @PowderMagazine Jamie Pierre 1973-2011 http://t.co/m ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ESPN_Ski: A legend in the sport, Jamie Pierre killed in avalanche in Snowbird backcountry today. First avy fatality of season. http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBig_Sam: And FIFA relents. Once again, Big Sam unsheathes his baton of righteousness and smashes in the face of injustice with de ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #Hibs hire Jim Jeffries, I will be just short of washing my hands of them. amazed at the support that he's got for the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah does this mean that yours arrived?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilesBarrie: #DTZ was always going to be too much trouble for #CBRE or #Cushman. #BNP Paribas has missed big chance to dine at top table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilesBarrie: Relief at last for #DTZ! http://t.co/SFP6ftMC Big Aussie FM specialist #UGL announces 'firm intention' to conclude merg ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae not bad thanks how was the deen? picked up a bit of man-flu #baws. Why am I always ill just now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/glerO2y9 @rmcnairn spurs next year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I was Long John Silver, You'd be first to walk the plank, ya wank". Classic Winston. #stillgame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamSpiers: Colin Calderwood sacked by Hibs. Please, can we say it right here and now: Gordon Strachan no chance, Mchael O'Neill e ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrMarkBeaumont: Best of luck to @MarkCavendish at #SPOTYAWARD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to be @MarkCavendish for #SPOTY #Cav4SPOTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ruaridh_jackson: Sad to see Chris Paterson hang up his boots, real legend of Scottish rugby and a great role model. He will be misse ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suarez banned for 8 games and fined £40,000. Terry could be fined £2,500 and no ban for the same offence. #fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Suarez banned for 8 games. Huge chance for Andy Carroll!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#home. The English are too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DownhillWriter: I'll never retire my old Dynastar ski bag. #coupedumonde http://t.co/ZTYUsfDh”  It's a classic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview over. Not a clue how that went!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nervous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really have not got the hang of Robinson's double concentrate yet! #buzzing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for a yo sushi lunch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zachbraff: I used to like Trump. Honestly thought he was funny. Now it appears he's lost his mind. I cringe when I see him and chang ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah #icouldbethewalrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philmcnulty: Sure best wishes of everybody in football goes to Darren Fletcher as he takes a break from the game for health reasons. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheBig_Sam: Enjoying the Chelsea v City game with a cheeky Punk IPA and a Wagon Wheel.” big Sam drinks @brewdog . Who knew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBig_Sam: Enjoying the Chelsea v City game with a cheeky Punk IPA and a Wagon Wheel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 getting pished in stocky so all yours. By spaceship do you mean the house? Don't really understand the question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 baws #itsspeltbauer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to the #blackkeys for the first time? How did I miss this? Unbelievably good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Love that guy that begrudgingly accepted scientific "facts"
Ha ha. 
Just believe anything you want. Who needs evidence ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WengenLauberhor: The Lauberhorn downhill race in Wengen in real time and real speed!! Driven by Bruno Kernen. http://t.co/KyoIXvIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thebeatcroft: There is an evil abroad in the world, and it is Leona Lewis's cover of Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FRabbits: I spewed. RT @airshipband: FUCK NO. I can't believe i just turned on the tv to see Leona Lewis singing Hurt. Brain Explode ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now Leona Lewis is covering nine inch nails #spew #xfactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valdes you absolute plum! #elclasico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@skiracingnews: New ski specifications approved http://t.co/Wjlk4nYo” unbelievable- hard headed bureaucrats #fisworldcup #fisalpine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 the man seems to be baw deep in goals these days. Surely not going to get picked for scotland...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aspy87: BOOM snoddy you hero!!! #lufclateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@slashfilm: Ben Kingsley is Mazer Rackham in ‘Ender’s Game’ http://t.co/lYJ3V6Xy” @rustyboy2310]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's united lost the title then #vidic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: The United Kingdom consists of 90,060 square miles. David Cameron has fought tooth and nail for 1 of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aspy87: http://t.co/w8SlOkfh
BOOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Holiday Message from Ricky Gervais: Why I'm An Atheist - Speakeasy - WSJ http://t.co/U2GmNE52 (via Instapaper)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@BBCNews: Highest wind gust in #scotstorm now 151mph at Cairngorm Summit, @metoffice says http://t.co/NWk1wFxe #ukstorm” where else???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Steps to a More Marketable LinkedIn Profile http://t.co/RDpviX1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Great news for Capello, #eng & #Rooney. Not great news for the English game/grass-roots. FA has just undermined its own ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Vonn is just an absolute cut above the rest. #fisworldcup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating valuation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First exam tomorrow.  #Pixies proving to be somehow good revision music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 cheers pal! Finished on the 14th! Skitesville!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 horrific. First one tomorrow. When do yours start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely brilliant article from Tim Vickery about #Socrates  http://t.co/v7hK5hfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Peston: Harsh RT @tommo_85: "This Christmas naughty children will be getting some Euros instead of that expensive lump of coal."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyBarretTimes: If Wenger & Martinez had a race with Caldwell & Mertesacker the managers would definitely win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmcnairn @domdunnett that is quite superb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hungover, man flu, can't sleep. #starwars time! Lets begin with part 4...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomEnglishSport: Scotland in the Six Nations. It's not the dejection that kills you, it's the hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh Brian Moore get oaf ma telly #sixnations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NYDNSportsITeam: The U.S. Attorney's Office in Central District of California closes investigation of 7-time Tour de France champ La ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bushywayne: Better to have loved and lost then too never have loved at all. http://t.co/EPVHNNm7 real good Sarah edit.  Thanks for a ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>