<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In bad times and good, I have never lost my sense of zest for life. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends don't bail on you, and they're always there to catch you if you fail. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/evdtwQnyWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say nothing is impossible, but I do nothing every day. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't think, then you shouldn't talk. –March Hare in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/3VoaQU9Iuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/oUPJowbjn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All it takes is faith and trust. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't hate you. I'm just mad. –Scrooge McDuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between pretty and beautiful is, pretty is temporal, whereas beautiful is eternal. –Miss Piggy in "The Muppets"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/mvjIcQplBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends are wonderful, don't you think? They're always there to lend a helping hand. –Jasmine "Aladdin Series"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a little problem, I could try to lend a hand. If you're feeling sad, just tell me and I'll try to understand. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is beautiful. Love is wonderful. Love is everything. Do you agree? –Ray "Princess and the Frog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your chin up, someday there will be happiness again. You’ll see. –Robin Hood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams connect us even when we're far apart because dreams come from inside your heart. –Ariel from "The Little Mermaid Series"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing in even the possibility of a happy ending is a powerful thing. –Snow White's Once Upon A Time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Potts in "Beauty and the Beast"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, and tomorrow we diet. –Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never really know until you think, think, think. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I listened earlier, I wouldn't be here, but that's just the trouble with me. –Alice in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look inside yourself. You are more than what you have become. –Mufasa in "The Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hi everyone. I’m Olaf. And I like warm hugs –Olaf in Frozen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think, believe, dream, and dare. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There'll always be Christmas, so there always will be a time when the world is filled with peace and love. –Belle (Enchanted Christmas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't change anything. You can't change the past. –Simba in "The Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might find something that we weren't looking for, which might be just what we were looking for, really. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little consideration, a little thought for others, makes all the difference. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time in forever, I won't be alone. –Anna in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be right beside you, because we're friends. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/M9KzTnHs1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate your friends, today and every day. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know where you are going, any road will get you there. –Cheshire Cat in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where one thing falls, another grows. Maybe not what was there before, but something new and wonderful all the same. –Bambi’s Mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm brave, but I'm careful. –Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody’s perfect, but you sure are lovely. –Daisy Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t think the worst. Don’t fear a thing. You'll get through it if you try. –Doc McStuffins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't run from love. It has a way of tracking you down. –Tug in "Brother Bear 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Patient" is very good advice, but the waiting makes me curious. –Alice in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won’t get lost with your heart to guide you. –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm with you, I don't feel so alone. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, buddy. I'm here for you. Everything's gonna be okay. –Timon in "The Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do your best each and every day, good things are sure to come your way. –Tiana in "Princess and the Frog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday, I will be a beautiful butterfly, and then everything will be better. –Heimlich in  "A Bug’s Life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends are more important than anything else. –Snow White (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends are wonderful, don't you think? They're always there to lend a helping hand. – Jasmine "Aladdin Series"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/HADDeqOD7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather die tomorrow than live a hundred years without knowing you. –John Smith in "Pocahontas"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need someone to be my friend, someone who won't run away.... Maybe send me an angel, the nicest angel you have. –Lilo in "Lilo &amp; Stitch"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tag your friends http://t.co/vs4RLPxCkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope he’s dreaming of no one but me. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they’re mad, or scared, or stressed, throw a little love their way and you’ll bring out their best. –Bulda in  "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't pick someone I'm not in love with. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're weird, but I like you. –Dot "A Bug’s Life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a world of laughter, a world of tears. It's a world of hopes, and a world of fears. - It’s A Small World]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll know he's the one when he makes me laugh. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't you ever had a dream, something you wanted so bad you'd do anything? –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a chance ‘cause you can and you will see all the possibilities. If you try, you will find. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just focused on the bad stuff when all you had to do was, let go of the past and keep moving forward. –Lewis in "Meet the Robinsons"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand tall. You're in a class by yourself. Be proud, you're not like anyone else. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megara: “He would never do anything to hurt me.” | Hades: “He's a guy.” in "Hercules"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My one true love. I'll find him someday. He's out there. I just know it. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab a dream before it takes off. Dusty in "Planes"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7wVy2eeOdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you do the things that you can do, you will find a way. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my dream. I'll decide where it goes from here. –Alice in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/VW8dvKHof2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is taking a few steps backward, maybe even more, to give way to the happiness of the person you love. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one to tell us no, or where to go, or say we're only dreaming. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A photograph can take you back in time to places and embraces that you thought you'd left behind. –The Tigger Movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/CEwsCOKR0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe you don’t need the whole world to love. Maybe you just need one person. –Kermit the frog (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one decides my fate but me. –Belle (Once Upon A Time)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flower that blooms in adversity is the most rare and beautiful of all. –The Emperor "Mulan"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I was doing this right now.... #Mondays #Monday http://t.co/f4ynhH2KiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don’t see things as they are. We see things as we are. –Rafiki in "Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's because I like you, I don't want to be with you. It's a complicated emotion. –Marlin in "Finding Nemo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frozen. She raps!  https://t.co/7125AVutiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heart is not so easily changed, but the head can be persuaded. –Pabbie in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People make bad choices if they’re mad, or scared, or stressed. –Bulda in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be so hard on yourself. Everyone makes mistakes. –Belle in "Belle's Magical World"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes you different makes you beautiful. – Princess Diaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to live in fear, ‘cause for the first time in forever, I will be right here. –Anna in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just don't see how a world that makes such wonderful things could be bad. –Ariel (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't lose hope, love. Once you've lost that, you've lost everything. –Mrs.Potts in "Belle's Magical World"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says you have to grow up? –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can’t understand something, it doesn’t mean it’s wrong. –Arthur (The Sword in the Stone)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With you here, I know that life is much more fun. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise me you won't forget about me, ever, not even when I am a hundred. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you’re grown up, you can’t come back. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, but today is a gift, that’s why its called the present. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your eyes now before you get hurt. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be with you forever. I want you right here beside me forever. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t give you anything but love. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz Lightyear: “Whatever happens, at least we’ll be together.” | Woody: “For infinity and beyond.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look inside yourself. You are more than what you have become. –Mufasa (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends always see your best side. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you follow your dreams and keep giving it your all, you can accomplish aything. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody deserves true love. –King (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>