<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/Nc9NK9aUFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/LmnoDQQ1pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/NHm9m8Ym7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/iixcD6PuIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/VXr0K0n9ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/ITpdfn372N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/cdO1X7g0L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/vruK3dCc5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/ETNrvxunIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/WQrDFRuz2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/1j6nyxdu8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/UqdPOsIG2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/AkVSwc5Kaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/j2rhcSGn5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/m9KqEJjiK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/kTLG0fFN4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/sDcS8U93dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/4mMebEiRjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/mSyPLV7es9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/1j6nyxdu8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/MwRbEFoG1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/tA7TIwqLS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/ARKqUAu9P9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/2ouQQBknIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/ih7aRmH3lM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/MmGSO674Jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/LsqHhkewhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/Nuex1k1tPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/WhnfjZAvSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/0Xx9M0528x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/CYWtTgUY5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/UUpRexu88k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/d4WkyGivmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/qGijWHZT47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/fmtynvbHBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/izPGsmllPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/SeyM1bgtwp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>