<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["It's right over us": Tornadoes strike parts of Iowa, injuring several, leaving path of destruction - CBS News: CBS News "It's right over us": Tornadoes strike parts of Iowa, injuring several, leaving path of destruction CBS News DES MOINES, Iowa -- A… https://t.co/FuyTmY85Li https://t.co/yMK94p1EmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.T. Developer II: I.T. Developer II – Smyrna, Georgia, United States, 30080 Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation – Careers Home – About Us – Career Areas – Students &amp; Grads – Disability Assistance – All Jobs – Join Our Talent Network Kiosk mode… https://t.co/O162UjiYLS https://t.co/7tF6VHxDby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESM/ITSM Developer | design and develop Enterprise Service Management solutions using ServiceNow: ESM/ITSM Developer | design and develop Enterprise Service Management solutions using ServiceNow Columbus, OH 07-15-2018 Location: Dublin, OH For more than… https://t.co/SDLMuacAkr https://t.co/3MUgkA1uKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Says About 1600 Separated Children Have Reunification Approval - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal US Says About 1600 Separated Children Have Reunification Approval Wall Street Journal The Trump administration told a federal court Thursday that… https://t.co/o0716wpyHG https://t.co/izrj6yd2N2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waitress groped by man slams him into wall in Savannah, Georgia, surveillance video shows - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Waitress groped by man slams him into wall in Savannah, Georgia, surveillance video shows USA TODAY A waitress slammed a man into a wall… https://t.co/yRbIa9kuoL https://t.co/9eN8XCIV79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Times: Trump conoció la extensión de la injerencia rusa antes de la inauguración - Voz de América: Voz de América NY Times: Trump conoció la extensión de la injerencia rusa antes de la inauguración Voz de América Un informe en la edición del miércoles… https://t.co/u1F7XcZmI6 https://t.co/vJtEfyRZEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama encourages voter registration in star-studded PSA - CNN: CNN Michelle Obama encourages voter registration in star-studded PSA CNN Washington (CNN) Michelle Obama wants to get out the vote this November -— and she has recruited a… https://t.co/KxLdBNYYB4 https://t.co/UJG5GkYJr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic push to investigate Russia stymied by partisan acrimony - CNN: CNN Democratic push to investigate Russia stymied by partisan acrimony CNN (CNN) Democrats on the House Intelligence Committee thought they had scored a coup in their efforts to… https://t.co/ar8dXOTu0l https://t.co/8WAws4xOPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13-year-old boy bitten by possible shark off Fire Island, authorities investigating a second suspected attack - ABC News: ABC News 13-year-old boy bitten by possible shark off Fire Island, authorities investigating a second suspected attack ABC News… https://t.co/Ol8qJWHgch https://t.co/LYmpPTCWDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After crafty trade for Manny Machado, Dodgers must reel in some pitchers - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times After crafty trade for Manny Machado, Dodgers must reel in some pitchers Los Angeles Times How do they keep doing this? How do Andrew Friedman… https://t.co/T9rSZTCvcG https://t.co/y4pUuizW9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. – Design, develop, analyze, evaluate, test, debug, document, and implement moderately complex software automation applications and solutions from collected specifications or requirements. –… https://t.co/qwLfsGxteK https://t.co/llcljYtyXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kavanaugh's role in Bush-era detainee debate now an issue in his Supreme Court nomination - Washington Post: Washington Post Kavanaugh's role in Bush-era detainee debate now an issue in his Supreme Court nomination Washington Post Brett M. Kavanaugh was… https://t.co/YorwAcLMut https://t.co/6dksD9FtW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg Tries to Clarify Remarks About Holocaust Deniers After Outcry - New York Times: New York Times Zuckerberg Tries to Clarify Remarks About Holocaust Deniers After Outcry New York Times Mark Zuckerberg, Facebook's chief executive, has had a busy… https://t.co/0pwTIQgQ52 https://t.co/Ma3CcAvFSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of bodies exhumed in Texas likely those of black inmates forced to work on plantations - CBS News: CBS News Dozens of bodies exhumed in Texas likely those of black inmates forced to work on plantations CBS News FORT BEND COUNTY, Texas --… https://t.co/TMQBYMf15b https://t.co/dGBXyRIJt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the US is obligated to defend Montenegro - CNN: CNN Why the US is obligated to defend Montenegro CNN Washington (CNN) The country of Montenegro was thrust into the limelight after President Donald Trump was asked whether the US would come to the… https://t.co/FtYcLrmoF9 https://t.co/rdmxKMkyX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged Russian agent Maria Butina had ties to Russian intelligence agency, prosecutors say - Washington Post: Washington Post Alleged Russian agent Maria Butina had ties to Russian intelligence agency, prosecutors say Washington Post The Russian woman… https://t.co/A5efXwRKes https://t.co/9Z7GDBaN52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US Government Had Nelson Mandela on Terrorist Watch Lists Until 2008. Here's Why - TIME: TIME The US Government Had Nelson Mandela on Terrorist Watch Lists Until 2008. Here's Why TIME A full 100 years after Nelson Mandela's July 18, 1918, birth, he… https://t.co/OMPG0Lfud1 https://t.co/Lx4AIjG9CX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[States Sue IRS, Treasury To Strike Down SALT Cap Under New Tax Law - Forbes: Forbes States Sue IRS, Treasury To Strike Down SALT Cap Under New Tax Law Forbes In the days following tax reform, leaders in some states complained loudly about feeling… https://t.co/PTfz6AJTyW https://t.co/2b9A9za9pQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Air Force One will be painted red, white and blue, Trump says - Washington Post: Washington Post New Air Force One will be painted red, white and blue, Trump says Washington Post President Trump has ordered up a bold new paint job for Air Force One.… https://t.co/edGbe6sO4b https://t.co/cFVpknVP42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ETL Developer: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 5 months ago(2/8/2018 9:01 AM) Job ID 23122 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance Group. As one of the… https://t.co/YBSIaj81SI https://t.co/66LPxBNdjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Possible serial killer' cut off ankle monitor before killing three in Texas crime spree - New York Daily News: New York Daily News 'Possible serial killer' cut off ankle monitor before killing three in Texas crime spree New York Daily News A violent… https://t.co/XnXmq44qHi https://t.co/a5pCypZ2ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A stunt': Outrage builds over MGM Resorts' decision to sue victims of Las Vegas massacre - USA TODAY: USA TODAY 'A stunt': Outrage builds over MGM Resorts' decision to sue victims of Las Vegas massacre USA TODAY A lawsuit filed by MGM Resorts… https://t.co/u87Weu5SGp https://t.co/wiUy26Ml2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild video shows Las Vegas police pursuit, shootout with suspects - Fox News: Fox News Wild video shows Las Vegas police pursuit, shootout with suspects Fox News In bodycam footage so stunning it could be mistaken for a Hollywood action flick, a Las… https://t.co/AyLHQDdo1o https://t.co/UBCMgOVv0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild video shows Las Vegas police pursuit, shootout with suspects - Fox News: Fox News Wild video shows Las Vegas police pursuit, shootout with suspects Fox News In bodycam footage so stunning it could be mistaken for a Hollywood action flick, a Las… https://t.co/iWqIPbPbkp https://t.co/3eg2u6zLG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferguson Fire doubles in size, yet to reach Yosemite National Park - SFGate: SFGate Ferguson Fire doubles in size, yet to reach Yosemite National Park SFGate MARIPOSA — As the Ferguson Fire swelled to 9,266 acres Monday, residents of Mariposa, the… https://t.co/gmEDBGK7Fs https://t.co/lYS3UWsD92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care… https://t.co/MLPX975eGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Beacon Hill Technologies has an opportunity for an IT Project Manager with our client located in North Canton, Ohio. POSITION: * Manage a wide variety of projects across all business lines * Assist in evolving the Project Life Cycle… https://t.co/LSqs5AYaxw https://t.co/axLBo1l4G7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day 2018: The best deals so far (updated) - CNET: CNET Amazon Prime Day 2018: The best deals so far (updated) CNET The waiting is over: Amazon Prime Day officially kicked off as of noon PT (3 p.m. ET), and we're highlighting the best deals… https://t.co/DdYyMNJfkP https://t.co/4WHOf9iWJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court Orders Temporary Halt to Migrant Family Deportations - New York Times: New York Times Court Orders Temporary Halt to Migrant Family Deportations New York Times A federal judge in California on Monday temporarily blocked the government from… https://t.co/qcvBpZfkNS https://t.co/4hReCUYBix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third fox dies Monday after jaguar escape at Audubon Zoo - https://t.co/wvRsKGXqGm: https://t.co/wvRsKGXqGm Third fox dies Monday after jaguar escape at Audubon Zoo https://t.co/wvRsKGXqGm A third fox injured by a jaguar that escaped its enclosure at… https://t.co/S2gYndgiW7 https://t.co/jvGbXzzS6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 30 years, police say they've captured a child-killer who left a sickening trail of taunts - Washington Post: Washington Post After 30 years, police say they've captured a child-killer who left a sickening trail of taunts Washington Post The message… https://t.co/1Il9i5EmHS https://t.co/4iSWf0zg8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP Order to Cash – Pricing) (P-Mod): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely… https://t.co/jUXQU5hB7Q https://t.co/l42PPd4AOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police officer, bystander fatally shot near Boston - CNN: CNN Police officer, bystander fatally shot near Boston CNN (CNN) A policeman near Boston was fatally shot with his own service weapon Sunday morning by a man who used the same gun to kill a female… https://t.co/WKnbVkqtbi https://t.co/705V290mAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildfire Near Yosemite Quadruples in Size, Brings Smoky Conditions to Valley - KQED: KQED Wildfire Near Yosemite Quadruples in Size, Brings Smoky Conditions to Valley KQED A deadly wildfire burning in the Sierra National Forest, west of Yosemite National… https://t.co/4dEVwGGvjk https://t.co/8axbK2MIzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump can't beat Putin at his own game - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump can't beat Putin at his own game Washington Post Want smart analysis of the most important news in your inbox every weekday along with other global reads, interesting ideas… https://t.co/ftBZJbEDvF https://t.co/Hq3SdfZHS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer I: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Cleveland, OH Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/8/2018 Job Description SUMMARY: This individual will assist with the development and maintenance of detailed… https://t.co/2WgtYN02Pq https://t.co/jdRE7ry0xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France caps a frenetic and fabulous World Cup by blazing past Croatia for the title - Washington Post: Washington Post France caps a frenetic and fabulous World Cup by blazing past Croatia for the title Washington Post MOSCOW — Golden confetti mixed with… https://t.co/QH3SXeviQo https://t.co/Wo9wQnEPOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Blackhawks goaltender Ray Emery drowns in swimming accident in Ontario - Chicago Tribune: Chicago Tribune Former Blackhawks goaltender Ray Emery drowns in swimming accident in Ontario Chicago Tribune Retired goaltender Ray Emery, who helped the… https://t.co/gRecbQZsbm https://t.co/YPe9gEScTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash Application Coordinator: Cash Application Coordinator / Milford , OH Overview:TQL’s Cash &amp; Commission team is responsible for applying customer payments to open invoices, resolving short-pays/ unapplied cash issues, and processing/calculating… https://t.co/X1FKiUSvLA https://t.co/qQmg4nrYCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Data Architect Ref No.: 18-28638 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Position : Data Architect Job Location : Cincinnati, OH Job Title: Full time permanent JOB DESCRIPTION: 1. 8+ years of experience that must include data modeling for enterprise… https://t.co/pv6cxFsTOM https://t.co/mmqcmnSC9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Analyst: Perform tasks related to product engineering data management and release. Essential Duties: (This list is not exhaustive and other duties may be assigned) – Perform tasks related to product engineering data release. – Communicate… https://t.co/FvXidqkDok https://t.co/YQwo09NgkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus crash on New Mexico highway leaves 3 dead, dozens injured - CBS News: CBS News Bus crash on New Mexico highway leaves 3 dead, dozens injured CBS News BERNALILLO, N.M. -- Authorities say a crash involving a passenger bus and three other vehicles on a… https://t.co/BVtnBb0fAf https://t.co/Q0u8j0ATZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative – Tier I: Windstream is seeking entry level Specialist’s for Tier I Repair. Our Specialist will assist Windstream Broadband Internet customers with troubleshooting and incident creation to resolve customer trouble. In… https://t.co/XBVwNuzEnO https://t.co/cIVZIViEVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feinstein gets progressive smackdown - Politico: Politico Feinstein gets progressive smackdown Politico California Democrats, torn by infighting between moderate and progressive factions, rebuked Sen. Dianne Feinstein's bid for a fifth term — for the… https://t.co/cy3QbbBocN https://t.co/LUbtUS5acv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant Managed Services – Fusion Middleware: – Senior Consultant Managed Services – Fusion Middleware Posted Date 1 month ago(5/16/2018 1:56 AM) ID 2018-2944 # of Openings 3Category Consulting Work Site – City Columbus Department Consulting… https://t.co/ujIWstPVkq https://t.co/LdzGh6uI5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California firefighter killed while battling blaze near Yosemite National Park - Fox News: Fox News California firefighter killed while battling blaze near Yosemite National Park Fox News A California firefighter who was using a bulldozer to prevent a… https://t.co/4KHqAlzCk9 https://t.co/mIG1iHOjj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's UK Visit, Some See 'Infomercial' for Money-Losing Golf Resort - New York Times: New York Times In Trump's UK Visit, Some See 'Infomercial' for Money-Losing Golf Resort New York Times Mr. Trump at Turnberry on Saturday. Financial records show… https://t.co/9DGnVynJY1 https://t.co/ydZw7zE1bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer / Project Manager: Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, systems integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial… https://t.co/nqOW511oaP https://t.co/r3yoDsz5OF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman survives 7 days after SUV plunges off cliff in Big Sur - CNN: CNN Woman survives 7 days after SUV plunges off cliff in Big Sur CNN (CNN) An Oregon woman who disappeared a week ago was found alive at the bottom of an oceanside cliff in Big Sur,… https://t.co/ziIDdlBlYb https://t.co/ZKQJQTV1XX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job in US – OH – Wickliffe for Precision Castparts Corp. | Information Technology Software Developer US – OH – Wickliffe Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 17109 Req. Id 317 Req. Code ******.2… https://t.co/oaVzvS7Ss2 https://t.co/SRw53tBrWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Specialist, Appraisal Tax: Software Support Specialist, Appraisal &amp; Tax ============================================ Tyler Technologies creates some of the world’s most cutting-edge software products to help local governments thrive with… https://t.co/YWtuUOB3oP https://t.co/tbq8RQk5So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Mueller, pushing to finish parts of Russia probe, question of American involvement remains - Washington Post: Washington Post For Mueller, pushing to finish parts of Russia probe, question of American involvement remains Washington Post In a 29-page… https://t.co/vsx2XvpOb5 https://t.co/Yt6RFuv6GG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job in US – OH – Wickliffe for Precision Castparts Corp. | Information Technology Software Developer US – OH – Wickliffe Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 17109 Req. Id 317 Req. Code ******.2… https://t.co/mcVcygXZa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's UK Visit, Some See 'Infomercial' for Money-Losing Golf Resort - New York Times: New York Times In Trump's UK Visit, Some See 'Infomercial' for Money-Losing Golf Resort New York Times GLASGOW — On Monday, President Trump will have a closely… https://t.co/8s0UZ6S54S https://t.co/u5yAK9SLTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 arrested at 'Welcome Trump' rally in London - Chicago Tribune: Chicago Tribune 2 arrested at 'Welcome Trump' rally in London Chicago Tribune British police have arrested a man and a woman at a right-wing protest in London, where people supporting a… https://t.co/1nyCdkP72f https://t.co/9Rtex0pL0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's tough words for Merkel and May raise questions about his relationships with female leaders - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump's tough words for Merkel and May raise questions about his relationships with female leaders Washington Post… https://t.co/h8MDR7Ffca https://t.co/SDAjMk7PQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-28380 Location: perrysburg, Ohio Job Responsibilities: Experience in following technologies .Net C# Rest Api Services/WCF Developer with fullscale from development to unit testing https://t.co/1jltR6sDx4 https://t.co/LFl8O8YFP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – CAT Modeling: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/30/2018 3:29 PM) Job ID 23661 # Positions 1 Category Product Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/HA6qcO4TF2 https://t.co/PnuAUDgKEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Developer: JOB SUMMARY: Join our winning team with a 100-year track record of success. We’ve just completed our most successful year ever! Midmark has a corporate culture like no other in the markets we serve. As we continue to grow each… https://t.co/d4MwyNjG8t https://t.co/MtC1ijGHsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's walk with the Queen: Like 'wandering up and down a golf course' - CNN: CNN Trump's walk with the Queen: Like 'wandering up and down a golf course' CNN London (CNN) The British public does not appear amused with President Donald Trump walking in… https://t.co/BIBN41faGM https://t.co/3s9TeoQigT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Russia election bombshell, the Trump-Putin show will go on - CNN: CNN Despite Russia election bombshell, the Trump-Putin show will go on CNN (CNN) It is tough to believe that any President other than Donald Trump would hold a summit with Russia… https://t.co/6ZRDbibhS8 https://t.co/N79gUSbKla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Product Review Engineer: Location: Ohio Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers The Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security (BDS) organization is seeking an experienced Technical Lead – Product Review Engineer (Level 4) to… https://t.co/rfhtY7j1nT https://t.co/chKJPHAlCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up, Up And No Way! Greenpeace Paragliding Protester Buzzes Trump At Turnberry - HuffPost: HuffPost Up, Up And No Way! Greenpeace Paragliding Protester Buzzes Trump At Turnberry HuffPost Donald Trump might have hoped for a bit of a break from protesters… https://t.co/6GgxcUt8eB https://t.co/VIUSna7qIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer II: Posting Details Applications will be accepted until midnight (Eastern Time Zone) on the ‘Posting End Date’ shown below. Position Information Job TitleWeb Developer II Applications Accepted FromUniversity Wide, Public: Open to the public… https://t.co/9Rq0JEpkUn https://t.co/yBy4tHnU26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Russians Charged: Major Highlights of the Indictment and Rod Rosenstein's Statement - New York Times: New York Times 12 Russians Charged: Major Highlights of the Indictment and Rod Rosenstein's Statement New York Times Rod J. Rosenstein, the deputy… https://t.co/1aWUVijD7N https://t.co/H7C6sD75iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Computer Operations Technician: Lead Computer Operations Technician Support Center – Akron, OH This position provides leadership and on site management in the absence of the supervisor or manager of computer operations. It spends 40% of the time (2… https://t.co/8JThu8XVzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS Access Engineer – assessing of the code, what it does, and how to bring it together | Can you reverse engineer a MS A: MS Access Engineer – assessing of the code, what it does, and how to bring it together | Can you reverse engineer a MS Access… https://t.co/rRpzjwzilY https://t.co/qbt75qJt8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government says it will reunite up to 200 migrant children a day with their parents - Washington Post: Washington Post Government says it will reunite up to 200 migrant children a day with their parents Washington Post Federal officials said Friday they… https://t.co/S6t7zS7KyV https://t.co/SfZL2No95V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray Lewis, Britt McHenry hit hard by the Twitter purge - Washington Post: Washington Post Ray Lewis, Britt McHenry hit hard by the Twitter purge Washington Post Back in January, the New York Times took a deep dive into an obscure company called Devumi,… https://t.co/Ou5WMVCs6W https://t.co/20MwZzTyZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/24/2018 8:36 AM) Job ID 23536 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity… https://t.co/cPcGhvmPoh https://t.co/3z1ZeJzsZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Small Bottle' of Novichok Found by Police in UK Victim's Home - New York Times: New York Times 'Small Bottle' of Novichok Found by Police in UK Victim's Home New York Times LONDON — The British police announced on Friday that they had found “a small… https://t.co/XRQdqCXPZg https://t.co/koDS3ieAew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Text Exstream Developer: Open Text Exstream Developer Ref No.: 18-27660 Location: Columbus, Ohio Good Knowledge/Hands-on on working in OT Design Manager and Designer Creating, Mapping – Data files, Pages, Documents, templates, output queues, Rules,… https://t.co/OWGpZ1x9LG https://t.co/Fqn6FDO7lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer | full-stack C#/JavaScript developer: .NET Developer | full-stack C#/JavaScript developer – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security –… https://t.co/Y1vFQcEb2j https://t.co/wl7ev5OcUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona state lawmaker pulled over for speeding tells deputy on video he sometimes drives 140 mph - CBS News: CBS News Arizona state lawmaker pulled over for speeding tells deputy on video he sometimes drives 140 mph CBS News PHOENIX -- An Arizona state… https://t.co/yJjWCtGQrv https://t.co/KiLYNnIPdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering, Run Support: Accountabilities This position is a Run Support subject matter (SME) position on the Manufacturing Run IT Team. The main Applications supported are Camstar, Enovia, Maximo, JDEdwards and BPCS. Experience with… https://t.co/7Mte1l4AQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[800-pound boulder kills woman and her daughter after it flew off a truck - The Mercury News: The Mercury News 800-pound boulder kills woman and her daughter after it flew off a truck The Mercury News By Kyle Swenson | The Washington Post. The truck… https://t.co/tAyyTlmabk https://t.co/2DCq4094Th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIGINT Technical Analyst, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/24/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/C5lfG3xnD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Proves It Isn't Ready To Handle Fake News - BuzzFeed News: BuzzFeed News Facebook Proves It Isn't Ready To Handle Fake News BuzzFeed News On Wednesday afternoon, Facebook invited a handful of journalists to its New York offices for shrimp… https://t.co/kTBUUA9jUX https://t.co/6MHllf3vA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP S Enterprise Management – Sourcing Procurement: SAP S/4HANA Enterprise Management – Sourcing &amp; Procurement Ref No.: 18-29271 Location: Dublin, Ohio Functional Analyst Digital : EAS : SAP S/4HANA Enterprise Management – Sourcing &amp; Procurement * Should… https://t.co/hDDJRdCYKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/26/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/v86rYQwTze https://t.co/op9kYQGRg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic calls to 'abolish ICE' delight House Republicans - Washington Post: Washington Post Democratic calls to 'abolish ICE' delight House Republicans Washington Post A cadre of liberal House Democrats introduced legislation Thursday to abolish the… https://t.co/2IDRnSldEz https://t.co/XGBzteDoIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water Restoration/Clean-up Project Manager: Water Restoration/Clean-up Project Manager Roto-Rooter Services Company is one of the leading plumbing, drain cleaning and excavation companies across the US. In Cincinnati, we are the name Tri-State commercial… https://t.co/nT8LKTP400 https://t.co/GRP29K78ZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer: Job Description – NRP Group WE’RE HIRING – FIND OUT ABOUT OPEN POSTIONS NOW! APARTMENT LEASING NRP CONSTRUCTION CONTACT – About – Our Story – History – Core Values – Leadership – Board of Directors – Senior Leadership – –… https://t.co/BWyo0KnmhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One question that reopening the murder case of Emmett Till can't answer - CNN: CNN One question that reopening the murder case of Emmett Till can't answer CNN (CNN) When Angela Lewis first saw him, she felt a knot of bitterness tighten in her stomach. He… https://t.co/PABA2hQMFY https://t.co/0LrK5YG4Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead BioPharma Analytics Reporting: The BioPharma Reporting &amp; Analytics – Tech Lead is a software engineering craftsman that is a full-stack engineering lead and coach that is an expert at working in all layers of an application and guiding and… https://t.co/uKZBNZP53O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=105 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=IND ******************************************************************************… https://t.co/vtXymKQ4bN https://t.co/2Dl8Iq6Agu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Specialist Payroll Time and Attendance Systems: Description HCR ManorCare provides a range of services, including skilled nursing care, assisted living, post-acute medical and rehabilitation care, hospice care, home health care and… https://t.co/5EBZOlUGVH https://t.co/3WIuJ3XFTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Surprises From This Year's Emmy Nominations - BuzzFeed News: BuzzFeed News 9 Surprises From This Year's Emmy Nominations BuzzFeed News For the first time in 18 years, HBO did not receive the most nominations. (It still received 108 nominations but was… https://t.co/D0XmqIfaum https://t.co/QeW6GqKl2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mystery of Brett Kavanaugh's Baseball-Ticket Debt - The Atlantic: The Atlantic The Mystery of Brett Kavanaugh's Baseball-Ticket Debt The Atlantic During his confirmation hearings in 2005, Chief Justice John Roberts told senators that he saw his job… https://t.co/sokm8jzYEn https://t.co/wMMnsx29FK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst Testing: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Cleveland, OH Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/20/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position coordinates and participates in project… https://t.co/GdfVQasvJi https://t.co/7GaEfmsspi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest as Trump begins his UK visit - BBC News: BBC News Latest as Trump begins his UK visit BBC News Trump visit: Full story | Where will he go and what will he do? | Who's dining with Donald? | Why it's really, a unique visit | Two tribes: Protest and… https://t.co/1KaVjXtf6R https://t.co/J0qoYYqgK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial FBI official to testify about private text messages on Trump - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Controversial FBI official to testify about private text messages on Trump Los Angeles Times Peter Strzok, the FBI counterintelligence… https://t.co/66QDQv48yf https://t.co/7ZJBFNGdRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer resigns after not helping woman harassed for wearing a Puerto Rico flag shirt - CNN: CNN Officer resigns after not helping woman harassed for wearing a Puerto Rico flag shirt CNN (CNN) An Illinois police officer has resigned after being… https://t.co/9v3RGEPprl https://t.co/7tRjIvQg3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels was arrested at a strip club in Ohio, her attorney says - CNN: CNN Stormy Daniels was arrested at a strip club in Ohio, her attorney says CNN (CNN) Adult film actress Stormy Daniels was arrested for allegedly allowing a customer to touch… https://t.co/zlpJ2KvixZ https://t.co/M8k7oQlyUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Cleveland, OH, United States Posted By Dominion Resources Date Posted 6 hours ago Expires 11 Jul 2018 Qualifications None Programmer Analyst in Cleveland, OH, United States Cleveland, OH, United… https://t.co/eVGghcv4Ic https://t.co/UtSogik4Tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration to turn away far more asylum seekers at the border under new guidance - CNN: CNN Trump administration to turn away far more asylum seekers at the border under new guidance CNN Washington (CNN) The Trump administration is implementing… https://t.co/1cRDiKOJxu https://t.co/00X8yrUwaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# Developer: Our Fortune 500 client is looking for an experienced C#.NET programmer-senior with SSIS knowledge. The initial project will require versatility to work with the Robotic Process Automation (RPA) Required: C#, .NET, SQL, SSIS, SSRS,… https://t.co/gmXjANaCmu https://t.co/f96G9xNiez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer PLM Milford, OH: For Siemens Software Engineer PLM – Milford, OH job – Research &amp; Development – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – –… https://t.co/VF3lgUxWUA https://t.co/FDUIIJyHj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Capability Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/K2Od8LMjH3 https://t.co/94h74P5uO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevada Execution Is Blocked After Drugmaker Sues - New York Times: New York Times Nevada Execution Is Blocked After Drugmaker Sues New York Times Nevada's execution of a man convicted of murder was halted on Wednesday, after the manufacturer of one of… https://t.co/IYkdcVZsHo https://t.co/YoM0m2oS9m]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>