<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HausOfRizal: #favouritelyric 
I tell you all the time Heaven is a place on earth with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Love @LanaDelRey till the end of time :) RT If you too #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey GO FOLLOW » @lanadelbabe The Incredible #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Melanoboy: @LanaQuote Maybe you want to see this http://t.co/z1isBko0
RT if you like. Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I have to go and shoot the music video for my next single ‘National Anthem’.” - Lana Del Rey tells Digital Spy ( via: @lananow )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Cheryl is working on a song that I had written. It’s perfect for her and she really likes it. We talked on email.” - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And then 'Video Games' came out and I fell in love with her [ Lana ] as an artist as well, so yeah, she's super talented." - Cheryl Cole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: "... I just wanted something that sounded beautiful coming off the tip of the tongue." - Lana talks about alter-ego. # ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: "I never really needed a shift in persona because I feel I've been doing things the right way for me for a long time... "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doomed from the start, We met with a goodbye kiss." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rock and Roll, sent us insane, I hope someday that we will meet again." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDReyINDO You're welcome hun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: Follow @LanaQuote for the greatest collection of Lana Del Rey's quotes &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @GangstaDelRey &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @lanadelbabe &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @MermaidMoteI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @mermaid_m0tel &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LDRToday &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDelReyFact &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @PrincesssDie &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDelReyINDO &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDReyINDO &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @lananow &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @Hileeery &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDReyOnline &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDelReyUK &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @DelReyLane &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LoveLanaDelRey &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout To &gt;&gt; @LanaDelReyWorld &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I really think if would've been easier for me if you hadn't been so beautiful." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lights, camera, action. He didn't know he'd have this much fun." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If @LanaDelRey inspiring your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you know how expensive it is to look this cheap?" - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This sounds diplomatic, but I really do have other things that I'm a bit more worried about." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["American Dreams come true somehow, I swore I'd chase them till I was dead." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You think I'm pretty and you like the way I talk, I like your music and you like the way I walk." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Does she know I'm tattooed onto your heart? You can try to fight it, I have left my mark on you. There's nothing you can do." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Use that voice, sing that song and tell me to come on." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexiest Woman in the World : @LanaDelRey !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You think I'm pretty and you like the way I talk. I like your music and you like the way I walk, so, I think we're gonna get along."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I usually like to spend my money putting it back into the music." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hon, you never looked so beautiful as you do now my man." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hai @LanaDelRey :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Luck @LanaDelRey ! on The Voice UK tonight :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Feet don't fail me now, take me to the finish line." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is Art, Art is Lana Del Rey, Lana Del Rey is My Life. RT If you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Palm trees in black and white, last thing I saw before I died." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyINDO @LanaDReyIndo @Hileeery @LoveLanaDelRey @LanaDelReyUK @The_LanaDelRey @LanaDelReyBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell me I'm your national anthem." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you want LanaDelRey released a perfume called Dark Paradise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is she ride or die, bitch?" - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever we were to each other that we still are." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ARightLanatic You're welcome #TeamLana :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mon amor. Je sais que to m'aimes aussi. Tu as besoin de moi. Tu as besoin de moi dans ta vie. Tu ne peux vivre sans moi." - CARMEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always got." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted a name that sounded as beautiful as the music." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ARightLanatic: @LanaQuote I think Lana Del Rey would really like these mashups. they're really sensitively done http://t.co/4tebyFZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_LanaDelRey tumblr :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamLana is the Lovable fanbase! RT If you agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Putting your faith in the people is like building a house in the sand." - @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I did it the way I wanted to do it." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every man has to go trough hell to reach Paradise." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lana made a record that is incredible at a time when people aren't making albums." - Jimmy Lovine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stay out of those dark corners and walk towards the light." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sorelmusic: @LanaQuote Hope u will enjoy that ukulele cover of Summertime sadness : http://t.co/WQC7gs2m
#ukulele #summertimesadness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @mermaid_m0tel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @TheDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @XLanaDel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyFact @LanaDelReyWorld @LanaDReyOnline @LoveLanaDelRey @LanaDelReyUK @LanaDelReyWeb @The_LanaDelRey @Hileeery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyBR @LanaDelReyCAN @LanaDelReyDaily @lanadelbabe @MermaidMoteI @AlanahDelRey @LanaDelReyINDO @LanaDReyINDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Estellejour: @LanaQuote New pics & video lana Del Rey with Jaime King, so beautiful http://t.co/vwCINc9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you @LanaDelRey , I love you #TeamLana !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Overdosing, dying on our drugs and our love." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted a name that sounded as baeutiful as the music." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cause baby we were born to live fast and die young, born to be bad, have fun. Honey, you and me can be the one, just believe, come on." #LD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If @LanaDelRey is your sunshine, strenght, hearts desire, treasure, world and your greatest love!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big dreams, Gangster!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe that there is no doubts about who I am, an artist who loves music, above everything." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: "The music I’ve been most obsessed with lately is Lana Del Rey." - Ingrid Michaelson #LDRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Red, white, blue's in the skies. Summer's in the air and baby, heaven's in your eyes." #NationalAnthem LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think #NationalAnthem Video is Gorgeous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierrapritta: "Pick your model wisely, find out what they did, and do it" #LanaInterviewAtChatteu @LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Gaga released a parfum called "FAME", I think Lana should release a parfum called "DARK PARADISE". #JustMyOpinion :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be always at war with ur vices, at peace with ur neighbors, &amp; let each new year find you a better man." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kiss me hard before you go, Summertime Sadness. I just wanted you to know, that baby you're the best." #SummertimeSadness LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And I'm America's Sweetheart, cute delicious sweet tart." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We always love you till we die, You are our Hollywood Sadcore Queen @LanaDelRey #HappyBirthdayLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think Lana Del Rey is a Hot Female Indie Singer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey Is A Genius Musician. RT If you agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Once I was lost, but now I'm found." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I knew it was wrong, I'm beyond it. I tried to be strong, but I lost it." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If Lana Del Rey's songs make your mood good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter what you linger, cause you like me even when I'm your Queen." - #DumDum LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've spent my whole life driving in cars with boys, ridin' round town drinking in the white noise." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cos we're a match made in heaven, and this kind of love's forever." - #GhettoBaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like all the greats from every genre, just the masters of every genre." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey Is a Queen Of Hollywood Sadcore. RT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Is My Angel and No Doubt about It. RT If you agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pretty from afar like a dark star." - LanaDelRey (via: @LDRchina_doll)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So talk to me about why I'm your dream girl." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>