<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaeneySnow @RabbitWhat They catch flies, you'll be glad of them later in the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amcgauran @garethstack The only one with spin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acloudonastring: Saw a Robin strike a Blackbird, a Blackbird go at a Starling, a Song Thrush hit the window, &amp; endless attacks &amp; counte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @E2Klassic: Mood: #sneachtageddon https://t.co/xXf3FhovjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ccferrie: Don't let #sneachtageddon stop you from cycling - get yourself some cable ties and hey presto, snow tyres! https://t.co/5UBZf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IrPsych: Overnight #Sneachta, #GrandCanal, #Dublin, #Ireland, 28.02.18 (2). #BeastFromTheEast https://t.co/7hKUj26kGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DogsTrust_IE: Trapp had snow much fun today we just had to share another video of the wee man! To find out more about him: https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IrishRail: The Connolly crew clearing points ahead of the evening peak #BeastFromTheEast #sneachta https://t.co/dSVpmmaXlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @newschambers: If you’ve the day off work and thought about a run out to IKEA, you may forget about it. It’s closed for the day, I under…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IrishRail: Here’s our frozen crews pictured while clearing frozen points in #Maynooth to keep trains moving #snowselfie #beastfromtheea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TG4TV @MargaretMolloy @CiaraODoherty @_snaithe_ @Wearing_Irish Go raibh maith agaibh as Snáithe. #snaithe #Irishfashion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harney_terry @daraobriain A chop of the ruler/the dreaded bata - all things you could usually dodge, unlike bullets. On the bright side, once a teacher slammed his fist on the desk of the girl beside me in bad temper. She was paring a pencil and all the splinters went into his hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days until the new Game of Thrones season... https://t.co/B8MdhsUPNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chlomoj They remade 'Day of the Triffids'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeanieMary @LeeDrinksTea @christinaemoss Interesting how different schools are. I also started at 4. The class cried for ages. I tried to cheer them up. Our parents said they would come back for us after lunch. Why cry? It'll be ok. Our first teacher deserves a medal. Imagine facing 35 wailing children every September.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BookRiot: Librarians are often seen as community superheroes, but those expectations come at a price: https://t.co/M1t8D2wt4c https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freesafelegal: Order our Valentine's Day Cards today! https://t.co/NCAU5W1RG0 via @freesafelegal https://t.co/eLWYPEFi1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_GerryManderin: Is that a little hat-tip to #Outlander in the Jacobite #Lego display at #StirlingCastle @welovehistory ? @Outlander_STA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gardainfo: As Christmas fast approaches, online sales and offers will be commencing in the coming days. Here are some Golden Rules of s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gardainfo: D/Sgt McCormack from the Online Child Sexual Exploitation Unit with advice for parents &amp; teenagers of what to be aware of on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KernanAndrews: Why is it vital to #repealthe8th and to make #women not the unborn the centre of debates on #Abortion? @Repeal8Galway di…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmmyMaher: Come on, people. One of you buggers had better volunteer to be my valentine. I'm sick of buying my own Toblerones. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MyDoncaster: We’re pleased to unveil our own real-time gritter map, where you can track our fleet as they go about their route! It took…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daraobriain: This is a very funny thread, although very Irish. Non-irish people  should consult a map. https://t.co/7Bhz87vwOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizCarolan Thanks for this. Relieved to see that my TDs are in favour of choice. All of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botzarelli @daraobriain In my limited experience, most would stay put and start a petition...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'The Brexit dream is dying... we're headed for the status of a colony': Turmoil i - https://t.co/ELaJwQxXIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Eight down, five to go as rescue efforts to resume tomorrow in Thai cave - https://t.co/GbC6y5uLAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Rodent infestation, flies and insects in ingredients: Eight food businesses close - https://t.co/P6DaiXp3y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Coins, ID cards, and false teeth... what they found when they dredged canals in A - https://t.co/occc7CjfPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Government to fund US and Canadian students to come here to learn Irish - https://t.co/qqWztDLFUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Filibustering is parliamentary vandalism': Ross says TDs against drink-driving l - https://t.co/iWEhhA10HR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Public servants will be able to work until 70 under new Bill  - https://t.co/WMKnQXMchm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Primal fears come out': The conditions inside the Thai cave and how the rescuers - https://t.co/j8k7KxaTwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: An Post delivers its first parcel to an island by drone - https://t.co/bkDgczZx7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water has received 40 reports of people disobeying the hosepipe ban - https://t.co/I9W7ddjsXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I reported the teacher who abused me but he was left teaching for three years af - https://t.co/6Sq56mrNVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Explainer: How the new Dublin Bus network plans would change your route - https://t.co/AIiYOdqPZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: This plan could see an iceberg being towed to Cape Town to ease drought condition - https://t.co/zW1h7OEp91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you support the new drink-driving laws? - https://t.co/JNM6hyvSgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I had a glass window put in on top of me': Young offender armed with iron bar ca - https://t.co/r3tnTVJL01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Like rabbits caught in headlights': Catholic schools head says sex ed has not mo - https://t.co/P2X0O2oemL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mother Teresa charity 'sold babies' born to unwed mothers - https://t.co/oWrMSVfLLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Drink-driving laws passed by the Dáil as Danny Healy-Rae shouts, 'This is a sad  - https://t.co/Kg7XUmfWCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Inquiry into suicide of Donegal sergeant who was investigated by Gsoc finds 'mist - https://t.co/Nxne2Y4LgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Tuam: Ex-residents and families want further excavation and DNA analysis - https://t.co/ISnFCzPB0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Garda dressed as a postman to deliver 36,000 ecstasy pills to suspected dealer - https://t.co/pCPIchQTUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Supermacs to introduce recyclable cups, paper straws and biodegradable burger wra - https://t.co/mtbC9OkcHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Shatter slams proposed trade ban with lands occupied by Israel; Senator tells him - https://t.co/ole3LkaMbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish sprint sensation breaks record en route to European 100m final - https://t.co/AGK1U9LEqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland and US agree to share travel information of convicted child sex offenders - https://t.co/j5wJJ3GHMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Chris Froome booed and whistled at Team Sky's Tour de France presentation  - https://t.co/SXZKEJOenU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Heart condition medication recalled over 'probable carcinogen' impurity - https://t.co/iHThXp21ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Drugs unit garda suffers acid attack at hands of heroin gang he's investigating - https://t.co/Mg2jmhJt7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Republican group stages 'action against colonialism' by spraying over 'Victoria'  - https://t.co/nZnUtcorYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Six stores closed as over 240 Lloyds Pharmacy workers to take part in a strike to - https://t.co/pe2AUWEeTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trump's environment chief quits amid investigations into first-class flights and  - https://t.co/wFJHDMUeYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Drink-driving laws passed by the Dáil as Danny Healy-Rae shouts, 'This is a sad  - https://t.co/Kg7XUmfWCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Severe safety risk': Public warned not to fly drones above wildfires - https://t.co/fiHLwbv0RI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Three suspected rhino poachers eaten by lions in South Africa - https://t.co/laSlCInZQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Are you making an effort to conserve water?  - https://t.co/YCmKcLvCsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Hundreds of nudists to descend on Paris for a spot of trampolining today - https://t.co/g6xin5MKDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Posters and postcards show how Irish suffragists were 'ridiculed and feared'  - https://t.co/JjcDbvgwNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Minister calls on supermarkets to reduce the use of non-recyclable plastic packag - https://t.co/4z27GfHCI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí in three stations to start wearing controversial new summer uniform from  - https://t.co/qd6aptXyoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Therapists were relieved when the WHO listed gaming addiction as a mental health - https://t.co/lzHGHzWD7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Will you try to catch a glimpse of Harry and Meghan in Ireland? - https://t.co/8i6OqRwJAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Met Police issue appeal for missing siblings who may be travelling to Ireland - https://t.co/TspfNvJEb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Australian woman was trying to feed sharks when one bit her finger and pulled her - https://t.co/hzLDtOWWLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Easing of bad weather opens crucial window in search for missing football team in - https://t.co/bw71cMrvjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: ‘A lot of people would have said I was mad, but it seems to be going from stren - https://t.co/Iv6xZP9y90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Customers complain over widespread Vodafone broadband outage - https://t.co/lnDS0z2Mkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water issues another urgent appeal for people to conserve water as Dublin h - https://t.co/kALjgkACre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I think of it like a puzzle': The Irish architect who turns tiny spaces into env - https://t.co/BqDfSjCxjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Kitchen Secrets: What's your best tip for choosing ripe avocados? - https://t.co/xiOwhtoDJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: The perfect summer feast: Crave-worthy Mexican chilli and the only guacamole reci - https://t.co/sRgsDOJWEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Column: '61% of girls my age are embarrassed about their period' - https://t.co/S21jDRm2fO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland plans to ban sale of new cars with tailpipes by 2030 - https://t.co/DcMRo9xWRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Farmers say Aldi's €1.30 two-litre bottle of milk is 'socially irresponsible' - https://t.co/y6Mtl3QntE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Men's testosterone levels largely determined by their childhood environment, stud - https://t.co/RvxEJMTQsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland plans to ban sale of new cars with tailpipes by 2030 - https://t.co/DcMRo9glsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man arrested after rock thrown through window of Pantibar - https://t.co/sBk2M0x8WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Is it ok to wear shorts at work? - https://t.co/hVf6XccImA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AaronReguTV: someone said Theresa May curtsying reminds them of a velociraptor and, well, I couldn't stop thinking about this scene htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Here are some of the best photos readers around the country have sent in this wee - https://t.co/nBepNo5hLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 16,000 travellers stranded after massive volcanic eruption in Bali - https://t.co/A5lF7miRkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Arlene Foster says opposing marriage equality doesn't mean she can't value LGBT p - https://t.co/DzQdCNAd8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man loses High Court challenge against Northern Ireland Secretary over border pol - https://t.co/izYMGepmDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man loses High Court challenge against Northern Ireland Secretary over border pol - https://t.co/izYMGe7LeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water has imposed a hosepipe ban in Greater Dublin Area from Monday - https://t.co/NBMfNqIZyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should there be an upper age limit to running for public office? - https://t.co/eX6ginHCJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ice cream van smashes through church doors in Kerry  - https://t.co/9Zw4BwbVCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water set to announce specific bans on water use - https://t.co/EyPBAaM8dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: US Supreme Court judge Anthony Kennedy announces retirement - https://t.co/v5dLaNCTiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Senior gardaí allegedly spread rumours that whistleblower was having an affair t - https://t.co/1Dd60eehn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Raped at 11: 'Why wasn't I told my attacker tried to be taken off the Sex Offende - https://t.co/TMjVPIfHT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Calls for hosepipe ban as Irish Water says it is operating 'on a knife edge'  - https://t.co/eKzhfMBEgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Council urged to stop 'Mickey Mouse' road patch-ups and invest in full improvemen - https://t.co/RwVI3IYHIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Eircom fined €23,500 for continually over-charging customers  - https://t.co/qPr5ycsikQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Having a tough time sleeping in the heat? Here's how to stay cool as temperatures - https://t.co/86g08CZYpO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>