<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A TQ Member Visited Mr.Silver - Treasure Quest Metal Detecting Forum http://bit.ly/bV5GN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JFActivist: How Many Children in America Are Not Taught to Read? http://bit.ly/FEhMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sgs,uscgs,unc,ani ????? - Coin Talk http://bit.ly/Co8t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Tweets about Buy Coins as of July 31, 2009 - Starting Your ... http://bit.ly/Ox7Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE MARK TAYLOR CANDLESHORE BLOG » How Many Children In The United ... http://bit.ly/1ArAuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Anyone Buy Gold Or Silver Coins Or Bullion As Investment? http://bit.ly/kJ2sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finest Rare Coin http://bit.ly/B1i3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coin Collecting : Buying Old Silver Coins | Coin Collecting http://bit.ly/Dm32r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dashchang Thank God!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyChristian Love Maui. We sold out timeshare at Kaanapali Beach Resrt to help fend off the wolves at home  Silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[capitalismpulse: Follow the Swiss &quot;big money&quot; managers and buy gold http://bit.ly/fqmo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Purchase Gold Bullion | Gold Bullion http://bit.ly/aEJ4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonnyAhuja Congrats u are having an wonderful life. Tnx 4 the follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking out the great followers I am accumulating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhinvestments Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loadedbeachbum Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woodys_tavern Thanks for the follow. We used to have a Woodys Pizza in town but they downsized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlavan Treasure those moments with the kids they are so important for you and them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmytheJamokie Protect your wealth with silversnowball.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinBooren Yes, for sure.  The most important things in Life are invisible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loadedbeachbum Sorry Im late getting back to you. Let me know what is going on where you live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronabber So how did you get 50k followers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@successmastery   Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelBlock Thanks for the follow! Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Preston777 Thanks for the follow! Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffKowalczuk Thanks for the follow! Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awebbiz Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Investo2 Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dapsiua5 Thanks for the follow! Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronabber  Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mynetincome Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielstorer  Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickwilmott  Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlDigitalEye  Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParklandFlorida Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinBooren Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twitta_links Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonwhite Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcEisenman Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanEllis Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrangeCountyFL Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewMaDotCom Thanks for the follow! Send me an @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing. SilverSnowBall.com/1438]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on my Twitter promotion... looking good so far.   http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laplante_ent Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country Story – Coin Cheat | CMWONG.COM http://bit.ly/1kTDBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given $2000 what would you buy? - Coin Talk http://bit.ly/JR0s7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charging lithium company http://bit.ly/4Gjvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! The followers are flooding in!  What a great bunch of fascinating people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarieVENEZIA Hi, Marie Thanks for the follow! See my little website at create- great-art.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Allinson Thanks for the follow. Tweet me @SilverSaver and tell me what you are doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Chapman News: Bob Chapman bullish on gold and Silver Bearish ... http://bit.ly/ze65l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold and Silver update 11/7/08 | Silver Bullion Bars http://bit.ly/FNX6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mickydaic: cash for gold jewelry http://bit.ly/tmiRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Self-directed IRA: the Pros and Cons - Finance and Investment ... http://bit.ly/16Rxv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@serennu I have interests similar to yours. How are things in the UK? We are having prolonged Spring here in Colorado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehotpicks Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@factlets Thanks for the follow! Would you liike to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrvingBloggist Thanks for the follow! Like to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bizmarketcoach Love your bio.Thanks for the follow! Like to grow your followers on auto-pilot and make money?  http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abigails59 Thanks for the follow! Would you liike to grow you list of followers on auto-pilot and make money as you do? http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesWMagee Would you like to build your followers on auto-pilot and make money when you do?   http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nathan_Johnson Would you like to build followers on auto-pilot and make money to do it?   http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scoldon Would you liike to grow your followers wile making money doing it?
 http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connecting with new followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting my new twitter builder set up  - so far looks good!   http://bit.ly/BYHES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PCGS Launches All-New CoinFacts Site : Coin Collecting News http://bit.ly/41jdhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Bullion Dealer | Gold Bullion http://bit.ly/UZChf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revenue from agriculture and Traveler&#39;s Back pack for WoW Gold ... http://bit.ly/18KGnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Self-directed IRA: the Pros and Cons http://bit.ly/NcYea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth&#39;s Blog: Silver http://bit.ly/kk5XO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikepfs Glenn Beck had a white board full of information which made BOs plot rather clear, I thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melaka Coinage-Portuguse Tin Coins | lunaticg banknote &amp; coin http://bit.ly/2J4FqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beginners Guide To Coin Collecting | Teach Me To Do http://bit.ly/hFi2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COIN BUYING EDUCTION 101-6 ( New 9/4) - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/snBIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe Haven | Let&#39;s Get Physical With China http://bit.ly/1AeRfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Time to Buy Sarah - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/4NsLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coin Collectors: Do You Have Coin Insurance? - The Fun Times Guide ... http://bit.ly/SGpXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who thinks Gold drops big tomorrow? - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/TlIqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superior Gold Group renews advertising support of the Fox News ... http://bit.ly/xbXmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Nears $1000, Silver Tops $16, Stocks Rally Late - Coin News http://bit.ly/jIygB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is The United States Bankrupt? - Investor&#39;s Iraq Forum - Iraq ... http://bit.ly/16vd0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Back Within Striking Distance Of $1000 http://bit.ly/QbTWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Harden Boredom can lead to innovation. Failure is the normal pathway to success. Try art! http://create-great-art.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don&#39;t Take Cash For Gold | Bukisa.com http://bit.ly/9Bggv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Mint Shifts UHR and First Spouse Gold Coin Prices Higher | Gold ... http://bit.ly/ORbix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Konformist Blog: Debt: The first five thousand years http://bit.ly/3XsKPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy American Silver Eagle Perfect Us Coin Obama Ms Bu Stand For ... http://bit.ly/1008CH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Jumps vs. All Currencies on &quot;Job-Loss Recovery&quot; Data - Buy ... http://bit.ly/zkUYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth Silver Tigers - CoinTalk http://bit.ly/2m1TZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GEEK KEN: Lightening the coin load. http://bit.ly/3I4cMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Coin Collector&#39;s Payoff: When Bank Rolls Yield Valuable Coins ... http://bit.ly/3pAuOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-Time Most Complete Collection of Early Large Cents to be ... http://bit.ly/CWHYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Purchase Gold Coins | www.gold-coin.com http://bit.ly/4D5aIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change coming to Silver - Kitco Forums http://bit.ly/1rFagp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coins sell | Gold Scrap Biz http://bit.ly/enPUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[~ Peace Dollar Buy Silver Coins | Us Mint| Sell Silver Coins ... http://bit.ly/FnOFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy 2009 Proof Sterling Silver / President Barak Obama Coin For ... http://bit.ly/RrfLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where is the best place to buy gold/silver bullion online? | Buy ... http://bit.ly/vxcIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fly Buy: SONS | Stock Picks and Discussion at iBankCoin | The Fly http://bit.ly/3pEbxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vegas Collection Featured at Heritage&#39;s Long Beach Auction ... http://bit.ly/100wCg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>