<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/G0gSfVdFYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/evpipUminW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/bGva8viJeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/nqKYxBAUGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/1RkJi5baKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl 1:  I spent my vacation fishing  Girl 2: Then why did you buy a new bathing suit?   Girl 1:  That was my bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/7mIuJRcOZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/yPHswpCtJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/9vxUHo6W4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/o5i8uhMjV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/6JWIiFMfkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/7N0yYQNNkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/LFMDPicFpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/Wq4r5Sx614]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/3tjtGpk990]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/YLDnjNyVba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/5bJ78us0jN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/bG2LRueHw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/0FxYU2QYRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/TklAGjiz7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/MiwanCvnxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/m9cF9KegkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/bVmZNcyTzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/KO7ZK16nVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/JANOQaNGQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoes are special shoes for discerning feet. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/9CgJVUg8XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/15dJxc76YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/8E0wyvav2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/KOvoRJN6ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/iNwlqeuCGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/VXQh3jK8gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/iU12YhXWF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/NH6ufdj3qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/ktKHexlUg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/F4VgrwmMZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/KZxvf8w9LZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/lIlm9m8Ys2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/5IIstxwgwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/dsC3MYSvmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/EJh6TmlPP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/vbacsNAIfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/bo3fsdS6EL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/zs7TvOvc6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/bYFgrV15P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>