<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/4qLmWRMxBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic actress opens up about mother's suicide: A new HBO documentary by award-winning filmmaker Susan Lacy highlights the drama and on-screen work that have marked actress and political activist Jane Fonda's career. https://t.co/1Wj4f33eel https://t.co/QGreI4p8n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Developer: Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Java Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to design, develop, and modify web-based enterprise software applications throughout the software development life cycle (SDLC)… https://t.co/eKinKeiD5c https://t.co/fq3QVo7W1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennifer Garner's school pickup look is epic: Jennifer Garner posted a video on Instagram of her taking advice from Reese Witherspoon's new book, "Whiskey in a Teacup." https://t.co/IpP2JxibzU https://t.co/OTYrzoLNFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated Driving Software Engineer: Automated Driving Software Engineer, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – English – Italiano – Franais – Espaol – Portugus – – Japanese – Korean – English English en – Italiano Italiano it –… https://t.co/RycE2KFHMe https://t.co/BNvtC97qQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commerce Secretary Ross ordered to testify in lawsuit over Census question: Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross must sit for a deposition in a lawsuit against his department over its decision to include a question about citizenship in the 2020 Census, a… https://t.co/I8RIBbcOmu https://t.co/6iMP3s1AcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captain arrested in ferry disaster as death toll climbs to 209: Tanzanian President John Magufuli has ordered the arrest of the operators of an overloaded ferry that capsized this week on Lake Victoria, killing nearly 200 people in the latest maritime… https://t.co/L5pfFINZXV https://t.co/85G8KIw0md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Administrator: Roush Management, LLC, full-service eng’g company in Troy, MI, seeks Senior Database Administrator to lead data storage activities for data mgmt solut’ns for custom vehicles. Duties: study system reqs, customer reqs,… https://t.co/4E7bOh04Ne https://t.co/dWxciWPjzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/LdcVMxeSIe https://t.co/1oth695AJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In one 24-hour period gunfire broke out a 3 different workplaces https://t.co/IaKAiKvH8n https://t.co/UbXFeuMhUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/85dOVPgLof https://t.co/rQreCfQMuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLC Programmer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or function, every… https://t.co/CuTGEWUiVq https://t.co/Rnyb9JmkYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: A financial services organization is looking for a Data Architect to join their team in Detroit. Responsibilities: Maintaining the logical design and implementation of databases and data systems Resolving complex data related issues,… https://t.co/1SMEHfdfp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst – Data Analytics: At Roush, we fuse technology and engineering to provide product development solutions to customers in a diverse range of industries. Widely recognized for providing engineering, testing, prototype, and manufacturing… https://t.co/UFSmwmfk8t https://t.co/dhrt2qcog6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway to Cuomo in fiery debate: I'll walk away: Counselor to the President Kellyanne Conway spars with CNN's Chris Cuomo over whether the FBI should investigate allegations against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. https://t.co/WDlQas6CUd https://t.co/8V9daCxyFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: General Summary The Software Engineer will contribute to the future success of the company by significantly contributing to the engineering processes necessary for the manufacturing and performance of on time, on quality, machine… https://t.co/EwMFqET0t1 https://t.co/2pcQb3wLd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: Job Description – Zeeland, MI, USA – Full Time If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career opportunity for you!… https://t.co/xz0X2xPX6T https://t.co/vnFioN4KMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution =============================== The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with… https://t.co/EQgpg1ILRF https://t.co/cqYcGMNA09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile App Developer – Innovation Lab: As an App Developer you will be part of a small R &amp; D Innovation team developing products and services utilizing future technology. We are looking for a candidate to work with us on innovative products and services… https://t.co/L7qaoGz48q https://t.co/U7rD5E3qhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China just blocked Amazon's streaming service https://t.co/RVgNU2aFAM https://t.co/oKcFwAXrVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Cyber Security Manager: Electrical Supervisor – Ferris State University. Responsible for the 7200 volt distribution system. Supervise and coordinate work activities of the Electrical Department engaged in assembly, installation and repair of equipment… https://t.co/eLpBifVBmO https://t.co/Vbz1Ao3MEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CES Interior Electronics Senior Software Engineer: Job opening: CES Interior Electronics – Senior Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly… https://t.co/k51gRZdq7X https://t.co/jUlaS9EqzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Safety Technical Support: Job Title: Process Safety Technical Support Location: Wyandotte, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: BASF – We Create Chemistry Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Chemical, Pesticide and Fertilizer Career… https://t.co/HK0kL9MjfM https://t.co/2UbaAf9QMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer: Gestamp Chattanooga, LLC. Job Description TITLE: CNC Programmer Reports To: Tool &amp; Die Supervisor Department: Tool &amp; Die Exemption Status: Non-exempt Location: Chattanooga TN Date: 08/12/15 Approved By: HR JOB SUMMARY Responsible for… https://t.co/tzG6RBD1Er https://t.co/hlJmvZX30i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with PCF Experience: Java Developer with PCF Experience Ref No.:18-15685 Location: Dearborn, Michigan Position Type:Contract Start Date: 08/31/2018 Java Developer with PCF Experience Dearborn, MI Contract Detailed JD: Must Have Strong… https://t.co/37lCiF243Y https://t.co/0ZrwdQboLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBIEE Developer: OBIEE Developer Ref No.: 18-41092 Location: Midland, Michigan Title: OBIEE Developer Location: Midland, MI Duration: Long term Role Description – Working on OBIEE ad-hoc reports + dashboard developer. – OBIEE 11 reports development… https://t.co/tmvRoXPQ6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: A Lead Software Engineer (Operating System Software and Technical Lead) job in Pontiac, Michigan is currently available through Belcan. The Lead Software Engineer will be the technical lead for the development, verification,… https://t.co/7AghAuwIZ6 https://t.co/aABlSpQ8aF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suge Knight pleads no contest to manslaughter, faces 28 years in prison: Former rap mogul Marion "Suge" Knight pleaded no contest Thursday to manslaughter in connection with the death of a man during a hit-and-run incident after a confrontation on the… https://t.co/U1HXWdvF53 https://t.co/1udqFeYxku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBilingual Customer CareBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck Consulting-NonActuarialBusiness &amp; Market… https://t.co/CmXKHxV25J https://t.co/nXCSQlWnDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer: A CNC Programmer job in Wixom, MI is currently available through Belcan. In this role, you will be responsible for offline programming for turning on CNC Lathes using G- and M-codes on aerospace materials using Mastercam software. To be… https://t.co/v5rgIUZzNq https://t.co/tuVkte1epw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Democrats can finally win here, they could take back the House: Republican Rep. Mike Coffman is sitting in a church communicating with a group of Spanish-speaking parishioners in their native tongue with a heavy American accent. https://t.co/0w7lV2qMk2 https://t.co/HSuH0BSqst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst 1: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Programmer Analyst 1 for location Lansing , MI for one of our Top client. Responsible for developing and maintaining existing applications for the Michigan… https://t.co/ybS3S2yBlB https://t.co/EqYND0FRUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-39478 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Salesforce Developer job description Job brief The Salesforce Developer will perform hands-on technical implementation, with a focus on delivering functional… https://t.co/RjIEAF2ErB https://t.co/fSePnctfCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panelist: Don't talk to me like that: A CNN panel discussion gets heated over the Brett Kavanaugh sexual assault allegations. https://t.co/kEnkVcjfcX https://t.co/YxhNJNgTii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Business Intelligence: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/ev6Alzb7fL https://t.co/ivUPVg4ney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/e1ieALPj2u https://t.co/GaBmGsZYJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrated food researcher to step down after research is questioned: Brian Wansink may have helped shape our country's relationship with food. As director of Cornell University's Food and Brand Lab and in roles for the US Department of Agriculture,… https://t.co/VOgsEsyjLp https://t.co/KHHqqiK5xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developers///only Green Card And Citizens Can Apply: Android developers///Only Green Card and Citizens can apply Michigan Center, Michigan TechnogenInc Jobs Toggle navigation Failure Message Sign In Sign Up Career Portal How to Sign up to career… https://t.co/e4NMyUCsEh https://t.co/uEdnGQDeeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – Engine / Transmission Controls Designs and integrates engine control software. The selected individual will work within DENSO’s Engine / Transmission Controls team. This individual will help integrate DENSO software… https://t.co/fT3A17Cr0G https://t.co/nYZXZzilMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Benefits –… https://t.co/iM44OWAdSC https://t.co/Fy2NuugiPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Devops Engineer Ref No.:18-16322 Location: Dearborn, Michigan Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 09/11/2018 Role: Devops Engineer Location: Dearborn, MI Duration: Contract Job Description: Mac/OSX knowledge iOS, Android, or PCF… https://t.co/McDKexw3IF https://t.co/Ffbt4OHgBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Applications Analyst – HR / HCM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as… https://t.co/lMcPmJHGoB https://t.co/mPgfEXQolQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Functional Support (PP / MM): SAP Functional Support (PP / MM) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering Jobs – Accounting and… https://t.co/lbHclBxR5s https://t.co/sobJHErIny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Analyst I- Production Systems: This position is a primary support for the Manufacturing plant floor, supporting the local IT department. Support in the area of network communication IT Analyst I- Production Systems Responsibilities: IT Analyst I-… https://t.co/5rpMI37L7r https://t.co/fqS63NZtYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/4Ot0jKT7lN https://t.co/Zq2lJJcllq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: It’s fun to work in a company where people truly BELIEVE in what they are doing! We’re committed to bringing passion and customer focus to the business. Are you looking for a rewarding career with the opportunity for… https://t.co/p05OkvKmYe https://t.co/o02PiS6BUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Engineer: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as… https://t.co/FcRKZblrU9 https://t.co/9NUH1VcnXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL-Developer: ETL Developer Populus Group seeks an ETL Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide database development in the healthcare industry; develop, design, debug, test, and document ETL process for Date… https://t.co/gJC5ApPAoU https://t.co/vcfDQWNqRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Util Systems Specialist Grand Rapids, MI MRE: Job Description Util Systems Specialist – Grand Rapids, MI MRE #32302 Date: Jul 24, 2018 Location: Grand Rapids, MI, 50123 Company: The Davey Tree Expert Company Requisition Number: 32302 Company Name: DRG… https://t.co/uOjiqIlff9 https://t.co/9IL1U5TMGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEM Technical Architect: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. | AEM Technical Architect Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including… https://t.co/LbExTGUlsU https://t.co/I90Moqe7HR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution: Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution =================================================== The Technical Services Support Specialist provides systems management technical support and… https://t.co/FkmZUC0WAX https://t.co/EbnEZRU0Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Human Resources Analyst: Associate Human Resources Analyst HARMAN International Date: Aug 21, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Job Description A Career at HARMAN We are ONE HARMAN.… https://t.co/UPjDvGTepF https://t.co/tzkDW8Sk73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Lead: Career Opportunity: Test Lead- Farmington Hills, MI Are you thrilled to work on the latest in in-dash navigation and services for cars? TomTom s Custom Systems teams are challenging, fast-paced environments where people are empowered to make… https://t.co/82U3cjKWOy https://t.co/YuC8hMUIgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBIEE Developer Lead: OBIEE Developer Lead Ref No.: 18-41011 Location: Midland, Michigan Title: OBIEE Developer Lead Location: Midland, MI Job Description: Working on OBIEE ad-hoc reports + dashboard developer. OBIEE 11 reports development experience of… https://t.co/5RvSTif1n5 https://t.co/XjFf4lCWnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critics shamed man in viral video, then they learned this: A video of a passenger shaving on a train went viral and many shamed the man on social media. The Associated Press tracked down the man in the video and reported on his life story. https://t.co/2xWExtusHe https://t.co/bfYWdxHdFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airline misspells its own name on plane: Sometimes, a massive typo is right in front of your eyes and you can't see it. https://t.co/SUkp8Ujb8Y https://t.co/9Eo8jce01A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer: Job opening: CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the… https://t.co/ivaMfeKpPB https://t.co/xBWJUSAmse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Cyber Security Manager: Electrical Supervisor – Ferris State University. Responsible for the 7200 volt distribution system. Supervise and coordinate work activities of the Electrical Department engaged in assembly, installation and repair of equipment… https://t.co/LRiC0bowfA https://t.co/KwAGuEMnwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Model Based Systems Engineering (MBSE) and Requirements Application Technical Lead: Model Based Systems Engineering (MBSE) and Requirements Application Technical Lead – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob… https://t.co/dvToa1YBw0 https://t.co/qJNAduFcqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career… https://t.co/7EXCCko24J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GM Basic Software: Software Engineer – GM Basic Software – GPS******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/OGodYltCIJ https://t.co/wlQ8ZBikRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woolworths pulls needles from shelves after strawberry crisis: Australian retail giant Woolworths has temporarily pulled sewing needles from its stores after at least 100 reported cases of the objects being inserted into strawberries nationwide. https://t.co/nczxWbU9ut https://t.co/1FYuae5LBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Software Engineer Technical Lead (Contingent) – Warren, MI: Davidson Technologies | Career Opportunities Davidson Technologies, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer (M/F/D/V). Start Over with Job Search Already have a profile? Login Now… https://t.co/j3qR23xsp8 https://t.co/iHXEhcOM2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Dawn Technologies – Home – Organization – Partners – Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use – Services – IT Strategy – Application Development – Mobile Application Development – Business Intelligence – Cloud Computing – QA Service Offerings –… https://t.co/4yMiHS4VSH https://t.co/Z3cxVlvuxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interaction Designer 3: Interaction Designer 3 – Warren, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip… https://t.co/Ya4zJPPjeh https://t.co/gGomZsXLqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Cybersecurity Engineer: Embedded Systems Cybersecurity Engineer (RMF/DOD) job in Sterling Heights, Michigan, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our… https://t.co/A4AIj2xQpJ https://t.co/B79tK4YVip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Software Testers: As a member of the corporate team, you’ll focus on enhancing the relationship with our clients as we provide outstanding business solution services. Within departments like Accounting &amp; Finance, Human Resources, and Engineering,… https://t.co/pruKI5bwyq https://t.co/24GC8csE0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Developer: Senior Embedded Software Developer – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/bK0jduz5Z7 https://t.co/SEfAaAj6At]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisconsin shooting leaves 3, suspect injured: Police are responding to a report of an active shooter in Middleton, Wisconsin. Authorities are asking everyone near the 1800 block of Deming Way to shelter in place. Police have not released details on… https://t.co/bSiFUUDBSw https://t.co/0C8SLhNSnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect (JDA WMS): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/7DqiZUA6X3 https://t.co/xPGcGy7bgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Business Intelligence: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/qGDj68HnGi https://t.co/pXPPrpFIMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/1eoKkbGEgK https://t.co/2zt2WhZu26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Chassis Controls (REF23961Q): Company Description Do you want beneficial technologies being shaped by your ideas? Whether in the areas of mobility solutions, consumer goods, industrial technology or energy and building technology with… https://t.co/2LKYHs6FdA https://t.co/m0aihfnt87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer I: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/2OJ3b4w0E7 https://t.co/nk4NYo1yV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new iPhones are boring. Investors should rejoice https://t.co/oT13Nw8VN5 https://t.co/wAokDOdoUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMM Programmer/Quality Technician- 2nd or 3rd Shift: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No… https://t.co/FiqZ49EdqR https://t.co/CTLPHhGzVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 411 on scoliosis: CNN'S Holly Firfer has the details about scoliosis.. what it is and what you can do. https://t.co/GmUWlFNj9x https://t.co/N3g81ZmWnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Auburn Hills, MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Software Developer The Software Developer is responsible for leading configuration projects on multiple credit application systems used in the end to end… https://t.co/oypHkcM9ia https://t.co/S6l2jnS6Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Clapper: This is domestic terrorism: Former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper reacts to news of a suspicious package being addressed to him at CNN in New York. https://t.co/ktruyeovWR https://t.co/BWfCXhRe7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer – Infotainment: Senior Embedded Software Engineer – Infotainment – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our… https://t.co/TJ6aWR6inT https://t.co/JHRZX6SGYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Intern, ERP Solution: Software Development Intern, ERP Solution ========================================= We are seeking software engineering interns to join our fast paced, dynamic team during the summer of 2019. Location Troy,… https://t.co/NqnzaaTdSB https://t.co/q0UJlm2PC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst Digital: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No.… https://t.co/PJLmn3nVXu https://t.co/LdxUbpXfvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nasdaq set to fall, dragged down by Amazon: Get ready for another scary day on Wall Street. Amazon is leading a brutal selloff in tech stocks. https://t.co/xhQBT9bFWj https://t.co/ddxgmaU8Bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, who has based his political career on crushing norms, is constantly tripped up by the conventions of the White House: Washington is locked in a destructive and acrimonious ritual that plays out every time President Donald Trump is called upon to… https://t.co/7S5Ouuk6iQ https://t.co/e1nzSEslMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer: Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBilingual Customer CareBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck… https://t.co/hY410HhhKS https://t.co/GolpHU639F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Modern Family' character killed off: Fans knew a death was coming to "Modern Family," but did you guess right? https://t.co/at8BtG0dpj https://t.co/CdOZqvqKT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stories behind hip-hop's most iconic images https://t.co/FhgI2CfzTi https://t.co/U0N5XZOaYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with accepted development department… https://t.co/MJ1bghQhbl https://t.co/soYqm3ubT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials: Packages may be linked to Florida mail facility https://t.co/yV8j6OBoRR https://t.co/yUngWEi577]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Programmer (Plymouth): CNC Programmer (Plymouth) – Job Listing – Loc Performance Jobs Search Jobs | Submit an Application | Home CNC Programmer (Plymouth) Salary Range:Negotiable Exempt/Non-Exempt:Non-Exempt Benefits:Medical, Dental, Life and… https://t.co/ULD04f17GT https://t.co/JTZLJXx2UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders defends Trump's attacks on media: White House press secretary Sarah Sanders defends President Trump's comments against the media following the discovery of an explosive device at CNN's New York offices. https://t.co/1b3V11v3BX https://t.co/zO8lfdNvlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Java Developer: IT Java Developer Alliance Inspection Management (AiM) is the premier new and pre-owned vehicle inspection partnership in North America that combines breakthrough technology with deep industry experience to provide a trustworthy,… https://t.co/FAzMpEMpMR https://t.co/loOIr4lzoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Data Analyst – Operations Improvement: Additional Job Information City, State: SE Michigan Location: SE Michigan or Grand Blanc Michigan – This opportunity offer flexibility in office location within our Michigan Ministry offices Department:… https://t.co/jcgWW3HdIY https://t.co/P8ODdc4DyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: DESCRIPTIONLoc Performance Products; Michigan’s premiere full service manufacturer of large CNC machined components and assemblies for military and commercial applications. Loc Performance is looking for an enthusiastic and… https://t.co/NqweEj2fft https://t.co/L0vL4nH8RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 foods that trigger migraines https://t.co/BkdAug5Mtk https://t.co/s05oCVNOsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: JOB SUMMARY: As a component of the product development lifecycle, analyze, design, program and test computer software programs and applications applying standard coding methodologies and disciplines throughout the software development… https://t.co/uWGHMuxWJi https://t.co/s3gJsGDsPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Interface Deployment: Software Engineer, Interface Deployment Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Software Engineer to join our Public Safety Interface Development team. Responsibilities for this position include design,… https://t.co/Yov2QDsu4s https://t.co/vsf7FYzdMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, seen with tag dangling from dress: The British Royal family isn't known for scrimping on its wardrobe budget, but Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, has left some wondering whether she hopes to return her latest outfit for a refund. https://t.co/UDsCDpE2bV https://t.co/g6Pr36AvpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wire Support Analyst: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Wire Support Analyst This position is primarily responsible for receiving and processing domestic and international outgoing payment orders from internal and external… https://t.co/ktqRQwKCtx https://t.co/mvr34FbZeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II – Cambridge MA – Relocation Expenses an: Our team is what makes Octo great. At Octo you’ll work with some of the smartest and most accomplished people you’ll find in your career. Octo offers fantastic benefits, and its an amazing… https://t.co/DwLYDdRpTm https://t.co/XOkmuJKlCA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>