<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Go after your dream, no matter how unattainable others think it is. -Linda Mastandrea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at your problems as problems &amp; they'll continue to hold you down. See them as blessings in disguise &amp; that's what they truly become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna make the REST of my LIFE, the BEST of my LIFE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't stress. Do your best. Forget the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never do a kindness to soon because you never know how soon it will be too late. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep dreaming. https://t.co/Rw2YXIF7zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after another. - Walter Elliott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brick walls aren't there to keep us out, the brick walls are there to give us a chance to show how badly we want something. -R Pausch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Only they understand that puppy love! ;)

Get your dog mom tee here --&gt; https://t.co/RtEShIb0IR https://t.co/tXb5jIJESO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Never let your fear decide your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity follows struggle. It follows effort. It follows hard work. It doesn't come before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discouragement and failure are two of the surest stepping stones to success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this life we cannot always do great things. But we can do small things with great love. -Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: First morning rule ;D 

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/PqVZRIFgkA https://t.co/hmAlr4VfSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/H5uys5lHHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can be anything, BE KIND. https://t.co/shjsofP6uO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most precious possession that ever comes to a man in this world is a woman's heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impossible is not a fact, it's an opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Some of the best advice. https://t.co/i8oGOjjhEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you make a commitment, you build hope. When you keep it, you build trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always have hope. https://t.co/Cibg9ljxnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out. - Robert Collier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not joy that makes us grateful. It is gratitude that makes us joyful. -David Rast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May your life preach more loudly than your lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging a person doesn't define who they are, it defines who you are. https://t.co/Vsr1c6WWzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovmydog: The i am cute but not interested face https://t.co/Mqae1UO2Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is not counted by how high you have climbed but by how many people you brought with you. - Wil Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take control of your emotions before emotions take control of you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true. https://t.co/xKaYsGSSND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who believe, better things come to those who are patient, and the best things come to those who don't give up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person who chases two rabbits catches neither. #stayfocused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FORTUNE FAVORS THE BOLD https://t.co/fZoUERuuct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ninety-nine percent of the failures comes from people who have the habit of making excuses. -George W. Carve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being honest may not get you a lot of FRIENDS but it'll always get you the RIGHT ONES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of us are just about as happy as we make up our minds to be. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Feelin' fabulous B)

Get this fab tee here --&gt; https://t.co/PxgsjtI6eE https://t.co/Pu0YENd8d1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God loves you more in a moment than anyone could in a lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovemypug: Everything seems clearer now https://t.co/MxAquk5cEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't make footprints on the sands of time by sitting on your butt... and who wants to make buttprints?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be slow to fall into friendship; but when thou art in, continue firm &amp; constant. -Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/TiM3tE84CU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why compare yourself with others? No one in the entire world can do a better job of being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Epic_Women: A woman is like a tea bag: you cannot tell how strong she is until you put her in hot water. -Nancy Reagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why try and be fake when being real takes less effort?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes some courage to stand up and speak; it takes even more courage to open your mind and listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the first step in faith. You don't have to see the whole staircase, just take the first step. -Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In life you are either a passenger or a pilot, it's your choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything if you have enthusiasm. Enthusiasm is the yeast that makes your hopes rise to the stars. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Do you know what my favorite part of the game is? The opportunity to play. -Mike Singletary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep calm, you may be weak but God is strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You always have a place to run to, always. The place is GOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your smile change the world but never let the world change your smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We either win or we learn. https://t.co/1Vepq6voRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take responsibility for yourself.., because no one's going to take responsibility for you. -Tyra Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We plan the way we want to live, but only God makes us able to live it. It Pays to Take Life Seriously -Proverbs 16:9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the good in every moment. https://t.co/q75VNQfPNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is peace of mind which is a direct result of knowing u did your best to become the best that u are capable of being. -John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is love that makes the impossible possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To wish you were someone else is to waste the person you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ship is safe in harbor, but that's not what ships are for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/LTjMg1BPSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be a lion for a day than a sheep all your life. - Sister Elizabeth Kenny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effort doesn't matter if love is left behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: We were born to succeed, not to fail. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were born to succeed, not to fail. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God didn't bring you this far to leave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmazingiGrace: Prayer is powerful, it's amazing what it can do. https://t.co/VKt1KNcXEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something now that will make the person you'll be tomorrow proud to have been the person you are today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do all the good you can, to as many people as you can, as often as you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step through new doors. The majority of the time there's something fantastic on the other side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to make an impact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent is God given. Be humble. Fame is man-given. Be grateful. Conceit is self-given. Be careful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Subscribe to our daily emails by VISITING -&gt; https://t.co/f4NMDRwDHD https://t.co/G3amADkEcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not hope, you will not find what is beyond your hopes. - St. Clement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: Excellent Advise!
https://t.co/6upoVikvZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life is your message to the world. Make sure it's inspiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_HQ: A healthy mind in a healthy body! ;)

Get your hoodie here --&gt; https://t.co/iqayMryOZr https://t.co/ZmdTWZW07B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mother_know: Mom1034 https://t.co/HrrSUqUJWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power. - Mary Pickford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Care less, smile more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Christmas cartoon shirt is terrific for Weimaraner dog lovers for Christmas holidays! :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/wLTWnlzlAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honest answer is like a kiss on the lips. -Proverbs 24:26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're bored with life, if you don't get up every morning with a burning desire to do things - you don't have enough goals. -Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every saint has a past. Every sinner has a future. -Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True bravery is doing what is right even when it's not popular. https://t.co/TLw5b3lspG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allow yourself to be a beginner. No one starts off being excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't count the days, make the days count. -Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great movie even better quote. https://t.co/oEqYVqBIhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has a blessing with your name on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: If you have never made a mistake then it means you have never tried something new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to win, although to be a winner, you must plan to win, prepare to win, &amp; expect to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't measure a man's success by how high he climbs, but how high he bounces when he hits bottom. - George Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot push anyone up the ladder unless he is willing to climb. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/rgE9wUorcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Good vibes only :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/QNMeASPe54 https://t.co/Yc2wQ2GYXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the best you can until you know better. Then when you know better, do better.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>