<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Eloqua Developer: Eloqua Developer $85-95K +Bonus *Can be located in Alpharetta, GA; Arden Hills, MN; Bloomington, IL* As a Eloqua Developer, you will provide best practice marketing automation direction, implementation assistance, and ongoing… https://t.co/Xbbt6ajbtA https://t.co/PbBCfVh9TZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: i9 Technologies is a growing Albuquerque-based small software development company seeking talented software developers to create and extend existing business applications. The Software Developer is responsible for the design, development… https://t.co/hTBTbhrMoB https://t.co/T2erw3oT50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Systems Specialist 2: U.S. CITIZENSHIP REQUIRED* RESPONSIBILITIES: * Assist reviewing proposals, contracts, regulatory, program and customer requirements to prepare quality assurance plans and tests for hardware and software products, processes… https://t.co/VutTPaeOsq https://t.co/cqi3VTjtkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The Principal Architects serve as the technical design authority and architectural expert for sales opportunities across multiple vertical and geographic regions, in support of the… https://t.co/LIkPZGpyHX https://t.co/jveCObpRYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Arlington, VA Job Type: Design, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/27/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/3y03LyNHZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer w/ Active Secret Clearance: Job Opening | Columbus – Facebook – Twitter – Linkedin – Home – Home – Default – Home – Corporate hot – Home – Color – Home – Light – Home – Video – Home – Video – Light – One Page Website – Sliders… https://t.co/7tzku0tC4F https://t.co/19idEpaKGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead of TAM Information Security: TECH LEAD OF TAM INFORMATION SECURITY RESPONSIBILITIES * Protect and secure company resources in the cloud, virtual and physical infrastructures. * Coordinate with Information Security team to ensure solution… https://t.co/vO3VYZHCaw https://t.co/LG7g1HVvc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Technical Support Representative Our Technical Support Representatives are the front line support for more than 290 million customers. As a Technical Support Representative, you will: – Maintain exceptional customer… https://t.co/X5Sqxk6V8L https://t.co/BCzO2FglK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Solutions Architect: – Solutions Architect Job Locations US-IL-Chicago Req No. 2017-4239 Category Sales Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience, Cloud Networking, and Cloud Edge solutions, Riverbed – The Digital… https://t.co/p71JpXnQWV https://t.co/dbjt9dRT7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer – NTX: Principal Software Engineer – NTX Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture –… https://t.co/pMGDn4fnWk https://t.co/BhTaX42my2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/1/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/a2rIDS5eeg https://t.co/CfNPwDmSWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer @ Cox Automotive Corporate Services, LLC (Mission, KS) – Dsgn, dvlp, test, implmnt &amp; maintain core integ softw tech &amp; sys integs. Reqts: Master’s deg (or foreign equiv) in CS, Engg (any), IT, IS or rel +… https://t.co/TdjCvurWel https://t.co/MP7SUYJKX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Engineer: At Periscope Data, engineers work the whole stack – from shipping UI to optimizing the billions of rows in the data cache. We’re constantly making the SQL faster and the charting more powerful. You’ll be working on the full… https://t.co/IHfBcjo3d0 https://t.co/U17VaW7h54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Fremont, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based in beautiful Union City, we are an exciting, ground-breaking and passionate Construction company that specializes in the Mechanical Industry. If you are interested in joining a… https://t.co/8UGSl5U3OS https://t.co/DIgFIZUs2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Lead (up to Profit Sharing): Software Engineer, Lead (up to 25% Profit Sharing) ================================================== Req #: ******Location: Sterling, VA USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with… https://t.co/HjRgM8EZwu https://t.co/JOx3MHKAAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equipment Tool Technical Analyst (Early Career): Location: Renton, Washington Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Analyst Jobs Boeing Commercial Airplanes is seeking Early Career Equipment &amp; Tool Technical Analysts to support the 737… https://t.co/fvulYc4kCT https://t.co/mTa601GDLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southeast Asia's Grab launches innovation arm to develop tech start-ups: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Southeast Asia's Grab on Tuesday launched Grab Ventures, its innovation arm to develop technology start-ups in sectors such as transport, food services,… https://t.co/m8xwJut5jh https://t.co/dcVEZzUqrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst #KS-01: Senior Business Systems Analyst – Service sought by ICU Medical, Inc. in San Clemente, CA: Work with business to document requirements &amp; assist in the development of designs for implementation.   recblid… https://t.co/WbLWqIRw0G https://t.co/1vjq60EzQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Director: Own And Drive Our Content And Creative Strategy: Periscope Data’s mission is to become the default data analytics software solution for data teams. The problem is, right now, our brand isn’t known far and wide. As our first Creative… https://t.co/KW83v51cvT https://t.co/DDESWFZpCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Engineer: At Periscope Data, engineers work the whole stack – from shipping UI to optimizing the billions of rows in the data cache. We’re constantly making the SQL faster and the charting more powerful. You’ll be working on the full… https://t.co/vNhyaAOgaR https://t.co/3t88k43vVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #R48397: Software Engineer Req ID R48397 Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Perform technical design, development, modification, and implementation of computer… https://t.co/G1vY5zkS9k https://t.co/dwQq3SEhE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Demand Generation: Help Drive Demand For The System Of Record For Data Teams: Periscope Data is looking for a Director of Marketing to drive our GTM, customer acquisition and demand generation strategies and tactics. You’ll drive our… https://t.co/DsVgcLNlv0 https://t.co/7vAf9wo1aF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End UI Engineer for Massive Media Company: Are you interested in working on a critical data-driven product for a multinational media conglomerate? Were seeking a Senior Front End Developer to build out the front end and UI of our new platform. Who… https://t.co/NwSDiWOQ9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal PeopleSoft Application Modeler/Developer: Manages the software application development, configuration, unit testing and deployment and integration of technical solutions for the IPPS-A project. Provides data models from business systems… https://t.co/YgmA1NvRny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Specialist 2:   Job Description – Configuration Management Specialist 2 (17020446) Configuration Management Specialist 2 Requisition ID : 17020446 Location : United States-Virginia-McLean US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/YZhYPNeiNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Systems Assurance Engineer: 112686BR Sr Principal Systems Assurance Engineer MA – Marlborough 112686BR Senior Principal System Assurance Engineer System Assurance is a new role within IDS Engineering Quality responsible for assuring products… https://t.co/0fVrjr1Qfg https://t.co/WOuKNIOgKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-24916 Work Location US-CO-Longmont Department / Discipline Project Management Additional Work Location .. Position Type Staff / Permanent Job Description Overview / Responsibilities Wood is currently seeking a Project… https://t.co/753apyBnox https://t.co/xOCM4CH4Lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Engineer – React: Salt Lake City, UT Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today We are a growing innovative Health Care Company looking to bring on a talented engineer with iOS and React experience. What You Will Be Doing – Developing new user-facing… https://t.co/R6QPVtPrVw https://t.co/jS703LOAmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA TESTER: Product owner Ref No.: 18-23025 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Experiences as Product Owner, Business Analyst Java /JEE Web technologies development experiences Preferable Agile Product owner certification . Excellent analytical and problem… https://t.co/bWCaikOzNs https://t.co/mvJTD7e2u9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workday Integrations Developer: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/eQp6THlJE6 https://t.co/Gng07EcIER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/Front-End Developer: UI/Front-End Developer Ref No.: 18-23653 Location: Irving, Texas Job Description: — Candidate should have minimum 1 years of IT experience as a front end developer. — The candidate should have prior experience on front end… https://t.co/N6enccA22a https://t.co/yxxT3VZVK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing IT Technical Analyst: Chevron is one of the world’s leading energy companies, with approximately 60,000 employees working in countries around the world. We explore, produce and transport crude oil and natural gas; refine, market and… https://t.co/mSoJ2uRcmy https://t.co/fBNThWft6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Sharepoint Developer: Job Information: Mid level point Developer Job Email Opening Title Mid level point Developer EOE StatementWe are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment… https://t.co/6ejw6sw9KW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-22214 Location: PA, Pennsylvania TCS Project: Requirement / Java Developer / Norristown, PA / 12 Months duration Essential Skills Rest/Soap Web Services, Java, Java Scripts and Angular Role Description… https://t.co/JsTddj3A3y https://t.co/lm0H1WxGCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-09288 Location: Irving, Texas Position Type:Contract Start Date: 05/21/2018 JAVA/J2EE, Spring Core, Spring ORM/Hibernate, REST, Spring Boot, Spring Integration, Hands on in Java/J2EE Design patterns , PL/SQL… https://t.co/FwssFQcWSO https://t.co/xOFQofE58D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Developer: Job TitleSAP ABAP Developer – ID:31298 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsABAP FIORI AND UI5 AND BAPI LocationAshburn, VA Date Posted03/23/2018 SAP ABAP Developer Location: Asburn, VA Duration: 6+ months Contract Responsible… https://t.co/rFrTSvZPrH https://t.co/MJNMLIKI8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Scrum Master: Job Description Make a Difference Every Day with Team Applied The people of Applied are making a difference every day through innovation and a commitment to help safeguard and protect what matters most. With first-to-market… https://t.co/ystBeBiDxg https://t.co/VxLWWF6ZIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Web Developer – https://t.co/FpSKRyGFkw: ********** has entry level programming positions for recent college graduates with science, math, or engineering related majors including multiple programming courses. We will provide advanced web… https://t.co/03pIamkSHX https://t.co/TxkE2AsWPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Design, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/Zez8vEhAFp https://t.co/6yiep5bi1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: Description Join the Information Technology Services team with The Space Telescope Science Institute (STScI) as we continue to expand the frontiers of space astronomy. STScI is located on the Johns Hopkins University Campus in Baltimore, MD.… https://t.co/dFT2MOq7OM https://t.co/YrwZxceeHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Real-time Control / Power Systems: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As… https://t.co/i4IKjpEQpm https://t.co/QZnKRJRmqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications Systems Engineer 3:   Job Description – Communications Systems Engineer 3 (18009777) Communications Systems Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18009777 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position:… https://t.co/kzkkJxfY2E https://t.co/GQgomVb4YB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Validation and Data Integrity Specialist: System Validation and Data Integrity Specialist Quality Chemical Laboratories is seeking a full time System Validation and Data Integrity Specialist. A Bachelor’s degree in an IT or related discipline with… https://t.co/NrPD0ynt1J https://t.co/KmwQQfFVv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Informatica Developer: ETL Informatica Developer Ref No.: 18-22589 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for ETL Informatica Developer in Tysons, VA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new… https://t.co/Ew9oDUxRXA https://t.co/FEcdAINj69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: * Business Intelligence Analyst (Requisition#A44URZ) Manage Data &amp; Logistics system that drive &amp; support the operations for Apple in the Americas region. *… https://t.co/8Q8aIXYDf0 https://t.co/7gp9VlFVbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Career Fair May 8th: Plan to attend this Professional Job Fair and meet with several of the area’s finest employers. Employers at our events typically recruit for the following categories: Sales, Customer Service, Retail, Administration, Management, IT,… https://t.co/pj4dhvBgRa https://t.co/hXpjbR6kPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services: Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA or Mountain View, CA The Twilio platform enables companies to integrate communications directly into their applications via… https://t.co/11RbOGvGKc https://t.co/ePOd19xm2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer 3:   Job Description – Systems Engineer 3 (17011618) Systems Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 17011618 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/t7917UmuZA https://t.co/nZjDMvmdAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Imaging Scientist: United States of America, California, Mountain View Staff Imaging Scientist ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS: Researches, designs and develops new and robust solutions in image segmentation, registration, machine learning for analysis of… https://t.co/GOVUrDaJY1 https://t.co/xIbsN3Gdap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sap Apo: SAP APO Ref No.: 18-23107 Location: Loveland, California – 10+ years of SAP Planning experience. – 5+ years of hand on consulting experience in F2B process. – 2+ years of experience in forecasting &amp; planning. – 1+ end to end green field… https://t.co/tyPqcrlV0t https://t.co/BxHKMLYi3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Support Engineer: Java Application Support Engineer at Fiserv, Inc. Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations –… https://t.co/NAnNifDlv4 https://t.co/8YZcnOT0xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Ninja: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today Are you an IOS Ninja? If so, read on… We are building a brand that is synonymous with real-time discovery and decision making. We are growing far beyond college deals, and eventually… https://t.co/VUbYKUKCaG https://t.co/NVZUfDJzkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Positions: Sr. Systems Administrator (Sacramento): Responsible for managing all service delivery resilience, efficiency, and audit programs as well as ensuring engineering standards and products are integrated across the ESX estate. Responsible… https://t.co/GM56QOuHFu https://t.co/xFHiP12CO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmers/Analysts, System Administrator, Software Developers: Clutchpoint LLC seeks: * Programmers/Analysts * System Administrator * Software Developers * Data Base Administrators Primary worksite Herndon VA, but relocation possible.  recblid… https://t.co/YCNLP4v8qQ https://t.co/XhLgmy4uJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist III (Clinical Informatics): Data Scientist III (Clinical Informatics) UT Southwestern Medical Center Dallas, TX The UT Southwestern Medical Center seeks Data Scientist III (Clinical Informatics).     Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action… https://t.co/WARiJtxptv https://t.co/vspIAwm3cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Software Engineer: Advisory Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Develop, specify, and support Electronic Design Automation (EDA) tools used to create integrated circuits in controlled methodology flows. Research and develop… https://t.co/VItkrSDmA9 https://t.co/YC7rt0WByE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trainer: Ref. No.: 2387 Job Title: Accounts Payable Specialist Office: WASHINGTON D.C. Practice Area: Accounting Posted Date: 09/07/2017 Job Type: Full Time Job Description: McDermott Will &amp; Emery LLP is a leading international law firm with a… https://t.co/FR6VQ7ddtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Technical Officer – https://t.co/FpSKRyGFkw: ********** is looking for a hands-on Chief Technical Officer to manage a team of developers and data scientists. ********** is a leading online service provider to lawyers and consumers. Our servers… https://t.co/pjxYwnuaiS https://t.co/ltddZFfUpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/KnS55JDRG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Local candidates preferred Software Engineer II is responsible for the development and implementation of Digital Technologies like Chatbot, NLP and strategy, and ensure the internal and external clients have a great digital experience.… https://t.co/N6OnYmCVmw https://t.co/Xp0uvLpuqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Business Analyst: * Create user stories, acceptance criteria, and manage tickets * Assist the Product Manager/Program Manager to develop necessary artifacts to define and deliver products * Provide feature testing of end-to-end features * Respond… https://t.co/YzvzYB9Mrn https://t.co/b3YAgG9Tix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Front End Developer: Overview Sally Beauty Holdings (NYSE: SBH) is the world’s largest wholesale and retail distributor of beauty supplies. Our world headquarters is conveniently located in Denton Texas, just 5 minutes north of Lake Lewisville off of… https://t.co/1bePajZYFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – eCommerce Catalog Services Platform: Senior Software Engineer – eCommerce Catalog Services Platform at GoDaddy Skip Navigation Careers Open Menu – GoDaddy Life – Our Teams – Benefits – University Students – Blog – GoDaddy Home… https://t.co/gErcdqqbui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I – Civil Engineering – Transportation: Job Description – Project Manager I – Civil Engineering – Transportation Job LocationUS-TX-Dallas | US-TX-PlanoJob ID1217-17491 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular… https://t.co/gS4NoZMcv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Job ID: DG-******* Description: As the healthcare industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable healthcare for our… https://t.co/srURW05MRG https://t.co/JX2qjCr20O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Specialist /Associate Solution Delivery Consultant: Job ID 2018-3835 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Services &amp; Support About the Job Associate Solution Delivery Consultant The Associate Solution Delivery Consultant is responsible for… https://t.co/GkI8w8KSuA https://t.co/xmYhXvEBU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/lqXOOCXPc5 https://t.co/eplYp1fjhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/pVcAL4rF6G https://t.co/Fo7PrbVi5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/zfi2MJywSV https://t.co/CPajSKKYIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/otNRe7JxOT https://t.co/6ICety3gvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/abRYwFygit https://t.co/Audu6hnAJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/DkoTkJwUFU https://t.co/qdUXGffOsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/8T04Cryvwa https://t.co/fBGuoQawJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer II, Applications – Specialty Meat: Sysco Associate Apply – Click Here Company: CORP Enclave Location: US-TX-Houston Zip Code: 77077 Minimum Level of Education: Bachelor’s Degree Minimum Years of Experience: 3 Position Type: Exempt Travel… https://t.co/LgxAIjPgj4 https://t.co/nEzsQFYCa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Engineer: Location: San Rafael, CA Requisition ID: 17WD24867 Position Overview Are you looking for a high energy team where you can make a direct contribution to building a new data API platform? Autodesk is looking for a talented Sr.… https://t.co/K3FuXUbb26 https://t.co/tUIxuZqGQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[information security engineer: Location: San Francisco, CA- United States Job ID: 18WD27936 Position Overview Autodesk is seeking an Information Security Engineer who will be responsible for designing, building, assessing and deploying systems to protect… https://t.co/mkeHtzFCrc https://t.co/7ZA7FHG5Ih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Developer-(User Assistance): About the Team: The OpenEdge Content team’s mission is to deliver a persona-based, self-serviced, crowd-sourced, measurable experience through compelling content to rapidly enable our customers, partners and… https://t.co/YrUWw0NaFr https://t.co/47D3GTjWro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Sr. Systems Administrator: Linux Sr. Systems Administrator for Caelum Research Corporation in College Park, MD 20740(map) POSITION SCOPE: This position serves as the principal Systems Administrator and IT resource for the Ocean Surface Winds… https://t.co/4QMVgCR1k1 https://t.co/up7CsnpRLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Technical Support Interface #2435404: Engineering Technical Support Interface Bechtel National, Inc. in Richland, WA seeks an Engineering Technical Support Interface to act as technical assistant to a project technical director and manager on… https://t.co/mKolnIgBC5 https://t.co/vVEkMu40pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouting CEO, changing rules: inside Tesla's Model 3-building sprint: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - A tense and short-tempered Chief Executive Elon Musk barked at engineers on the Fremont, California assembly line. Tesla Inc pulled workers from other… https://t.co/CRjgW58oka https://t.co/PwesRHC7Sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D Engineer IC Design 3: ENGINEERING Broadcom Corporation has an opening in Irvine, CA for R&amp;D Engineer IC Design 3 (IRYHW) for definition, design, verification, &amp;docu-mentation for ASIC Development. recblid fsxgeq1xb0duson7sd2d4dges9uk9f https://t.co/6yrLAyviZs https://t.co/OEDxt0Oly6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump moves to block China Mobile's U.S. entry, citing security concerns: (Reuters) - The U.S. government moved on Monday to block China Mobile from offering services to the U.S. telecommunications market, recommending its application be rejected because… https://t.co/wPKJjDZOHm https://t.co/OF2GLInsbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer II: Application Developer II Richmond, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/26/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex Systems, part of On Assignment &amp; the 2nd largest IT staffing Solutions firm… https://t.co/dMeiE2EQ5f https://t.co/xkr5WJQa7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Software Engineer – NLP Job Description Summary As a critical member of the Asurion Labs team working on the Asurion Virtual Assistant (AVA) bot, the NLP Engineer will be responsible for defining innovative technology… https://t.co/sgvtfCr0uP https://t.co/kPDFVjppua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Databse Architect: TECHNOLOGY Concerto Health 85 Enterprise, Suite 200, Aliso Viejo, CA 92656 Database Architect As a Database Architect in the Business Intelligence department, architects will be responsible for building data warehouse facts,… https://t.co/a0ILM4LCB8 https://t.co/jbE3JXyCvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to to work in a cross functional development or testing team with special focus on quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process. Bachelor’s degree… https://t.co/TsuuhPZGB0 https://t.co/ZJxCjZZWIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Programmer Consultant Leads: Web Programmer Consultant Leads (El Dorado Hills, CA): Wrk on a Prdct Mngmt team rspnsble for the life cycle, roadmap, &amp; ongoing dvlpmt of the prdct pltfrm, &amp; Wrk interactively w/ busnss usrs &amp; IT staff to deliver prfssnl… https://t.co/4EtVzsDl8l https://t.co/dggOsc0XdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Solution Architect: Business Intelligence Solution Architect Date: May 31, 2018 Location: Clinton, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co Apply now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Apply Now EmailStart Please… https://t.co/MS1OwRRNDA https://t.co/yJj5M2XTle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multi Cloud Senior Operations Analyst: Multi Cloud Senior Operations Analyst Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by… https://t.co/MZjQpLYm7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Federal Energy Efficiency Renewables Construction: Job Description – Project Manager – Federal Energy Efficiency &amp; Renewables Construction Job LocationsUS-HI-Oahu Job ID2018-1302 CategoryProject Management Overview Fueled by a dedicated… https://t.co/7XSPsyk16g https://t.co/fJ64QSC1sJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Who you are You are a full-stack SOA engineer / generalist. Experience and (just as important) interest in working in a variety of layers and technologies within a SOA is a must for our team. This… https://t.co/dBBKHdJwxx https://t.co/GklFlFgjFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management 3:   Job Description – Project Management 3 (18012117) Project Management 3 Requisition ID : 18012117 Location : United States-California-El Segundo US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/R1pbANm0oA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/Designer: YOUR MISSION: Drive technology supporting our marketing efforts including website, blog, landing pages, banner ads and email marketing templates. Design and code with focus on interactive sections of the website and mobile… https://t.co/g5vf8fpAFx https://t.co/JE4C8GZDMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Executive Support Technician: Requisition ID 2018-42378 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description – Provides ‘White Glove’ IT Customer Support Services for the… https://t.co/UHG1ACoRbZ https://t.co/MQprDIf9Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer Java/AngularJS/JavaScript Secret Clearance VA: Senior Developer – Java/AngularJS/JavaScript – Secret Clearance – VA in Arlington, Virginia, United States | Information Technology at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte –… https://t.co/ULlFiiGdbN https://t.co/SLlK2XXIYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student Intern/ Project Manager: **Student Intern/ Project Manager** Locations:Sacramento, California Job Family: Project Management New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Energy Management **Business Unit:** Urban Transport… https://t.co/Zv0DjVzOTz https://t.co/mCVxR9k1fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect, Office 365: We are looking for Solutions Architect in Office 365 space who loves and understands Office 365 stack. We will provide you with the opportunity of a lifetime. You provide enthusiasm, a good work ethic, and the ability to… https://t.co/otqsOWr460 https://t.co/02twpgrWkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior NEPA Project Manager/Environmental Planner: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning,… https://t.co/8T8CUDbp2s https://t.co/mp2xhlSGNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (6+ Months Contract): Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We… https://t.co/bETrIdRCFQ https://t.co/tWRGDSxMfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Force Developer: The Salesforce Software Engineer will collaborate with the Salseforce Architect to develop Salesforce applications in an agile continuous delivery model. The position is part of a team that is responsible for application and… https://t.co/npkDLki1dS https://t.co/AaKTgYUqgA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>