<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/j4ED0SYfEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/Nf9d696q7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/INRXmB5Txy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/uYtBfrdqGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/OkLZzEvQ8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/lepdN2psld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/uXM7WZ0TZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/Hej2gQbe8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/A8cYMZNB32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/i6BebaGTy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/M8ZA2sqqia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/Rh53GadIZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/ZiIeIh8xbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/Z8QqOzwF1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/6u4fb1LK5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/mrbO6rAktr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/vLz5YSji9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/jVkTiRKJxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/0DKWgcRfFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/YeQxViDeRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/hdqr6m95CO  http://t.co/yo97rzuQfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/bn2iEmCoLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/ilQ4uIC1pJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/5WPP0OknBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/w6S41H3ITE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/uq90YQ2iKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/EsxI7D7zWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/oyhpssQ675]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/fWsjvIjpsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/AV9CwSyzOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/LWqSHh6P6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/cgrHwxkYC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/j5dZURXIhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/VTLalTV9yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/L3NB3yjzI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/usx7PfamSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/cJ90jSTMOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/zelKKitsTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/v6HkzDtqsJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>