<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/A07sLkzNbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/77pufxBsKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/5VZAsm3E5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/o37nAP0EWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/CaN9324AuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affiliate marketing has made businesses millions and ordinary people millionaires. - Bo Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/bTJ3dzVAQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/MRw4ct4zfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/OCU9c68pSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/MdQ9bsuwuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/TUHlMCGlQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/9kI7IuTpVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/sOJ8n3c5Zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/BPsD01ctCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/GmmwbdK2K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/cMuJRJcec8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kYvHkYahs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/8Cg5emLo8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/mF5nyVxRu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/Hpaxzvvvw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/IOC49CrseT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/ye98SPzv2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/Q5qq05acMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/ovONqBCjSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/IEGoAYu41v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/o1M1aNMMEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/h0WRCebFKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/s84XZS1Uft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/IDe7O3ekN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/XS2spOT14k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/2ekLKHNBX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/W04euiQiFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/6aZAGcCumE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/1wgCq3IZ6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/ym4k9UzL1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/0Y15LpdMDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/KioPKIEuz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/OWlJ77exAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/6sE0kOat0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/vEqvwRZxkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/iAFmpalyqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/jvhMrh4zVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/KNk9f0qOCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/RxIgAXCHbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/Wq2KiDJrFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/zzQW6DmPHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/PDUKR7mrsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/mFYiQokL4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/kEtQ43h1l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/YOQwS765UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/dyQCn9c6Op]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/o1M1aNMMEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/FlxSbB5HKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/9MVcNyQwTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/47JItw1oNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/Rh0rka0CVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>