<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Star Wars: The Last Jedi" Is Coming To Netflix In June https://t.co/WVAUvwV5GV https://t.co/vgauwNNwO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Lili Reinhart Story About Her Cystic Acne Will Make You Cry And Then Inspire The Hell Out Of You https://t.co/pZXm1EVMXx https://t.co/LTvMrKer9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlize Theron Is Playing Megyn Kelly In A New Movie About Fox News And Roger Ailes https://t.co/AHAzG0L3fy https://t.co/AJ2w7d1ta9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlannaBennett: Multiple of these women (Sandy &amp; Anne) have talked about the commonality of women feeling like an island on sets or only…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlannaBennett: Gary Ross: “One of the things we’re saying is you don’t have to grow up to be a princess” 
Anne Hathaway, Queen of Genov…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlannaBennett: “I’m really excited for the moment when this doesn’t feel special anymore,” except for the other special feeling of a bu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlannaBennett: We gonna heist. https://t.co/psHdT3lmsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonam Kapoor And Swara Bhasker Called Out The Double Standards For Woman-Led Films In Bollywood https://t.co/8YKFPztgRv https://t.co/bGBss09tys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khloé Kardashian Hit Back At People Saying She's More Focused On Her Body Than Her Baby https://t.co/gUvdBbseKs https://t.co/14DOivubhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's A Lovely Detail You May Have Missed In Harry And Meghan's Official Wedding Photos https://t.co/zK5AQFD8kD https://t.co/moDiDtjrnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katy Perry Kissed Someone's Hand For 10 Seconds Before Being Dragged Off Stage https://t.co/K6qSGEMm0B https://t.co/4fPqqb9avw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Corden Nearly Sneezed At A Very Awkward Moment During The Royal Wedding https://t.co/dhX3RQfAqm https://t.co/fpoVmeT8Iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Hilarious Uday Chopra Tweets That Prove He Is His Own Biggest Troll https://t.co/GzlNFkELBS https://t.co/PrRRD7T6qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grimes Says Boyfriend Elon Musk Never Stopped Workers From Unionizing https://t.co/6xJWUBw3sB https://t.co/nkqosjOw5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Movie Theaters That'll Make You Wonder Why Every Theater Doesn't Have These Things https://t.co/nIf90kblRs https://t.co/aKcO6A8ldA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Details From "13 Reasons Why" Season 2 You Might've Missed https://t.co/crL9iXmNeq https://t.co/Bmh2wbJC44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Pics From Cannes That Honestly Shook Up My Gay Lil' Heart https://t.co/2Qp7eqXVom https://t.co/YAEoWhqGXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Looks Mom AF In This Photo And It's Hilarious https://t.co/JCgtR3vj5i https://t.co/fHH1aGpEpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Travel Ideas Inspired By Filipino Movies https://t.co/JAjAT2DuPH https://t.co/EPzxnvK41H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Area Of Expertise: "Bridezillas" https://t.co/D3TQYkmpy0 https://t.co/DEXlu0NXq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mario Batali Is Being Investigated By The NYPD Following Sexual Assault Allegations https://t.co/ZrjSxpwvDb https://t.co/s5eS99V83i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mowgli" Looks Like The Darkest Adaptation Of "The Jungle Book" Yet https://t.co/cNW9qwhORs https://t.co/pDzBTmpoHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Memes You'll Only Get If You've Watched "13 Reasons Why" Season 2 https://t.co/srPPRYzG95 https://t.co/4Zh6byeXyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Things You Might Not Have Known About "13 Reasons Why" https://t.co/AW5E801b6i https://t.co/38FOyEarRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jake Gyllenhaal Might Be In The Next "Spider-Man" Movie https://t.co/5t84GVIGzY https://t.co/y5xXz1JCj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obamas Signed A Netflix Deal To Produce Films, Documentaries, And Other Series https://t.co/tByCD26A6n https://t.co/TH1kQ9FMh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Your "Schitt's Creek" Soulmate? https://t.co/kTcwyBwZzl https://t.co/Yl5bPMJcFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Well Do You Remember These '80s Cartoon Theme Songs? https://t.co/ECHvaa8Bvo https://t.co/6NFuTFvfXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What 24 Alt-Rock Stars Looked Like In 2008 Vs. Today https://t.co/eTtPd7iDqJ https://t.co/Xj8yGEK9RR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen Just Got So Fucking Real About Giving Birth And People Love Her For It https://t.co/GpzFkvhw45 https://t.co/eTn30c2Hip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet The Cast Of "Love Island" Australia https://t.co/3KA7AkhBvk https://t.co/WOXpLszlZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Tweets To Send To Your Friends Who Aren't Setting You Up With Princes https://t.co/zA2rTIxNev https://t.co/uMyQAUMcZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Suuuuuper Awkward Moments From The Billboard Music Awards https://t.co/zuLKn4NpJY https://t.co/jzGJ2sEO2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Janet Jackson Is Somehow 52 Years Old https://t.co/nnes6XNVm3 https://t.co/wBpmoAFWKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift's BBMAs Dress Took Over 800 Hours To Make https://t.co/f4GsZZooLl https://t.co/Ky8mkeqd9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 People Who Lost Their Shit Over Janet Jackson's BBMAs Performance https://t.co/tJBCQUtUgz https://t.co/9YZmLDc0pP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift And BTS Just Met Backstage At The BBMAs And I Don't Know Who To Be More Jealous Of https://t.co/zUn3Y0Mw5w https://t.co/qzOD80ldyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Metz Attended The Billboard Music Awards In Flats And I Feel SEEN https://t.co/FAvVgLzU4P https://t.co/4AAUi8B42N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troye Sivan Just Performed With Taylor Swift At Her "Reputation" Tour And I Am Well And Truly Shook https://t.co/BdBg5rvXtv https://t.co/3l5o6kTS5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI: Andy Cohen Was Actually The Best Part About The Billboard Music Awards And Here Are The Receipts https://t.co/hc9Cj6Ehcm https://t.co/6aTZQOQ6mL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Whole Cast Of "Queer Eye" Trolled Antoni And It's Hilarious https://t.co/tEB5173Frz https://t.co/ZNVPBxV6Xh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Clarkson Honored Mass Shooting Victims With A Tearful Speech At The 2018 BBMAs https://t.co/cpGktW4JjR https://t.co/dhe6WgOq8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amber Rose's Son Finally Met Taylor Swift And It's Honestly Just Too Pure https://t.co/BZuyFNwNKq https://t.co/ISmzyIg13h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 Times Regular People Really Fucked Up In Front Of Celebrities https://t.co/Zuh8EHYhVc https://t.co/4mtNuHR5SO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halsey Showed Up To The 2018 Billboard Music Awards Looking Like A Goddamn Emo Queen https://t.co/sGBJ8enwJ8 https://t.co/xrXoSdgBNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[55 Things You May Not Know About Prince Harry And Meghan Markle https://t.co/faTMfJYgso https://t.co/CVY6GWSu0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All The Looks From The 2018 Billboard Music Awards https://t.co/53WENEozv5 https://t.co/tSCPwUH8l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Radio Interview Moments That Are Fucking Bonkers https://t.co/dxhanTrajZ https://t.co/KRMqvfTCb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re Either A “Harry Potter” Wizard Or A Pixar Character — But Which One? https://t.co/RyNjxyBayE https://t.co/MfTrpIgDPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Sorry To Make You Feel Old, But Kylie Minogue's Song "Shocked" Just Turned 27 Today https://t.co/hf4UwY7Ay5 https://t.co/EMDul5d3ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[29 TV Show Couples People Loved, But Ultimately Grew To Hate https://t.co/oy5bVHFAAE https://t.co/Eh9LfqfOK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Probably Had No Idea That These Celebs Are Actual Brainiacs https://t.co/Hh02NBluQZ https://t.co/w4bR3bBfFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go House Hunting With “House Hunters” And We’ll Reveal What Area Of The US You Should Live In https://t.co/4NKZFzNd85 https://t.co/mZBaaTQ9lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is What Went Into Creating Deadpool's…You Know What https://t.co/b7J5ovz0vO https://t.co/oPO2odqH1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what went into creating Deadpool's…you know what (obviously: #spoilers) https://t.co/RCjJceiSoZ via @adambvary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen And John Legend Just Shared A Photo Of Their Baby Miles https://t.co/7A48vS82hg https://t.co/SQPxP9TXeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: UPDATE: #Deadpool2 fell a bit short of early projections, and won't quite surpass its predecessor. But it will still debut w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only A True Disney Expert Will Know How Old These Disney Princesses Are https://t.co/MS7mKnLrYa https://t.co/u8RmnpTLQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This "Halloweentown" Star Is A Silver Fox Now And It's Not A Trick, Just A Treat https://t.co/ppT4KWSiHA https://t.co/z05hxwTkPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 13 Wholesome Things Jennifer Garner Has Been Up To Lately https://t.co/OVS1UE3hUc https://t.co/qkUVSSrso6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandon Flynn Compared Bryce From “13 Reasons Why” To Harvey Weinstein And Donald Trump https://t.co/AV1oVtYGkg https://t.co/MGYRazKAFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Hoffman Went On Instagram To Explain The Meme Of Him At The Royal Wedding https://t.co/UCRQoWEiKE https://t.co/ZzjJpNpvnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Rewatched "She's All That" As An Adult And It Was Actually Still Good https://t.co/s4gLxM56ZM https://t.co/f5sE1ruUyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Moments That Prove "Superstore" Is Hilarious AF https://t.co/JrI4caVfMX https://t.co/URQYSZqsxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Of These Royal Movies Have You Actually Seen? https://t.co/HkScYi5t5I https://t.co/OJ7JTEHo1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 "Deadpool 2" Easter Eggs That Are Too Great Not To Be Shared https://t.co/VkKabxMQm7 https://t.co/XwISkqmqxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What % Elizabeth Wakefield And What % Jessica Wakefield Are You? https://t.co/kIwHYKLmy3 https://t.co/ZigghwPkRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Someone With A PhD In "Friends" Can Get 10/10 On This Quiz https://t.co/bN0p6xSOYc https://t.co/EQGIMp7H7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Reasons Why Terry Crews Is A Gift To The World https://t.co/cNXdFneRLN https://t.co/P80kN2lVWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia Argento Just Told The Audience At Cannes "I Was Raped By Harvey Weinstein Here" https://t.co/Jvo3NPu8Uq https://t.co/SVAQaaQ1b8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 21 Times Mindy Kaling Was An OG Wellness Hoe https://t.co/grhOLTMrnk https://t.co/xwehcyyzLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Royal Wedding Was Served With An Extra Side Of Black Excellence And People Are Loving It https://t.co/dw8HHJKjNT https://t.co/DbwhUSuifv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are All 58 Pop Culture References In "Deadpool 2" https://t.co/HPJMpC88ll https://t.co/BZr3r64yXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Unbelievably Cute Moments From The Royal Wedding https://t.co/XGMytyawmU https://t.co/Q4Jrbn1IBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Has Made Her First Appearance Since Giving Birth To Prince Louis At Prince Harry And Meghan's Wedding https://t.co/ndeaenVQa7 https://t.co/SjLNr04cMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Tweets That Perfectly Sum Up The Royal Wedding https://t.co/UnLPectlor https://t.co/I1bkrLRV36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats On The Royal Wedding But Priyanka Chopra Is Where My Heart Was At https://t.co/LZMTsE4873 https://t.co/IfjJQf1wkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Harry And Meghan Markle Just Shared Their First Kiss As Husband And Wife https://t.co/BRekgYWWgJ https://t.co/pCo1as95Qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Hilarious Tweets By Indians About The Royal Wedding https://t.co/1Eifp4bh0r https://t.co/ltLsQ2VJ9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are The First Pictures Of Meghan Markle's Wedding Dress https://t.co/1z4LS6qyAg https://t.co/nRyQUUKFGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Harry Said "You Look Amazing" And "I'm So Lucky" When He Saw Meghan At The Royal Wedding https://t.co/Aa8PH8L1ur https://t.co/TfHlPNgcmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are All The Celebrities Who Attended The Royal Wedding https://t.co/VHRrQB1bDe https://t.co/BDbiwyUSjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amal Clooney Went To The Royal Wedding Looking Like The Actual Sun https://t.co/QhDumSEkEg https://t.co/DyByCT5cmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Seasons Do You Associate These Iconic Pop Albums With? https://t.co/ZdZEzPdqbJ https://t.co/zLflNuzOVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone Is A Combination Of A Villain And Hero From "Shrek" — Here's Yours https://t.co/cW8wjPNDIe https://t.co/Wh6hTvcOKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Celebrity Instagrams You Missed This Week https://t.co/5k6V6eIWNj https://t.co/hOsrd17gJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Hilarious "Avengers: Infinity War" Jokes From "Deadpool 2" https://t.co/8NRl51kuXn https://t.co/7LblCAYrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rate These Movie/Food Combos And We'll Reveal Which Generation You Actually Belong In https://t.co/VoeWevcVwj https://t.co/DkFmJXs2C5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KateAurthur: After #Upfronts week has blessedly come to a close, here's the final-ish list of renewals and cancellations. It's rare for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Dateline” Headlined CrimeCon And The Fans Went Wild. Here’s Why. https://t.co/cWgrlHuXUW https://t.co/EsWyJQJUgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix Is Making A Sequel To "A Christmas Prince" So Prepare Yourself For More Yuletide Memes https://t.co/bbO2UaOBcs https://t.co/Uq2eyvueV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone's A Combination Of Two "Brooklyn Nine-Nine" Characters — Here's Yours https://t.co/HlndzU3Rhf https://t.co/8cqy7gbI7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New "Bachelorette" Cast Is Here, And The Bios Are Amazing https://t.co/5Pe2UOpVy2 https://t.co/TouT20GKzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennifer Aniston And Tig Notaro Will Play The President And First Lady In A Netflix Comedy https://t.co/fuYtdoBO5I https://t.co/uAsPuCnuNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's An R-Rated Muppet Movie Coming Out And Holy Shit, It's Filthy https://t.co/PmcwsWF5Lk https://t.co/Dfx1YBasJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTS Played With Puppies While Answering Fan Questions And Revealed Who's Going To Drop The Next Mixtape https://t.co/KmwArFBsxo https://t.co/MX5eklRLyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quel candidat emblématique de «Secret Story» êtes-vous? https://t.co/JlDloQojFW https://t.co/MxRqjHi611]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Or How Little Do You Care About The Royal Wedding? https://t.co/clgDZeXSIy https://t.co/llmRf8P4qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Celeb Tweets You Missed This Week https://t.co/c9kfOl1X8L https://t.co/Pz9RnCHHRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khloé Kardashian Has Posted A Bunch Of ~Cryptic~ Instagram Stories Which Suggest She And Tristan Are Back Together https://t.co/La3d6wtIpJ https://t.co/Hp6KZ1oaUE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>