<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Software Engineer (Linux Graphics Stack): We are now looking for a Senior Systems Software Engineer (Linux Graphics Stack): Nvidia’s invention of the GPU 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics,… https://t.co/nGsanT3Yr4 https://t.co/dwm1FzZOA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Angular Web/Mobile UI Engineer: Specialists On Call is the nations largest provider of telemedicine consultations at acute care setting, performed by board certified, fellowship trained specialty physicians. Nationwide, 400+ hospitals partner… https://t.co/Sw841H54BA https://t.co/Fc5jSL7DRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Staff: DESKTOP Support Staff DAS33530205 *Des Moines, IA* Will perform all roles of a Desktop Support staff.  Will be first contact for Support tickets and will assist Desktop Support 3 staff with harware issues and imaging staff desktop… https://t.co/gLzoZClFdx https://t.co/xZ5br0fE9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL Developer DSS86528656 *Richmond, VA* ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very… https://t.co/V8NA9SBO0A https://t.co/7Hm2XyJgL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6AnCBdW4Kx Architect/Developer: Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and… https://t.co/ZUUjonIyFX https://t.co/zQQRCdgYsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Google employees organize to fight cyber bullying at work: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - About 100 Google U.S. employees concerned about cyber bullying inside the company have organized into a group proposing new policies for conduct at the unit… https://t.co/vrsIBS7PLC https://t.co/gbO6XLBUE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Space Systems Engineer Job: Sr. Space Systems Engineer (Job Number:426382) Description: SAIC is seeking a seasoned senior space systems engineer and acquisition professional to provide systems engineering, acquisition strategy, and technical support… https://t.co/hMsuDqWeFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iLog Sustaining Program Manager: iLog Sustaining Program Manager Job Number: 113302870 Austin, Texas, United States Posted: Dec. 14, 2017 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job Summary The Support Shared Services PMO is looking for a strong Program Manager to drive the… https://t.co/OVhO7szct7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Financial Services Technology Lead – US UI Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/kPjPwCUSbP https://t.co/ALjlC65ole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer: Database Developer | Rigil Corporation – View All Jobs – Rigil Corporation Database Developer Location Oklahoma City, OK Type Full Time this posting 2018 – 005 Database Developer About Rigil Rigil is an award-winning, woman-owned,… https://t.co/OzJYCj6FUH https://t.co/k3iQL3rsrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional HSE Sr. Manager – America's:   Job Description – Regional HSE Sr. Manager – America's (51139) Job Description  Regional HSE Sr. Manager – America's – 51139  Description   This role is accountable for deploying the Corporate HSE policy and… https://t.co/stX9Kd0hhB https://t.co/ZtdAQbGR8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Analyst/Programmer – C and C++ experience – Cleared Position!: Belay Tech is seeking a CNO Analyst/Programmer to work on a critical mission within a fun group. You should have strong C Programming experience, a CNO background, and C++ programming… https://t.co/6GAqNyBaHu https://t.co/8zkO3PuNRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c#,.net, SOA, angular developer: Job Titlec#,.net, SOA, angular developer – ID:31088 Duration8 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsC#, .net LocationIrving, TX Date Posted02/23/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for… https://t.co/ITPcJmsGrO https://t.co/qwgXh6HS7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Engineer: GILLIG LLC is the largest and most dependable manufacturer of Heavy Duty Transit Buses in North America. Our customers are in all 50 states, and include cities, counties, transit districts, universities and major private… https://t.co/UszIlZ4joY https://t.co/HHy9MQYd3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Data Engineering: ASCAP is home to more than 625,000 music creator members across all genres – the greatest names in music, and thousands more in the early stages of their careers. We are the world leader in performance royalties, advocacy and… https://t.co/8AQA4QWGxy https://t.co/59QEtyHXih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level System Test &amp; Qualification Engineer: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical reconnaissance radars, as well as advanced… https://t.co/hOl42edY1T https://t.co/VzaA5FUFJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across… https://t.co/IXD7kzaieu https://t.co/sRtoJyXoZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippine banks on alert after cyber attack at Malaysia central bank: MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippine central bank has sounded an alert to local financial institutions following a cyber attack at the Malaysian central bank, in which hackers sought to… https://t.co/FYs1rZKii7 https://t.co/GsHcaW1abH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Platform Software Engineer (iOS): Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered… https://t.co/uYS96bBR3h https://t.co/IDeSIBPU0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Applications Architect: Anonyome Labs was created to give people control and freedom over their personal and private information. We believe that people should be able to determine how, what, and with whom they share their personal details. We are… https://t.co/ZI1g8ORe6A https://t.co/orPuqOPz9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Software Engineering: SUMMARY This role will be responsible for Leading and developing a global software engineering product team responsible for the development of Jamfs flagship Apple device management solution, Jamf Pro, and the Jamf… https://t.co/8VyMB9vocw https://t.co/vmpkOiwToU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Sales Specialist: Technical Sales Specialist Come work with us at NanoTemper Technologies. NanoTemper has a big mission — to enable researchers to do the best science of their lives. We’ve been around since 2008, developing, producing and… https://t.co/BcD94UTJZ5 https://t.co/xRy55PEJSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Overview New position alert! KUBRA Arizona is looking for a skilled Developer. As a Developer, you will work on a team to implement enterprise customer experience management software for our clients. What you get to do every day * Write code… https://t.co/n585lrOEQv https://t.co/97DvehHbS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Data Engineer: Junior Data Engineer Stonecrop Technologies, a telecom innovator focusing on improving the speed and motions of developing and improving communication networks seeks a savvy Data Engineering Manager to lead our Supply Chain Data &amp;… https://t.co/jEGRstzuo4 https://t.co/8XQj0kFFKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Consultant: Description QGenda is a fast growing Atlanta-based healthcare software company, with an amazing corporate culture, where we strive to be the best place to be a customer. Our software is used by thousands of hospital departments… https://t.co/HjuQEFfs2T https://t.co/ns996lpros]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banner 9 Developer: Need LOCAL or who can come for Face to Face Interview Position : Banner 9 Developer Location : Atlanta, GA Duration : 6-12+ Months Job Details: Banner 9 Developer with the following skills and experience: – Experience coding in: o… https://t.co/I2rVhaTQX9 https://t.co/LtthAXFIUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Required Experience: * Within the last seven (7) years, a minimum of three (3) years experience developing with Java in a Linux environment * Within the last three… https://t.co/Ulp8NaW2Sk https://t.co/RBUG0mBkRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer / Developer: Automation Engineer / Developer Location: Woodbridge, VA J.G. Wentworth Home Lending is seeking a motivated, energetic Automation Engineer / Developer for our Woodbridge, VA location. We are looking for a team player with… https://t.co/NQSn26aFAw https://t.co/1sjNHB6iJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Engineer:       Position Summary   As a member of the Corporate Construction team reporting to either the U.S. Construction Manager or other senior project manager, the Project Engineer will work on capital projects including new… https://t.co/Gk45NIXdYk https://t.co/niVjCvT7Oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer UI: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across more… https://t.co/wvAH5E0ctK https://t.co/KBKLZGy7uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn fourth-quarter net profit estimated T$71.66 billion, up 4 percent from year ago: TAIPEI (Reuters) - Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker and a key Apple Inc supplier, reported on Friday 4.2 percent growth in fourth… https://t.co/LcNNItlSc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Great opportunity to join a small team as it designs and develops a new enterprise software product for the FBI. The project is a modernization of a robust JEE application, rebuilding it in the cloud with a newer technology stack. (See… https://t.co/ItGqs9PBlQ https://t.co/lbRgCCvdP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer, Accurate Background: QA Automation Engineer will ensure the delivery of world-class high-quality applications for the various Accurate Background platforms. You will be triaging bug reports, performing tests, and expanding the use… https://t.co/35AJvAWmsw https://t.co/IlfKuuqtEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Engineer/ Project Manager: TheCompanyCompanies is an employee-owned, multi-disciplinary firm regularly named by The Business Review and The Times Union as one of the Best Places to Work. Celebrating our 70th year, the firm has deep… https://t.co/aE40TzwLBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Business Consultant – Entry Level: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Seattle, WA Job Type: General Business, Other Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 3/7/2018 Job Description Avenica actively recruits college graduates… https://t.co/9AvHmZdWoo https://t.co/Cyr4LqrJpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer: .Net Software Developer Chicago, IL $95-115K Prestigious Company is seeking a .NET Software Developer. You are going to be responsible for developing and maintaining our production platform. You do best with tight deadlines,… https://t.co/25CGUNudBk https://t.co/biN3xRnJHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Trenton, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 03/19/18, Posted Date – 03/19/18 Primary SkillsJ2EE,Spring MVC,Java Developer,Spring Batch,Spring Core,Spring AOP,Spring Transactions and Spring ORM,JPA with HibernateTax… https://t.co/DfihqKXtl8 https://t.co/TOiN1aSJbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Mgr., SC LCM Excellence: Job ID ******BR Posting Title Sr. Project Mgr., SC LCM Excellence Division ALCON Business Unit MFG/TECH OPERATIONS AL Country USA Work Location Fort Worth, TX Company/Legal Entity Alcon Laboratories, Inc. Functional… https://t.co/DDLyFcWWYe https://t.co/O9TydDFerB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: https://t.co/YrEWvtteet Services, Inc. and A2Z Development Center, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Quality Assurance Engineer I, Job Code AZ0078: Adopt best practices in software engineering to test code at… https://t.co/udrLlsAQ6J https://t.co/CE7iAWswEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Requirements: Bachelor’s degree in computer science, Management information systems, Information technology.  Experience/familiarity with Windows Server, MS Exchange, Cisco routers, WAN networking, SAN, VMware. $28.92 – $33.25 Hourly… https://t.co/mSqiPAsTgE https://t.co/r71zZrN3RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Software Engineers (Job code: SW318): Apply software development practices to design, implement, and support individual software projects. Senior… https://t.co/AE09Dqybqo https://t.co/fSZwWAgfWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scm/Devops #MP6334: Senior Scm/DevOps Engineers (Calabasas, CA) Be part of team responsible for development &amp; support our continuous integration/ deployment infrastructure which consists of automated software version management, software build,… https://t.co/suMbDEckuM https://t.co/RfcgzhVL7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator approves SpaceX plan for broadband satellite services: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The top U.S. telecommunications regulator on Thursday gave formal approval to a plan by Elon Musk's SpaceX to build a global broadband network using satellites. https://t.co/iWsje50r7q https://t.co/hYBN5je378]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: Position Summary Analyzes data and conducts research to assist with ERIE projects or initiatives. Develops and communicates change management plans in support of project management staff. Assists project managers with related project… https://t.co/UL5ZHzD5TG https://t.co/0M7d3UNkqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scientist: PROJECT SCIENTIST sought by University of California, Irvine in Irvine, CA. Conduct research on human-computer interaction applied to the “Internet of Things” including electronic devices and software applications for advancements in… https://t.co/eeHxBMewx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Senior Software Engineer: Position Summary Translates and develops requirements into workable software solutions. Maintains and develops programs for use in business and IT automation. Incorporates various accepted methodologies to… https://t.co/oDmnU0JNMn https://t.co/JY08eVdShu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Software Engineer – CUDA Driver: Senior System Software Engineer – CUDA Driver NVIDIA’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More… https://t.co/EE56KOq4cq https://t.co/fw5oTeketg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: How You Will Impact the Success of Workiva: * Write cutting edge code * Work on any part of the stack – from very rich, highly complex HTML5 applications to hugely scalable distributed systems * Deploy quickly to production *… https://t.co/9vHmKe0CBf https://t.co/JvO2w3wVAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Open Architecture Software Developer: Returning Candidate? Log back in to the Career Portal and click on ‘Job Browsing/History’ and find the job you’re looking for. 2018-025-EGR: Senior Open Architecture Software Developer Directorate Engineering… https://t.co/HIwTzOeTF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer: JOB TITLE: Senior iOS Developer LOCATION: Greenbelt, MD; Ft. Meade, MD CLEARANCE: Active Secret Clearance CITIZENSHIP: US Citizen POSITION OVERVIEW: We are seeking a full time senior iOS Developer with a strong passion for pushing… https://t.co/FuYjcTrMpJ https://t.co/DG920luTqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join our… https://t.co/Cs4QX5fX2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICA with Hybris – Senior Consultant: Are you looking for a career trajectory that few other organizations can offer in SAP? What about access to a high-quality portfolio of businesses and clients with opportunities to work across capabilities,… https://t.co/SOI2Wb4LKt https://t.co/ttj2tV8Gmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach, Lead: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and engineering… https://t.co/2MTZ5Rv7vQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Rails Developer: The Senior Rails Developer is a critical member of the product team, working on all of the products within Kalkomey, and an integral part of moving the business forward. This member would work within a Scrum team of UI/UX… https://t.co/nIZviS3STZ https://t.co/hEuZMDMDSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OS – PROJECT MANAGER – Washington: Responsible for the day-to-day operation and administrative activities to ensure conformance to contract requirements. Develops and implements cost control measures and level of service standards to ensure compliance… https://t.co/mBzdUkCJ3m https://t.co/aQAJ390aTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Salesforce Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/Kz5TtJULix https://t.co/ePrVZAweIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst IT Security Ops: Job Description   Position Summary: Performs monitoring and support for information technology systems and services related to security, network, applications, and infrastructure operations. Trains analysts and may direct… https://t.co/HwdGurkg55 https://t.co/yErMKsI5uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Digital Technology Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/r7wLIlmLW0 https://t.co/fcMNCeJKEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adv Financial Services Digital Tech Manager, Enterprise Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/HsGSoFL9d1 https://t.co/3A8egGDq3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analysis Consultant – Non Technical: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Business… https://t.co/TPkvpSCyF0 https://t.co/MF8cyzl7Uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer (React / Node): REACT / NODE DEVELOPER LOCATION: San Bruno, CA SALARY:up to $120k/yr Full time permanent position VISA SPONSORSHIP AND RELOCATION ASSISTANCE IS AVAILABLE REACT / NODE DEVELOPER SUMMARY The React / Node Developer… https://t.co/iY8UX0NYXm https://t.co/9mwMasfNey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Expert: Software Engineer, Expert ========================= Req #: ******Location: Herndon, VA USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description POSITION SUMMARY:… https://t.co/r9g4AJt3l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Cyber Vulnerability Researcher: Req ID : 429771BR Job Code/Title : E2553:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Job Description : Cyber is critical element of Space’s strategy for growth as these skillsets have become essential to meeting customer and… https://t.co/pnosU4RUzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: JobDescription : THE ROLE: We are in search of a highly motivated Business Analyst who is ready to take their career to the next level in a fast growing company. Do you enjoy leading Technical Projects as well as getting in the… https://t.co/GjF9Syde8H https://t.co/QNUILVMnEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Consultant: Mygo Consulting Job ID – 20189001 Mygo Consulting Inc has openings for the position SAP Consultant with Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering(any),Technology or related and 2 years of experience to analyze, design, code and… https://t.co/nfa1aVQq8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Analyst – Transaction Management (Corporate Real Estate): JOB SUMMARY The purpose of this position is to provide analysis in support to the Program Management Office (PMO). ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES Prepares and presents results of… https://t.co/VqXJE5rUtn https://t.co/82st8s7T0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Design) – Ringmer, East Sussex: CH2M is now Jacobs. Support our East Sussex Highways Joint Venture and have a hand in transforming tomorrow. We have formed a Joint Venture with Costain to deliver the end to end Highways Service for East… https://t.co/HxiHFu0zAg https://t.co/6XETZ6WAit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management:   Job Description – VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management (00018850) Job Description  VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management – (00018850) Description   Improve… https://t.co/Y6N4ACnPcC https://t.co/OCQ9AJvd9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Systems 3:   Job Description – Engineer Systems 3 (18007914) Engineer Systems 3 Requisition ID : 18007914 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/01md3G2qY4 https://t.co/l1jk2Fyy7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Technical Consultant – Cisco Solutions- Central Region IL, TX, MI: Looking for the next step in your career? Enjoy a challenge? Do you have an ambition for innovation? Want to make a difference? If you join our growing global team, you ll be… https://t.co/7ckHX0nD82 https://t.co/GPxYtSc21m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: SOFTWARE Broadcom Corporation has an opening in Irvine, CA for R&amp;D Engineer Software 4 (IRECE) to analyze, design, program, debug, &amp;modify software. recblid ljysjxinnhwdjce2ru7uudvxqfoo60 https://t.co/UEMnsffEIC https://t.co/BPMRF9X7NE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Location: Arlington, Virginia Duration: 5 years. Contract awarded July 2017. Type: Full-Time Clearance: Public Trust. Must be willing to pass company background check. Education: Bachelor’s degree in Computer… https://t.co/dTIBxbLyyW https://t.co/sWNOybeZMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist: Spring River Mental Health &amp; Wellness Inc. IT Specialist Full time position with competitive salary and benefits providing technical support to end users in an outpatient community mental health center. Applicant should have verifiable… https://t.co/srFcxVWTmu https://t.co/mYjRbM8xK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Great opportunity to join a small team as it designs and develops a new enterprise software product for the FBI. The project is a modernization of a robust JEE application, rebuilding it in the cloud with a newer technology stack. (See… https://t.co/DxOBSQajr6 https://t.co/T52WYVaiU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patent Prosecution Attorney: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Patent Prosecution Attorney with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing We are a Patent Litigation and Prosecution firm looking to have attorney… https://t.co/KWRiFtSDVh https://t.co/8ZGt7yDDs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Health Solution Architect: Digital Health Solution Architect (45703) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 45703 Job Description Job Summary Define standards, guidelines,… https://t.co/HdlyMLJwJA https://t.co/S0S0kaMqpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Cyber Systems Engineer 4: TS/SCI/Poly:   Job Description – AWS Cyber Systems Engineer 4: TS/SCI/Poly (18007447) AWS Cyber Systems Engineer 4: TS/SCI/Poly Requisition ID : 18007447 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship Required for… https://t.co/konBSSUyIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/QeOMkIaNOf https://t.co/iX6n16Ewjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Engineer: EchoStar Corporation (NASDAQ: SATS) headquartered in Englewood, CO, with additional locations world-wide, is a premier global provider of satellite solutions and technology services. Together with its major… https://t.co/EnE1pXzNFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: As a Project Manager II, you will manage the cost, quality, and schedule of wireless infrastructure projects for new site builds and for modifications to existing facilities. This involves preparing the scope of work, pricing,… https://t.co/5OvjRHCuuZ https://t.co/fqc26z7Djw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Temple): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/j5kKu1Ngfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Operations: Client Reference Code: 216381 JOB SUMMARY: Serves as a liaison to the business community in order to provide technical solutions to meet user needs. Possesses expertise in the business unit(s) they support, as well as an… https://t.co/JDAXWCWRQb https://t.co/GCiW2m0Crh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Client Reference Code: 203976-1 JOB SUMMARY The incumbent will development software to solve problems and add features that directly impact the consumer experience. The role will create innovative solutions by developing and… https://t.co/kboZppIG7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: ******/Java/J2EE Developer Ref No.: 18-18666 Location: Portland, Oregon Skills : Core java , Spring MVC , Hibernate Below is the detailed JD . Required Skills: – The ability to demonstrate thorough understanding of object oriented design… https://t.co/U2jKhzWJM3 https://t.co/gEqJpRrqyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/RucnFqCUSN https://t.co/AdUkNO5ofL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst : Google LLC, San Francisco, CA 94126 job # below: Business Systems Analyst (Mountain View, CA) Define business intelligence technologies for Google. #1615.32770 Exp Incl: enterprise resource planning… https://t.co/wyAoKAmlGv https://t.co/swBIti7OgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Specialist: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Business Analytics… https://t.co/pSoPo59xPB https://t.co/DmHQ6pAsBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Engineer: JOB SUMMARY Any journeyman license preferred. Electrical and mechanical aptitude strongly preferred. Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings, industrial systems, vehicles,… https://t.co/BkKvRf4FpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Development Engineer: An excellent career and lifestyle opportunity for the correct individual exists to work on state-of-the-art, and break-through research and development of various emerging technologies having both near-term and future… https://t.co/mY4RcXEKaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process/Control Systems Analyst: Process/Control Systems Analyst Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Please read our Recruitment Privacy Policy and related Legal Notice Accept – Careers Home – Why… https://t.co/XaQdUy2pXP https://t.co/UM0k9hmsWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – Careers Skip to content Kronos Canada (fr-CA) United States (en-US) – Search jobs – Login Search jobs / Job detail Careers Transcend the day-to-day work experience. Work inspired. Software Engineer Location: Lowell… https://t.co/TeFIhnmpxK https://t.co/p27DV39Ymh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health and Benefits Systems Analyst – Voluntary Benefit Enrollment Solutions: Job Description Aon is looking for a Health and Benefits System Analyst – Voluntary Benefits Enrollment Solutions As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower… https://t.co/hOVGI7RjSL https://t.co/2BPwh2mTfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back end (Architect) Lead: Come join and exciting and talented team. This is a full stack team with challenges from React apps to building ETL pipelines. If you want to bring your skill set to bear across scalable distributed systems, commerce,… https://t.co/9fscsiWuaV https://t.co/qfSh0qwNtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Eng’g: Human Factor Engr (Irvine, CA) Eyefinity, Inc.: Dvlp user intrfc desns for web, tablet, mobile, &amp; desktop user apps; lead/improve process of defin’g user intrfce app desn &amp; behavior. EOE recblid sf12gi4n5cp1kw2r5qm6byoeenyh3z https://t.co/3coHsEhZwI https://t.co/M0MyY1pP9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: SOFTWARE ARCHITECT. Netsmart Technologies, Inc. Raleigh, NC. Design, develop &amp; implement Netsmart Homecare &amp; other post-acute SW solutions. Work M-F 8a-5p, on call &amp; overtime as needed. Reqs at least Bach degree in Comp IS/ Comp Apps/… https://t.co/d3DVJoBQKn https://t.co/nMKUHmBWSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst : Google LLC, San Francisco, CA 94126 job # below: Business Systems Analyst (Mountain View, CA) Define business intelligence technologies for Google. #1615.32770 Exp Incl: enterprise resource planning… https://t.co/H8XkLhwrqk https://t.co/m3mTfMBEaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Analyst: Mygo Consulting Job ID – 20189002 Mygo Consulting Inc has openings for the position SAP Analyst with Master’s degree in Computer Science/Information Systems, Engineering (any),Technology or related to involve in various deployment activities… https://t.co/5H52z08kVn https://t.co/GDK3P8nbsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist I: For well over a century, Fish &amp; Richardson has been winning cases worth billions in controversy – often by making new law – for the world’s most innovative and influential technology leaders. Join Fish’s downtown Minneapolis team in our… https://t.co/gT6ElVvS4J https://t.co/jOlld97SaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Integration and Test Engineer: 109236BR Principal Integration and Test Engineer CO – Aurora 109236BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers… https://t.co/qnqfXuLNsi https://t.co/byuBtmr96p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: The Software Engineer will code high-volume software, suggest, collect, and synthesize requirements and create effective feature roadmap. This individual will create scalable software that enable a wide range of machine learning,… https://t.co/y0HQ2sUEUR https://t.co/Ch6YWlQL64]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>