<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ORachaelO Unusual how? I recall there was more officially-tolerated violence than in Canadian schools of the same era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Yorkshire_Hero: Will someone please return the vicar's bicycle http://t.co/3vyZKHbuS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The Beatles in 1957. George Harrison is 14, John Lennon is 16, and Paul McCartney is 15. http://t.co/vwUosbfx6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Dammit! It's like they're making you wait on purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulieFalatko: Remember that kids still like bedtime books that are actual stories and not just pocket watches swaying in their faces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: Midnight in Paris
(2011, Woody Allen) http://t.co/d1OCqcD5xP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ORachaelO Surprisingly common. I know a bunch of actors who get really offended when someone thinks anyone can show a menu and serve food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heretical statement that happens to be true: "The Lord of the Rings" -- books and movies -- is really boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSMUGCAT: My cat is smug because his many admirers love to be next to him, in the hope his majestic aura will rub off on them. http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WstonesOxfordSt: BOOK FACT: If you rip out a book page, hold it up to the light and look carefully, you'll see that you're a monster. S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Astronaut Neil Armstrong floats in his space suit in a pool of water, 1967. http://t.co/2MIPwoLfbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hessiebell And all the cats! Alas, they usually selfishly insist on keeping their heat to themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_youhadonejob Actually, it doesn't look as if Heather will be having a job any time soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hessiebell Yay you! If you need any help memorizing your lines, let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @300PoundSamoan: http://t.co/HhVjCb6utZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Slate: Someone remade the Hannibal title sequence in the style of Friends: http://t.co/B4uyK0hugK http://t.co/gyfIb8pru4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freyburg: Apple eyes move into original video programming, report says... (Interesting but not unexpected...) http://t.co/HPkXAwyI8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He later found a more efficient way achieve that look. https://t.co/avfnCGrUXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Albert Einstein, sunbathing, 1932. http://t.co/BBKi0Os7qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: @HistoryInPics Margaret Hamilton with the computer code that guided the Apollo 11 lander to the moon. http://t.co/EfioqE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take heart, micro-budget movie-makers! http://t.co/QWtfsFC9AU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TroyStoryToo: There's a nice little write-up about me and The Duck Says in the September issue of @MondayMag (page 22). 
http://t.co/Xz…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: When I write, I feel like an armless, legless man with a crayon in his mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trains are cool! https://t.co/4vTd5D5gQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gregpak: Thank you, comics readers. Thank you for buying comics in any form. And a very special thank you for loving and buying physica…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanier Certainly my genitals are very near to my heart! -- but then again, I don't have an abdomen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uvic: It's your turn to experience the mystery, power, and beauty of the deep sea: http://t.co/NcmETBH459 http://t.co/SjtPbKvBhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pourmecoffee: Yay, you found a random stranger who said something terrible on social media int the wake of a tragedy! http://t.co/zz3h6…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee Ha! Check it out: https://t.co/w18jYHa7WV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whew! "Scientists Confident Artificially Intelligent Machines Can Be Programmed To Be Lenient Slave Masters": http://t.co/UsisGqXJ6i.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Reading plays is crazy hard. Watching plays is often dull. But you have to do both, or your playwright self is doomed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Well ... were you about to say something libellous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pickover: The joy of logic. These 2 books, in theory, contain the sum total of all human knowledge http://t.co/CW5seS3QbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DiscretObscur: #JohnCarpenter (@TheHorrorMaster) on the set of #TheyLive http://t.co/Xhap7IVngu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Superman 1950 "Keep your school all American" by Wayne Boring. http://t.co/JtVjuEboBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson (I recognize the show you're referencing. Other episodes are quite good too.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson She was okay until he asked her to don the false snout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now 50 hours since @Microsoft technical support said they'd call me back "soon".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because people told him him to "dance like nobody's watching" so he did but he felt like a total dick. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximum_z I'm with you on that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximum_z On the plus side, movie-literate people will get it. On the minus side, conventional wisdom is that no one will make a western.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dick_nixon: .@paulpakler Many actors are dumb. It helps to have intelligence to act but you don't need it. We all know that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 hours since @Microsoft tech support said they'd call me back "soon".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell Crowe is not a good enough actor to be that big a douche-face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee That is one of the most distinctive things about you! (Your loud laugh, not your labrynthitis. Though I guess that too, now.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MysteryActress: O captain! my captain! http://t.co/ZsMMLJ3FDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @slatest: Romantic-comedy behavior gets real-life man arrested: http://t.co/6uaR3bRjKH http://t.co/5s9rS6Cy1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we know where "Little Stevie" Harper, Niggle Right, et al got their line of defence:  https://t.co/c3xJLv0Xya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now five hours since @Microsoft tech support said they would call me back "soon". I want Windows 7 updates without installing Windows 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: when Lee Van Cleef
comes to town http://t.co/BiDZfXV4vW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ... 40 minutes on the phone with @Microsoft technical support, only to be told by the representative that he cannot help me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does @Microsoft inform me that Windows 7 requires critical updates, and then not let me download them until I upgrade to Windows 10?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far, online with @Microsoft customer service for 20 minutes waiting for Windows Update to check for updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 minutes on hold waiting for @Microsoft technical support. The representative is unable to help but wants lots of my personal information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On hold with @Microsoft for 20 minutes so far, trying to find out how to install Windows 7 updates without installing Windows 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sage50CDN Oh dear. Do you really think that article is helpful ti end-users? In any case, it does not offer a solution to my case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReneeStephen: So... like... what if, say... I DIDN'T want to upgrade to Windows 10...? (I am so mad about this forced update bullshit I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there are critical updates to Windows 7. @Microsoft won't let me install them unless I first upgrade to Windows 10. Fuck you, @Microsoft!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Don't be reckless with other people's hearts, and don't put up with people that are reckless with yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon's promised huge savings on Criterion Collection movies are so huge they're only slightly more expensive than buying from Criterion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sage50CDN Indeed it shouldn't do that! There is no error message; it simply says "Starting Sage 50" and then doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sage50CDN For starters, why does Sage 50 simply not open about 40 percent of the time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brenopolis: Are Sea Monkeys in the #marveluniverse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, @Sage50cdn! Your application lets me down again and again! Random crashes, sometimes won't start at all. What a piece of ... crud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he went outside but some bigger, cruel cats told him "you ooze woe and your face is too round". http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dam3ian: "Little Stevie" Harper is rightt! Smoke too many marijuanas, and look what could happen to you: http://t.co/r73auOYYwg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pourmecoffee: Explains a lot. 

"Cannabis discovered in 400-year-old pipes found in William Shakespeare's garden" http://t.co/ezLx7KLbkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeanwhileinCana: I'm going to put this sign over every mirror I see. http://t.co/BmsaozRdTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCNewsWire: You’re less happy when you have a child, study says  http://t.co/8jf8Ni9d5p #parenting #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ditzkoff: In Sunday’s NY Times, I write about how “Key &amp; Peele” is/was the sketch comedy series of this American moment.  http://t.co/j…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCFerrys: On busy sailings, please park within the vehicle in front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnnapurnaPics: San Dimas High School football rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Frank Sinatra, arrested in New Jersey for "carrying on with a married woman", 1938. http://t.co/xQvHWpirHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeanwhileinCana: http://t.co/07fQ8zUhaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMDeMatteis: Help, Hide Your Love Away, Ticket to Ride, Yesterday, Just Seen a Face. You could argue that there are stronger songs on H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMDeMatteis: Fifty years ago today.  And it's only improved with time.  https://t.co/KGYyvHOhec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: Rainer Werner Fassbinder and Werner Herzog, Room 666 http://t.co/3D87XcJEbo http://t.co/NaXAtAOSs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: Sydney Pollack directs Dustin Hoffman on the set of TOOTSIE. http://t.co/A6D0azfCLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: "To be is to do"-Socrates   "To do is to be"-Sartre  "Do Be Do Be Do"-Sinatra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Now let's hear you say, "Showtime, Synergy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe in front of Niagara Falls, 1953. http://t.co/UYmG4Ij93c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StatsBritain: 89% of British Jedi use the force mainly to tell when their tea is ready to drink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Times Square, 1953. Photograph by Samuel Gottscho. http://t.co/3e4HovletZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee I think "being a fan of all things nerdy" is committing an act of nerdery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshRimer: A true breakdown of the week http://t.co/GSV0C9wJbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit! Scripts from "http://t.co/3PWw8xx8qe" keep crashing and freezing my browser! I hate "Google Plus" and never use it. Why run scripts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there an Indian porn star named Amandeep Insadme? If not I'm going to trademark the name, in case I decide to become an Indian porn star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The Beatles in their final concert on the roof of Apple Records, 1969. http://t.co/7G4M92izLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMDeMatteis: It's Miguel de Cervantes' birthday:  tilt at a windmill today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he tries to be strong but each time a library closes a salty tear rolls softly down his cheek. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he has made a tactless remark to my other cat, which has resulted in an atmosphere of tension. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mccrabb_will: On ERASERHEAD Catherine Coulson 
Created Henry's Hairstyle 
Loaded Film
Pulled Focus
Boom Op
&amp;
Cooked All Meals. http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: Forty seconds I was away for. FORTY SECONDS. http://t.co/v304j1IRrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: The function of the artist is to make people like life better than they have before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: A Woman Is a Woman
(1961, Jean-Luc Godard) http://t.co/AbmlMGOLkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GoIntoTheStory: Scott Adam: “Creativity is allowing yourself to make mistakes. Art is knowing which ones to keep."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched "Margaret Cho: Assassin". Disappointing. I used to really like her. Of course, she used to be funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brenopolis 668 is the Neighbour of the The Beast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marlon Brando in A Streetcar Named Desire, 1951. http://t.co/yawMHP50lu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: ‘Yippee ki yah, motherfucker.’ (Photos by Robert Isenberg &amp; Virgil Mirano). For more: http://t.co/pYwaamsdcL http://t.…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>