<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/jXDrfSdlW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/HFuNbH2zdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/SE0BjItGof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/DwJNfItcsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/GkmrpDQhjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/uZrn6880Oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/IGYjl39AdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/1OCKpfBhXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/D9hNnl5Q3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/2DMCpQoDIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/SvAcbL4Uq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/jttYpW1yrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/7t9UlaISSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/T6F8Mmb53d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/0Fnk6ypBdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/XN66bRC1T2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/MgYHNMMrfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/vRAZ4Nc9Ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/Tqt6rj6SuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/5tySyYwxyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/gqifAdMYDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/eeB0Fq6JZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/gi3ZwAy9bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/KNsJrbEKug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/JVHvcKhyCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Facebook-Top Tips for Business Success  http://t.co/mzCRa52X29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/j9PoWKzu1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/5adaZkWTkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/hTasqasrw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/IGYjl39AdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/jVIAFvoNiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/MZgVJxp0Ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/28DhHNTcvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/j42fy3mwsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theory is a hunch with a college education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/jlpypYJwvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/IDpC6Sq6qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/vdjK8qXGTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/6rAYHb4I1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/qjkR3LF5Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/iA042sE0cu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/MD5VKxIdA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/v0yE2hVgwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/ZEV9RYfnCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/pp4UUHunL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/aSegZGGPhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>