<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mlevel "The price of hating other human beings is loving oneself less." - Eldridge Cleaver, died 11y ago today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) "... in our society can be traced back to this negative emotional climate in families."  John Gottman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) "The real cradle that holds the baby is the emotional climate between new parents. Many significant social problems [like violence]..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I liken an affair to shattering a Waterford crystal vase. U can glue it back together, but it will never be the same again." - John Gottman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Contempt is the sulfuric acid of love." - John Gottman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be committed to the process, rather than the outcome." - John Amodeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" A holy longing moves us toward each other. There is no greater delight than 2 hearts resonating together in love & openness." John Amodeao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SpiritQuoter "We can live without religion and meditation, but we cannot survive without human affection." - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Touch the earth, love the earth, honour the earth, her plains, valleys, hills, seas; rest your spirit in her solitary places" -Henry Beston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must be our own before we can be another's." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be Impeccable With Your Word. Speak with integrity....Use the power of your word in the direction of truth and love." - Don Miguel Ruiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things ppl in love do 2 each other thy remember & if thy stay 2gether it's not bcause thy 4get it's bcause thy 4give" frm Indecent Proposal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hisholiness "I have found that the greatest degree of inner tranquility comes from the development of love and compassion."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most precious possession that ever comes to a man in this world is a womans heart." - Josiah G. Holland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The meeting of two personalities is like the contact of 2 chemical substances: if there is any reaction, both are transformed." - Carl Jung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Difficult times always create opportunities for you to experience more love in your life." - Barbara de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no remedy for love but to love more." -Henry David Thoreau, author, poet, naturalist, tax resister, philosopher, transcendentalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes "By all means marry; if you get a good wife, you'll be happy. If you get a bad one, you'll become a philosopher." - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Him that I love, I wish to be free -- even from me." - Anne Morrow Lindbergh, pioneering aviator, author, and wife of Charles Lindbergh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnodeaJudith Doing work u love means bringing love into every aspect of your work. That's loving what u do. http://www.sacredcenters.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If there is no joy in love, it is not true love." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pretty much everyone you know just wants you to love them. Good thing it's free, huh? -The Universe" (Mike Dooley, Notes from the Universe)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Existential love is possible only for the mature, authentic individual. This is the 1st theme of existential love." - Peter Koestenbaum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can choose love; you do not have to." - Peter Koestenbaum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes "Love is never wrong." - Melissa Etheridge, 48 today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I take my whole, passionate, spiritual and physical love to the woman who in return loves me, that is how I serve God."- D.H. Lawrence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2of2 "...It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." - Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1of2 "Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness & errors & betrayals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The one thing we can never get enough of is love. And the one thing we can never give enough of is love." - Henry Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2of2 "... either, a human being, without feeling fear, restraint, or obligation." - Simone de Beauvoir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1of2 "In itself, homosexuality is as limiting as heterosexuality: the ideal should be to be capable of loving a woman or a man; ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It always seemed to me a bit pointless to disapprove of homosexuality. It's like disapproving of rain." Francis Maude, British Parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the only gold." - Alfred Lord Tennyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate lesson all of us have 2 learn is unconditional luv, which includes not only others but ourselves as well -Elisabeth Kübler-Ross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Eventually you will come to understand that love heals everything, and love is all there is." - Gary Zukav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) ..."By listening with calm and understanding, we can ease the suffering of another person." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) "If we love someone, we should train in being able to listen....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Immature love says: 'I love you because I need you.' 
Mature love says: 'I need you because I love you'" - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A friend is always good to have, but a lover's kiss is better than angels raining down on me." - Dave Matthews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most precious gift we cn offer others is R presence. When mindfulness embraces those we luv they will bloom lk flowers" Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He loves his country best who strives to make it best." - Robert G. Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Relationship is an art. The dream that two people create is more difficult to master than one." - Don Miguel Ruiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My experience is that the teachers we need most are the people we’re living with right now." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A dream you dream alone is only a dream. A dream you dream together is reality." - John Lennon; musician, songwriter, peace activist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What else is love but understanding & rejoicing in the fact that another person lives,acts,& experiences otherwise than we do?" Nietzsche]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You never lose by loving. You always lose by holding back." - Barbara de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love and pregnancy and riding on a camel cannot be hid." - Arabic Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is like a violin. The music may stop now and then, but the strings remain forever." - June Masters Bacher (thanks @M_Gotti781)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love you now; and I love you forever. There's no goodbyes - there's only love... only love." - from film The Perfect Storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To give pleasure to a single heart by a single act is better than a thousand heads bowing in prayer." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "Love isn't blind; it's only love that sees!"
-Sarah Orne Jewett, died 100y ago today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You can grow without destroying the things that you love.” - Ed McMahon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBetterSexDoc "Do not seek perfection in a changing world; instead, perfect your love." - Master Sengstan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is an endless mystery, for it has nothing else to explain it." - Rabindranath Tagore; poet, artist, playwright, novelist, composer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’re all looking for love, in our confusion, until we find our way back to the realization that love is what we already are" Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love and win is the best thing. To love and lose, the next best." -  William MacNeile Dixon; poet, historian, scholar; 1866 - 1946]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is natural to love & it is natural for love to be spiritual 1st and physical 2nd. ...9th theme of existential love." - Peter Koestenbaum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The relationship you have with yourself is reflected in your relationships with others." - Don Miguel Ruiz, The Mastery of Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where love rules, there is no will 2 power; & where power predominates, there love is lacking. The 1 is the shadow of the other." Carl Jung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing outside you can ever give you what you’re looking for." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even stones have a love, a love that seeks the ground." - Meister Eckhart
von Hochheim, a German theologian, philosopher and mystic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha "The source of all happiness lies in thinking of others." ~Shantideva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Spiritual relationship is far more precious than physical. Physical relationship divorced from spiritual is body without soul." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Power up imagination's collaboration with possibility and make love with the perpetual reciprocity of the infinite." @AnodeaJudith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Twitter, lk birdsong, takes us up into air, element of the heart chakra. May we tweet the song that awakens the global heart" @AnodeaJudith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To be able to give happiness and joy, you must practice deep looking directed toward the person you love." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." - Friedrich Nietzsche]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In love the paradox occurs that two beings become one and yet remain two." - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is nothing but a dream & if we R artists then we can create our life w/ Love & our dream becomes a masterpiece of art" Don Miguel Ruiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is always some madness in love. But there is also always some reason in madness." - Friedrich Nietzsche]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the only sane and satisfactory answer to the problem of human existence." - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "To be angry is to let others' mistakes punish yourself. To forgive others is to be good to yourself." ~Cheng Yen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Morality is the basis of things and truth is the substance of all morality." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’ve been looking outside us for our own peace. We’ve been looking in the wrong direction." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "All the elements for your happiness are already here. There's no need to run, strive, search or struggle. Just be." ~Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yenni27 yup! & if u substitute place for person: happy with self before one can be happy w/ another :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He that is discontented in one place will seldom be happy in another." -  Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Holding on to anger is like grasping a hot coal with the intent of throwing it at someone else; you are the one who gets burned." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the only reality & it is not a mere sentiment. It is the ultimate truth that lies at the heart of creation." - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: The power of love came into me, and I became fierce like a lion, then tender like the evening star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Until you can see everything in the world as your friend, your work is not done." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2of2 "Though the sword hidden among his pinions may wound you." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1of2 "When love beckons to you, follow him, Though his ways are hard and steep. And when his wings enfold you yield to him..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @todayquotes: "If love means never having to say you're sorry, then marriage means always having to say everything twice."-Estelle Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: This moment this love comes to rest in me, many beings in one being. In one wheat-grain a thousand sheaf stacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Romance is the fuel that keeps love burning hot." - Rusty Silvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love, in the context of Buddhism, is above all to be there." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True friendship can afford true knowledge. It does not depend on darkness and ignorance." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llunabelle "I love quotations because it is a joy to find thoughts one might have, beautifully expressed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llunabelle "The wisdom of the wise, and the experience of ages, may be preserved by quotations." - Isaac D'Israeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is with our passions as it is with fire and water, they are good servants, but bad masters" -  Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just entered @TinyBuddha's pre-launch contest! Find helpful words of wisdom at http://bit.ly/tinybuddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Beware that you do not lose the substance by grasping at the shadow." - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are, each of us angels with only one wing; and we can only fly by embracing one another." - Luciano de Crescenzo, writer & engineer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The heart is forever inexperienced." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Love is the master key that opens the gates of happiness.” - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love, love will be my strongest weapon. I do believe that I am not alone." - R.E.M. lyrics: "Final Straw"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your work is to discover your world and then with all your heart give yourself to it. " - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The demand to be loved is the greatest of all arrogant presumptions." - Friedrich Nietzsche]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>