<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Infection Control Specialist: Job ID: 250006 Infection Control Specialist Saginaw, Michigan Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Infection Control Specialist City, State:  Saginaw,MI Location:  St Mary’s of Michigan-MedCtr Department:  … https://t.co/DzXWIRiLkK https://t.co/LZe1CFh7yO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Software Developer: Are you ready to be part of a leading global engineering design house specializing in the design and development of embedded software, electronics, and electro-mechanics? What we’re looking for · Highly motivated software… https://t.co/PdHfeE9nkR https://t.co/Akck7E1zeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Tester: JOB TITLE: QA Tester LOCATION: Alexandria, VA CLEARANCE: Active Secret Clearance CITIZENSHIP: US Citizen Swingtech Consulting is currently supporting K-12 education for the military families within &amp; outside United States on a contract that is… https://t.co/BvQlHuEkXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst: Seattle, WA Full-time $70k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Network Analyst with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – HUGE Room for Growth – Great Work/Life Balance/Autonomy – Competitive Pay What You Will Be Doing… https://t.co/vYgmDdf5ZM https://t.co/zI02hKuWYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Westworld' Recap, Season 2 Episode 3: Robot, Human, and Everything in Between: The rebellion engulfing the show's theme parks is spreading—and leading to some existential questions about what is real. https://t.co/eZtOMkVvMk https://t.co/Uf0LkdyvfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Photos of the Week: A Tale of Two Galaxies: The Large Magellanic Cloud is actually rather small, and NGC 2655 is a blobby "lenticular" shape. https://t.co/uBAWM2tXYW https://t.co/jYy5vJf7ho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Info Security Analyst: Req ID 97866BR Business Title Technical Info Security Analyst Group MCIS Location USA CALIFORNIA San Francisco Clearance Level Needed Public Trust Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of… https://t.co/ZZV9OTJyv4 https://t.co/ylfqa3iTOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Revenue Lead Analyst: Job ID: 249205 Net Revenue Lead Analyst Glendale, Wisconsin Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Net Revenue Lead Analyst City, State:  Glendale, WI Location:  AW Glendale Office Department:   Reimbursement Additional… https://t.co/vld9YZWxqJ https://t.co/cYsz3KdDgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Amazon Device Deals: 20-30% Sale on Echos, Kindles, Fires (May 2018): Save up to 30 percent off almost all Fire tablets, Fire TVs, Cloud Cams, and Echo speakers. https://t.co/H7cQS1HV4d https://t.co/GTb9ThinU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Full Stack Cloud Engieer: Job Description Job ID: R45868 Benjamin Franklin (18052), United States of America, Wilmington, Delaware At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/mS8IULTcSY https://t.co/ag4f8pWwTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Keep Hackers Out of Your Facebook and Twitter Accounts: Scammers, pranksters, and bad actors all want to break into whatever social media accounts they can. Here's how to keep yours safe. https://t.co/baQJnZ10Rd https://t.co/cFD19WPxv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Non Technical: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Business Analyst (Non… https://t.co/03xSnPJwno https://t.co/HxAgyBR0Je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Charts Its Own Path on Artificial Intelligence: Google and Facebook are building custom chips for AI. Microsoft is using Intel chips that can be reprogrammed for different uses. https://t.co/LTWNWm8Gu4 https://t.co/TWYNuxyGik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/PU3fOFEcWv https://t.co/spCopPNa8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer: Hardware Engineer Job – Why Work For Us – Get to Know PACCAR – A Great Place to Work – Equal Opportunity Employer – Job Opportunities – Engineering Jobs – Finance &amp; Accounting Jobs – Human Resources &amp; Admin Jobs – Information… https://t.co/GDkkjTma3W https://t.co/nUO9d8AShG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: SUNDIAL SOFTWARE IS CURRENTLY RECRUITING FOR A DATA ANALYST FOR A ONE YEAR CONTRACT. EBUSINESS ANALYST:DATA ANALYST DESCRIPTION Job Description: Summary We are looking for a Data Analyst to turn data into information, information into… https://t.co/rwTjlSiPYe https://t.co/fWf5RoQFNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo's Self-Driving Car Crash Revives Hard Questions: Whether or not the autonomous Pacifica minivan was at fault, it's bad news for a young industry trying to prove it can makes roads safer for everyone. https://t.co/urrLCuiXbU https://t.co/pOgYYKyQoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[District Manager: At Extra Space Storage, if it matters to you, it matters to us!It is a really exciting time to be at Extra Space Storage! We got our start in 1977. Today we are a New York Stock Exchange-traded company leading the self-storage industry… https://t.co/RNqy5NCp9Y https://t.co/9ovEgPENMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: You may not have heard of irth Solutions before, but its likely that your home and safety has been protected with its industry-leading services. Every oil &amp; gas company and utility has distributed facilities and workers. Our… https://t.co/OURUBrefjR https://t.co/sBV0L6bw0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer: Description: Position is supporting Active Directory Design/Build for a multi-discipline engineering team for our DTRA program in Fort Belvoir, Virginia.   Serves as the Lead Active Directory Architect for a 4000+ user active… https://t.co/TyZEwE4AKz https://t.co/uH1XkyFNdT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist Ref No.: 18-16673 Location: McLean, Virginia Title: Data Scientist Location: McLean, VA Duration: Full Time Job Description:- MUST HAVE SKILLS – Expert quantitative skills and solid grasp of key concepts in probability,… https://t.co/C7vOhZhxFZ https://t.co/S5JKdZGWHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Fight Climate Change: Figure Out Who's to Blame, and Sue Them: It's only possible with the new science of extreme weather attribution. https://t.co/mop6EyhMwY https://t.co/reXhPGjEyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: DESCRIPTION: Employer has a great opportunity for a Web Developer in San Antonio, TX. Position requires a current TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. The candidate will beusing standard scripting languages, must be able to… https://t.co/7hYgqrQsEZ https://t.co/lUdCEAWUri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Golden Age of Subtweeting: What was once a way to dodge Twitter's notification settings has turned trolling into a refined linguistic art. https://t.co/c0hg8nw7Qq https://t.co/DkgEwa5vLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Elon Musk Threatens to Become a Liability: After the CEO attacked analysts for asking hard questions about Tesla's finances, investors might be wary of Musk's role in the company's future. https://t.co/Hmv9oydARA https://t.co/RA6UPp4qMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Intelligence Analyst Manager: Description:Leidos Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center has an immediate opening for an experienced, and motivated Cyber Intelligence Analyst Manager.   Reporting to the Director of the Cybersecurity… https://t.co/QeTp5nPI17 https://t.co/uBYoMuCHQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Favorite Autopilot Safety Statistic Doesn't Hold Up: Elon Musk's automaker says the semi-autonomous feature cuts crashes by 40 percent, but a closer look at the math reveals some major caveats. https://t.co/g6Ggh7uZQM https://t.co/O4171H8Uy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JRSS Operational Engineering Manager: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a JRSS Operational Engineering Manager. Our customer is the Defense… https://t.co/TwKSEC3UdA https://t.co/04cSvZTH3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer – Project Manager: Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment… https://t.co/R4WoAyfm3M https://t.co/xbedeWwzul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Engineer I: 107717BR Sr Systems Engineer I MA – Marlborough 107717BR Senior Systems Engineer I/II The Whole Life Engineering Directorate (WLED) is made up of several disciplines whose main objective is to influence hardware and systems early… https://t.co/E9ZzTzhyy9 https://t.co/mdvQadndlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering UNIX/Linux Technician (Consultant): Engineering UNIX/Linux Technician (Consultant) Orangeburg Posted Feb 2, 2018 – Requisition No. 64957 An exciting opportunity exists for a UNIX/Linux technician within a world-class Operations center. You… https://t.co/mXqIa6UUnq https://t.co/BJaP54pCtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Is NASA's InSight Mars Mission Launching from California?: This month, NASA will fire its first interplanetary mission from Vandenberg Air Force Base north of Los Angeles. Why the snub for Cape Canaveral in Florida? https://t.co/IfwUnrkHur https://t.co/YSD7uWZz9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer – What We Do Featured Using React Native to Build Two Native Apps &amp; Increase Paid B2B Subscriptions for Itemize Customer Story – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work – Financial… https://t.co/bB56GeHwDR https://t.co/QrAMWiL8W5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI Tech Ambulatory Surgery Center Experienced: Facility: University of Colo Hospital Department: Lone Tree Amb Surgery Center Schedule: Part-time Shift: 1st Shift – Days Scheduled Days &amp; Hours: varies Requisition number: 70920 Summary – Endoscopy… https://t.co/tlzR2NT4vp https://t.co/ZF9x0190fI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/tDYanMHEOt https://t.co/kctj8TvrQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Information Technology &amp; Chief Information Officer: Exciting Senior Leadership Opportunity Nathan Littauer Hospital and Nursing Home is currently recruiting for a VP of IT/CIO for our growing healthcare organization.  Nathan Littauer… https://t.co/HbBTCuHimj https://t.co/IGVdEvJ2tU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Business Intelligence: Director of Business Intelligence (BI), Western Governors University, Salt Lake City, UT. Manage BI Developers and BI Analysts and oversee the improvement of BI capabilities as the senior technical expert. Lead agile… https://t.co/UjOjmOdwIA https://t.co/4CMInyzfPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Wars Is Becoming a Religion, and May 4 Is Its Spring Festival: May the Fourth may be a cheap pun, but it's also got all the makings of a real religious holiday. https://t.co/1RoxAPjl0O https://t.co/WX8wH7BEAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEERS: Sr. Software Engineers, Fort Worth, Texas: Develop s/w reqs specs, functional specs, &amp; s/w design docs. Develop, design, test, implement &amp; support modular s/w components, memory mgmt techniques, standard calling conventions, low… https://t.co/yhMyIhYvVu https://t.co/1Xhad0sqNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per Diem IT Assistant: $15 – $25 per hour based on education and experience. Position is with a mid-size labor union in Albany NY. Duties include: desktop publishing, web editing, user support, troubleshooting, Windows desktop support, network support,… https://t.co/CJrZgs6JaJ https://t.co/wHwdlM5ZPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biology Will Be the Next Great Computing Platform: New companies are popping up to become the Amazons, Apples, and Intels of genome engineering. https://t.co/jkET7hjtyI https://t.co/Wag8JC4yVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Resources and Data Systems Technician and Fiscal Service Technician: Human Resources and Data Systems Technician Salary Range – $23.12 – $30.16 hourly (Depends on experience) Fiscal Service Technician (Assistant to the CBO) Salary Range – $29.61 –… https://t.co/JYvuO6NLC7 https://t.co/fVFz80R7oA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-Sales Engineer – SF Bay Area: Why Silver Peak?: Silver Peak is currently at the forefront one of the most exciting and disruptive trends in the history of the networking industry – the software-defined wide area network, or SD-WAN. Enterprises and… https://t.co/qyuYXu5CeV https://t.co/Jo1xuI1RiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead of TAM Information Security: TECH LEAD OF TAM INFORMATION SECURITY RESPONSIBILITIES * Protect and secure company resources in the cloud, virtual and physical infrastructures. * Coordinate with Information Security team to ensure solution… https://t.co/MAn8KmWps1 https://t.co/gFMpGbYMdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to Prune Trees More Easily? Use Physics: A blade will slice into a limb at some particular minimum pressure—but there are different ways to reach that value. https://t.co/kjCWWprj9a https://t.co/u3w8hUmnwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Operations Manager: Grade Level: 12 Position &amp; FLSA Status: Full-Time Exempt Date of Latest Revision: March 2018 Position Summary: To cultivate and maintain positive strategic relationships with City leadership and end-user… https://t.co/J9P0KeujPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA’s InSight Lander Will Probe Mars, Measure Its Quakes: Brace yourself, Mars. NASA's sending a 5-meter probe to take your temperature. https://t.co/XWiARzDfyF https://t.co/aXYbCbD9Yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOC System Administrator: Systems Engineering Solutions (SES) Corporation is a service disabled veteran owned small business with over 15 years of past performance. If you would like to learn more, we would encourage you to check out our past performance… https://t.co/CZ44CgAVf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Designer – UI/UX Design: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Product Designer with strong web &amp; mobile UI/UX experience, we're looking for you! Our mobile-first platform is disrupting the multi-billion dollar… https://t.co/tfLLoI0sLp https://t.co/t2EItigFyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Mueller Likely Knows How the Trump Russia Investigation Ends: Nearly a year since his appointment as special counsel, Robert Mueller has accelerated the pace of his investigation. https://t.co/qonO5bIxZq https://t.co/Fcw5D0tIYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Website Developer: Lead Website Developer Ref No.:18-00146 Category: ************* Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type:Contingent Experience Level: 11 Years Start Date: 04/09/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work… https://t.co/FnVpsLioNF https://t.co/TeZuaduZNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Ref No.: 18-00807 Location: Highlands Ranch, Colorado Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 04/23/2018 to 04/23/2019 Must have skills: 7+ years of network engineering experience in large data center… https://t.co/TGUMqCOpOH https://t.co/fSUtDgCdzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Role/Responsibilities Role/Responsibilities: Moodys SFG Technology team seeks a Software Engineer, with a strong focus on development of analytic tools and databases, to work on cutting edge projects related to… https://t.co/WIVOU9ZZr3 https://t.co/8ogIsO15vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Job Description – Network Engineer Job ID2018-26676 Area of InterestInformation Technology Location NameHospital Main Campus FTE/Hours per pay period1.0 FTE (80 hours per bi-weekly pay periods) Work StatusRegular… https://t.co/5mewZHefOV https://t.co/urYouip9fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MoviePass Unlimited Plan Is Back: Two weeks after MoviePass' unlimited plan disappeared, the service is reviving it—and explaining some of its controversial practices. https://t.co/ymkq48Mwpo https://t.co/E3O0s1DIFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project ManagerVDOT89559444*Richmond, VA*Seeking a senior technical Project Manager to manage and deliver complex projects with multiple teams and work streams coordinated to an aggressive delivery schedule. CLIENT MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS:… https://t.co/LAe7UZf4lw https://t.co/LU0pQvHNzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: SOFTWARE Broadcom Corporation has an opening in Irvine, CA for R&amp;D Engineer Software 4 (IRECE) to analyze, design, program, debug, &amp;modify software. Ref job code &amp;mail resume to: Broadcom Corporation, Attn: HR (IS), 1320 Ridder Park Drive,… https://t.co/ZQ3OJOFDrd https://t.co/Vbf9MKNcgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (East Walpole): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/r8TVq9eqXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – TS/SCI Poly: Web Developer. EDUCATION, CERTIFICATION &amp; MINIMUM EXPERIENCE * Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or similar * Minimum 5 years of relevant experience KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS, ABILITIES &amp; ATTRIBUTES This particular position… https://t.co/VwPfPbeuAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Engineer Staff: Req ID : 425531BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Software/Solution Architect/Systems Engineer/Project Engineering Lead/Project Manager to join the Advanced Programs Intelligence Systems… https://t.co/H08ywgY8dv https://t.co/BQInIm2DnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Engineer, Java, Javascript: Req ID : 430520BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Are you a highly skilled Software engineer who is ready for a new challenge? Lockheed Martin is a global technology leader… https://t.co/AsJUEM7hjK https://t.co/HUPFaf4jsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Early Career: Location: Dallas, Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers The Boeing Company is seeking Software Engineers in support of a Flight Electronics Tools Development Team. This position will part of… https://t.co/No3jzB9Ut4 https://t.co/zlfivNtW5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testosterone Ruling for Athletes Fuels Debate Over ‘Natural’ Ability: Women with high levels of testosterone—like Olympic gold medalist Caster Semenya—must either compete against men or take medication. https://t.co/wQNlBHWB2a https://t.co/rmIgn3Nds2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growlerwerks uKeg Review: Keeps Your Beer Bubbly: This steampunk vessel might be the ultimate personal beer transportation device. https://t.co/r74EzL6vFq https://t.co/7IW8NvneaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Engineer: Solutions Engineer (Trading Services Analyst), Centennial, CO. (Full Time) Among others, understand &amp; define trading life cycle for different Equity &amp; FI asset types. Analyze &amp; develop complex investments system apps &amp; business… https://t.co/i2U1nXmvuD https://t.co/aJSwiSGopc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Authors of Wikipedia's Most-Cited Source Had No Idea: How a climate study by three Australians came to dominate the online encyclopedia. https://t.co/tkVurogSsB https://t.co/HfPQHUfSb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administration T3: Description:JOB DESCRIPTION:  Leidos is looking for a System Administrator to join our Origin program team. The ideal candidate will serve as an engineer on the Service Operations Team on a classified government contract. The… https://t.co/DzVwGVD291]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager- Transit and Rail: CH2M is now Jacobs. The Challenge? Help support our Transportation Clients and have a hand in transforming tomorrow.  Senior Project Manager- Transit and Rail-Toronto,   CH2M provides industry leadership in… https://t.co/N1kR3ou2k9 https://t.co/gfdvemR41g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Devops Engineer: Devops/ Build Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: software development, build infrastructure engineering experience Expertise in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery Experience with build… https://t.co/s0x4L74isu https://t.co/PDf6rCogKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DDoS for Hire, a CIA Card Game, and More Security News This Week: A major DDoS for hire site gets taken down, the CIA has a card game that you can play soon too, and more security news this week. https://t.co/zcHnSQMZPU https://t.co/DUEB8Xz5X6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Management Analyst 3:   Job Description – Data Management Analyst 3 (18008022) Data Management Analyst 3 Requisition ID : 18008022 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/YDv8wSVp65 https://t.co/53DBt1Gl7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP SD/Retail AFS with Customer Analytics – Senior Consultant (Customer): Are you looking for a career trajectory that few other organizations can offer in SAP? What about access to a high-quality portfolio of businesses and clients with opportunities to… https://t.co/7NuYCFTNmL https://t.co/JrYdK1ELxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defense Readiness and Training Support Analyst: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Defense Readiness and Training Support Analyst Key Role: Assist the DoD client onsite as a training and readiness coordinator. Act as a Schools or Range… https://t.co/I68oh7g8DN https://t.co/airvoWXsU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Westworld' Recap, Season 2 Episode 2: The Facade Is Crumbling: The second episode of season two of 'Westworld' finally shows the places beyond the parks. https://t.co/OxuUDBuQlh https://t.co/qWB71VtCJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Analyst: SAP Finance/Purchasing Functional Analyst in Kansas City, MO: Responsible for analyzing business requirements and developing detail design specifications for enhancements and new functionality based on business SAP best practices to… https://t.co/W85oIC20Dw https://t.co/58cOFR2ZCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Mechanical Engineer: Lead Mechanical Engineer, Envelope Division InfoSend, Inc. has job opp. in Anaheim, CA: Lead Mechanical Engineer, Envelope Division. Oversee installtn, upkeep, maintenance, repair, &amp; upgrading of envelope convert’g equipmnt &amp;… https://t.co/x6tj4fjkC0 https://t.co/pa9FvAhXan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild Rides From Beijing's Bling-Flinging Car Show: Automakers like Mercedes-Benz, BMW, and Lexus, hankering for a piece of the booming Chinese market brought some of the swankiest wares to the capital city's auto show this week. https://t.co/igf1rHRmOz https://t.co/uF24NTpSpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart Home Expert: What does a Smart Home Design Expert do? The Smart Home Design Expert is responsible for delivering an end-to-end Connected Home Experience across all aspects of the Connected Home ecosystem and Vivint product assortment. This role… https://t.co/2cdJsQX6Hq https://t.co/2mkl625NSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator Location: Arlington, VA Job Code: 3135 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the… https://t.co/7NYudnvc0v https://t.co/ruenMeY92A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI Can Help Cybersecurity—If It Can Fight Through the Hype: There are a ton of claims around AI and cybersecurity that don't quite add up. Here's what's really going on. https://t.co/bXi1AuNKQE https://t.co/s8KNMR8cTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Microsoft IT Specialist: Position Summary / Responsibilities: We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Junior Microsoft IT Specialist, interested in joining our team in Boyce, VA (with occasional visits to Winchester, VA and… https://t.co/3yl1XGoW9q https://t.co/zLZ1iZOEBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Technician – Internal Candidates Only (Technology): Overview Goodwill works to enhance the dignity and quality of life of individuals and families by strengthening communities, eliminating barriers to opportunity, and helping people in need… https://t.co/Ft637JcYOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybach's Electric SUV, Tesla's Autopilot Shakeup, and More Car News: Plus: why self-driving car developers should be aiming lower. https://t.co/ZDgB8QQmoM https://t.co/Ep7J8HZy9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Environment/Storage Admin/MySQL/Data warehouse Admin: Virtual Environment/Storage Admin/MySQL/Data warehouse Admin Ref No.:18-00175 Category: ************* Location: Rockville, Maryland Position Type:Full-time Experience Level: 5 Years Start… https://t.co/ELUt5xBhs1 https://t.co/dNoBgoNMnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Photos of the Week: ESA's Gaia Tallies Up Our Milky Way: The European Space Agency's craft has already has catalogued more than 1 billion stars. https://t.co/aecr1JYVk3 https://t.co/a1brUD0DwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemists Orchestrate the Molecular Union of Two Single Atoms: It’s a molecular Parent Trap: Stick two atoms in a vacuum chamber, and steer them together with lasers. https://t.co/o3UFGzvbb8 https://t.co/4KSgcMMQZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineer – UDA: In January 2018, we launched one of the industry’s largest technical transformation projects, in effect building a new bank from the ground up. This project isn’t greenfield in the way most banks claim projects are; we’ve… https://t.co/WnVnwIrc7V https://t.co/A6QZWgXNRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance – Cyber Security Professionals – ISSO, ISSM: 107482BR Information Assurance – Cyber Security Professionals – ISSO, ISSM MA – Andover, MA – Marlborough, MA – Tewksbury, MA – Woburn, RI – Portsmouth 107482BR One global team creating… https://t.co/jrab1eD5fK https://t.co/Q73nqs1Bbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator Qualities you must possess: Self-motivated Enjoy solving problems Strong organizational skills, ability to track multiple issues Independent, curious, wishing to learn Strong communication skills (verbal and… https://t.co/3P6KNMf59s https://t.co/TpFwK8VY5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Badass, the Grassroots Activists Hitting Revenge Porn Where It Lives: From posting "boner killers" to helping law enforcement, victims of nonconsensual pornography are fighting back. https://t.co/uXRuELKSpR https://t.co/mK1UI52PUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Sr. Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-00787 Location: Dallas, Texas Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 05/01/2018 to 03/31/2019 Responsibilities: " 5-7 years of hands-on software engineering. " 4+ years current experience… https://t.co/RRIjRCwNGj https://t.co/IcCaRuGrhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title AV Systems Administrator – Media Services: * AV Systems Administrator – Media Services Posted Date 18 hours ago(4/24/2018 3:09 PM) Job ID 2017-2372 # Positions 1 Department Information Services Category Administrator Overview Quinnipiac… https://t.co/nxbKwq6RmA https://t.co/tAXWwebjfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer, Mid: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Front End Developer, Mid Key Role: Perform complex analysis, design, development, testing, and debugging of computer software in support of distinct product hardware or… https://t.co/T6WlsHbp9b https://t.co/xz5oUiVSXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ominous Views of Japan's New Concrete Seawalls: Can these 41-foot-high walls protect the country from another tsunami? https://t.co/RlD6hwz4Gf https://t.co/iH2PD4Q0ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Sr: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As an Application Developer Sr within… https://t.co/QjOXjbDPNB https://t.co/3YFp72qbOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6M53uGz8a7 Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/u3NhjvtWxP https://t.co/TR8pZVYN3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 'Dirty Computer' Janelle Monáe Breaks Out of Her Android Persona: If her new album says anything, it’s that all she ever needed to be was herself. https://t.co/WnkFSuradO https://t.co/SLEuqrmcsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PwC IT Salesforce Environment Manager (DevOps): PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/wTcVAvkfDD https://t.co/6aY1jg0GFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – CAPAM Engineer – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/ZknyN432PY https://t.co/d51or8oa5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Manchaug): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/cMNqiqTSvS https://t.co/MazhsbMiCz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>