<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/igxk9wKwPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/4f2dOUYJuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/eWVS1b5DqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/tL4NP6IcWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/Np8i1qy191]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/uZKRTetrj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/eiPwjKHEh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/mNyExZUn9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/kwSdTi3l2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/NjnEWMPBra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/pkq6v1Xk8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/IqPWYy7c61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/StVWu0dFqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/PqHnzbCbIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/W2VZQZJ5mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/frpMnYL14K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/9qxTmKVdgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/Ch0aB6BSNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/V9vhxnB2Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/OfTTWy3WbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/WR8Z5sbXGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/etyxuVULiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/ipzT8XNV1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/DMeaOzpF1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedestrian is someone who thought there were a couple of gallons left in the tank. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/vbacsNAIfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/roNPJTbvbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/15dJxc76YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/jj8ssdHmq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/ljRAIC8urF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/RB8oWX57Ik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/xAfXEBZesv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/RaiDDLBxU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/lfuwtByAac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/3tjtGpk990]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/doDJJg8OzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/eADK473T5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/W2VZQZruet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/QwZ5jcOWSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/vAVXpOOxPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/NI3xCBbJJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/0t2J8R4a44]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>