<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the type of girl who is willing to brighten your day even if I can't brighten my own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day, you'll really fall for a girl and you are going to give her everything in the world because you know she deserves it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget to thank God in every something. The more you keep breathing, the greater His plans for your everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real boyfriend knows his girl like the back of his hand. He knows when she's mad, sad, aggravated, happy, hurt, because that's his girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why compare yourself with others? No one in the entire world can do a better job of being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has a plan and one day I will understand it, but for now I just have to trust Him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just simply miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is knowing that nobody's perfect &amp; everyone makes mistakes, but u still work for it cause u know it would all worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can come into your life &amp; say how much they love u. It takes someone really special to stay in your life &amp; show how much they love u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy your life today because yesterday had gone and tomorrow may never come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every relationship has its problems, but what makes it perfect is when you wouldn't want to be anywhere else, even when times are tough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't block you or delete you. I'm keeping you there so you will be able to see how happy I am without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the hardest decisions you'll ever face in life is choosing whether to walk away or try harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's loyalty is tested when her man has nothing. A man's loyalty is tested when he has everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you have to do now so you can do what you want to do later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiest people are not those who own all the best things, but the ones who can really appreciate the beauty of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be thankful for all you have now, because you honestly never know what will happen next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go that extra mile for someone who isn't even worth the run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just a girl who is in love with the most annoying, cutest, funniest, nicest, and completely perfect guy in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for someone else to make you happy is the best way to be sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no use trying to rush fate, because the best things in life are worth the wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's crazy what people do for love, and it's even more crazy what love does to people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want a prince charming. I want a boy that loves me for me, will care for me, promises me forever, and actually follows through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 billion people in the world and he's the only one I want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real boyfriend knows his girl like the back of his hand. He knows when she's mad, sad, aggravated, happy, hurt, because that's his girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe 'finding the one' is a process of elimination. So, with every breakup, you're one step closer to finding your true love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every story has an ending. But in life, every ending is a new beginning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships don't need promises, terms, and conditions. It just needs two people: who can trust and who can understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is blind, hard to find, difficult to get, and impossible to forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I don't understand about life. We meet thousands of people, then we will meet that one person and our life will change forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone is strong enough to bring you down, show them you are strong enough to get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best relationship are when you can lay with each other and just talk about anything and everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have two eyes but can't see u everyday &amp; two ears but can't hear u all the time. But I have only one heart that cares for u all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop learning, because life never stops teaching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving is not just looking at each other‚ it's looking in the same direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to stop thinking so much, and just go where your heart takes you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive thinking will let you do everything better than negative thinking will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to feel rich, just count all the great things you have that money can't buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need a certain number of friends, just a number of friends I can be certain of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In life, you'll never have exactly what you want, but in the end God always gives you exactly what you NEED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiest couples never have the same character. They have the best understanding of their differences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still miss you and maybe even still like you, but I'm done chasing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just never know... that I have so many emotions I choose not to show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone can tell you how wrong someone is for you, but in the end, all it comes down to is that you can't help who you fall in love with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't need another to make us whole, but it's nice to have that 1 person that will hold you &amp; tell you how special you are to their life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: When did you know you loved me? Him: When I wanted to be with you forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being honest may not get you a lot of friends, but it'll always get you the right ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only once in your life, I truly believe that you can find someone who can completely turn your world around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life can be unfair at times, but that isn't a reason to give up. God never said it would always be easy, but it will be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know why, but I fall more in love with you everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not use today better than yesterday, then why do you need tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're important to another person, that person will always find a way to make time for you. No excuses, no lies, no broken promises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search your inner most feelings, who do you truly love and who truly loves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you really want to text someone, but you have nothing to talk about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your're nothing, people will ignore you, but when you're on top that's when everybody swear they know you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love + Trust + Honesty = Long Lasting Relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even knowing that we wouldn't be anything more than friends, yet I'm here trying to believe that one day things might change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When yesterday is a disappointment &amp; today isn't better, remember there's always a tomorrow, &amp; make it something to look forward to &amp; smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A boyfriend should always send u a good morning &amp; goodnight text even if u don't talk all day, just to let you know that you're on his mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God works in mysterious ways and He knows what's best for us. Put all your trust in Him, and go with the flow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbyes are hard. It may be hard for the person leaving, but it's always harder for the one left behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have no idea how hard it is to force myself to stop thinking about you, sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage should be like football; you must show up fully committed and prepared and score every opportunity you get!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A relationship with God is the most important relationship you can have. Trust him and everything will always turn out fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love people who can make me laugh when I don't even want to smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you can do better than anyone else is be yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A problem isn't something to get u down. It's something that challenges you to be a better &amp; stronger person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to tell your mind to stop loving someone when your heart still does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life isn't perfect, but I thankful for everything what I have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's something you really want, fight for it. Don't give up no matter how hopeless it seems right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst regret we can have in life is not for the wrong things we did, but for the right things we could have done but we never did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what I do, I always think of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, or throbbing moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm silent, it doesn't mean I have nothing to say. It just means I care enough not to hurt your feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not popular, but I can make you feel like you are the most important person in the world every day, every minute, and every second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never stop believing that God has my best interest in mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love your parents. We are so busy growing up, we often forget they are also growing old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to realize he doesn't care, and you could be missing out on someone who does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're in love when you're having the worst day, and just talking to him makes everything better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to know that the best wishes are the wishes inside your heart. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To let go is to be thankful for the experiences that made you laugh, made you cry, and made you grow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't hate you. I just lost all my respect for you though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I knew missing you was going to be part of my life, I never would have let you in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday is a new beginning. Treat it that way. Stay away from what might have been, and look at what can be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone asks me who I want to be with, I would simply say someone who will never leave me because of someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mind is a powerful thing. When you fill it with positive thoughts your life will start to change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like a garden. Sometimes you have to bury your feelings, water them with tears, and then wait to see where they grow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand people could tell me I was beautiful, but it doesn't mean anything unless it's coming from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a strong relationship, both people motivate each other to go further in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is more fun when you don't take it too hard. Take it as a game, then play and enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls always find things out, they might not say anything right away, but they know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a snowflake for everytime I thought of you, we'd have a really white Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hal terindah adalah ketika kamu bertemu dengan dia yang mencintaimu tanpa syarat, meski mungkin kamu bukan yang terbaik.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't search for love, search for someone that makes you happy. Sooner or later, that happiness will evolve into love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to wish everyone a very Merry Christmas! Hope everybody has a wonderful day!!! God Bless You! (*^・^)ノ⌒☆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas Eve _(≥∇≤)ノミ☆. Don't forget to go to the Church, ok? ♪( ´▽｀)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm down, I remember that there is someone who will ALWAYS love me, and that is God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop fighting for what you love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up on love, because there is always someone who loves you. Even if it's not the person you were hoping for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday everything will make sense. So laugh at the confusion, smile through the tears &amp; remind yourself, everything happens for a reason.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>