<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/rRKgw6Lkix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/FJLsVetQ7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/068tkZ58Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trouble with a kitten is that eventually it becomes a Cat - Ogden Nash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/IF8f3ugxwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/Dmc3cGrbLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/ol2nIYDhbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/aB7IgaoH2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/83XMeBzEFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/LEpV7zS1hG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/lYqb2G0RZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/j3SSiiuDPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/1K23NTipa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of America  http://t.co/vLKlURdhbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/ZYcx2HXmSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/vh5sSBDNXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/MfWACXpSVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/8vjTEEutsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/AEgcx5LUqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/276q9nC0zL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/7TPOLYTDGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/qddeVJSz3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/7zIPWxi95U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A business has to be involving, it has to be fun, and it has to exercise your creative instincts. - Richard Branson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/2ZLQJH2LkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/n7LLUoVCBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/o89xAvJZEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/lXdQZ8wziS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/QPBt6Nofdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/xYOtvFHRuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/t0R91Dm7XE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/7hGLr5fJ86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/oXTifvJmQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/h3zGScxDoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/MjZjbyP5Sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/BQESP8vLj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/ou3NvPqIW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget how fast you did a job - but they remember how well you did it. - Howard Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mets have found ways of losing that I never knew existed. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/6qXbqqgwLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/w2rsmjQslz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/CYL0swJ1Bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A business has to be involving, it has to be fun, and it has to exercise your creative instincts. - Richard Branson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/2xUq741bx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>