<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Workplaces Better Recognize https://t.co/Xd0Iw0tgeS

As part of its ongoing research into employee engagement,… https://t.co/oYrSSFg57i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Zenefits Copied Zappos’ Staff Buyout Idea https://t.co/qQZmBxezm2

Zappos made headlines last year when it off… https://t.co/E0rtBOGRaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Autonomous Workplace Eats the Open Office for Breakfast https://t.co/2axJ0FyK4H

Open-plan offices have proven… https://t.co/JkqhzNIgxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Overhauls Recruiting Process, Shifting Away From Elite Schools https://t.co/mRjfdgvVhI

Last week, G… https://t.co/qdeqMfN6TE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Leaders, Be Careful What You Say About Brexit https://t.co/3ozdtsanw6

When people make a decision, espec… https://t.co/BYBQPhTJhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Sectors Will Feel the Biggest Impact from Brexit? https://t.co/B7Qr3I5A8z

While the overall economic impact… https://t.co/AhcQktsNlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Does Brexit Mean for the Future of Science in the UK? https://t.co/ee2yQNRrOR

Home to some of the world’s ol… https://t.co/bisIiNGmle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_TlntMonitor: Listen to @briankropp's podcast for a deep dive on labor market trends https://t.co/pg231zNHZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Examining Intel's latest diversity report, which shows little progress from last year (+ analysis from @JLindzon): http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Technology isn't just a way to execute HR strategy anymore; now technology *is* HR strategy: https://t.co/Iptl5dcJF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Per new @payscale study, US employees , when they know their CEOs salary, are OK with it. Not as much in UK tho: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FallsChurchGov: What's your vision for the City of Falls Church in the year 2040? Take this survey: https://t.co/oNnUWKBqgT Due 8/24 ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mary_CEBNews: @briankropp on what spurs employees to leave their jobs in @HarvardBiz https://t.co/FQI4VEqdwH @CEB_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarvardBiz @beygelman for more detail on how to get career pathing to work see: https://t.co/tvsw70N8Ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Should babysitting be considered a legitimate travel expense? Our D&amp;I team considers the implications: https://t.co/J1C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @landisl: Volunesia: How Volunteering Impacted My Life https://t.co/bwHJDlboCv #CEBGivesBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @changemblog: @briankropp A very interesting take on open source change management!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DCFencersClub: From @USAFencing #Rio2016 Alexander Massialas silver in Men's Foil today is the first fencing individual medal for a US…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@landisl @k9lifesavers can't beat puppy day at #CEB.  You can adopt this one. https://t.co/0YX8vhoACb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drshow this might be an interesting topic for an upcoming show https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: One of our D&amp;I researchers reviews the excellent D&amp;I-focused Harvard Business Review issue that came out last month: ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @landisl: Volunteering with K-9 Lifesavers https://t.co/PXUrRTWBJv #CEBGivesBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great review of HBR focus on d&amp;i by jenna louie @CEBTalentDaily https://t.co/RA2bQDRUBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: If Market Shifts Mean Changes to Retirement Plans, How Will You Communicate Those Changes? https://t.co/xGRtEQteed https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massachusetts equal pay law a benefit for all @MsJessicaCash @jenamcgregor  https://t.co/7WibEwLNyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Most UK employers aren't discussing the impact of Brexit with their employees, according to a @totaljobsUK survey: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyRPeck it is working hard, but according to this research anything after 25 hours week has diminishing returns https://t.co/Yypxo2kdfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mary_CEBNews: @briankropp says new equal pay law in Massachusetts is unambiguously a good thing @jenamcgregor @post_lead @ceb_news http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Our analysis roundup on Apple's new diversity report w/ @nickstatt @HRileyBowles @lizzadwoskin @deborahtodd @hshaban ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FallsChurchGov: Last Concerts in the Park (of the season) TOMORROW at 7PM! Free concert features: Tom Principato! Bring a blanket! http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: As investment returns drop &amp; employers redesign benefits, it's crucial that employees understand the changes clearly ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Death by overwork remains a serious problem in Japan, where unpaid overtime is high and job satisfaction is low: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Equal representation shouldn't just be about employers ticking the boxes, but aiming for a diversity-enabled outcome ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonsmedstad: CEB is hiring in the DC area: Consultant, Sales Solutions: https://t.co/3y3XirhpQ4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Should employers conduct the equiv. of an exit interview when a job candidate turns them down? https://t.co/vaFbctCdzy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban @StephanAarstol #sharktank idea making great progress in HR space #5hourworkweek https://t.co/fJi2LWguad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyRPeck @HuffPostBiz Companies that hire in multiple states should follow this rather than have diff rules https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Many employers want to shorten the workday but don't know how, @BrianKropp notes some advice from @StephanAarstol: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonsmedstad @CEBTalentDaily not only does it improve productivity, but it also makes you a more attractive employer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonsmedstad: "The new law updates the state’s 1945 equal pay law to introduce new protections meant to help close the gender pay…ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FallsChurchGov: Visit the Farmers Market on Saturdays from 8-12PM! Use the new Farmers Market map to help navigate easily! https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton  good news for employees https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj and not only piece of important policy in MA today https://t.co/n1w5VXGYyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: MA updated its equal pay law to address gender pay gap. We roundup w/ @shiraschoenberg @brycecovert @humanworkplace: ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: As unpaid internship programs keep getting taken to court - what are the larger implications of the practice? https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: In tight talent market, orgs can and should get better at targeting passive job candidates (re @humanworkplace post) ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When employees don't take their paid vacations, should we start offering them paid, paid vacations? https://t.co/tBiZrGVlJF h/t @EmilyRPeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@changemblog new insights from CEB -change managers should be where change is occurring (not necessairly in a COE) ( https://t.co/FOdJe0mcWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just over a month from away until CEB's reimagineHR in Miami -- largest ever gathering of senior HR executives https://t.co/QTYc63tJ8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josh_Bersin but a lot of those vacation spots are making it easier for you to do work from them! https://t.co/5rfdoPTz1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jack_welch jack is right: employees most likely to make quit/stay decisions on vacations, birthdays and reunions https://t.co/ONffqi7JYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Via @sarahkliff, how time &amp; the value of certain work hours can drive the gender pay gap + what can be done about it ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Matt Dudek looks at the downsides of forcing employees to be positive, suggests real dialogue as an alternative: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Is it a good idea to extend the workplace to the beach? https://t.co/jrqdxmGxNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeadershipARL: We are seeking a fall Communications Intern! Apply by 8/19. Position description: https://t.co/JSATskwWcm https://t.co/9…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @USDOL: These #STEM jobs don't need a 4-year-degree, and they pay near or above the median. More: https://t.co/yEQYK98khQ https://t.co/5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: New @Gallup polling indicates that Americans are becoming more aware of gender inequality in the workplace: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Yes, who you sit next to at the office influences your productivity, suggests a new study (via @LydiaBreakfast): https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: How company culture can help address the health risks of workplace stress (feat. some new @HarvardChanSPH research): ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Matt Dudek points to yet another survey highlighting how UK employees are seeking better work-life balance: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CEB doing some great things with @LeanInOrg
@CEBCareers #WomenAtCEB https://t.co/0vf3v0L8Qn @MsJessicaCash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: .@Google's influential talent chief Laszlo Bock has stepped down; veteran Googler  @EileenTNaughton will take over: htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Some new research shows that small businesses are joining trend of increased education requirements (via @CBpetej): htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Would something like the NBA's ‘hustle stat’ help orgs do a better job recognizing women's unsung contributions? https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research suggests working longer hours may reduce productivity. If that's true, the implications are profound: https://t.co/Yypxo2kdfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuercusApp: Instead of removing ratings focus on three #PerformanceManagement strategies! via @CEB_HR https://t.co/FiyaLlZtHn https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: RT @TINYpulse: @Pat_Clunie @CEB_HR #PerformanceReviews Yes, yes and yes! 100% agree! https://t.co/Cibsp1Wx1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How JPMorgan's recent min wage hike is another example of HR becoming a kind of new PR: https://t.co/4jlcttarea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top British Firms Show Little Progress Toward Gender Parity on Executive Committees https://t.co/ySIVKHGgcT

Crack… https://t.co/VFMKHp7cEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ElaineKTurville: @HardballChris 'Leadership is someone who will back you on your worst week' re VP pick @MartinWRodgers @bldublya @AmyT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Employers Offer the Best Work-Life Balance? https://t.co/QpIHrcZsZ2

Indeed has compiled a ranking of the 25… https://t.co/22IgipP7IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Isn’t Alone: All Employers Are Under Pressure to Raise Wages https://t.co/Ouh85TeSuA

Guardian reporter t… https://t.co/rgPhio6Xg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit Puts Pressure on Science and Agriculture https://t.co/P9TI6h0qSZ

In the wake of last month’s Brexit refere… https://t.co/nzmfBVX1pH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working 9 to 5 Is Going Out of Style https://t.co/hworevCfEf

Employers and productivity experts have lately been … https://t.co/6WyUYPnrtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lesson for Fired HR Leaders? Don’t Drive Change Alone! https://t.co/Ay6x9dGOog

In an interview a few years ag… https://t.co/ebtbo743nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If Meritocracy Is a Myth? https://t.co/bEoYDj1ee9

At the LSE Review of Books, Dan McArthur praises economist… https://t.co/VmJY9bcia4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is Failing at Putting Ex-Prisoners Back to Work https://t.co/Mxvk4upD2g

Some 70 million Americans have so… https://t.co/Jlx2UdvA18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yearning for a Smarter Office https://t.co/dqt1W1ZCcZ

Sara Bean at Workplace Insight highlights the findings of D… https://t.co/JwUjrj9Cte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minding Mindfulness in the Workplace https://t.co/CmgLt7Fsvj

Livia Gershon at Pacific Standard investigates the t… https://t.co/dRb3OBAAI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber’s Contractor Model Challenged in UK Tribunal https://t.co/2Eq8qxGliV

Uber, which considers its drivers indep… https://t.co/2a0oLPiqkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pokémon Go: Ban It, or Embrace It? https://t.co/4k7bavz0DB

While the augmented-reality game Pokémon Go doesn’t ne… https://t.co/v8HN6RGTKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Becoming more and more clear that the US labor market has become talent-driven, w/ employees in the driver's seat: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: In the US, job openings, job creation, and wages all seem to be on the rise, as the economy continues to recover: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eacushing: Thank you @StanMcChrystal for encouraging leaders to say "I don't know exactly how we'll get there." Our teams can lead. #Re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: 5 challenges + trends that emerged in a meeting of diversity &amp; inclusion professionals @ CEB's #ReimagineHR in Miami ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michelleMsmith9: Thank you @CEB_HR for an outstanding #conference incredibly well done in every way! Go DC in 2017. #ReimagineHR #HR ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Thank you for joining us at #ReimagineHR! Save the date for next year: 18 - 20 October, in Washington, DC. We hope to see you t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob cross: avoid collaborative overload by always taking a direct report to meetings #ReimagineHR https://t.co/RvEhah27HZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob cross: people not tools critical to making collaboration work #ReimagineHR https://t.co/wQpen4y1Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanMcChrystal how leadership skills change #ReimagineHR https://t.co/GTIJFw8fgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanMcChrystal must understand communications to understand leadership #ReimagineHR https://t.co/Ed2v3ilVno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValeriePlame listening to great insights about building trust #ReimagineHR https://t.co/zaffTFA9Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighGroundHQ @HDScorp talking about boom boxes and talent at #ReimagineHR https://t.co/eufATrRWmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eacushing teaching CEB #ReimagineHR how to play @Playworks https://t.co/vY2Q1a8i7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: When Senior Leaders Understand the Importance of D&amp;I #ReimagineHR #DiversityAndInclusion https://t.co/iMxnndPSxP https://t.co/8…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colindaymude: #ReimagineHR Top down ownership of implementation plan has negative impact. Add 11+ points when employees own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A full house for CEBs #ReimagineHR https://t.co/mUcUFIWFht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking off #reimagineHR https://t.co/RGPPvJEmlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ElaineKTurville: Yacht Rock Radio, I am crying it is over. Bring it back! No Babs 18 #YachtRockRadio @SIRIUSXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @post_lead: This software startup can tell your boss if you’re looking for a job https://t.co/ipGQ9Ejm2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEBTalentDaily: Millennial mythbusting via an incisive @lmlauramarsh essay + new @TalentInnovate pushback on the job-hopping theory: ht…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>