<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @khalafroula: FT Person of the Year is George Soros 
For who he is, what he does and why they hate him
⁦@FT⁩  https://t.co/78NN2xevd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmosToh: .@tumblr's ill-conceived ban on adult content is yet another example of the troubling gap between the tech sector’s #humanrigh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should anyone believe Facebook anymore? Good question. https://t.co/wcvHC7F4gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @snoep_IT: Facebook Fights Back on Secret Data-Sharing Partnerships.. https://t.co/D7bvZBBhui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hoofnagle: Decades of privacy agitation and we seem to have learned so little from it…Facebook still gets away with calling third parti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: Curbing Speech in the Name of Helping Israel   via @NYTimes https://t.co/F1F6nZm6Nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT Person of the Year: George Soros https://t.co/7JCbVEvRE8 via @financialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: Yes, tech platforms can and should change their business models. They're in non-stop crisis control because the ad-financed mod…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sheeraf: NEW NYT INVESTIGATION: Internal documents show that Facebook gave, "Netflix and Spotify the ability to read Facebook users’ pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Advox: Anti-violence protests continue in Belgrade, after journalist survives assassination attempt https://t.co/uCZqHMt9Y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: The so-called ’#SlaveryLaw’ will raise the 250-hour annual cap on overtime work to 400 hours. Moreover, employers will be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: 100 days for Alaa: Family of Egyptian activist counts the days until his release from prison https://t.co/XY9ptDZTLc "The…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: Will the reinstatement of Prime Minister Ranil Wickremesinghe end Sri Lanka's political crisis? https://t.co/s8pSwR3kuf "…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s time for a Bill of Data Rights - great piece by @martintisne via @techreview https://t.co/POXeHNNISX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's time for significant changes': civil rights groups call for Facebook leaders to step down https://t.co/IzHLGQjlQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who invented the word processor and online flight booking system has died https://t.co/Q2W5bRbMse via @quartzatwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @privacyint: Our #metadata can be used to to infer extremely intimate details about ourselves, even things like our religious beliefs. F…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man. https://t.co/D59BVNenqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 days for Alaa: Family of Egyptian activist counts the days until his release from prison  #FreeAlaa https://t.co/P1WpTvlc3q via @Afaf_TN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: How did the ideal of the internet morph into a habit-forming outrage machine that spies on us?

"It's an infrastructure…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dmonett: "Most dangerously, we take successful algorithms &amp; assign stories to their successes that extrapolate far beyond what they act…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpenSecretsDC: More #Transparency may be coming to political ads thanks to this bill that was quietly introduced to Congress this week…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathonmorgan: The new playbook for information warfare will be hyper-personalized. Propaganda created just for you, delivered by swar…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: #MostRead this week: Acts of Intimidation: In Pakistan, journalists' fear and censorship grow even as fatal violence decl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dw_business: Digital activists, politicians, entrepreneurs and scientists are meeting in Accra, Ghana. #rpAccra 

https://t.co/KDTVZchC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ammir: Apps used by a reported combined 30 MILLION users in #Iran operating under the #Telegram company's name are "unsafe," @telegram…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @privacyint: Sign up to our mailing list to receive our news on privacy and surveillance as they happen!
https://t.co/YMUzk1ZEmX https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: More than 1,330 journalists have been killed since 1992 in the line of duty. Support #pressfreedom today: https://t.co/J8…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Want alternatives to Facebook and Google? They’re out there, as are local allies to help you navigate the ecosystem of tech platfo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: We are one of sixteen consumer privacy and civil rights groups to remind Congress that while we support federal baseline data priv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @befoune: "The Internet shutdown in #Cameroon was intended to shut down dissent, but the actual effect was it created a new generation o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @signalapp: Setback in the outback: https://t.co/TUIml7sT4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Rome's decline was caused less by gaping wounds than gaping inequality, and by leaders unable or willing to remedy it htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lawyerpants: @davidakaye @UN_SPExperts @UNHumanRights I'm really excited to help @UNHumanRights shine light onto this dark and destruct…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: new @UN_SPExperts @UNHumanRights project and call for submissions: the #surveillance industry and #humanrights. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How McKinsey Has Helped Raise the Stature of Authoritarian Governments   via @NYTimes https://t.co/FiOQAhcJUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: Spanish authorities should immediately return equipment and documentation seized from the news agency @europapress and fr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Encrypted Messaging App Signal Says It Won’t Comply With Australia’s New Backdoor Bill https://t.co/RtH4Rh1O5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: This past week, #HumanRightsDay was a chance for many of us to reflect on #UDHR70 &amp; what it means for our digital future [ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: The Elf on the Shelf is a cop. https://t.co/euCrK0R8tJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: HTTPS Everywhere remains an important tool in your toolbox for keeping yourself safe on the web. https://t.co/NOxRchVlIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankPasquale: The most efficient way to keep billions of people acquiescent “might be to engineer their preferences to expect very lit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sivavaid Yup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gigibsohn @EFF Great news! Congratulations Gigi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CyberhedgeInc: "It’s time to elevate cybersecurity as a macro risk equal to finance" featured in Finance Derivative written by Ryan Dod…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brennan_mike: We are hiring 3 new tech fellows at @FordFoundation! Join us for a 2 year term with Gender Racial &amp; Ethnic Justice, Civic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: Why should #encryption matter to you? You’re using it every day.
This game from our friends at @hrw is a fun way to learn ab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: A 7-year old girl died of dehydration while in Border Patrol custody. She had been detained for eight hours when the seizures s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: There are 251 journalists jailed for their work worldwide:

Turkey 68
China 47
Egypt 25
Eritrea 16
Saudi Arabia 16
Vietna…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hoofnagle: Thread + let’s not forget Sharona Coutts’ article about using this location data to target women at Planned Parenthood https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations!!! https://t.co/J1dEOXSVoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenBrianSchatz: Today I introduced the #DataCareAct which will help make sure that when people give online companies their information,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Through their investment decisions and corporate engagements, investors play a crucial role in respecting human rights.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids Shouldn’t Have to Sacrifice Privacy for Education  https://t.co/qYcdAHnDXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me as a founding supporter of The Correspondent @the_corres New ideas and new business models for journalism are vital for the survival of democracy. Don't wait. Do it now. https://t.co/w6OnK70dZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrageous: Journalists fleeing threats at home trapped in ICE detention over US asylum seeker policy   https://t.co/NHqfn6niCe via @pressfreedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['They don't care': Facebook fact-checking in disarray as journalists push to cut ties https://t.co/2dTHN03cP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BKCHarvard: We are seeking a Managing Director to join our team at the Berkman Klein Center! https://t.co/Lwb6yT9jZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bellvisuals: Projecting with @Global_Witness at the Trump International Hotel. #TrumpDeals https://t.co/yP8h64ED3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonDeibert: Washington must wake up to the abuse of software that kills - The Washington Post https://t.co/8RmEtVdb55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook among firms named on Myanmar human rights 'dirty list' https://t.co/EtNcsqTCa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @netizenrights: While Everyone's Busy, Hollywood &amp; Record Labels Suggest Congress Bring Back SOPA https://t.co/WuorYC9coy via @Techdirt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: Crackdown in Beijing: ‘Using Twitter is more dangerous than street demonstrations’ https://t.co/A3JNpZpxXX "Since Twitter…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: Lebanese journalist goes on trial for covering migrant worker abuse allegations https://t.co/mjKtu0n6Vk "The Cybercrime b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: For the first time, a digital security app is available in Aymara thanks to Bolivian language activists https://t.co/O4Q3…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must rethink the purpose of the corporation via @FT
By ⁦@martinwolf_⁩  https://t.co/FWwx3mwpNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HongKongFP: Open letter: Over 50 NGOs urge Google not to aid China’s censorship and surveillance regime https://t.co/Ga6eijSEVY @mediac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: #Encryption matters for #privacy &amp; other #humanrights, but for our basic functioning in today’s digital world. 
The brillian…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wamandajd: How am I spending my evening, you ask?

Oh, just sifting through 3.5 hours of hearing footage to put together all of the hil…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @seanjtaylor: The New York Times has an awesome (PhD-level) data science position open: https://t.co/mEIFzaLSqx
Fascinating job with gre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: Time did the right thing today by awarding #TimePersonOfTheYear to journalists. It inspired me to look back at how @UN_SPEx…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: please check out this great &amp; very informative thread on #business &amp; #humanrights, focused on tech, by @MichaelSamway, for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealAWiM: Do you know of an African woman in the media doing a remarkable job? She could be a producer, writer, reporter, filmmaker, na…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: EU institutions are considering online #terrorist content proposal. @NiAolainF, SR Privacy &amp; I raise serious concerns &amp; urg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnnCavoukian: Agreed: Surveillance shrinks your cognitive bandwidth — it chills creativity and innovation. https://t.co/axaTyQ33h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Petition signed by 4 million Europeans has been delivered to the negotiators in charge of #Article13, opposing mass censorship in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: this is such the right move, @TIME. when demagogues &amp; authoritarians attack truth, &amp; when govts fail to uphold their pledge…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffreyfowler: Google hearing is over.
- No major screw-ups from @sundarpichai.
- Concern over Google’s data-privacy practices is clea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ericamarat: Every single researcher/expert of Central Asia, read this now: https://t.co/4UXszc8LAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the new @congressfellows bringing badly needed tech expertise to the U.S. congress!! Congratulations to another great class. https://t.co/5pNMRMTHg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So funny. https://t.co/z2j6d5BToL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the new batch of TechCongress @congresfellows. This is such an important and badly needed program. https://t.co/5pNMRMTHg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: @Google CEO @sundarpichai is set to testify on Capitol Hill today.

Will #ProjectDragonfly, the company's plan to re-ent…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ParisPeaceForum: Did you know? 

Heads of State, Government, International Organizations and project leaders from across the world came…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Advox: Lebanese journalist goes on trial for covering migrant worker abuse allegations https://t.co/tNJsqb0WLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Advox: Crackdown in Beijing: ‘Using Twitter is more dangerous than street demonstrations’ https://t.co/05TvSMGL3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Advox: Singapore government threatens critics and independent media with defamation claims https://t.co/CCcRhFh0Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kuminaidoo: At #GoogleHearing, CEO @sundarpichai keeps repeating “we have no plans right now” to launch censored search engine in #Chin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: The @nytimes provides worrying new details on just how precise the little location trackers on your smartphone can be: h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dschilling44: When investors respect human rights through their investment decisions and corporate engagements, they contribute to the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @article19UN: “I am embarrassed and saddened that my government is not represented here today,” says @Madeleine #Albright, speaking at t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robinberjon: People often think that "surveillance capitalism" is some sort of militant exaggeration from rabid privacy activists. If y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wang_maya: Fresh off the press: Organisation of Islamic Cooperation's (OIC) independent rights body says reports from Xinjiang are "dis…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SixthTone: Chinese tech giant Baidu has been accused of deceiving consumers through its search engine. 

“Baidu’s ‘advertising’ label i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZachMarko: An amazing new map and report of network connectivity and innovation networks across the US from @NewAmerica https://t.co/Fr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @natashanyt: The tech industry argues that regulation chills innovation. 
But this story on smartphone location tracking by @jenvalentin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: we're tracked, &amp; this story is must-read (esp online, where it's displayed so well). but it's worse. imagine governments as…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @riptari: ".. powerful political actors are increasingly leveraging social media to manufacture consensus, manipulate public opinion, an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EvanSelinger: "We would be horrified if law-enforcement agents were to walk through a protest demanding that everybody show their ident…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rasmus_kleis: “This story was generated by…” @lisagibbs954 says @AP expects to publish at least 40,000 auto-generated stories in 2019 a…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>