<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/sXhBwfIM3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/lbzGPUwv3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/HT9rLnzMDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/gCpwRcDlrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/ZpYufivdFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/Fa78bKR8HI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/O85N3ZOu2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/sVbE0I69ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/2eHigM0Nat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/ybrfmtsSL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/X6N0deIFvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/tynhOl6IIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/UjkujWqOJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/LPQTFZPSYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/GpXucu9stD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/jjKW5wrihz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/247fC2qLKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/A8Z6NZi1QQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/g2YRn3FSpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/M5EI2DhUKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/0HsmAZ6SU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/rA1bRyVFR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/lGx5HTQEWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/Q954tNm80i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/TRzi94iRue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/wE3d7XodCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/RSmTmCJX9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/bEIDXMzVzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to roll a hard six. Commander William Adama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/EhkNW76Fsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/YpPnnWvsDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/TVaWhRCsVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/bbsuNDkocR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/1NiJ1oB29H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/t4GLgZvhtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/BJzUWRhguL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/bh9ZAimsSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/GHEPFC2Gwb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>