<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to complain... so here we go:
If D&amp;D wanted Dany to come save the day why not have her travel with Jon and Davos to Eastwatch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super disappointed with #GoTS7e6 I really miss @GRRMspeaking's story/characters/thoroughness. Not enjoying this season much at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could've been solved by sending a few at a time. Thus establishing a longer time frame for the boys to survive and show Jon's leadership. https://t.co/wNz63CxGPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@67sound Keep this going please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish Why not have Jon challenge Nights King the way he did Ramsey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish Have Jorah die defending Jon and Dany. Have Jon tell the team to break the ice except a small path so they could fight them off slowly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish Why not show Jon as a strong military leader?Why didnt they have dany at east watch to begin with?Why not send someone else besides gendry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke could've killed the snowman and then hung out in the cave. Instead he runs out into the snow and dark... pft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand physics at all.
#BenAnnaWatchStarWars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke cares more about Obi's death than he does about his uncle...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the dude that just wants to get in the elevator with Han Luke and Chewie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not asking for you all to tweet me about it but just putting it out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all I'm not gonna lie. I've seen Star Wars a bunch of times... I still have no idea how Leia is a princess...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who moved into Unvle Owens place after Luke left? #PrimeRealestate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've never seen a Jedi use the "whooping" technique that Obi Wan uses against the sand people.  I'd use it daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WallE in Star Wars is classic #Disney. Wait what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can there be a expansion movie about #jawas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on the beach for five seconds and there's a dune of sand in my shoes... but r2 is just wheeling around like Aint No Thang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #DarthVadar just happens to be floating by #tattoine and he doesn't say anything? He doesn't acknowledge the fact that sand is course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There goes another one." Who were in the other escape pods? What happened to them? Why not just shoot it down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gonna get annoying sorry y'all. #BenAnnaWatchStarWars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett Go on. Tell us more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has there been a tv comedy sketch of #Trump's staff meetings being an episode of #Survivor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDungeonRats @patlikestotweet Literally listening to this right now:
https://t.co/8Fm32qVuOS
You're all so young.  #HiddenBlades... #HiddenBlades!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This popped up in my work chat... I don't know these people.  But my 3 years of high school #Spanish prepared me for this! https://t.co/yzlDZ89Fvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pfholden @tjyoshie77 That was three years ago... I haven't done a single thing with my life since. #OneAndDone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BryndenBFish: I'm content most of the time turning my brain off (I'm an American), but visualizing Jon's journey vs the White Walkers i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett *fewer*... wait... nevermind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@griffinmcelroy #PlayWithMe https://t.co/WfbCAew4Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish "Ask your sister."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7point34 @BryndenBFish What is dead may never die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish can the 0.1% bad of this episode be the fact that Davos gave a ton of money to those guards and then never got it back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish Fan service ideas:
Jon meets up with Benjen
Jon finds Ghost and rides him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish Quack. https://t.co/rwUtBYpfkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJC_95 He would have done it himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quack... quack... quack quack quack!! https://t.co/lHVoF1dKpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyWifeTriesToExplainStarWars https://t.co/84mYtFmJ2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyWifeTriesToExplainStarWars https://t.co/26BxwNexO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1vlobK6LTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyWifeTriesToExplainStarWars 01/? https://t.co/BgzwhQbtGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tylerduchaine New twitter, who dis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New haircut, who dis? https://t.co/lXFl1JV9R1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMarreiros question.  anyway you'd DM me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett Excited for the RMNB Memoires one of these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish I moved to Antarctica because this take is so #hot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamsSonoma Have called &amp; talked to multiple reps. They havent been very helpful.I  just want our funds so we can get our gifts &amp; move on from ur store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamsSonoma hi, so it's been 4 months since we returned hundreds of dollars worth of merch. And we are still waiting for our gift card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westelm hey, just got this carpet. Is this much #shedding normal? 
(Just in case you're wondering we do not have an animal) https://t.co/tjc2lhs3ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett Love you boo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My in depth analysis of @russianmachine's @peterhassett's @CorsicaHockey video... https://t.co/G5Lq9pmW8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notbuckingham Ask it why Medieval Times is sneaking up on your tweets. Also... get me a discount!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guy on base should be able to steal during the whole pitcher/catcher meeting. #BaseballThoughts. #OrRelationshipGoals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife just said the #Caps will break the curse like the Cubs did... see you all in 2045!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeBr0n11 @russianmachine Alexander Ovechkin, first of his name, Captain of the Capitals, President's Trophy Winner, 30+ goal scorer, and King of the Russians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first #Nationals game of the season. Okay so who is the Kuznetsov of the #Nats? 
Where my Russians at?? https://t.co/Pjw891Bmbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine Old RMNB followers you need to unfollow right now @1bscarbro @Ryan_Deem @notbuckingham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["THE OVECHKIN EXPERIMENT IS OVER!" - some NBC analyst that actually gets paid to say dumb crap. https://t.co/4TwbWLF8jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine STICK TO SPOR... wait... what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo @Steve_Dangle @AdamWylde  @JesseBlake It's time to update. https://t.co/G9xWZwk1cI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone. https://t.co/7k7wGESj20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde You answered this question with your previous tweet... https://t.co/gLvK6icr9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElyseBee @Steve_Dangle I'd take 36 fake followers over the 2 real ones I got... those jackasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodsfallDC Hey... so can I just have your (I'm assuming) Indesign file? K, thanks bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just said "What is Jonathan Taylor Thomas up to anyway?" out loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodsfallDC You're missing me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyJayJRogers If Vrana is with Eller and Connolly does that mean Wilson is on with Kuzy and Ovi?...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Howdy, is there any plan or way to show playlists on the website/webplayer?  Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NerdAlert: How does one go about finding a #DM in #DC? #DnD #DnD5e #DungeonsAndDragons #RPG #Tabletop #pathfinder #dungeonmaster #GM #role]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinfung Haha. We all read/watch for its realistic physics!
I'm all for the pointing out the plot holes of last season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I see a Subway commericial for that carved turkey I think of @davelozo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @Rennfest you get to be whoever you want to be. https://t.co/juP2cy6kG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJC_95 @ElyseBee This.
And maybe Luther or The Following (meh)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_po @Ryan_Deem @ElyseBee @holtbyfanclub @HeyJayJRogers @AWallace39 Let's all compromise and once #Jagr2DC happens... we elect him to host SNL on our behalf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimFilipovic I was constantly waiting to hear #Caps... maybe because my wounds are just soo fresh, I just figured they'd be so much lower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodsfallDC My friends &amp; I had our first taste of D&amp;D last night at @labyrinthdc. It went awesome. Know anyone in #DC (NE) that wants to DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Deem No. But I did speak "Friend" to try and enter... it didn't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tldmPodcast Great.  I ruined the intro battle by making a Dragon roar near the wolves to scare them away.  Later I put half the rats to sleep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a success. I killed everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nominrath @DnDDomain Why Light?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight l'm playing my first ever #dnd session. Any tips for a level one #wizard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the people tweeting @GRRMspeaking saying"get back to writing",when the books are done do they think that it was their tweet that helped?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde As a #caps fan to the core, I can't support anything from #Pittsburgh.
Come visit, I'll show you @Abbey_Burger / #CamdenYards / @brewersart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde if you're every back in Baltimore, I'll show you "why baltimore?" Jerk face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoorQuentyn yeah but what is "is"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't everyone on the internet act like they are a colorblind person putting on those glasses for the first time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear #innovative &amp; #green &amp; #LEED (&amp; other buzz words) people. Why not figure out a way for buildings to stop throwing away rolls of TP? https://t.co/xvC1ylC4wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davosfingers As a #ASOIAF and a #Hockey person you might enjoy the work of @kat326 
https://t.co/EG7Y57P20a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @2jmarshall: I just backed Instant Film Photo Bus: Capturing moments in time on @Kickstarter https://t.co/t5n1ZMfgDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But like... how? #thezonecast https://t.co/oLGyTdlPK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine Me. Asking the hard hitting questions in the comments. https://t.co/M3RA5mJyiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluthmodelhome The doctor approves. https://t.co/HzZayBgawI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #MBMBAM fans, why isn't anyone dressed up as blue apron or mvmt watches or Casper mattresses??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh @griffinmcelroy doesn't have a head. And is a protrait video. I failed. #MBMBaM https://t.co/Wo1WprFKKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do 1000 high fives make a high five thousand? @travismcelroy #mbmbam https://t.co/YIbdpvPAWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I worry for @JustinMcElroy's hand strength. https://t.co/a4Q4UkxF8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in line for #MBMBAM is reading each other's tweets but we are all too socially awkward to talk to each other. #dc #friendship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reggiesfriend @GodsfallDC D.C.? Let's party.
I'm doing my first dnd on the 20th... unless you need a noob for a game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett you at mbmbam tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @JustinMcElroy, In preparation for tomorrow's @MBMBaM #DC show my wife just yelled out SQUAD! She's never heard a #munchsquad. #MBMBaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's say I'm a 230 lbs 32yr old man, and then there's a 120 lbs 27yr old woman. Should we really both be taking the same amount of #NyQuil?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>