<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs March Three: Weekend Favs March ThreeThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend blog post ro... http://t.co/3MLw1kI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Facebook mobile ad breakthrough? | Precision Health Media ad network | 7 steps to measure SEO: Mob... http://t.co/je9rXmHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before You Opt for Reach Generator: Get the Facts: Facebook's Reach Generator is intriguing some brands, eager t... http://t.co/LkoNgYMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPad Users are the Same Everywhere. Their Campaigns Too: About 1% of all Russian internet users connect via the ... http://t.co/eg9BozRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Your Customers Know Who You Want for President?: The Presidential election will be an increasingly unavoida... http://t.co/FJOpJ3u4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Brad Gruno Ended in the Chips: The failed telecom executive became a raw foodie, started whipping up chips i... http://t.co/Ro2WX7LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Zynga | AT&T caps unlimited plans | iPad 3: Gaming:

A friend in need, supplied by Zynga.

Privacy... http://t.co/ihQaiKY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser Urges People to Track Their Bud, Via QR Code: Budweiser has introduced a digital campaign called "Trac... http://t.co/BzqHgNuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Facebook ad growth | Foursquare plans | Tablet reading now the norm: Social Media:

Substantial growth... http://t.co/1Pw4hBik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Leap Year’ Season Two Gets Go-Ahead – Hiscox Orders Second Series Of Hulu Web Video Hit: I’m writing this on Fe... http://t.co/9ZF5bvH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Facebook | Microsoft's Metro app store | $500B Apple market cap: Social Media:

Facebook debuts Of... http://t.co/zvcTzRNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DataSift Asks Marketers What They Would Do Two Years Of Twitter Data: Twitter search is a frustrating thing. It ... http://t.co/M5NRQtfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is TechCrunch Following the Aol Way Into Oblivion?: I rarely, if ever, write about other blogs. As you know, if ... http://t.co/2YBwsEK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Adds Follow Button for Companies: If you’re in the Business to Business business, then you need a new L... http://t.co/QZWtvFMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IAB Rewards Mobile Ad Unit Innovation: A smartphone is not a small computer. A tablet is not flat laptop. And ye... http://t.co/dvIMkd4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's Privacy Policy Change Almost Here. Will Users Revolt?: March 1 is almost here and so far, nothing, not ... http://t.co/oUaqiHGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AOL Launches Self-serve Ad Platform: AOL has launched a beta of its self-serve ad platform with agencies Digitas... http://t.co/ry2ooBUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainstream Media’s Take on Google+ v. Facebook: Google+ is not doing well if you listen to this report from the ... http://t.co/dfz7mbwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Kinect on the shopping cart | iPad 3 speculation | Windows Phone in 23 more countries: Mobile Comp... http://t.co/cTfRa3aL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Chief Says His Tablets Will be ‘Winning’ in 2012: From high-end iPads that do everything but make you a ... http://t.co/pSZJocTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another fMC Announcement: Reduced Character Count on Facebook Ads: Facebook is expected to announce a new charac... http://t.co/Y9ylO0SB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Tips to Inspire Innovation at Your Small Business: More innovation is needed for a business to thrive in to... http://t.co/WbcOajOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony Music Boss Loves YouTube, Hates GEMA: Wait, what? There’s a music label executive who thinks the Internet i... http://t.co/U9bedm3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the JOBS Act Mean More Surprises Like Groupon's?: The daily deal site’s recent accounting trouble is prompt... http://t.co/Oh4FIBgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building An Email Contact List Via Offline Venues: Building up an email marketing contact list is not an exclusi... http://t.co/LmnKek9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: iAD revenue share increases | Consumer Reports likes new iPad | OMGPOP: Online Ad Market:

Apple activ... http://t.co/Zs3CqwsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Single Most Important Way to Get More Out of the New Facebook: The Single Most Important Way to Get More Out... http://t.co/yhuTDMQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading List: 10 Insightful Books for Career Changers: Where to find step-by-step basics and inspiration if you'... http://t.co/eW2AcEUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisteria Is Stuff That Works: Wisteria Is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
This is a new S... http://t.co/wjVDXnj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Entrepreneur Craig Newmark on Charity, Collaboration and Being Cranky: A year after launching a web netwo... http://t.co/ypDugQIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Avoid the Biggest Bookkeeping Mistake (Video): Accountat Mark Kohler shares tips for how to steer clear o... http://t.co/Hbhwj9qB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs March Thirty One: Weekend Favs March Thirty OneThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend bl... http://t.co/z0691uOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: Come On Seriously, Are You Actually Making Money?: People on the internet like to talk a lot. And if... http://t.co/H2UPZQK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiration Alley: Miracle-Gro Meets FarmVille: Miracle-Gro is the latest brand to add their logo to Zynga’s Far... http://t.co/tlHCvBwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunkin' Donuts Launches Integrated Hispanic Campaign: Dunkin' Donuts is launching its campaign and tagline— "Ame... http://t.co/WRqIucp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Facebook Getting Serious About Search?: Facebook v. Google is no longer a David v. Goliath story. In fact, it... http://t.co/AqusGtWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kentucky Businesses Brace for NCAA Final Four Madness: Here are three tips for how you can prepare for a sudden ... http://t.co/0evnkg3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small-Exporter Support Facing Uncertainty: The charter for the Export-Import Bank is set to expire at the end of... http://t.co/lI1QqoNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&A: Founder of 'Sh-tter,' the Tweets-to-Toilet Paper Company: Australian entrepreneur David Gillespie on his ne... http://t.co/ButiXseG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Not Your Imagination: There is an Unfollow Bug in Twitter: Twitter has admitted that there is a "follow bug... http://t.co/OYjexbmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find the Right Person to Manage Social Media (Video): The key is choosing someone who embraces social par... http://t.co/ZC67Kgtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning to Network: Organized Study vs. Winging It: Do men and women network in different ways? Here's a look a... http://t.co/yciIUGmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retailers Choose Low Prices Over Discount Days and Coupons: There’s a shocking, new trend sweeping across the na... http://t.co/TRVdggMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Zuckerberg in China | Cisco buys ClearAccess | Siri: Global:

Zuckerberg's China trip sparks Faceb... http://t.co/QtttWhSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a Grip on Medicine's Slippery Price Tag: The cost of common health tests can vary by hundreds of dollars... http://t.co/1HXGoKCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Campaign Aims to Make One Follower Famous for a Day: Twitter is gearing up to make followers extremely f... http://t.co/IRFcn7xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Pinterest clamps down on spam | Apple's 4G refund | Free, profitable video games: Security:

Pinterest... http://t.co/In8ElLFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Competition: A Choice Activity for Young Entrepreneurs: In the final days of March Madness, do you feel like you... http://t.co/RnpFo9hS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adrian Grenier's New, Retro Beer Requires a Can Opener: The actor explains why he co-founded a Seattle brewery http://t.co/1EaoBRM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: SMB security bootcamp | Obama on Pinterest | Facebook, Google hiring trends: Security:

AVG launch... http://t.co/0yZRF7Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey Says Marketers See Social Media as an Experiment: Would you say that social media is an accepted and nece... http://t.co/vHUAUM5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search Marketers Eye Reported Commenting System from Google: Google is expected to announce the launch of a new ... http://t.co/Ib85voqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fracking Boom Divides Small Businesses: While some small companies benefit from the growth of fracking, a contro... http://t.co/w293JQS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How You Make Money: How You Make MoneyThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
Your business doesn’t really care h... http://t.co/j7ukiT4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Play Goes into Hard Sell Mode: Google Play was officially released earlier this month but I only just got... http://t.co/M1jLu2mS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, an Espresso Machine for the Car: The Handpresso Auto, available in France, brings espresso brewing from... http://t.co/TMIr7RiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FTC Releases Final Consumer Privacy Recommendations: If you have some free time today, the FTC just released a n... http://t.co/08yB5ECZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arby's Joins Plink's Facebook Credits Loyalty Program: The Facebook Credits-based loyalty program launched by Pl... http://t.co/u4uC9u0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese Court Orders Google to Suspend Autocomplete Feature: Google’s international legal team sure must be hop... http://t.co/spwVMhpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Pilgrim’s Spring Refresh!: You may have noticed that we look a little different today. While many use ... http://t.co/23ANSFx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Unconventional Guide to Public Speaking (Video): Entrepreneur's Esquire Guy columnist Ross McCammon offers hi... http://t.co/mrWAXLUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Moleskine Notebook Is Stuff That Works: My Moleskine Notebook Is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape... http://t.co/8ZuN90Fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clues to Find the Perfect Path for Your Personality: Still looking for your true calling? Author Nicholas Lore o... http://t.co/IXff9Cdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs March Twenty Four: Weekend Favs March Twenty FourThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend ... http://t.co/8fjvYHYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Take Your Business to the Next Level (Video): Many business owners dream about getting their products int... http://t.co/nuPiNaxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FTC Continues Crackdown on Sites that Sell Bogus Health Product; Legitimate Pharma Companies Still Floundering: ... http://t.co/wOoRaztQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B2B Marketers’ Social Media Efforts Have Much Room to Mature: Let’s just start by saying that the B2C approach v... http://t.co/IsORa1Mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Small-Business Lessons from 'The Hunger Games': The fictional heroine Katniss Everdeen provides some surviv... http://t.co/S1d8BByi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Remedies's Hip Pharma: With hip packaging, absurd videos, and youth targeting, pharmaceutical startup Help ... http://t.co/2T5FK7vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Carroll Turns Fabric Into an Energy Source: The Wake Forest physicist has created Power Felt, which genera... http://t.co/aYqoSUt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Nudges Viewers to Watch More Live TV: I love television. That’s not new news to anyone who regularly read... http://t.co/eMxAsXJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game-maker Bows to Power of Social Media: The ending to Mass Effect 3 left many gamers disgruntled–to the point ... http://t.co/8CIaVJqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MarketingVox News &amp; Trends:  http://t.co/undbcUUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston's 'Innovation District' Eagerly Awaits More Innovators: For some, Mayor Menino's Innovation District is s... http://t.co/mRjqLEKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google reconsiders mobile payment | Zynga buys OMGPop | 4G: Mobile Payments:

Google reconsiders m... http://t.co/Q6sQ4xg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revlon Tries Out the Story as Ad Format: Story telling has become the latest ad format—both in the digital realm... http://t.co/RvxWfUbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Ways You Can Avoid IP Theft: Here's how to keep your small firm's big digital assets out of the crosshairs ... http://t.co/3pqjx9eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to Lose Friends in Social Media? Be Political: What have you heard a million and one times in business? Don... http://t.co/BXCcqhim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JOBS Act Hits Delays in Senate: A bipartisan bundle of legislation aimed at increasing entrepreneurs' ability to... http://t.co/57Fkv5N3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Say Email is Best but Could Be Better: What do you do when your best isn’t good enough? This is the di... http://t.co/m0TQ0kwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six Design Mistakes to Avoid in Your Store: Careful planning can head of potential problems with your retail spa... http://t.co/KFs0JQh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should You Be the Leader of Your Small Business?: Some entrepreneurs are born to start businesses, but not all o... http://t.co/RoPRsf86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Points Out 5 Common SEO Mistakes [VIDEO]: It appears that Google may now be getting deeper into the busin... http://t.co/S5uUyK75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overdue Jaffe Sharing on Entrepreneurship and Flipping Funnels: I had the pleasure recently of doing interviews ... http://t.co/YR8kq3U3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: iPad sells 3M | In-app ad security | No plans for Xbox: Security:

Researchers question security o... http://t.co/da9VkIXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Ways to Make Your App Stand Out (Video): Andrew Cohen of Brainscape makes dozens of educational apps. The ... http://t.co/slVYDt26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally CNN is breaking the story about the Silversea cruise crash we were on: http://t.co/A3IkAe5m - I reported about it on Friday ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Changes to Google Search; TLD Not Part of the Mix: Google shows little sign of letting up on its changes to... http://t.co/D3tCz5vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: iPad 3 | Silverpop acquires CoreMotives | Google tablet: iPad 3:

New iPad 32GB, 4G version cost 9% mo... http://t.co/HAamrp50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Persol is Stuff that Works: Persol is Stuff that WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
This is a new Sunda... http://t.co/Y4ZSN0sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs March Seventeen: Weekend Favs March SeventeenThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend blog... http://t.co/AdAZFkC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Adds 19,000 Episodes Of Indian Television Shows, Leaving Rest Of World Behind: YouTube racks up over 19,... http://t.co/nR79nfwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Maintain a Positive Attitude As a Business Owner (Video): Running your own business can be a rollercoaste... http://t.co/UStSZuxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major League Baseball Debuts Lists of Social Media Do's and Don'ts for Players: Major League Baseball has rolled... http://t.co/tmAvk7Mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Curious Plea to Stay with Their Browser: Browser wars are a touchy subject, especially around the fo... http://t.co/oMj1jqlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS: Italian cruise liner Silversea Silver Shadow in Vietnam just crashed into another ship.  We're on board http://t.co/Uiz28ssr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCAA March Madness Google Earth Style: Google has given college hoops fans a neat video of 3D renderings of site... http://t.co/Ke3luZqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Review: 'The Power of Habit', by Charles Duhigg: How companies can profit by understanding and tweaking our... http://t.co/CWgUAE0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As SXSW Ends, Austin Ventures Goes to Work: The venture fund is focused on local talent, but has designs on Sili... http://t.co/zAXVH9xm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Microfinance for You?: Here's how a $25 loan can change the world. (But do your homework before investing.) http://t.co/p8AHTluG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>