<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: Our government has indicted 19 Witches and 5 have plead guilty. https://t.co/wwSQkEdN8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWorld: Sridevi: Bollywood superstar dies at 54 of cardiac arrest https://t.co/f4YW6UIaL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Daily_Express: #Sridevi dead: Bollywood actress dies aged 54 following cardiac arrest: https://t.co/GnrDFNGTXa https://t.co/Wc76OpXVUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahchad_: I’m a junior. https://t.co/P9clE1ks5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ApplyToBU: Admission to BU will not be jeopardized should your school levy a penalty for participating in peaceful protests, such as th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BostonGlobe: BU joins the list of schools that say applicants won't be penalized for joining in on gun protests https://t.co/WBPhMN5vJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Seychelles preserves swathes of marine territory in debt-for-nature deal https://t.co/robYZsuxGM https://t.co/whhaWvT8Jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_cingraham: 67% public support, per Quinnipiac. Gun violence researchers rate it as one of the most effective policies for preventing m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_cingraham: Rubio says the 1994 assault weapons ban "failed." Absolutely untrue. "Compared with the 10-year period before the ban, the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Donald Trump Jr. says he likes India’s poor people because they "smile" https://t.co/OpWYotwMBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#freshsnow #sundaystroll #SundayMorning @CityOfBoston https://t.co/0t5fEcIJoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: “They said I was very handsome...for an Indian” https://t.co/3Nhzh6aiXW From @1843mag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Indian artist challenging 'dirty taboos' on Instagram - BBC News https://t.co/8lirx9OMTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeo: Some animals change coats in the winter to match the snow—but what if there's no snow and you can’t take off your coat? https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahmccammon: Broward Sheriff offering to help south FL residents who want to turn in guns in the wake of the deadly #ParklandSchoolSh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @united4wildlife: #DidYouKnow Pangolins are the most trafficked mammal in the world?

Spread the word that pangolins are #WorthMoreAlive…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @madeleine: The only thing more stunning than the scale of Russian interference uncovered today is the fact that an American President i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aardvarsk: There are so many ways to call someone an idiot. In the south, you say “bless their heart.” In LA you say “they’re on their…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_cingraham: Support for an assault weapons ban:
Among all Americans: 68%
Among gun owners: 48%
Source: 2017 Pew Research Center survey…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: The Trump-Cotton-McConnell immigration plan couldn't even get 40 votes. 

They are the minority.

Their ideas are the extreme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gelliottmorris: Here’s what the data say: Experts and the public agree on a wide variety of policies to help fix gun violence. So why i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_cingraham: The shooter used an AR-15. An assault weapons ban -- even a ban on high-capacity magazines -- could have prevented it or mi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_cingraham: Some Las Vegas victims "survived on the ground for 60 to 90 seconds, their heart continued to beat, the blood filled up int…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: “Since Columbine in 1999, there have been 25 fatal, active school shootings at elementary and high schools in America” —…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TerrierHockey: GOAL!!!! Jordan deposits a rebound at the right crease to double Team USA's lead. #BUSA #TeamUSA https://t.co/JWKNbsAz1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CC20rake: Clutch liked the book. Phew! He's a pretty tough critic!
https://t.co/A2R2cbtdpN https://t.co/93scp9Yc47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidfrum: Risk-averse corporate entities making highly visible contributions to formerly controversial causes is exactly what profound…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: President Trump's order would ban most transgender troops from serving. https://t.co/M5gh3zmENv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZekeJMiller: Statement from the Press Secretary Regarding Service by Transgender Individuals in the Military https://t.co/3gQ0vqDTkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Today, 17-year-old Draylen Mason would have learned that he had been offered one of 130 spots at the renowned Oberlin Con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: UPDATE: French PM says incident in southern France appears to be 'terrorist act' https://t.co/Ocg6XqyoAx https://t.co/YeIDXWFS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Police union official says a hostage-taker has killed at least one person inside a supermarket in southern France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: Addendum to this - focusing on what staff does instead of what POTUS does is what he prefers. It diffuses the criticism of h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @krassenstein: The DOW has just closed, down 717 points.  This is the 5th worst daily point decline in American history.  

Trump also o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewYorker: A cartoon by Peter Kuper. https://t.co/i3Sj0IP1cv https://t.co/gBimCLMPzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: ONE. WEEK. AGO. https://t.co/0yISggIOGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: BREAKING: John Bolton to replace H.R. McMaster as national security adviser https://t.co/z2wHobvC7C https://t.co/eq7jdO7qSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: JUST IN: Dow closes down more than 700 points, S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq end down more than 2 percent after Trump tariff action https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: White House takes step to restrict Chinese investment and put tariffs on $50B in Chinese imports for stealing technology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnlyInBOS: Such a Toby move to not start snowing yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Is settling down an outmoded concept? These modern nomads think so https://t.co/OVdzMiexGW From @1843mag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWorld: Families of IS India victims learned of deaths on television https://t.co/ixz0P62KOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fahrenthold: In Jan., 80% of the $ that the @gop spent on catering/ballroom rentals went to @realdonaldtrump. In Feb? It was 86%. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @APCentralRegion: Authorities say the latest explosion to hit #Austin was caused by an "incendiary device" and is not related to the ser…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisWeekABC: Sen. McCain on Pres. Trump congratulating Putin on election win: “An American president does not lead the Free World by co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BostonGlobe: Trump calls Putin to congratulate him on reelection https://t.co/IscMErmQ79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: Shooting reported at Southern Maryland high school
https://t.co/Wy8fPSPnv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wef: They'll help investigate gender-specific crimes. Learn more: https://t.co/bzfZfv9yj8 https://t.co/tI1X6zxiGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: Sudan, the world’s last northern white rhino, dies https://t.co/bMju2Cfaxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: 'Socially responsible' investors reassess Facebook ownership https://t.co/HBrTBHreez https://t.co/cQArleFONm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Mississippi governor signs bill banning abortions after 15 weeks https://t.co/0yNPpCFxOd https://t.co/LKWYeeCoNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: Supreme Court turns down GOP request to stop Pennsylvania congressional map
https://t.co/67pLwu9n2w https://t.co/TUi7gF9X3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeoTravel: Known as the fish-eyed goddess because of her perfectly shaped eyes, Meenakshi represents fertility and love for Hindus h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinWolfers: I’ve never seen a better graphical representation of the reproduction of inequality and racial gaps. So good. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWorld: John McEnroe paid more than Martina Navratilova by BBC https://t.co/ERKaNsaUmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NPR: Facebook has suspended the data analytics firm the Trump campaign relied on during the 2016 election, saying the firm improperly r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PreetBharara: Yes https://t.co/Fpha3djATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @renato_mariotti: THREAD: Why does it matter that Andrew McCabe wrote memos memorializing his conversations with Trump shortly after the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidaxelrod: If you had any doubt about whether the McCabe firing was an act of retribution, here is a flagrant victory dance from the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BFriedmanDC: If you don't know who he is, McCaffrey served as a senior White House appointee for five years. When he retired from the A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markberman: “Trump has sometimes expressed confusion about what agencies and secretaries are in charge of what duties, a senior adminis…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Trump has decided to remove his national security adviser: Washington Post https://t.co/NxxtojV2ip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: In a first, U.S. blames Russia for cyber attacks on energy grid https://t.co/ewhuI9B0f6 https://t.co/VUUMHNAA2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: In joint statement, US, UK, French and German leaders agree Russia was behind nerve agent attack on former spy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kairyssdal: In fundraising speech, Trump says he made up trade claim in meeting with Justin Trudeau - The Washington Post https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wxdam: 17 people die in a high school and a month later there's a nationwide protest to get the attention of lawmakers.

One dog dies o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BostonGlobe: Did you know that Near East was started out of an Armenian grocery store in Worcester? https://t.co/27zssL22ft https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for parade day! #Boston https://t.co/6iLvK6eqZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: A Facebook group of ex-sellers from LulaRoe, Amway, and other multilevel marketing companies is exposing how these busin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Philippines Duterte to issue notice of withdrawal from ICC https://t.co/dV2FumB5YT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Stephen Hawking dies at the age of 76 - Press Association https://t.co/eSVT902D9h https://t.co/sRmcvF5t8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nate_Cohn: Alright folks, we've shut the needle down. As mentioned earlier, Westmoreland County isn't going to produce precinct results…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: YouTube to display Wikipedia blurbs alongside conspiracy videos https://t.co/HWoMfx5TfS https://t.co/W8NWdEeywA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanTrende: People getting riled up about whether Lamb wins or loses are missing the point(s). This district is history, and Saccone wi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BostonGlobe: Producers of "The Crown" admitted Tuesday that Queen Elizabeth actress Claire Foy was paid less than the actor who played…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Pompeo, who has raised doubts about climate change, would lead State during key climate negotiations https://t.co/6cfWY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimsciutto: Breaking: Nikolai Glushkov, a Russian émigré who the UK refused to extradite to Russia on fraud charges, died in his home i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @APWestRegion: The U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement spokesman in San Francisco says he's resigning over misleading statements fr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessicaYellin: A day after Tillerson says UK nerve agent attack “clearly” came from Russia, and Russia “must face consequences” — he’s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasonKander: Rex Tillerson, recipient of the Russian Order of Friendship, canned by Trump for being too tough on Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PJCrowley: Not only does @realDonaldTrump agree to a meeting with North Korean leader #KimJongUn without any preparatory work, now he w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForeignPolicy: Here’s a rundown of Pompeo’s CIA legacy: https://t.co/mmTgER4QjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?! This entire administration needs to stop by @BUPardeeSchool IR 271]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewYorker: The passage of a Florida gun-control bill raising the legal age for purchases of long guns to 21 and imposing a three-day wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Trump blocks Broadcom’s $117 billion bid for Qualcomm out of national security concerns, a highly unusual move https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: BREAKING: White House says it’s blocking Broadcom bid for rival Qualcomm
https://t.co/uGcAIsWgOC https://t.co/RSRM23tNOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Tillerson says ex-spy's poisoning in UK 'clearly came from Russia,' vows it 'will trigger a response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jodikantor: Waitresses on the brutal logic of putting up with harassment by customers:

"I needed the $20 tip."

“A significant portion…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: MORE: Britain's May says after suspected poisoning of Skripal, Britain will stand ready to take more extensive measures agains…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Forbes: The story behind the MIT report that dragged Uber through a PR disaster: https://t.co/LLIHJieEZF https://t.co/02O8q7z3I8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pronounced_ing: Lady behind me told me I dropped my coat. Man behind me said he’d wanted to say something but was afraid—“You know, sex…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: Just to be clear on what happened just now:

Trump said he won 52% of women, but he was apparently referring to  *white*…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Powerful new Serena Williams ad for Nike: "I’ve never been the right kind of woman. Oversized and overconfident. Too mean…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy as a snail... #bdaydinner @LESPALIER  w/@aconnnnna #another35years https://t.co/4i3GHulKD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: President Trump pardons a Navy sailor who took photos of classified areas inside a submarine and served a year in prison. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrookingsInst: Male same-sex couples tend to earn more than heterosexual couples, while female same-sex couples make about $5,000 less…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: President Trump getting Washington military parade - but without tanks. https://t.co/sbc9dwuFKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: NRA files federal lawsuit challenging Florida gun-safety bill https://t.co/3RAU7FVd3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CincinnatiZoo: Fiona thinks you’re cute too, but it’s what’s on the inside that counts! Your DNA will decide if you’re the one for our…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jezebel: Mississippi is one step away from banning abortion after 15 weeks https://t.co/cyqF5WT54E https://t.co/pMAH7MuBcu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>