<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Administration Proposes Corporate Tax Rate Cut to 28%: The Obama administration called for reducing the co... http://t.co/a8BxpIqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast’s New Streampix is About Giving Customers What They Want: Comcast has a new video streaming service call... http://t.co/GnBxDr7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bing Debuts Linked Pages: Social and search have taken another step toward each other: Bing is rolling out a new... http://t.co/FpiQmJdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Hot Export Markets for Small Businesses: A look at a range of export opportunities, as well as challenges, fo... http://t.co/5WXvpgmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Stages of the Content Hourglass: 7 Stages of the Content HourglassThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
The n... http://t.co/t7kyDj0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Social Study: Men Get Personal, Women Talk Shop: Women may be tops when it comes to communicating but online... http://t.co/AAjtk2W1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Will Hit 500M Registered Users on Wednesday: Twitter will reach 500 million registered users on Wednesda... http://t.co/Nw1hqCIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan UK Billboard Campaign Takes Gender Targeting to New Level: Plan UK is launching a campaign to highlight the... http://t.co/KlPqyMAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks’s Schultz Expands Small Biz Loan Fund: Since the fall, Starbucks has collected about $2 million in don... http://t.co/sglUIKiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphone Data Should Tell Marketers to Get Mobile Now: Smartphones are not the wave of the future. They are th... http://t.co/Jh9HsKVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google and IE privacy | SkyDrive and Windows 8 | Angry Birds teams with NASA: Privacy:

Google byp... http://t.co/EbFSFj5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Stars for Microsoft’s People Powered Stories Ads: Social advertising is all about using the comments and re... http://t.co/B1ESBGRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burberry Steps Up Social Media Creds with Animated GIFs in Tweetwalk: Burberry has been pushing the luxury brand... http://t.co/wZuoA9hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adafruit Targets Tinkerers with 'Open Source':  http://t.co/Dj1uJobB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Eye Digital Advances in the Car. Highway Officials Look to Head Off More Developments: Marketers have ... http://t.co/vqSg14N4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dividing the Family Fortune: Passing on the family fortune can be tricky when it's tied up in a small business. ... http://t.co/Be5zOJDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Mobile marketing rises in importance | Fire eats into iPad's market share | Barclays targets PayPal: M... http://t.co/PwiZcp70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's With All the Interest in Pinterest?: Here are six reasons you might want to try the wildly popular online... http://t.co/hZ4mmPHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbuck’s Schultz Expands Small Biz Loan Fund: Since the fall, Starbucks has collected about $2 million in dona... http://t.co/iPq1Yvgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbuck’s Schultz Expands Small Biz Loan Fund: Since the fall, Starbucks has collected about $2 million in dona... http://t.co/jzGfTxUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Former Bank Analyst's Thing for Bling: Charlie Chanaratsopon left the cubicle behind and built an empire found... http://t.co/hCshypF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Timelines for Brands? Time to Start Thinking Inside the Box: On February 29, Facebook will be conductin... http://t.co/70LCCIk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Matter What, Google Can't Put Those Questions about Engagement to Rest: Ever since Google+ launched, question... http://t.co/ee8uqWqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Usability: Effectively Turning Communication Into Action: This post comes from our Social Media Channe... http://t.co/eZHdZuMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There Can Be No Real Commitment Until You Surrender All Doubt: There Can Be No Real Commitment Until You Surrend... http://t.co/e3VB9SIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elections, The Olympics and the End of the World: What’s Next for Social Video: “In February 2011, Volkswagen’s ... http://t.co/qwBbwKuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Your Business Survive Without You?: Seventy-five percent of small-business owners have no real succession ... http://t.co/RJqHjOXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Entrepreneur's Top Leadership Challenges -- and How to Overcome Them: As their companies expand, business own... http://t.co/ngU66IoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Salary Guide [Infographic]: One of the most interesting exercises anyone can undertake is discoveri... http://t.co/TdvesCyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Inkling | iCloud grows by 15M users in 21 days | Amazon Prime falls: Publishing:

Inkling introduc... http://t.co/jZCRTnvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop the Question. It Will Help Your Business (Opinion): Getting married is a good idea if you're an entrepreneur... http://t.co/sDDRJo9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QR Codes Move into the School Room: It appears that Millennials are not drawn to QR Codes, but the generation af... http://t.co/yKWY2HFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Ways to Get Investors to Listen to Your Business Pitch: Wooing investors is a challenge even for entrepreneur... http://t.co/j4hVjpp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google's Motorola deal | Apple purchases | Tumblr: Legal/Regulatory:

Europe OKs Google's $12.5B M... http://t.co/Lb83WnQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real Men Like Mobile Ads: File this one under, I’m not sure what to make of it, but here goes.
eMarketer reports... http://t.co/3rNAlVuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterest: Online Marketers New Job Board?: Clearly Pinterest is becoming a social media site of strong interest... http://t.co/OGx5nDBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the Grammys in LA http://t.co/Ve2rPVL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Visa Policy May Hurt Luxury Retailers:  http://t.co/dTB5Gv4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transaction Emails as Marketing Channel? Yes, But Tread Carefully: Transaction emails—that is, those emails that... http://t.co/4uULND0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Do Not Track tools | Apple readies iPad 3 apps | Gamers love to hate Sony: Mobile Computing:

Apple is... http://t.co/i5F6QG28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrome for Android Beta Arrives: If you live in the right place and are running Android 4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich)... http://t.co/yBZIcnIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Adds Viacom To Prime Instant Video But Isn’t Planning Standalone Netflix Rival: Watch out, Netflix, you h... http://t.co/VcnkYmC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Users Say Social Networkers Are Kind and Caring: Need a shot of the milk of human kindness? Spend a ... http://t.co/6JwanCD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is Easy to Fudge Social Media Numbers: Google has been taken to task for being obtuse with its engagement met... http://t.co/kLpG6Onh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groupon’s First Public Quarter Is No Deal for Investors: We haven’t talked about Groupon in a while. There is ac... http://t.co/dWaTGgZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Mogul Christopher Burch Talks Business: As Fashion Week kicks off, we sat down with the man behind brand... http://t.co/o9gKNoAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day Shoppers Plan for a Budget Holiday: It’s February. Love is in the air and the chocolates are pil... http://t.co/8SoocIfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Path CEO a Zuckerberg Disciple?: Today, the fledgling social network Path was forced to issue an apology base... http://t.co/sEujE8In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions Emerge about Pinterest's Linking Tactics: Pinterest may be facing user backlash in the wake of the new... http://t.co/dCs0i3Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Pinterest hits 10M monthly uniques | Amazon, Viacom close deal | Yammer closes $50M funding: Social Me... http://t.co/YxCWPBTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Marketing Tips from the Social Commerce Summit: Right now, some of the top internet entrepreneurs are in New Y... http://t.co/5uGZYO8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redbox Hits Netflix with a Strong Right Hook: We have a Blockbuster store in our town that is still open for bus... http://t.co/BQmfvVIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's Panda May Be a Real-time Proposition: Reading between the lines of Google’s latest search update, Barry... http://t.co/YZCLWDef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Broader Corporate Adoption of Apple’s iOS Invite Trouble?: One of the attractive feature of Apple products ... http://t.co/35NLrVcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Privacy Tips [Infographic]: Online security and privacy will always be an issue. There is nothing that wi... http://t.co/9oaAgUcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Seeks Cuts Amid Regulations Debate:  http://t.co/y697TN71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: AOL won't kill IM | Broadband developments | Android tablets will rule by 2015: Productivity:

AOL... http://t.co/27IQGVNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bing Promotes Itself with Adam Lambert Twitter Campaign: Microsoft has booked American Idol alumni Adam Lambert ... http://t.co/iRIojoCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Posting a Net Loss Isn't a Bad Thing Come Tax Time (Video): Accountant Mark Kohler explains how you can make... http://t.co/o0Clr0kH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why You Might Not Upgrade to Windows 8: The new operating system is so different from its predecessors, business... http://t.co/aRbwscfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google+ mobile gets refresh | Apple subpoenaed | Intel and pay TV: Mobile Computing:

Google+ mobi... http://t.co/XMV70sXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best T-shirts of SXSWi 2012: If you're headed to South By Southwest, you better have a hip T-shirt. Here's a... http://t.co/v8ZvGfyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cycle of Getting the Important Stuff Done: The Cycle of Getting the Important Stuff DoneThis content from: D... http://t.co/vCAtm9DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Twitter buys Posterous | SXSW | E-texbook revolution: Social Media:

Twitter buys Posterous (So you'd ... http://t.co/RhunLOGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Planning iTunes-Style Service For Content | TV Shows Available As Digital Downloads: The BBC could soon be s... http://t.co/uMAVczwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it Over for Location Check-in Apps?: Foursquare has always been the leader in the location check-in app battl... http://t.co/6I28N5Rt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside a Google Meeting of Search Engineers [VIDEO]: While I have not had the chance to watch all of this video ... http://t.co/h3mHcDk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Ad Budgets Follow Mobile Trends: With studies showing that there are 100 million smartphones in the US a... http://t.co/DVb7e3pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hierarchy of Getting The Important Stuff Done: The Hierarchy of Getting The Important Stuff DoneThis content... http://t.co/66PsPXQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SXSW 2012: The Sights, Sounds and Buzzwords (Video): Entrepreneur's Colleen DeBaise reports on the themes emergi... http://t.co/lZuW7MHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Blank on the Era of the Lean Startup: People are starting to realize that startups are not merely small ve... http://t.co/GUAyBhln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob’s Red Mill is Stuff That Works: Bob’s Red Mill is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
Thi... http://t.co/ZRqMcdVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Length Disney Shows Now On YouTube | 70-Plus Episodes Including Hannah Montana: You can now watch full-leng... http://t.co/bBYKeHgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find the 'Goosebumps' Moment in Your Startup Story: At this year's SXSW Interactive Festival, Austin entr... http://t.co/a0SL1Ve6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs March Ten: Weekend Favs March TenThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend blog post routin... http://t.co/G5EeGpUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Dermalogica is Giving Women Entrepreneurs a Boost: To alleviate many of the problems in the world, Dermalogi... http://t.co/5dutQ0Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterest Tops Twitter for Referral Traffic: If you’re on the web daily, you’ve heard of Pinterest. You’ve proba... http://t.co/FMrbcesq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nordstrom Custom Suit iPad App Shows Off B2B Strengths: Joseph Abboud and Nordstrom have launched a B2B iPad app... http://t.co/PfrQMtK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effective Networking Takes Commitment and Clarity: Effective Networking Takes Commitment and ClarityThis content... http://t.co/dXWvC6r6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the End Near for Traditional Advertising?: The future of advertising may already be written on a Facebook wall. http://t.co/kUdRcbk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nirav Tolia: Hyperlocal Boy Makes Good: The small-town native of Odessa, Tex., aims to master the so-called hype... http://t.co/HWQBz7ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HomeAway Co-founder on Curiosity, Influence and Rejection (Video): Brian Sharples shares his personal story and ... http://t.co/6KXXRt5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Videos' Promise Driving Digital Ads for Olympics: NBC Sports has more than doubled the $25 million in dig... http://t.co/XLWUQftx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: iPad 3 | iWallet patent | Eye-controlled games: iPad 3:

Apple's New iPad: 6 key features.

Apple upg... http://t.co/zu4pV40t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring the Next Generation: Hiring the Next GenerationThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
Marketing podcast w... http://t.co/Cg5n9dau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s Some Internet and Social Media Marketing Jobs If You Want Them: Each time we post about the jobs on our J... http://t.co/WjVhDtMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Apple TV Unveiled Alongside New iPad 3 | Not Much Has Changed, Except The Marketing: It looks exactly the sa... http://t.co/Fgiw6fza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New iPad and the Marketer: The new iPad and the Marketer. Sounds like the name of a modern fairytale but don... http://t.co/TmQbvyNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cosmopolitan Passes Digital Subscription Milestone: Print isn’t dead. . . yet, but we can start writing the obit... http://t.co/qH36Wd4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Yelp Still Strong-Arming Merchants?: For years the complaints about Yelp’s “sales” tactics have been heard. M... http://t.co/GpuIctOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play Is Latest Consolidation Effort from Google: Google continues its quest to integrate and consolidate the dis... http://t.co/PAUOHLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joining the (Cash) Mob to Help Main Street: Organizers are preparing for the first National Cash Mob Day, when t... http://t.co/UvAgw1Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google Play | New mobile ads | Guide to AdWorlds display: Mobile Marketing:

Former Apple executiv... http://t.co/85EBfHvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Networking Personas: Who Are Your Customers?: “Untangling the Social Web” is a multi-part whitepaper from... http://t.co/7Q7sbMtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: More about iPad 3 | Disney on YouTube | New tech coverage at Bloomberg: Mobile Computing:

iPad 3 will... http://t.co/2d95OEiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Bing launches search qualities series | iPad 3 rumor mill | Yahoo eyes layoffs: Search:

Keeping u... http://t.co/INQIDgwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialbakers Ranks Social Media’s Top Brands [Infographic]: Socialbakers, a social media statistics portal, has ... http://t.co/OXrsNKx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Companies Devote Scarce Marketing Resources to A New Comment Policy for Facebook?: Facebook’s changes, an... http://t.co/dlj1pVOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Google plans Siri-like assistant | Square iPad, analytics | Apple apps surpass 25B downloads: Search:
... http://t.co/q3ysl5J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Guild Guitar Is Stuff That Works: My Guild Guitar Is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
T... http://t.co/MsoHTXxP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>