<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/WFu7LSJQ1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/qN0EsTcYjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/Y0HJkHVKfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/BU2kCcfSwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/3ufsNxpInz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/bbeVXZwiKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/dcgagxN0XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/pdE76JODgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/nNWem8bwPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/ndOC15W577]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/KpYeED4paf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/29aKdlDF82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/GwPcWbXVZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ZUO1CbGopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/aQDuNd19Bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/0LMO3P3DuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/RJ7HXUyolN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/qWgCIB7HXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/tfG5xWNhsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/BiUuU9934p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/4pZUxdCZXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to roll a hard six. Commander William Adama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/dv8ODTKt5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/EEzLUbojgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/O8D0aEAa8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/yO7SopGpbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/J76SiTAdXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/99yKZJcXI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/ZOr8egEgK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/hVhQbcb3x0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/W0oSwZSVwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/REhfMjTB7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/sxF7BFLAie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/ZXHpswbzV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/xD5L0DtudI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ZUO1CbGopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/pwKrIPRsww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/WaSXabrogQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/eLPlQ1q6UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/M7HzQhGNcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/o3h8AGLBeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/MzP8UAy98p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/OVaJyZ7OpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/vD2G8xqXVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/nhOnwUAZrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/MvWcAfwWlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/Y4pVJt11To]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/NeGcBSBbSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/bgA9i9O8xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/YeAIscR2LU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>