<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell "Reaux Tide" & "99 Problems but the Kicker ain't one"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@darrenrovell: I'd pay $15 right now to skip the 4th quarter & get to the trophy presentation.” &gt; in for $20. #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MittRomney would love to fire these two offenses. 

#BCSChampionship #LSU #Bama #BCS #mitt2012 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murphymike could you wake up the woman over DG's right shoulder. She's missing all the excitement!  #nbcdebate  #nbcfbdebate #coffeeplease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibly the funniest moment of the campaign from @GovernorPerry. Way to own it. Well done. #NBCFBDebate #nb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get it! They're all morning people! #nbcfbdebate #piousbaloney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Perry only changed his tie. #NBCFBDebate #coffeeplease #nopartylikeaNHparty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know where you can get some of this delicious "pious bologna" that @newtgingrich is talking about? #yummywitheggs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crap!  Someone send me score of the BCS Title game!  Newt/Santo/Mitt all say it's on TV and I've been watching them pillow fight all night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@sportspickle The term is EARN beads...not get. You gotta EARN them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool, what's that Words w/ Friends ID again? “@2chambers: RT @alecbaldwin: Back on Twitter”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's awesome. @attackerman: The commanding officer of the @USNavy ship that saved the Iranian fishermen from pirates? Yeah, she's a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheFix: If Romney/Paul/Santorum all end up in a tie (basically), who does the tie go to? #iacaucus” &gt; everyone not running...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John King and his fancy map are gonna cause someone a seizure.  #slowdownchamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even this  Sparty still loves the Fab's unis... “@drewhenson7: And @jalenrose's iconic shorts”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackmon = Bad Man. #FiestaBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was Monte Balls before that run &gt; “@PaulPabst: Helmet to helmet contact...no flag. http://t.co/FHs0Hbua”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell &gt; Timothy 4:1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet Tebow could find $1.2 Trillion in cuts...

#TimmyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Te-boom goes the dynamite! #TimmyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@HotlineReid: Woah, it's an omen! New Hampshire Pick 3 winning numbers on Monday: 9-9-9 #cainmentum #HotlineSort”...is it rapture again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone knows of worse Customer Service in the UNIVERSE than @sprint please let me know so I can call them and be completely amazed by it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WolfpackAlan: RIGHT NOW YOU HAVE: 3 fingers behind your phone, your pinky tucked under for support and your scrolling with your thum ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[med/small/big 3 u mean “@Espngreeny: Move over Miami, we're the new Big 3.
Please help us fight cancer. 
http://t.co/zFnGajop
#Vfoundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brendan_Buck: That was a great event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see #BryceIn12 make the #ASG - but really hate to see @IanDesmond20 miss the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nationals: If this tweet gets 500 RTs we'll give away this #BryceIn12 signed bat! http://t.co/qoGAZsG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@WestWingReport: WWR wonders who will be hosting next year's July 4 party” ...thats easy...POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheRickWilson: What's with the blue text on @DRUDGE_REPORT?” &gt; happy birthday America...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RCNconnects &gt; In DC. Just lost cable 20 mins ago. Is this storm related?  ETA on having service back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the people who are having issues, I'm not having any problems w/ @twitter.  Oh wait...you cant see that.  #thatsucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Espngreeny: The trailer for that Chernobyl movie is incredibly disturbing...
#SleepWithLightOn” &gt; or just sleep in America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheRickWilson: Is #miamicannibal a thing yet?” &gt; Hearing about it in St. Lucia if that counts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@sportspickle: Brandon Weeden is so old ... He's actually going to play for Art Modell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nikegolf: Nice job @abergervt @MichaelCorcora @ndoyle - @TigerWoods is sporting these looks in his 5th green jacket quest http://t.c ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@AP: AP PHOTO: #Obama performs traditional O-H-I-O cheer with students after speaking at Ohio State &gt; MI tv ad right there @MittRomney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thesnews: Students starting to leave #CedarVillage, police say situation is under control and students have been cooperative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BellsBrewery: 5 days until Oberon - the Eccentric Cafe will open at 9 am on Monday http://t.co/Nn2ZyLON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goo Goo Goo! “@LuISmyname213: @KyleKizzier_DC that tweet amped me even more. Get ready! #NoLa”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeoThum: He is still on scholarship. #ncaa -  What's the big deal?! #LetDelvonPlay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeriouslybySeth: If the NCAA will let Ohio State have 2 coaching staffs for football, why won't they #LetDelvonPlay .......Seriously?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NCAA is ridiculous. #LetDelvonPlay
@JayBilas @MSU_Basketball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmartpolitico: And there it is: first MI poll - Mitchell - w Mitt up.  Just 2.  But it's the trend that counts This was the prob for ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#siriusxm 80's on 8. It's a #rickroll!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JimGaffigan: Women like bald spots, right?” - second only to a beer gut. Trust me...I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell: Shoot...190,000 followers is pretty solid to start with before you start a game...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@PaulPabst: Is Lance Armstrong not allowed to ever ride a bicycle again?” &gt; Yes. But with no seat as punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheFix: Todd Akin, winner. Of the "Worst Week in Washington", that is. http://t.co/Ey4vV5wu” &gt; that cat had the worst week anywhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogUnleashed these NFL guys watch film all week. Not just Sundays. No biggie for Strahan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyFratto “@richlatour: Empty chair needs a twitter account” &lt; you mean @akinemptychair ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[life changer &amp; don't forget @Uber_DC @BonnieBernstein: How cool. There's a parking app in Washington, DC, where you just log on and pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meaghanjameson: The man who you'll have to prove your worth to if you want to win my heart. http://t.co/Hxu9P3VD &gt; dig his shirt! Go green!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NATITUDE #NATITUDE #NATITUDE #NATITUDE #NATITUDE #NATITUDE #NATITUDE !!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salami!  #NATITUDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed the Giraffes! “@briancalley: Karagan is ready for the train ride at @binderparkzoo in #BattleCreek @PureMichigan http://t.co/xWuf2O48”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@_DoesNotSimply_: One does not simply smell what the Rock is cooking.” 

unless u are one of the millions....

@TheRock #TeamBringIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PureMichigan &gt; can't wait to get home for a week later today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sportspickle: A.J. Burnett just got Silver in the No-Hitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Spangled Banner = Victory. 

#olympicstoday #Olympics2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DavidMDrucker: What song do they play if an independent Olympian wins e gold?” &gt; Gotye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkCousins8: Have never practiced any sport in my entire life in the kind of heat we practiced in today &gt; welcome to DC in July/August!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't follow “@MSU_Football: Dantonio thinks 2 B1G division winners should get BCS bids But might think differently if MSU finished 2nd”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarioBatali &gt; Chef, my homemade pasta has a flour taste when cooked. What am I doing wrong or how can I fix it. #heymb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh snap “@darrenrovell: Boom RT @WagerMinds Some bettor got Els at 469 to 1 odds during today's round. $70 bet paid $33K”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always gonna be a #Tigers fan (thanks Mr. Harwell) - but I love this #Nats team. So fun to watch each day.  #NATITUDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ESPN_Colin: No idea what NCAA will do (does anyone ever?) but destroying a program by hammering people not involved in scandal doesn ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewhenson7 &gt; tomato juice, dude. Tomato juice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow's pitch counts: Jackson 135 and Lanan 126. #NATITUDE #Nats #twinbill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper = Due. #NATITUDE #Nats  #thekid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@GeoffBurr: This #Nats team is incredible.” &gt; won't have a bullpen for a month. Incredible none the less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major League is seriously the funniest movie. Oh wait...I'm watching the Nats game.  Never mind.  #Nats #NATITUDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is better &gt; @BonnieBernstein: #since #7 #of #today's #11 #tweets #are #sans #hashtag, #I'd #venture #to #say #yes RT @shermanshungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wowsers.  RT @BrianHughesDC: Carney on why jobs council hasn't met in 6 months: "The president has a lot on his plate."”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@padrefan858 @Buster_ESPN &gt; tell that to the ball Harper just ripped the cover off of in the 10th to tie it. 
#NATITUDE #bambam #curlyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@karabellespn: Bobby Parnell certainly can make things interesting.” &gt; he's certainly good for some bonus baseball! #NATITUDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell &gt; Houston...we have a Prob-Lin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@darrenrovell: What should the NY papers go with tomorrow? Need your never heard before Lin puns!” &gt; Let me play my Bye-O-Lin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Moses &gt; “@jaketapper: Nielsen: An estimated 67.2 million people watched the debate.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greggutfeld: watching MSNBC discuss the debate is like watching the Titanic discuss the iceberg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Matthews has lost his mind. #2012debate #Election2012 #MittRomney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeAndMike @Espngreeny &gt; when did it become The Lone Ranger and Mike in the Morning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow! “@BonnieBernstein: Who's watching presidential debate at 9pm? U registered to vote? If not, uh, hello? Do it here@RockTheVote”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@MarkZuckerman: Mark DeRosa starting tonight. At shortstop. Yup.” &gt; I better hurry then. Apparently I'm catching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SC_DougFarrar: SPIDER 2 Y BANANA ALERT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattcharboneau: For the UM fans. #msugameday http://t.co/pW099BAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Ryan_Huddle: Wishing i was in #beastlansing today...” &gt; co-sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@AP_NFL: it was only a matter of time: "@RepIacementRef: Yeah, I have Golden Tate on my fantasy team ... So what?" &gt; Other guy had GB Def.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@ESPNStatsInfo: How many asterisks is Elias using for tonight's game. THAT'S a stat worth having! #MNF #packers #seahawks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PPPPolling: Bain Capital invested in three replacement referee companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kimsfirst: Replacement refs doing the best they can. That's the problem. Sort of like President Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyFratto &gt; I won on the extra point. Guy I played had GB Def. #theserefsarecool #nonotreally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@mortreport: I believe @SamuelLJackson just tweeted something” &gt; he's right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RSLC_President: Seahawks won this game the way Democrats win close elections in Washington...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimrome: 6000 miles home, Chuckie?  The Packers play in London?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESPNFantasy @MatthewBerryTMR &gt; gonna lose to GB Def if they don't try this extra point. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A little Spider 2 - Y Banana." Jon Gruden is awesome.  @miketirico 

#MNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerexrode: ESPN College GameDay in East Lansing for MSU-OSU. See, people still like the Big Ten. &gt; I heard its cuz Corso likes Rick's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CollegeGameDay: We’re heading to East Lansing to see the Ohio St. Buckeyes take on the Michigan St. Spartans! See you Saturday Spart ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@PaulPabst: @PGA_JohnDaly you should be head coach.” &gt; the current head coach could prob use the helmet though. #duckandcover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FakeLeyland: Denard Robinson could learn a thing or two about throwing the ball away from Omar Infante]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>