<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not my past. I am what I chose to become. https://t.co/Ua9hPslaDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything you truly want must be worth fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people are not gifted; they just work hard, then succeed on purpose. - G.K. Nielson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: A house is never lonely where a loving dog waits :)

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/BrwO9sbd6j&gt;9823 https://t.co/jNH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is some good in this world, and it's worth fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True bravery is doing what is right even when it's not popular. https://t.co/mq60XqzXtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need a reason to help people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovLikeJesus: Worry about nothing, pray about everything. https://t.co/q1S9kLKcP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If daily you feel a sense of gratitude for the blessings of this life it will be a cushion &amp; buffer when challenges arise. -Rose W-T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do more for the world than it does for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak unless you can improve the silence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything we hear is an opinion, not a fact. Everything we see is a perspective, not the truth. - Marcus Aurelius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real measure of our wealth is how much we'd be worth if we lost all our money. -Jowett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear can keep us up all night long, but faith makes one fine pillow. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know when to cry, know when to laugh, know when to be silent. - Mark Crow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day is a NEW beginning, take a deep breath and START AGAIN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who follow the crowd usually get lost in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is to be ready when your opportunity comes. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better three hours too soon than a minute too late. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people pass through our lives in a shorter time frame than we had hoped to teach us things they never could have taught if they stayed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Perfect plan for this afternoon! :)

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/Ha4fQZ3rPx https://t.co/AZe4jhda2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love him who least deserves it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovmydog: How dare you eat my scooby snacks! https://t.co/q3QAyeoiRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who does not read good books has no advantage over the man who can't read them. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age is of no importance unless you are a cheese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be thankful for where you are. https://t.co/cbplvH1wm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't compare your progress with that of others. We all need our own time to travel our own distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovmydog: Your a ticklish little thing aren't you https://t.co/sfcUvVM1PI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day, you'll be just a memory for some people. Do your best to be a good one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong :) https://t.co/ppEa0LJRRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest weapon against stress is our ability to choose one thought over another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone Dies. But not everyone really lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if it's difficult keep moving forward. https://t.co/h0f2y9XViF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not do to others what angers you if done to you by others. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Expect the best. Prepare for the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life may not be the party we hoped for, but while we're here we should dance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be happy in the moment, that's enough. Each moment is all we need, not more. -Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am done with the past, the future has plenty of room for change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this!!! https://t.co/E1ZPDrEP3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expert in anything was once a beginner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on the things that make you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith the good is just around the corner. https://t.co/F5ry33zQnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live a life you are proud of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It requires less character to discover the faults of others, than to tolerate them. -J. Petit Senn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: Do what is right, not what is easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count your blessings and give thanks to the Lord God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing looks better on you. https://t.co/g37t1wyP1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live like each day is your last! Love like you have never been hurt before! Sing like no one is listening! Dance like no one is watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: So, how was your Friday evening? :')

Get this awesome tee here --&gt; https://t.co/vvIp4ZxNwN https://t.co/oDcK1YTTTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may not be there yet, but you're closer than you were yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith, relax, and give it your best. https://t.co/T0Kwqvxqha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is love that makes the impossible possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Looking rather dapper https://t.co/NhuWRogKmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To wish you were someone else is to waste the person you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgiveness does not change the past, but it does enlarge the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ship is safe in harbor, but that's not what ships are for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Epic_Women: You cannot always wait for the perfect time. Sometimes you must dare to jump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be a lion for a day than a sheep all your life. - Sister Elizabeth Kenny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this thought. https://t.co/33zHsIbXLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you remember who you were before the world told you who you should be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effort doesn't matter if love is left behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were born to succeed, not to fail. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God didn't bring you this far to leave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Dogs are the best! :)

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/xlBJL5vsJo https://t.co/GRr09QUpq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a good listener. Your ears will never get you in trouble. -Frank Tyger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/KztJZe8sZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For I know the plans I have for you, declares the LORD, plans to prosper u &amp; not to harm you, plans to give you hope &amp; a future. -Jer 29:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something now that will make the person you'll be tomorrow proud to have been the person you are today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do all the good you can, to as many people as you can, as often as you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step through new doors. The majority of the time there's something fantastic on the other side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: The greatest act of faith some days is to simply get up and face another day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust yourself. Create the kind of self that you will be happy to live with all your life. -Golda Meir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to make an impact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be PROUD of who you are, and everything you've overcome. https://t.co/mC8KnVTl8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is not permanent &amp; failure is not fatal. -Mike Ditka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where God guides He provides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We tend to judge others by their behavior, and ourselves by our intentions. #foodforthought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @llovemypug: Too cool for school https://t.co/ATa2vLgBew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love people who make me smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prove yourself to yourself not others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be pushed around by your problems. Be led by your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I BELIEVE THAT HAPPY GIRLS ARE THE PRETTIEST GIRLS. -Audrey Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovLikeJesus: Jesus is my top priority!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success seems to be connected to action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don't quit. - Conrad Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humility is not thinking less of yourself, but thinking of yourself less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We rise by lifting others. https://t.co/fjpJBIHRMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't brag about yourself let others praise you. -Proverbs 27:2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do small things with great love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not ask God to guide your footsteps if you're not willing to move your feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am in charge of how I feel and TODAY I am choosing HAPPINESS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let love win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a verb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Great pieces of advice. https://t.co/9JfSAW5ANN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mother's LOVE is WHOLE, no matter how many times DIVIDED...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: true. https://t.co/Nq6xGzjYlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can complain because roses have thorns, or rejoice because thorns have roses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you're ready or not, just start right now.  There is magic in action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith! https://t.co/5Gf9Xr6Itq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>