<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Please consider writing to your MP before the badger cull debate this wednesday 5 june #stopthecull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 247: BRILLIANT BADGER MARCH – DID I BREAK BRIAN MAY’S GUITAR FINGER? http://t.co/o0opmpsRJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in beautiful Somerset to help the badgers. The science is black and white #stopthecull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@expresident you've used my photo of queuing fox without any credit. Please add link to http://t.co/KfAJSqu4sA or remove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and bill Oddie looking not so pleased at the badger march #stopthebadgercull http://t.co/GQc2EmNrkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mapitup: Still to understand really why, but I like this very much. Words by Joseph Markovitch, photographs by @MartinUsborne http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best badger costumes I've seen so far http://t.co/rkLpS2VEFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for badger march #againstthecull http://t.co/nM909yHhCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Network4Animals: @ArtfulBadgerUK @MartinUsborne - Our underground die-in against #badgercull popped up in Independent: http://t.co/HWYS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 245: BADGERS GET A SAY IN PARLIAMENT AND I GET A CHANCE TO MEET A FASCIST http://t.co/vY7XdgT1fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its going to be sunny tomorrow - who's joining me on the march against the badger cull? http://t.co/XYpgkWbVgt #badg… http://t.co/gR8GXaKbiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS RE BADGER CULL: A binding vote. Please write to your MP. http://t.co/DoBrjOSP8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEFRA Finally Reveals Shocking Details of Badger Cull Suffering @HSIGlobal http://t.co/WqftU0Ec8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SHADOWWABBITS8: @MartinUsborne Me too. it's just horrible. The badgers that are getting culled don't even carry bovine TB - just stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevetims @MetPoliceEvents I hope not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to download your badger mask for the march tomorrow! http://t.co/KqzLKvlEtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: Shocking badger cull suffering revealed – pls write to your MP today http://t.co/EBHJUaR2KN via @HSIGlobal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[majority of MPs oppose the cull, most of public too &amp; science slams it as option for controlling TB in cattle. http://t.co/YulWQF89XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who wants to join me saturday to march against the badger cull in central london? info here: http://t.co/XYpgkWbVgt #badgermarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time I have political passion. This badger cull has got me worked up in a fever.... http://t.co/YulWQF89XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 242: MY DAY OF TRESPASS – LOOKING FOR BADGER SETTS OUT IN THE WEST COUNTRY http://t.co/YulWQF89XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MuseeMagazine: "The Silences of Dogs in Cars" by @MartinUsborne has proved to be a successful hit! Read why on Musée.... http://t.co/8p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 240: ARE LOST DOGS FOLLOWING ME?? Japanese Akita found in street http://t.co/mbjWI1PLLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 239: CUTE HEDGEHOG POSTER WARNS OF GARDEN DISASTERS http://t.co/it5CPUHLC5 http://t.co/dOWemHUDmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Attenborugh on the badger cull: http://t.co/4Umop3xitA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 236: WHAT’S THIS BADGER CULL ALL ABOUT? SOME BASIC FACTS http://t.co/ymW3u4kvJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FlakPhoto: Today's @FlakPhoto - @MartinUsborne, Peggy (2), 2011 http://t.co/zzTVwaORpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andreasokphoto: @FlakPhoto: Martin Usborne, Peggy (2) http://t.co/1vm2oGpZcH - from The Silence of Dogs in Cars, beautiful project ... …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bish_ben The cull is a flawed attempt to control bovine TB which will waste farmer's money. Shame you want to see farmers suffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book arrived from Nazraeli! I've 20 AP's with print. Looks lovely. Order AP here:  http://t.co/weuTljmyK9 http://t.co/NR0efI4CDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper yes that's them!!! I was on it too but brutally cut out of edit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show your badger love and write to Defra voicing your opposition to the cull: http://t.co/AGBE4ci0Q3 #badgercull @Network4Animals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who saw moose and bug on the apprentice last night?! http://t.co/rj7aOP0bml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lunaandcurious great will send you an email now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Badgers dying on the underground http://t.co/kFZhOYfQoG http://t.co/RfpEXlGsAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lunaandcurious we still have copies of the book sold in special edition box with print. Let me know if you are interested in more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/gWQgiaWnLi Network for Animals blog on our underground 'die-in' highlighting the brutality of impending badger cull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 234: IN THE UK- I KISSED A MAN-BADGER OUTSIDE PARLIAMENT AFTER DYING ON THE TUBE http://t.co/kFZhOYfQoG @ArtfulBadgerUK @Network4Animals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't already please sign + share this: http://t.co/eOV1EWWzB6 to stop cruel puppy farming #wheresmum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 232: FINAL DAY IN INDIA…NOW HEADING BACK TO HELP THE BADGERS http://t.co/mB6H4B3GyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lunaandcurious: Just re-read I've Lived In East London for 85 1/2 years by @MartinUsborne. It really is the perfect book. I suggest you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithHopkin excellent! would love to be back in NY sometime. we should meet up if / when!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pawsandpurrs sure please send me a message at martinusborne@mac.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on the underground as a dead badger #againstthecull #badgermonday http://t.co/sY8dzOhzjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dogsmountain1: @MartinUsborne  World day today #notodogmeat awareness spreads far and wide with groups of like minded - caring people s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SCPLtd: Joseph Markovitch is an original East Ender. Nearly 86, he has lived in Hoxton for his entire life http://t.co/CrQXaC36Gk @Mart…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My answers to some of the negative comments on daily mail article: http://t.co/8NCmV7FAhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper not yet, but we haven't actively searched until she arrives. Are you looking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I mention the Daily Mail wrote about Mango?! http://t.co/WNKM5qaGmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog Post: DAY 226: WHAT I AM NOT ABLE TO TELL YOU….FOR NOW http://t.co/8NCmV7FAhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this very important petition to get cruel puppy farming banned in UK! @marcthevet http://t.co/P0qejFgKgM  #wheresmum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marcthevet: WOW guys 10,000 signatures in 2 days! Seems we really do want puppy farming banned pls RT as need 100,000 http://t.co/YVkTY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets stop puppy farming. Please sign this #wheresmum http://t.co/iUd9xpiNlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 215: BEAR RESCUE ENDS MYSTERIOUSLY http://t.co/v7TPOWvgrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hi @DanChallender , not sure if you saw my email but I'm trying to contact re a book I am writing on wildlife trade. Can we chat/email? thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 268: A GUEST PORTFOLIO FROM A GREAT DOG SUPPORTER http://t.co/FcHBTbTGR1 @TOLFA http://t.co/zWqzYYl8CQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @fourandsons for featuring 'Nice to Meet You!' http://t.co/CvxcD9FtwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fourandsons: NEW FEATURE: EVERYTHING IS ILLUMINATED
In his enigmatic new series, Nice to meet you, Martin Usborne... http://t.co/C1ktpi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boarding flight to Vietnam, tiny family with 3 inch legs in emergency row, I'm in back seat eating my knees. Screen this close is like IMAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_sillyfilly I don't think there are enough photos am afraid. I may well do more though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[less angry &amp; more balanced view than my own on dog meat festival happening right now in china: http://t.co/Xeql1yyYL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 269: TODAY IS BEST DAY OF THE YEAR – IT JUST TURNED TO SHIT. CHINA TO KILL 1000′s OF DOGS http://t.co/qRSmQpJlJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denounce the dog meat trade! thousands of dogs being killed in china right now in summer festival http://t.co/QtzZF4RSDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Animals1st: Starting in China this Friday, Yulin Dog Meat Festival over 10,000 dogs slaughtered! #stopyulindogmeatfest http://t.co/IPsb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the best dog art-blog ever @fourandsons , they've been kind enough to feature my work a few times. http://t.co/wVMJwGATfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kocicenka not a sausage!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLacquerie @miss_moss thanks stacy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pah!! Not a sausage!! No award, no food. Onwards and downwards!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In abbey road studios for award ceremony waiting to hear if I lost (for book about old man) standing by door for free vege sausages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneak peek: new Hoxton Mini Press art book in the works. With Adam Dant. Out for Xmas #hoxtonminipress http://t.co/pXBntVkKki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dogsmountain1: @MartinUsborne 15,000+ dogs 2B tortured &amp; slaughtered in Yulin 'CHINA this weekend - #notodogmeat Campaigns to end Horro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 265: THE SAN MIGUEL SIGN ON DOG-MEAT RESTAURANT IS REPLACED BY COKE ADVERT http://t.co/z9jPVBIYYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The work @AnimalsAsia do to stop bear farming is incredible. Please support urgently http://t.co/0dLPqSptcG @PeterEgan6 @moonbearJill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCNews: Ban on use of face-down restraint in English mental hospitals is being considered by government http://t.co/6NT9HYLie5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnimalsAsia: For those enjoying the #moonbearmonday pics of climbing Isis - here's a little extra pic of her enjoying the pool: http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnimalsAsia: Happy Moon Bear Monday.  Rescued cubs Misty &amp; Rain take a bubble bath. More pics here:http://t.co/eylXwL2WVt http://t.co/D…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met inspirational Jill Robinson @moonbearJill and Peter Egan @PeterEgan6 at screening on the bear bile farm trade in china for @AnimalsAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thisispapermag: Nice to meet you by @MartinUsborne → http://t.co/mJVQiMpGvU http://t.co/phFoNvnvka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 263: ANT ATTACK STRETCHES MY COMPASSION TOO FAR http://t.co/PfegKvhprb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally pics of the adult category of Britiain's Cutest Staffy! More here: http://t.co/4FcWE56TcK http://t.co/Fqm3RCFarl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 261: 24 HOURS FROM DEATH AND NOW BRITAIN’S CUTEST STAFFY? http://t.co/4FcWE56TcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered the nature reserve and canal by hackney marshes, gorgeous!! Nice cafes too http://t.co/L0p5cx2YDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iamalexandra_: Amazing project by @MartinUsborne to save as many animals as possible in 365 days! http://t.co/qGIgVWtz9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 260: MAD MEN AND UNCERTAIN VEGANS http://t.co/PfuYi6nPE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizwan_uk ha! thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @sophiesimmons ! Very kind of you to say. Glad to you like the series!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great coverage of my new series over on Its Nice That @itsnicethat  http://t.co/EYnEoHJjmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Images from a new series here: http://t.co/juOlzz5ngu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha!! My book about old Man just been nominated for design award, the invite is too good! http://t.co/BG0FiLpb16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 259: SOME (VEGETARIAN) FOOD FOR THOUGHT http://t.co/6nvp5Vnvmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anoyone in Vienna go support the protest at the british embassy against the badger cull!! info here: http://t.co/qjOcJovLkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MANGO UPDATE!! She's doing great! More here: http://t.co/sXHIHwMzR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 258: MINI-ME FINDS NEW HOME more here: http://t.co/ZAZ10Wrhiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 256: AN UPDATE ON MANGO: http://t.co/sXHIHwMzR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adorable baby fox spotted in garden. I love urban foxes despite what people say http://t.co/19QwlzFq7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Network4Animals seems like san miguel has deleted ALL the comments on their FB page from us asking them to denounce dog meat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Network4Animals @lauelle4 just posted a brief update on mango here: http://t.co/sXHIHwMzR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Network4Animals: Badger Cull: Saboteurs Plan Mass Invasion of Countryside - IBTimes UK http://t.co/etkjySDGVo #badgercull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Mass Download Monday!! Help Get 'BADGER SWAGGER' To No.1: http://t.co/WPKG2QfxEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper yay!!! Looks great!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>