<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Right?? #charismaticmegafauna https://t.co/msw1gvhmbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Donald Trump, we'll see you in court." @ddonigernrdc of @NRDC on fighting back to #DefendClimate https://t.co/a2DyNWNRog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone here has a reason why this is personal" says @GreenLatino's Mark Magana https://t.co/daxbsrjY7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporters at climate rally going straight for the bear shot, naturally #DefendClimate https://t.co/8TXnc8AuKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How many of you know someone with asthma?... that will increase." @enviRN #DefendClimate https://t.co/ju0xUjjo5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is giving the green light to corporations to pollute... indigenous people stand with you" says Rising Hearts Coalition https://t.co/eypAGAtfmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Trump's EO: @TomSteyer says "we are not compromising... they are dead wrong." #DefendClimate #ActOnClimate @NextGenClimate https://t.co/ALsES4UFIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rally against Trump's dangerous exec order  - speakers from SEIU and public health professionals here to #standupfightback, #DefendClimate https://t.co/LA0SYQJAMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Trump wants to undo the biggest step we’ve taken in fighting climate change. We won’t let him get away with it. https://t.co/t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current mood. #DefendClimate https://t.co/sL9t6vXC1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As he attacks climate action most Americans support, a quick reminder that Trump is historically unpopular. #DefendClimate #cleanpowerplan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeremyschulman: Great explainer from @rebleber on exactly what Trump's climate executive order will do https://t.co/XEjGyEpkkt https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hanchennrdc: There are so many lies in Trump @POTUS's energy speech right now -- cannot fact check fast enough....bear with me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: As Trump attacks U.S. climate progress, @NRDC just showed we know how to fight back when our government fails us. 

And win. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Agent350: “American pipelines, made with American steel. Can you believe someone would actually say that?” @POTUS. KXL is made with for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember what happened in Michigan?" Thought he might be referring to Flint water crisis. He was bragging about the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lindsaymeim14: ICYMI: As Trump unravels hard-won protections of people &amp; planet, concern about climate change reaches record high.

htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says we're going to have clean air and water - we're just not going to have any rules or hold polluters accountable. #defendclimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCVoters: .@SenJeffMerkley: "Carbon pollution is destroying the land and water in rural America." This is why we need to #ActOnClimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says his attacks on our climate and health will "restore economic freedom" as economic trends take us toward our Paris climate goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says "I guess they like what we're about to sign" to an applauding room that he filled with his people. #DefendClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretaryZinke says we can't power the country on "pixie dust." Then tells a rousing fairy tale about coal jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's attacks on environmental protections starting now. #DefendClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: Takes more than a stroke of the pen. Many steps to erase climate rules. We'll fight each one. Another deal Donald won't b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jschmidtnrdc: #Climate regulations aren't replaced or repealed by the stroke of Trump's Pen https://t.co/bacqFDEDs2 #ParisAgreement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConsumersUnion: CU: Withdrawing the #CleanPowerPlan means higher costs for consumers @SBB_CU https://t.co/zSfEDIapP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in California: reinforcing standards for #cleanercars  https://t.co/HwB90sRNOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: #KeystoneXL is all risk and no reward for the American people. It remains, and always will be, a threat to our land, water, an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyrswift: .@realDonaldTrump clearly hasn't read the old environmental review for #KXL... #noKXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshaxel: Looks like @POTUS can't stop lying to American workers. #noKXL is not a jobs solution, stop saying it is. More @NRDC https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PPact: Here's the picture of the leaders negotiating away birth control, maternity care &amp; abortion. Notice anything? #ProtectOurCare

(…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidaxelrod: Stunning rebuke from @WSJ: "Yet the president clings to his assertion like a drunk to an empty gin bottle." https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except that they didn't. https://t.co/A9O13WF2ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice toolkit from @UCSUSA on what you can do this Memorial Day weekend to fight Trump's budget cuts. #dirtybudget https://t.co/YIPjuiQ4EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GuardianUS: Republican candidate 'body-slams' Guardian reporter in Montana https://t.co/QbQ8Bh5e1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Trump is deleting climate change, one site at a time. https://t.co/uRekDeg8th via @guardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientific study specifically refutes Scott Pruitt's claims about "leveling off" global warming. https://t.co/XUAogR3Mn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health safeguards, clean energy and efficiency, climate research... All on Trump's #DirtyBudget hit list. @RheaSuh:  https://t.co/fxmZWEDPyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lived blocks from where Seth Rich died. Dear friends have been mugged nearby. Don't belittle DC's real tragedies. https://t.co/kEDD89G3JG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShelleyPoticha: The sweeping impact of @realDonaldTrump's proposed cuts to environmental protections: https://t.co/1LcItmf2LY https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: Trump budget director Mulvaney cuts vital climate research &amp; protection, calling it "crazy stuff."  https://t.co/LugrjXG8…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First glances of Trump's #dirtybudget proposal do not bode well. https://t.co/MxLBE84n9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: At @HouseScience hearing, Republican @RepGaryPalmer (AL) is disputing that air pollution is deadly, contrary to vast body o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @climate: China's solar output increased 80% in Q1 https://t.co/ibums5vukn https://t.co/NaJvJnkGL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCFedGov: .@NRDC President: Trump Budget Betrays Our Values and Puts Polluters First https://t.co/5eYYaCwskl #DirtyBudget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Trump eyes drastic cuts to clean #energy funding. https://t.co/2aO6lYUFim #TrumpWatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's budget makes deep cuts to critical environmental safeguards and health protections at @EPA.  https://t.co/Lu0RuDzW6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMConstible: This is an awfully-familiar move: Taking the #climate out of news about climate research. https://t.co/zibZDHkmaw #scicomm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahkendzior: Imagine if reporters had followed up on this at the time instead of mocking it as ludicrous, purposefully burying it, an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: @EPAScottPruitt 12 /...Bottomline: Proposal undercuts "back to basics," claims shift to states yet slashes state budgets,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: @EPAScottPruitt 10 / Knock-out punch for "geographic programs." That's $427m. Electeds frm Grt Lakes, Chesapeake, Puget So…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: @EPAScottPruitt 7/ A $129m cut to Clean Air line in EPA's EPM budget would demolish support to states managing GHG, ozone,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: @EPAScottPruitt 6/ Research for Sustainable and Healthy Communities cut by ~40% too. Among other things, hurts univ-based…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: @EPAScottPruitt 3/ EPA is charged w protecting nation’s critical water infrastructure from terrorist threats &amp; all-hazard…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ali_a_zaidi: National Association of Clean Air Agencies has posted @EPAScottPruitt FY18 Budget request: https://t.co/iQ9n4SItYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of America is hearing a completely different narrative on Trump scandals. https://t.co/DBE92rpKAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sethmoulton: As the Representative of Salem, MA, I can confirm that this is false. https://t.co/8yJIzZBSE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Revkin: Fab immersive 3-part @nytclimate package on sea-level rise &amp; Antarctic ice rightly stresses vulnerable underbelly. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thursday was not the first time Trump has made baseless claims without providing any evidence." https://t.co/dReIDYBRM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MEPFuller: A cool thing about Donald Trump is he led a year's-long effort to prove that Barack Obama was born in Kenya. https://t.co/jO…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we set a journalistic standard that "some people said this on twitter" is not an appropriate supporting argument for your opinion piece?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed up for Bike to Work Day and you should too! It's May 19th. https://t.co/9J0hOstdIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: "As a Coast Guard officer, I saw the effects of climate change firsthand." #ActOnClimate #ParisAgreement https://t.co/xZahsQor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaking what to the press? Why admit he has something to leak? Why imply your conversations are incriminating? Why ever tweet this? https://t.co/PyKffSEQkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tribelaw: How Abnormal Was Comey’s Firing? Experts Weigh In, via @nytimes https://t.co/78L9EhS69Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonshorman: Full story on Kobach's appointment to presidential commission coming soon. Here's the quick version https://t.co/0WSNv0woDu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, what? https://t.co/UU3EpM8ANe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanchait: I'm sure he has some good advice for handling the investigation. https://t.co/6walRSWFUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VocesVerdes: Here is why this is important: https://t.co/SoaBl4uS7m https://t.co/b8V3OANZWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undermining this rule in a matter of hours flies in the face of 330K public comments supporting effort to #cutMethane, says @SenatorCantwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorTomUdall: We did it—the BLM's #methanerule remains in place. This is a huge win for taxpayers, #publichealth and #cleanair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCVoters: Thanks to every Senator who stood up for common sense safeguards for clean air &amp; a safer climate today! https://t.co/eVCjh9X4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell is on the floor now talking abt waste and hazards of methane leaks. McConnell may be working twrd another vote. #CutMethane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradplumer And Collins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain, Collins, and Graham have opposed the motion - I hope because they recognize the dangers of methane pollution and leaks. https://t.co/grbQpyFIDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BradfordPearson: There's a lot going on today, but "Reporter Arrested For Asking Trump Cabinet Member Question" probably shouldn't slip…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gabbilevy: Woah. Trump has fired Comey. https://t.co/9HG2qOVDsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gabbilevy: Letters from AG Sessions to POTUS, Trump to Comey: https://t.co/gonatkpRvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: FBI officials acknowledge Comey gave inaccurate testimony on Clinton emails: report https://t.co/OdW8oM1j7M https://t.co/doqPj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: The Business Case for the Paris Climate Accord -- lead author, George Shultz, was also Reagan's SecState. https://t.co/7b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: Macron tells Trump he will defend 2015 Paris climate change agreement  https://t.co/8De0Mkh3gY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of largest companies in the U.S. call on Trump in the @nytimes to keep us in the Paris Climate Agreement: https://t.co/8j8n3SfDGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't click on that random google doc link.  https://t.co/nITVIuX3W3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a single tweet, Trump has suggested both the nuclear option and a government shutdown are good ideas. This is absurd and frightening. https://t.co/FPvGGMyxxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We weren't kidding, 96 days ago.#climatemarch #PeoplesClimate https://t.co/2KhMtx5mqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We will not go away! Welcome to your 100th day!" https://t.co/BiUs17vAvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front of the DC #climatemarch is moving! Slowly! https://t.co/YtT29xwIH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @duckytennent: 'We owe the people of the world an America that is not for sale to the fossil fuel industry." @SenWhitehouse at #climatem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And MA AG Maura Healey is here rocking the bullhorn @MassAGO https://t.co/PcdCvzLpBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @SenMarkey  rallying a few hundred of the thousands and thousands at the #climatemarch! @BostonGlobe https://t.co/1mcAY3w1w0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 9:30 Club concert tonight, @TheNewPornos just gave a mid-set shoutout to the #climatemarch. Thanks @NekoCase!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: On eve of climate march, @EPAScottPruitt sticks finger in eye of American majority who want action on climate pollution.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nrdc_org is getting ready for the #climatemarch! Are you? @ Natural Resource Defense Council https://t.co/lHrdhbWEL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorLeahy: 'Anti-Science Know-Nothingism' – Vice Chair Leahy Slams Trump Budget To Gut #EPA, In Approps Hg W. EPA Adm. Pruitt

https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not only in the toolbox, but you are obligated to take it out and use it, #PollutingPruitt. It's called the Clean Air Act. Do your job. https://t.co/twrws4LgYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt explicitly referred to SCOTUS cases that require climate regs, yet somehow managed mental gymnastics to suggest EPA isn't responsible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: Pruitt pretends Supreme Court rejected EPA's #CleanPowerPlan.  Wrong, Court upheld EPA's climate authority 3 times. 1/ ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what @ChrisVanHollen was just grilling @EPAScottPruitt on in the #dirtybudget hearing: https://t.co/h8tME8YXxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Environmental Topics on Trump EPA web page: Bed Bugs.

Environmental Topics not on Trump EPA web page: Climate Change. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCWater: BREAKING: @EPAScottPruitt announces proposal to undo protections for streams that provide drinking water supply for 1 in 3 A…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>