<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how "incubating" new products in limited markets before national roll-out could improve #innovation process https://t.co/LfVFErXDka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Organic #AnimalWelfare rule better aligns consumer expectations of organic w reality, @OrganicTrade says https://t.co/AOTdtIMHCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HealthWarrior shares advice for how doing good can help business. Plus deets on its new #kickstarter campaign https://t.co/Z4vKYL3vJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Innovation abounds in food &amp; beverage. Check out some leading #entrepreneurs who are pushing industry fwrd https://t.co/hepaEjYGJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA &amp; EPA push forward with modernizing #GMO regulations: https://t.co/KGNCsylffn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the significance of @mintelnews finding that only 38% of ppl think healthy food is worth extra expense? https://t.co/EPn9hx6uWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will new advice &amp; easy-to-read chart from @FDA and @EPA impact Americans' seafood consumption? https://t.co/p9oPqIr4Ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone wants pretzels and chicken tenders at a sports event. Some want healthy concession stand snacks https://t.co/NEf6CrNJhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The retail value of #glutenfree food grew 10% in 2016 over previous year, according to @Euromonitor https://t.co/mecb7OkihI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump thinks Sonny Perdue will do "great things" as @USDA Secretary. What do you think? https://t.co/z3sKycPTN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @BolthouseFarms' model of "incubating" new MAIO condiment in limited markets a better way to #innovate? https://t.co/LfVFErG2sC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final #organic #AnimalWelfare rule eases some compliance timelines https://t.co/AOTdtJ4j0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HealthWarrior's #kickstarter campaign dunks on other corporate giving campaigns by giving away all the profits https://t.co/Z4vKYKLUkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out why @LoveTheWildCo loves #aquaculture and believes it could improve US diet, ease environmental impact https://t.co/sTaEYDTnP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are low- and no-calorie sweeteners more helpful or harmful to consumers' health? https://t.co/4bxP7WFTha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you eat mayo, non-dairy milk and yogurt made from fava beans, lentils and other legumes? https://t.co/K0y9UOWdvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SupportAStrongPress One way is to subscribe something: newspaper, magazine, newsletter, digital outlet, podcast #WomensMarchOnWashington https://t.co/osmfAbc7ni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confusion over whether eggs are healthy or not continues https://t.co/Iqvdmau1xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rising consumption of no- and low-calorie sweeteners fuels debate around their safety: https://t.co/4bxP7WXu8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TABSAnalytics: Thoughts?? &gt;&gt; Trump presidency seen as negative for global food trade - survey says just-food https://t.co/aWhjOm0TXO vi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HealthWarrior talks about how doing good can be good for business in this wk's #SoupToNuts #podcast https://t.co/Z4vKYL3vJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding healthy #snack options at concession stands can boost revenue: https://t.co/NEf6CrNJhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is #glutenfree bread so much smaller than conventional loaves? @canyonbakehouse shows they don't have to be https://t.co/mecb7O2Hqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would a Sonny Perdue appointment as Sec. of @USDA mean for farmers &amp; food manufacturers? https://t.co/z3sKycyiou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NPRFood: Trump's Pick To Lead USDA Heads To Washington With Some Political Baggage https://t.co/76f4OfQyr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers who love #mayo but feel guilty eating it have a new, healthier option w @BolthouseFarms launch of MAIO https://t.co/LfVFErXDka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the 11th hour finalization of the #organic #AnimalWelfare be undone by the #trumpadministration? https://t.co/AOTdtJ4j0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 reasons why #aquaculture and farmed fish is good for business, according to @LoveTheWildCo https://t.co/sTaEYDBMqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should eggs be allowed to be marketed as healthy? https://t.co/IqvdmaLCVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25% of children and 41% of adults consume no or low calorie sweeteners every day, new research shows https://t.co/4bxP7WFTha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GeneralMills explores more #plantbased alternatives to milk, mayo &amp; yogurt using legumes https://t.co/K0y9UOECEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can influencers boost your brand &amp; how can they harm it if you aren't careful? @eatwellglobal shares all: https://t.co/x0WUMufljv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the bright spots in the the "underperforming" US #yogurt category: https://t.co/mVmA9bZWFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you break through the competition to catch retailer's attn w a new product? @Range_Me could help https://t.co/34KPNkjcw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could #aquaculture and farmed fish be a way to more sustainably improve American's diets? https://t.co/sTaEYDBMqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA is rethinking its definition of #healthy, but #eggs could still be left in the cold. Find out why: https://t.co/IqvdmaLCVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year of the pulse is over but @GeneralMills continues to innovate w them to create yogurt, mayo &amp; non-dairy milk https://t.co/K0y9UOECEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA pushes back against GAO recommendation to create a unified food safety system across agencies w oversight https://t.co/lRcsIYM0zE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legislators, industry hope to revamp food expiration dates to reduce #foodwaste https://t.co/swqdQb2Gnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For cold brew coffee there is no difference between the mass market and the upmarket says @LaColombeCoffee https://t.co/vuDUeNi3Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is bone broth really healthier than other stock? https://t.co/WKNKoAblaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recalls due to food spoilage issues offer "tough lessons" for those operating in the booming fresh segment https://t.co/zRLUybav8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44% of manufacturers cite concern about liability as reason why they did not donate food that ultimately was wasted https://t.co/swqdQb2Gnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who buys meal kits? https://t.co/rpbLFZdEj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What 'milk' means is causing quite the stir among dairy and plant-based producers https://t.co/y1f62Hs4PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three factors driving American's love affair with hot sauce https://t.co/jz9jzsOFhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California could soon require warnings on foods &amp; beverages with artificial dyes https://t.co/i2tipADjy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New products from @Unilever @Genius_Juice tap in #plantbased #protein trend https://t.co/QN5ojxnEqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standards of identity are created to protect consumers not manufacturers @GoodFoodInst argues in debate about 'milk' https://t.co/y1f62HJFH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23% of cos that conducted recalls related to food disease spent/lost more than $30 million on event, GAO reports https://t.co/lRcsIYupI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @USDA_AMS: LIVE #AgOutlook: several questions regarding consumer misperceptions of #egg labels - our quick guide is a start https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are cage free hens better off? They have 3x higher mortality,  higher rate of keel bone, feather loss, pests, researcher says at #agoutlook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#eggs offer most #protein per dollar spent w 55 grams compared to 38 for milk, 31 for chicken breast and 10 for popular shake #agoutlook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To meet commitments cos are making for cage free eggs US industry needs 197M more hens Current growth of 6.2% won't get us there. #agoutlook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of new #farmers entering field has dropped 20% w the average farmer age up to 58 now https://t.co/gWvh4SaU5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70% of ppl say they read labels often/ always but at store only 3% actually do says @GeneralMills' #organic guru at #agoutlook mtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In areas with a lot of #organic farming the ave household income is $2,094 higher than those wo according to data presented by @OrganicTrade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2015 value of US organic tracked exports (31 products, mostly fruit/veg) reached $545 million, USDA ERS rep says at #agoutlook mtg in DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganicTrade: . @OrganicTrade Laura Batcha encourages Cong Conaway to think about #organic as a bright spot in US ag and a win-win for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food inflation likely to be low in aggregate in 2017 w most Americans spending only 10% of disposable income on food USDA predicts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA predicts #agriculture prices in 2017/18 will go up 12% for wheat, 2.9% for corn, 1.1% for soy, 1.9% for rice. Cotton to drop 5.8%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 1/3 of young farmers are highly leveraged says usda chief economist Rob Johansson at USDA's The Future of Agriculture conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #farming too expensive for young professionals?  https://t.co/gWvh4SaU5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hot sauce category is, well, hot w 150% growth since 2000 to $1 billion. Find out how one co it tapping into opp https://t.co/jz9jzsx3Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C-stores offer a huge opportunity for #coldbrew #coffee https://t.co/vuDUeNi3Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who buys bone broth? https://t.co/WKNKoAblaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New legislation wants to make it easier for industry to donate food that otherwise would be wasted https://t.co/swqdQb2Gnf #foodwaste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh soup is bang on trend, and growing in the high single digits, according to @CampbellSoupCo https://t.co/zRLUybs6wX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shopping for groceries in a store is stuck in the last century, says @SunBasketMeals The future is meal kits https://t.co/rpbLFZdEj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More warnings about sugar &amp; artificial colors could be on the way depending on how legislation in Calif is received https://t.co/i2tipADjy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@noosayoghurt &amp; @siggisdairy take yogurt to the next level of decadence with high fat:  https://t.co/QN5ojxnEqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the Dairy Pride Act anti-competitive and unconstitutional? @GoodFoodInst says yes and 46,000 ppl agree: https://t.co/y1f62Hs4PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CollectiveBias: Soup To Nuts Podcast Paid #influencers make big impact w/ small budget in hot sauce category ft. @ElYucateco #client
ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W 1 in 6 Americans falling ill from foodborne diseases, does the US need a unified #foodsafety plan? GAO says yes: https://t.co/lRcsIYupI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a misconception that #vegetarians and #vegans are not looking for something meaty, says @noevilfoods https://t.co/QAMEpeET7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is milk, long upheld as nutritious, really showering us with sugar? https://t.co/8VFl07lunq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only is @LezzetliIceCrm 'chewy' it is also savory -- completely changing how Americans think of #icecream https://t.co/cJqpBuXaVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@siggisdairy introduces new decadent high-fat yogurt products https://t.co/hjaOzIfpwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convenience stores and food service are the next horizon for carbonated water co @SparklingIce https://t.co/gOkTlUS0qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you buy #nonGMO to avoid #glyphosate, then a new non-glyphosate certification might be more useful https://t.co/XCTuXtgioH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New legislation wants to entice more young people to #farming by offering loan forgiveness https://t.co/gWvh4SaU5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how paid influencers can give cos a bigger bang for the marketing dollar in this week's podcast https://t.co/jz9jzsOFhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next evolution of cold brew coffee https://t.co/vuDUeNi3Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The continuing rise of bone broth https://t.co/WKNKoAblaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh may be the future of grocery sales, but for @CampbellSoupCo it isn't coming fast enough https://t.co/zRLUybs6wX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavAsia: Survey says Asian consumers more interested in #nutrition than westerners. https://t.co/UOyh4bAGrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nestle: #DYK if female farmers had the same resources as men, 150 MILLION fewer people would go hungry? https://t.co/KAwssqx9xi #Social…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The meal kit phenomenon is a long term trend says @SunBasketMeals https://t.co/rpbLFZdEj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New and upcoming legislation seeks to redirect #foodwaste to hungry Americans https://t.co/swqdQaL5vH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#plantbased #proteins are now dressing the part as animal meat https://t.co/QAMEpeET7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heated debate about what "milk" is continues with new campaign from @RippleFoods https://t.co/8VFl07lunq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If 'chewy' ice cream seems like a stretch, that might be because it is -- literally https://t.co/cJqpBuXaVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#sugar is out and #fat is back for yogurt: https://t.co/hjaOzIx0o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New certification for non- #glyphosate gets to heart of why many shoppers buy #nonGMO
https://t.co/XCTuXtxTgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quirky ads position @SparklingIce as refreshing and flavorful but also fun https://t.co/gOkTlV9BPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are food expiration dates past due? https://t.co/swqdQaL5vH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the best #plantbased meat source? https://t.co/QAMEpeET7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is almond milk a sham? asks @RippleFoods https://t.co/8VFl07D5M0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American demand for international flavors brings to the US 'chewy' ice cream from @LezzetliIceCrm https://t.co/cJqpBveMk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Stonyfield slashes #sugar across its yogurt portfolio https://t.co/hjaOzIfpwu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>