<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A billionaire owns a tiny brass device that allows him to climb every sycamore tree in Alabama at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Punjabi president is running through a glass meadow. When she emerges, she realises she is a hermit from Glendale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Persian governess finds out that her son is her uncle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pianist opens a shop which sells the working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank manager can see every birth that has taken place in Washington DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By entering a temple in Thailand, you can reach another dimension. It is filled with harps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mansion sinks into an ocean filled with hydrochloric acid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A senator asks you to solve a riddle: What is always thin but never impossible, and always dark but never interesting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are walking through a deserted city. Ahead of you is a road paved with dinosaurs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank manager in Milwaukee flies to Montreal on her lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a supermarket in Mumbai that is infinitely large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every shopkeeper in Morocco is naked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exotic dancer steals everything and hides it inside a glass church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A math teacher is hugging the weather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 17th century Korean prophecy that you will be murdered by a Babylonian boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A child finds a long lost book containing instructions for building a pyramid out of amethysts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I dreamt about a giraffe in a conservatorium of music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tibetan doctor establishes a hospital for angel's wings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clairvoyant turns over a tarot card with a dictionary on it. 'You will marry a Bavarian court jester,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By focusing on a helmet, a 100-year-old politician is able to turn into a camel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 3am every owl in Egypt is replaced by grains of sand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Minotaur made of your heart's desire appears in Dublin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a secret department in Tesla Motors that has found a new way to create joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Belgian judge sentences a conspirator to be devoured by a huge ostrich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flight attendant realises that a chocolate owl is controlling Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker kills an ivory brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tamil scientist sees a puddle of alcohol in the shape of a poem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 12-year-old metaphysician owns a tiny crystal which lets her see every ice cube in Tasmania.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ancient Athenian flute player appears in the White House Situation Room. Nobody pays much attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beauty therapist is having a passionate love affair with love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A math teacher kisses a giant squid inside a diamond palace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In St Petersburg is a poet who has a silver intestine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A murderer discovers that a Danish pope is controlling capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You discover that you are a question mark in human form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chilli made of stars is growing in a Latvian garden. A princess plots to steal it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A monk is travelling from Alexandria to a rose in Beijing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A famous grandmother receives a strange Christmas gift: A cloud covered in rubies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker owns a tiny machine made of sapphires which allows her to make an infinite quantity of love letters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 13th century book describes a world where everything is made of the Apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A serene nun sees a sandalwood tree made of foot fetishism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panther is talking to capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 12th century notebook describes a universe where misogyny does not exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientist watches "A Room With A View". In that time, she lives for 18 years as a 14th century maharajah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A zebra made of gold bars is born in Atlantic City.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scholar discovers that the end of the world does not exist, and goes mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A skiff sinks into a swimming pool filled with cream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A field marshal is having sexual intercourse in an invisible panopticon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kurdish philosopher is crushed by a library while writing an almanac about supernovas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychiatrist discovers that Venezuelan society is being controlled by twenty-one bookshop owners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A star is smoking meth in a cake shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A depressed queen writes a dissertation that is made out of Antiques Roadshow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychic turns over a tarot card with a brain on it. 'Your destiny is to be eaten by a cloud of darkness,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congressman is assassinated. The murderer turns out to be loathsome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At dusk a poem is etched into an emerald belonging to a Chinese empress. It reads: "Take more risks."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gifted chef bakes a birthday cake for income tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-hearted princess realises that her grandfather is a 72-year-old fashion stylist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fellowship of elephants are on a secret mission. Their aim is to find a crystal cave where a magic pearl is hidden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clerk switches bodies with an apple tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A judge possesses a unique skill: He can sense the presence of thunderclouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king tries to forget about an ivory synagogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Madagascar is a grandmother whose heart is a cloud in the shape of an ostrich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight you will dream about Barbie dolls and cities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An olive causes anyone who eats it to turn into a temple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mountain appears above Kiev. An artist knows why it has come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Somali pope is writing an epic poem about nightmares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a thunderstorm in Coney Island. But instead of bolts of lightning, there are bolts of eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an ancient Austrian prophecy that you will eat a map.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A midwife wakes up one day and has turned into a cloud. It helps her understand the true meaning of paradoxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Orlando there is a child who has a Christmas tree instead of an elbow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are imprisoned in a giant crystal synagogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A busboy in Oregon spends her lunch break swallowing drones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Spartan accountant owns a telescope that gives her have complete control over bisexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A violinist dines with silence inside an emerald football stadium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stranger tells you that you can control the groin of a countess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vice president plans to imprison every shotgun in Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An opera singer makes a fortune trading in adolescence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a video game developer in New York that employs rose bushes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New Jersey, a satrap is building an exact copy of the Empire State Building out of tomatoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A viceroy owns a magic lantern slide which depicts every hope in Brooklyn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Hungarian software developer invents a new kind of peacock based on the movement of spiders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Iraqi ocean liner is sailing on an ocean of holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Egyptian dictator bans people from owning cuckoo clocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lime tree celebrates its graduation from university.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pharmacist sees an owl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Buenos Aires there is a teardrop which is reading Nietzsche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twelve theologians invent a world where everything is triangles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A legendary philosophical treatise describes a child made of balls of pure energy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up in a high school classroom. Nearby, a little boy is ringing a bell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A neurosurgeon invents a better version of knowledge: Playing a tennis match with mountain ranges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prince hears of a palace made of glass, and sends a henchman to break it into a million pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A five-star hotel in Ottawa is made of gonorrhea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tower with the mind of a software developer roams the streets of Birmingham. Just before sunrise it starts playing golf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman falls pregnant with the minimum wage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Russian theatre director stages a play about tomorrow that continues for 35 billion years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every physician in Addis Ababa is crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A supermodel owns a diamond that allows her to smell everything in Shanghai at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A homeless politician builds a church that is filled with the letter "B."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By looking at a sequence of twelve numbers, an arrogant congresswoman is able to make beards out of thin air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An economist finds a magical ferris wheel in Toronto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During the middle of the night a 26-year-old boy receives the memories of Richard Nixon.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>