<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump chickened out of going to Peru: On Tuesday, the White House announced that President Donald Trump was canceling his trip to Lima, Peru, for a regional summit with other heads of Latin American and Caribbean countries. His sudden cancellation… https://t.co/jWoYZ32haJ https://t.co/Ttgpikn2T1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: * Monitors and maintains Windows Server operating system and additional server components including but not limited to Active Directory, SharePoint, SQL Server, and Office Communications Server/Lync Server. * Applies patches to… https://t.co/SDWqrpGLVT https://t.co/sh5XkOdEmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance/Risk Management Framework (RMF) Specialist: * Provide Cybersecurity testing and security control validation and assessment of technical and non-technical security features implemented on a system or network in support of the DoD RMF… https://t.co/e6l9hYTA7Z https://t.co/VMehFWmXV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job Summary Assists in developing, implementing and maintaining an integrated program to protect the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of all information resources at MCH. Supports enterprise security applications… https://t.co/sh1tQkwkMO https://t.co/x9mDcycnsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design: Education-to-Hire Program: Are you looking to jumpstart a career in design? Do you have a design background, but youre looking to further your career? Then this is the opportunity is for you. The best part? No tuition payments until you are… https://t.co/u2Rq4wHsCh https://t.co/DgacuxbwCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip, trendsetting company looking for… https://t.co/AoXjD1w657]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Home Sales Counselor #2017-1777: New Home Sales Counselor For nine generations, Beazer Homes has built houses that families are proud to call home. Beazer Homes is hiring professional Sales Reps for our Hunt Club community in the Savannah, GA market.… https://t.co/9VmUSshbjA https://t.co/isXredQnUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preet Bharara: Likelihood that Cohen will be charged is high: Preet Bharara predicts the likelihood that Michael Cohen is going to be charged is "high." https://t.co/f1wyaLAQYG https://t.co/HXZ2uWBc1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFO with Healthcare Industry Experience: Miami, FL Full-time $175k – $200k Posted Today If you are a CFO with healthcare industry experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Chief… https://t.co/jPOmQ5HhKK https://t.co/QsgXyKM8ZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Administrator: Job description This candidate will be responsible for managing the CIELO Cloud VPN Infrastructure and CIELO Agent Deployments. These VPN tunnels connect CIELO to over 5,000 devices around the world for minutely around the clock… https://t.co/MbDfBmQZhL https://t.co/NO3ROQP0YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitecore Sr Developer: Sitecore Sr Developer – BrainTree Consulting Inc – Miami, FL – 03-12-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/SK8yPw1Cej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst Ref No.: 18-11510 Location: Miami, Florida Hi, Hope doing good!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job position Sr. Business Analyst with our client based in… https://t.co/R687cMOR4F https://t.co/wLhqMVImtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer: US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-12967 Location: miami, Florida WWS # 96843 CANDIDATE MUST HAVE NO VISA ISSUES OR CONTRACTUAL ISSUES THAT PREVENT CONVERSION TO FULL… https://t.co/cblV5QXH5t https://t.co/t0bCuvuJmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Based: Are you ready to join an inclusive work environment, contribute to our dynamic teams and "Seek and Achieve Excellence" in all you do? We are SBA Communications, (SBA) a leading independent owner and operator of wireless… https://t.co/XI7lkEUXSZ https://t.co/ec6RLlzLnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why it's better to search for a job while you already have one https://t.co/2m1j8s0amI https://t.co/CaVibsBwBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: What Business Development- Major Accounts contributes to Cardinal Health Business Development – Major Accounts is responsible for driving sales and services to new and existing customers. Responsible for maximizing customer… https://t.co/kuzMWcOYjL https://t.co/jPDJh9boLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Quality Systems and Analytics: What Advanced Analytics contributes to Cardinal Health Advanced Analytics is responsible for applying quantitative methodologies, techniques and tools to develop best in class analytic solutions that solve… https://t.co/5VXzyl1beQ https://t.co/JvJkpcyBhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See Cohen leaving hotel after raid: New CNN cellphone video shows President Donald Trump's personal attorney Michael Cohen leaving his hotel after the FBI raid. https://t.co/cTQp8fchG8 https://t.co/Ohv6fsiaJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannity's hypocrisy on Michelle and Melania: This entire incident began simply enough on Monday night when ABC's Jimmy Kimmel did what late-night comedy hosts do: He told a joke. But now that one joke has given way to an ugly episode involving Sean… https://t.co/0kBz83EuwV https://t.co/Jv3Nk6DblF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I was less valuable than a man' https://t.co/8qaQvVYa8N https://t.co/kUsP5WkF5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Estimator: Miami, FL Full-time $90k – $140k Posted Today If you are an Estimator with commercial construction experience, you'll want to read this… We are a Florida-based commercial construction company with 4 offices strategically located… https://t.co/sdB1m4YBby https://t.co/9injMSIlhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFO with Healthcare Industry Experience: Miami, FL Full-time $175k – $200k Posted Today If you are a CFO with healthcare industry experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Chief… https://t.co/HRuprfdlw9 https://t.co/0NM6fZwOUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Mueller team https://t.co/eqezzWnzf1 https://t.co/Ybc7Ljc4oK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior W/WW Project Manager (Seller/Doer), Miami: Tetra Tech is a leading provider of consulting, engineering, and technical services worldwide. Our reputation rests on the technical expertise and dedication of our employees16,000 people working together… https://t.co/AZ5KgvsJKv https://t.co/huaCZjJlHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer – Miami, FL – Contract: Title: Associate Engineer (.Net) L2 Type: Contract Duration: 5+ Months Location: Miami, FL Responsibilities: The dotNET Developers will be responsible for re-writing Graph DB and critical web services operations… https://t.co/y7WOhCu0Gv https://t.co/uxqfUbm5sL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Simpsons' addresses Apu criticism: Sunday night's episode of "The Simpsons" took on the controversy over a character, and not everyone thought the response was funny. https://t.co/4oVrJB7JWx https://t.co/Hm5nMctCfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design: Education-to-Hire Program: Are you looking to jumpstart a career in design? Do you have a design background, but youre looking to further your career? Then this is the opportunity is for you. The best part? No tuition payments until you are… https://t.co/UnG7XrQj23 https://t.co/wFKehW3BeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance/Risk Management Framework (RMF) Specialist: * Provide Cybersecurity testing and security control validation and assessment of technical and non-technical security features implemented on a system or network in support of the DoD RMF… https://t.co/Ks23XFOaGK https://t.co/9s2yD4Ir6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFO with Healthcare Industry Experience: Miami, FL Full-time $175k – $200k Posted Today If you are a CFO with healthcare industry experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Chief… https://t.co/1OR6VQZ57C https://t.co/SjtriHpDUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campus IT Technician (Part-Time – Evening/Weekend): West Coast University, a private university with the singular focus of educating health care professionals, is currently seeking a part-timeCampus Information Technology Technician. This is an… https://t.co/OdJXHZlYTa https://t.co/GShFgIctap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron): . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron) Engineer | Miamisburg, OH | Full Time Job Description Are… https://t.co/Tq4fgFP3pX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Network Defense – ACAS Specialist: * Investigate and analyze new threats, vulnerabilities, and exploits. This includes documenting and developing countermeasures using the Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA) Assured Compliance Assessment… https://t.co/kJ5OnW35AA https://t.co/4VLQ6b4Cre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hockey bus crash victims were misidentified; 1 survived, the other did not: The coroner misidentified two of the Humboldt Broncos hockey players involved in a fatal bus crash, according to the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. https://t.co/gBPnK5ZuZg https://t.co/X6c0INFcLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Dot Net developer: LOCATION: MIAMISBURG, OH/JACKSONVILLE, FL W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE POSITION (CAN’T WORK ON C2C) REQUIRED SKILLS: * .NET 4.5+ * C+ * Dependency Injection * WCF * Window Services NEED WORKING EXPERIENCE WITH THESE TOOLS: * Visual… https://t.co/0DQyH6y3Ho https://t.co/NFCoGKzQMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip, trendsetting company looking for… https://t.co/ipn0aLorJs https://t.co/WZZnuB7t9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IOS Developer (Miami): What you will do: Developing rich iOS applications that are used by millions of users worldwide. Developing Objective-C/Swift based SDK that is used by other developers. Participate and lead research and design of various… https://t.co/mWApul6q9y https://t.co/bPkstcXwtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr QA Consultant (For C# Application / Miami, FL: Job Tittle: QA for C# Applications Number of Contractors: 2 Rate: $Market/Hr Position: Contract Duration: Long-term Location: Miami, FL Required Skills:- * BS in Computer Science, Engineering discipline… https://t.co/ckZOgEnclo https://t.co/38kFfqAxb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: * Monitors and maintains Windows Server operating system and additional server components including but not limited to Active Directory, SharePoint, SQL Server, and Office Communications Server/Lync Server. * Applies patches to… https://t.co/0YZfaA9aW2 https://t.co/bpjJhE5O6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job Summary Assists in developing, implementing and maintaining an integrated program to protect the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of all information resources at MCH. Supports enterprise security applications… https://t.co/3qlPal36FK https://t.co/Cvf0GAe4nv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actress drops big news on Instagram: Kate Hudson and her boyfriend, musician Danny Fujikawa, made a big announcement on Instagram. https://t.co/ui0pIOtO9S https://t.co/fpvoYh485M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst/Programmer: The candidate must be local and available to start right away. Application Development Analyst/Programmer BXB-*******-485 6 Months+ Please No Third-Party Calls; this position is open for corp to corp, but… https://t.co/XfEERxE7Lf https://t.co/gG7tvbaWTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Paper Street Media has a small team of developers working on several new high traffic web products. As a senior developer, you will be working on new projects to add new features and solve problems in scalability, performance,… https://t.co/dvdBNjVg7s https://t.co/ioSPFvUsvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitecore Sr Developer: Sitecore Sr Developer – BrainTree Consulting Inc – Miami, FL – 03-12-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/daUE2Bfrsp https://t.co/0FxoHwJMJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst Ref No.: 18-11510 Location: Miami, Florida Hi, Hope doing good!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job position Sr. Business Analyst with our client based in… https://t.co/a0oAwhVW84 https://t.co/6RoPPmjQo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Based: Are you ready to join an inclusive work environment, contribute to our dynamic teams and "Seek and Achieve Excellence" in all you do? We are SBA Communications, (SBA) a leading independent owner and operator of wireless… https://t.co/12gy4Z3l0k https://t.co/qf2Q7geAxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer: US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-12967 Location: miami, Florida WWS # 96843 CANDIDATE MUST HAVE NO VISA ISSUES OR CONTRACTUAL ISSUES THAT PREVENT CONVERSION TO FULL… https://t.co/4JDiMGcwHw https://t.co/FhEcbKacUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters in Anchorage reject 'bathroom bill': Voters in Anchorage, Alaska, narrowly rejected a proposal to restrict bathroom access for transgender people, the first time such a measure was decided at the ballot box. https://t.co/tjGwdFYUl2 https://t.co/CUbxLCSAOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, JAVA Programmer: Careers Skip to Main Content Back Search Results Fluid Job Search Job Description Actions List – – – – – In List – In List – Return To List – Home – – – – – – – – Help – Sign Out Job Job Title Sr Analyst, JAVA Programmer –… https://t.co/67huOnsSsQ https://t.co/I8fKCpFcgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: What Business Development- Major Accounts contributes to Cardinal Health Business Development – Major Accounts is responsible for driving sales and services to new and existing customers. Responsible for maximizing customer… https://t.co/wXwo8QtYaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design: Education-to-Hire Program: Are you looking to jumpstart a career in design? Do you have a design background, but youre looking to further your career? Then this is the opportunity is for you. The best part? No tuition payments until you are… https://t.co/PHfCdRaQbp https://t.co/6uFvUyUYvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job Summary Assists in developing, implementing and maintaining an integrated program to protect the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of all information resources at MCH. Supports enterprise security applications… https://t.co/Sy93OlcNEW https://t.co/bRVN8ue3f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Joint Chiefs chairman worries about generals in Trump's White House: Retired Adm. Mike Mullen, a former chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff under Presidents George W. Bush and Barack Obama, said Sunday on CNN's "Fareed Zakaria GPS" that he has… https://t.co/cDhPIe5ggt https://t.co/TDJ48uHHsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip, trendsetting company looking for… https://t.co/C9w5wMIZkd https://t.co/8C9xcMBWD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: * Monitors and maintains Windows Server operating system and additional server components including but not limited to Active Directory, SharePoint, SQL Server, and Office Communications Server/Lync Server. * Applies patches to… https://t.co/FAmyFK87Az https://t.co/3r4CXJPH29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Paper Street Media has a small team of developers working on several new high traffic web products. As a senior developer, you will be working on new projects to add new features and solve problems in scalability, performance,… https://t.co/kZ78uXBUsi https://t.co/uQA3Is3nS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staffing Executive AT Salaried Professional Services – Miami Downtown: JOB REQUISITION Staffing Executive AT Salaried Professional Services – Miami Downtown LOCATION FL MIAMI JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within… https://t.co/jtNU9XHPdX https://t.co/y1CGatpC44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron): . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron) Engineer | Miamisburg, OH | Full Time Job Description Are… https://t.co/JzaeEg3ota https://t.co/VBmqQp4ZyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance/Risk Management Framework (RMF) Specialist: * Provide Cybersecurity testing and security control validation and assessment of technical and non-technical security features implemented on a system or network in support of the DoD RMF… https://t.co/Po2NyYO4k7 https://t.co/iPgLr3tLmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 resident dead, 6 firefighters hurt in Trump Tower fire: One person was seriously injured in a four-alarm fire at Trump Tower on Saturday, according to the New York City Fired Department. https://t.co/JhbipdSMxF https://t.co/6WXEdJzU0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitecore Sr Developer: Sitecore Sr Developer – BrainTree Consulting Inc – Miami, FL – 03-12-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/E5L8WXzwom https://t.co/kSBp6XVbvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior W/WW Project Manager (Seller/Doer), Miami: Tetra Tech is a leading provider of consulting, engineering, and technical services worldwide. Our reputation rests on the technical expertise and dedication of our employees16,000 people working together… https://t.co/gSPg0LH2wP https://t.co/quprav2Tid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst/Programmer: The candidate must be local and available to start right away. Application Development Analyst/Programmer BXB-*******-485 6 Months+ Please No Third-Party Calls; this position is open for corp to corp, but… https://t.co/4paJ6qcoSt https://t.co/Sanr6zgrLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Network Defense – ACAS Specialist: * Investigate and analyze new threats, vulnerabilities, and exploits. This includes documenting and developing countermeasures using the Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA) Assured Compliance Assessment… https://t.co/bUbDuKgaz0 https://t.co/ZwHPgqgnSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer – Miami, FL – Contract: Title: Associate Engineer (.Net) L2 Type: Contract Duration: 5+ Months Location: Miami, FL Responsibilities: The dotNET Developers will be responsible for re-writing Graph DB and critical web services operations… https://t.co/hRYE0ja67O https://t.co/o6gUcQCbrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campus IT Technician (Part-Time – Evening/Weekend): West Coast University, a private university with the singular focus of educating health care professionals, is currently seeking a part-timeCampus Information Technology Technician. This is an… https://t.co/erAZSvUhX2 https://t.co/mWEvxjaDut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 savings accounts pay 10x what your bank pays https://t.co/MGp1QrkH5O https://t.co/1WxmSyP15N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer: US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-12967 Location: miami, Florida WWS # 96843 CANDIDATE MUST HAVE NO VISA ISSUES OR CONTRACTUAL ISSUES THAT PREVENT CONVERSION TO FULL… https://t.co/ymU5u4wosw https://t.co/ULvPVeL3WP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst Ref No.: 18-11510 Location: Miami, Florida Hi, Hope doing good!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job position Sr. Business Analyst with our client based in… https://t.co/1VlIku2KEJ https://t.co/86yPDlaHPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr QA Consultant (For C# Application / Miami, FL: Job Tittle: QA for C# Applications Number of Contractors: 2 Rate: $Market/Hr Position: Contract Duration: Long-term Location: Miami, FL Required Skills:- * BS in Computer Science, Engineering discipline… https://t.co/DLQfkqK4MJ https://t.co/p6BfQ4GZB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Based: Are you ready to join an inclusive work environment, contribute to our dynamic teams and "Seek and Achieve Excellence" in all you do? We are SBA Communications, (SBA) a leading independent owner and operator of wireless… https://t.co/kNnWebh2jh https://t.co/uEeGh9IVkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IOS Developer (Miami): What you will do: Developing rich iOS applications that are used by millions of users worldwide. Developing Objective-C/Swift based SDK that is used by other developers. Participate and lead research and design of various… https://t.co/QruhdR8Vov https://t.co/lvilVyGTiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr QA Consultant (For C# Application / Miami, FL: Job Tittle: QA for C# Applications Number of Contractors: 2 Rate: $Market/Hr Position: Contract Duration: Long-term Location: Miami, FL Required Skills:- * BS in Computer Science, Engineering discipline… https://t.co/o8OdfH2Yyb https://t.co/orvL6lFYR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ally: I was poisoned: Former Trump adviser Roger Stone told CNN's Anderson Cooper his doctor believes he was poisoned with what may have been polonium. https://t.co/qk5qJFHvcr https://t.co/ep3vPvLB3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Dot Net developer: LOCATION: MIAMISBURG, OH/JACKSONVILLE, FL W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE POSITION (CAN’T WORK ON C2C) REQUIRED SKILLS: * .NET 4.5+ * C+ * Dependency Injection * WCF * Window Services NEED WORKING EXPERIENCE WITH THESE TOOLS: * Visual… https://t.co/XB8IGNkYXz https://t.co/UDsxQV2xQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, JAVA Programmer: Careers Skip to Main Content Back Search Results Fluid Job Search Job Description Actions List – – – – – In List – In List – Return To List – Home – – – – – – – – Help – Sign Out Job Job Title Sr Analyst, JAVA Programmer –… https://t.co/Mu8vakb6mx https://t.co/ocB3PgvFXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design: Education-to-Hire Program: Are you looking to jumpstart a career in design? Do you have a design background, but youre looking to further your career? Then this is the opportunity is for you. The best part? No tuition payments until you are… https://t.co/AIku8x6X4e https://t.co/D4Lt1ExTC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip, trendsetting company looking for… https://t.co/3onzdKNl1I https://t.co/kgk07OGTrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer – Miami, FL – Contract: Title: Associate Engineer (.Net) L2 Type: Contract Duration: 5+ Months Location: Miami, FL Responsibilities: The dotNET Developers will be responsible for re-writing Graph DB and critical web services operations… https://t.co/rfGORf42Eq https://t.co/ydch4TkA2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior W/WW Project Manager (Seller/Doer), Miami: Tetra Tech is a leading provider of consulting, engineering, and technical services worldwide. Our reputation rests on the technical expertise and dedication of our employees16,000 people working together… https://t.co/uqLYxWmbK8 https://t.co/Ii5g4IFbQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's originalist, Neil Gorsuch, finds his place: Neil Gorsuch slipped out his Colorado home a year ago to race to Washington and become President Donald Trump's first pick in a bid to reshape the judiciary. https://t.co/haY9E3CVJl https://t.co/76csdsqSWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance/Risk Management Framework (RMF) Specialist: * Provide Cybersecurity testing and security control validation and assessment of technical and non-technical security features implemented on a system or network in support of the DoD RMF… https://t.co/E2LMLlPwO8 https://t.co/Yh2LTBMXi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Paper Street Media has a small team of developers working on several new high traffic web products. As a senior developer, you will be working on new projects to add new features and solve problems in scalability, performance,… https://t.co/mE3reOZgMm https://t.co/hIrR2LYsxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job Summary Assists in developing, implementing and maintaining an integrated program to protect the integrity, confidentiality, and availability of all information resources at MCH. Supports enterprise security applications… https://t.co/IU4zbmp0WO https://t.co/QQzoefZ1WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFO with Healthcare Industry Experience: Miami, FL Full-time $175k – $200k Posted Today If you are a CFO with healthcare industry experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Chief… https://t.co/rZ9ZHglVNi https://t.co/AJi59riyog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design: Education-to-Hire Program: Are you looking to jumpstart a career in design? Do you have a design background, but youre looking to further your career? Then this is the opportunity is for you. The best part? No tuition payments until you are… https://t.co/FeBgEFQOWY https://t.co/BMFE5LUg0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorde roasted for Whitney Houston post: Pop star Lorde apologized after making what some thought was a joke about late singer Whitney Houston on social media. https://t.co/tZ9MVhPiIS https://t.co/6axO1TcalW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Manager- High Rise: Miami, FL Full-time $85k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Construction Manager with High Rise experience, please read on! We are one of the nation's top construction management and GC firms that has been around since… https://t.co/mBd0w7SNG2 https://t.co/JUtCeyCAMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Superintendent- High Rise: Miami, FL Full-time $85k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Construction Superintendent with High Rise experience, please read on! We are one of the nation's top construction management and GC firms that has been… https://t.co/VEY2s96Ryx https://t.co/PEFEfF8yA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst/Programmer: The candidate must be local and available to start right away. Application Development Analyst/Programmer BXB-*******-485 6 Months+ Please No Third-Party Calls; this position is open for corp to corp, but… https://t.co/ocvCTY52xl https://t.co/tvnwNnNlUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst Ref No.: 18-11510 Location: Miami, Florida Hi, Hope doing good!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job position Sr. Business Analyst with our client based in… https://t.co/Fpir6mtr0J https://t.co/5YeRyuSd1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campus IT Technician (Part-Time – Evening/Weekend): West Coast University, a private university with the singular focus of educating health care professionals, is currently seeking a part-timeCampus Information Technology Technician. This is an… https://t.co/BlCFxGmXR3 https://t.co/4T4phmWKh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staffing Executive AT Salaried Professional Services – Miami Downtown: JOB REQUISITION Staffing Executive AT Salaried Professional Services – Miami Downtown LOCATION FL MIAMI JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within… https://t.co/nmfj9xEYR2 https://t.co/2cEE9i7NgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt's revealing view on lights and sirens: There is precisely one specialty field in law enforcement that should command the immediate, unyielding and unquestioned respect of anyone focused enough to catch these unsung heroes in action. https://t.co/fpyBhPmpbp https://t.co/j0AgtUE08d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Network Defense – ACAS Specialist: * Investigate and analyze new threats, vulnerabilities, and exploits. This includes documenting and developing countermeasures using the Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA) Assured Compliance Assessment… https://t.co/RfNuX8Prah https://t.co/n8KsZB2jUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Dot Net developer: LOCATION: MIAMISBURG, OH/JACKSONVILLE, FL W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE POSITION (CAN’T WORK ON C2C) REQUIRED SKILLS: * .NET 4.5+ * C+ * Dependency Injection * WCF * Window Services NEED WORKING EXPERIENCE WITH THESE TOOLS: * Visual… https://t.co/L7K29LHYLH https://t.co/5LabfyohQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitecore Sr Developer: Sitecore Sr Developer – BrainTree Consulting Inc – Miami, FL – 03-12-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/HlXOOpbvll https://t.co/eQm75pvNH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IOS Developer (Miami): What you will do: Developing rich iOS applications that are used by millions of users worldwide. Developing Objective-C/Swift based SDK that is used by other developers. Participate and lead research and design of various… https://t.co/RqfueuyYF0 https://t.co/TBgGC15bJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer: US | Software Engineer-Developer / Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-12967 Location: miami, Florida WWS # 96843 CANDIDATE MUST HAVE NO VISA ISSUES OR CONTRACTUAL ISSUES THAT PREVENT CONVERSION TO FULL… https://t.co/sNFvXjnBE5 https://t.co/nkUgxjwr0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron): . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Project Manager, Civil Engineering (Dayton or Akron) Engineer | Miamisburg, OH | Full Time Job Description Are… https://t.co/t2lBTeiRk7 https://t.co/TAl6O4oE8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlords changed locks to keep Pruitt out, source says: The couple that rented out a room to Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt forced him out by changing the code on their locks after becoming increasingly frustrated with him as… https://t.co/ixJkKgHo5I https://t.co/JWnNuYtykD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>