<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/fZXvPtJsFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/CW55w3iERm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/pNuFoU089O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/VAJde5ncwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/6EtmDi8Rm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/B6fHT1jHE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/cNDE5ZQ9S3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/ibyodDCkna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/ysJzeZrgv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/af6QJXtjxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/00AHmjCGZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/RoAS0TQ0Tr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/bVYcGsnLy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/2pEwaDmicV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/JrsXLQExfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/62paQ4kn4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/uqPveGtklM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/tjcG7SDaUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/L4UsIDRy9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/minWhyfmx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/Oo1yHtRFNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/5FoAyiV0I3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/JuaM0XbTjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/txI9zP0dMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/vn7hRa5grg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/ifFvwwqYZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/5ZsGw1V7oX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/56OzuZ4MRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/4ieGxS5vDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/da3pMCI4eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/TprbHWhuSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/Cg4AXLHhKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/9og99l1pRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/LyQ1D6dR4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/2pEwaDmicV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/IfKNdiw4aA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/OrZeo6w5AT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/S6M9qM4Fkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/vNIqNjnpke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/sxedYG1zPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/ZF4yiCAmFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/7sYknW51T9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/N47ARItWp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/5k7Hz1oR0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>