<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Manager: Information Security Manager – Dunstable, Bedfordshire – Contract (Home Based 1-2 days per week). A global IT services company is searching for an Information Security Manager to join their team in Dunstable on a contract… https://t.co/ADGUUqUfBo https://t.co/bS3GUKphm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Developer – Birmingham: IOS Developer – Birmingham, West Midlands   Location – Birmingham, North Birmingham, Sutton Coldfield, West Midlands   Salary – 50k plus benefits   This advanced Software House based in North Birmingham are looking to add an… https://t.co/MGM40O2s6O https://t.co/J3qJDjmkme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position earning from £18k per annum? * Are you technically minded? * Do your family… https://t.co/cuKZsqL3po https://t.co/Xmvax8VBJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Consultant – London – £40-60k: BI Consultant – London – £40-60k This company was established 25 years ago, being one of Microsoft’s leading partner for Microsoft Data Platform solutions built on MS Azure in the UK. and within the past 5 years they… https://t.co/Twyc4ShPvW https://t.co/CEUPRcg1fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vimeo adds a channel exclusively for holograms: Vimeo has long regarded itself as the video-sharing site for those that want to get experimental. Well, the company has found a new medium to get creators pumped about, and I think it’s fair to say they’re… https://t.co/yJnWhFu8iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Support Technician: Has anyone told you that the IT department within any business is one of the most important parts of any company? This is an opportunity for you to be become part of a growing IT department who are currently stretched due to… https://t.co/Ut71vgOSxT https://t.co/Lvc578fGzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer – £60-70k – London – UK – Software Vendor, Personal Development Opportunity, Greenfield Project Work… Our client is looking for a Python Developer to come in and work in an agile environment on a variety of Greenfield… https://t.co/wnMJREpSF8 https://t.co/gBUVYsuxvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate guide to gifting STEM toys: tons of ideas for little builders: The holiday season is here again, touting all sorts of kids’ toys that pledge to pack ‘STEM smarts’ in the box, not just the usual battery-based fun. Educational playthings are… https://t.co/9ogiTM3ZN1 https://t.co/va1bnThADc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Platform Architect – UK Wide Travel: Microsoft O365 &amp; SharePoint Solutions Architect Remote – UK Wide Travel Salary: £65,000 – £70,000 + Benefits. Due to a period of continued expansion, my client based in the Midlands, is looking to extend… https://t.co/dCS3fCwFcW https://t.co/Wm1ruI1lKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Price cap will be good deal for customers, says Ofgem boss https://t.co/J9brp0T6NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook still isn’t taking Myanmar seriously: Facebook picked election evening in the U.S. to release a major report on its role in Myanmar, where it is widely accused of failing to prevent its social network from being used to incite genocide. The… https://t.co/9yGOIC00ni https://t.co/QEkDdINFPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Automation Test Engineer: Are you an experienced Automation Test Engineer? Looking to utilize your skills and experience and move into a senior position within an award-winning software company that is making waves across the global rail market?… https://t.co/XhPy9uUxp3 https://t.co/BF6We0fLh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer – C#, https://t.co/sI32uNl3fA – Junior / Mid: Full Stack Web Developer – C#, https://t.co/sI32uNl3fA – Graduate / Junior / Mid – Travel Website Haywards Heath Commutable from Brighton, Burgess Hill, Horsham and Crawley. Up to… https://t.co/bWV7r7nHue https://t.co/P0jfLZBcBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Tester: Cloud International are currently seeking an Automation Tester for their client who are a Market-Leading Software House based in York. You’ll be responsible for the design, implementation and delivery of scalable, maintainable,… https://t.co/M1AnhAoo3a https://t.co/dhwFm0sgwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIS Support Manager: Have you worked previously as an IT Manager or as a Management Information Systems Manager? We have an exciting opportunity not to be missed ….. gap personnel are currently recruiting for an MIS Support Manager to join a global… https://t.co/j6cdMKOapX https://t.co/t3SSqLs2Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: We are currently recruiting a 1st Line Support analyst working together in partnership with a successful and established business based in Peterborough. You will be responsible taking ownership and resolving users hardware and… https://t.co/09caGf5KYI https://t.co/k6l7eRMMO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy bills to be capped in new year https://t.co/C8lvTDY0nX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent to curb children's online gaming time https://t.co/LXg0vSx6ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PHP Developer: Looking for your next job as a PHP Web Developer in Attleborough South Norfolk, working with a cool, fun and vibrant global business? Then this is the opportunity for you. As a PHP Developer you will work closely with the… https://t.co/YUUShfjCdC https://t.co/F79W6DDgWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some online resources to help voters with disabilities on Election Day: After Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election, more states and counties in the United States are returning to paper ballots from electronic voting machines. While this… https://t.co/8XCujdnNVL https://t.co/wKAxYg70ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer (Tech stack: DevOps Engineer, Azure, AWS, C#, Docker, VSTS, ARM, Puppet, Chef, Jenkins, ELK, Grafana, Windows, Linux, DevOps Engineer, Urgent) At this very moment our client is constructing the world’s first intelligent… https://t.co/O3mZIN9Gra https://t.co/66KRv4nQY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Developer: Graduate Developer – do you want to launch your career the largest Open Source cloud telephony (VoIP) organisations in the UK? Do you want to learn and grow rapidly with the full support of every Senior Developer in our team? This is… https://t.co/IQDPhpnEkQ https://t.co/n5XDscQWu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One-year-old Bracket Capital is already an investor in Lyft, Bird, Airbnb and Coinbase: Two former private equity executives have entered the venture capital business via Bracket Capital. https://t.co/oSemREGAom https://t.co/5NKmTz9HRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SolutIon Architect: Location: Manchester or Leeds We are seeking an RPA Solution Architect to join a consultancy powerhouse with global reach. You will play a pivotal, full circle role in automation projects and drive the next generation of technology… https://t.co/xg7VQaZg8M https://t.co/pBSAwLom2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: Lead Developer C# Up to £55,000 doe +excellent benefits Based: Norwich Looking for a new job leading a team of developers who design, develop and test for one of the best known food supplier brands? Do you want to direct and be… https://t.co/ZjKM1pYvgp https://t.co/WwFoZa09rT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect: Technical Architect, Software Architect, LAMP, CI, DevOps Job Title: Technical Architect Salary: £60,000 Location: Bristol A growing Software House is looking for a Technical Architect to join their Development team. Benefits include… https://t.co/qmfPYg3iLX https://t.co/87giT0EfIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Analyst (Gatwick): Fusion Resources are seeking a competent and reliable Technical Analyst to join a highly successful global business based in Gatwick, London. The purpose of this role is to provide efficient support and solutions for IT needs… https://t.co/qWveaZzmKy https://t.co/QRRl9Am3Zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer – Back-end or Full-stack: PHP Developer – Back-end or Full-stack Dartford £20-35k VR/02426J Our client, a support and bespoke software/web development company based in Dartford, is looking for a Backend or Full Stack PHP Developer to join… https://t.co/D4uFIoVB3P https://t.co/XG6rRknVp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Analyst – FTSE 250 Business: IT Service Desk Analyst – FTSE 250 Business Human Capital Ventures is proud to be recruiting on behalf well known household name and FTSE 250 business head quartered in the Milton Keynes area, to join their… https://t.co/y4zb6O3eQn https://t.co/ck18hT47FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook opens its first small biz pop-up stores inside Macy’s: Facebook is bursting out of the ones and zeros into the physical realm with nine brick-and-mortar pop-up stores that will show off goods from 100 small business and online brands. Facebook… https://t.co/2AtqKrVWZS https://t.co/6p2nah53SQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position with excellent earning potential? * Are you technically minded? * Do your… https://t.co/529Twgx9Eg https://t.co/5YVfOonXNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procurement Manager: Procurement Manager Location: Europe, England, London Salary: £40000.00 – 60000.00 Job Type: Permanent Role: Procurement Manager Industry: FMCG Salary: £40,000 – £60,000 + Package Location: London Contact:… https://t.co/fYLAPQSezd https://t.co/Q9e0Xd8d16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subterranean drone mapping startup Emesent raises $2.5M to autonomously delve the deep: Seemingly every industry is finding ways to use drones in some way or another, but deep underground it's a different story. In the confines of a mine or pipeline,… https://t.co/scJDPDLor2 https://t.co/iPNRoqyFPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Speaking IT Business Integration Analyst: FRENCH SELECTION UK French Speaking IT Business Integration Analyst Support Engineer, Software, Technical Customer service, ERP, Fluent in French, CRM, Sage, Chef de Project, migration, implementation,… https://t.co/xJHtvPzU4X https://t.co/2qPoBVtJjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – C# Environment: Full Stack Developer – C# Environment Mid to senior level Developers with skills in C# / .NET / LINQ / AngularJS 2/ TypeScript / Bootstrap / NodeJS / jQuery / Entity Frameworks / HTML 5 / SQL / JSON Our client is a… https://t.co/fCMhqObBcI https://t.co/lleBL2gzwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung’s social logo teases a folding phone ahead of announcement: All of the major players have held events over the past few months, but hardware season still has a few last gasps left. The Samsung Developer Conference happening this week in San… https://t.co/Ywcs80F4kx https://t.co/f3vVdZ5wFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: If you are eager to learn and gain exposure to full stack of Microsoft Technologies &amp; other leading vendors and grow we want to hear from you today! A leading IT Provider is seeking an individual with an excellent customer service… https://t.co/ePmRST8oP7 https://t.co/gYfkBnwVxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenyans cash in on avocado craze https://t.co/aVCf7FO8Gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook’s election interference problem exponentially worse on eve of midterms, study suggests: An analysis of political advertisers running extensive campaigns on Facebook targeting users in the United States over the past six months has flagged a raft… https://t.co/woiAhAJKmQ https://t.co/Ga4J80NbL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Administrator: IT Administrator Our client, a legal body, requires an IT Administrator. This is a permanent, entry-level role which is ideal for an individual who is seeking a career in IT. This role is paying £20,000 P/A plus a discretionary bonus.… https://t.co/GWnTtG2Lt8 https://t.co/RCNFZDSWUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloqboard lets you lend others your hard-earned crypto: Vitaly Bahachuk wants you to share your crypto. His company lets you lend cryptocurrency peer-to-peer via smart contract, ensuring you can send your buds some red hot Ether and, in theory, they have… https://t.co/qAouP9VpCs https://t.co/SbKebbrL50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre Sales Solution Manager – Azure / AWS: Overall Job Purpose: As Solutions Manager, you will be part of the Cloud / Data Centre Services Pre-Sales team, reporting to the Head of DCS Pre-Sales. You will act as an advisor, consultant and thought leader… https://t.co/F5xsXmCzk2 https://t.co/Wv2u5d89uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xi Jinping pledges to cut Chinese import tariffs https://t.co/FdPodtTPRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New car sales fall again in October, say manufacturers https://t.co/9aOnB2vKyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Support &amp; Managed Service Manager: Client Support &amp; Managed Service Manager A new opportunity has a risen for a Client Support &amp; Managed Service Manager to join a well established Insurance Solution Provider based in Chelmsford. As the Client… https://t.co/TJQuS2qLkC https://t.co/kuADVqcHk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lime is putting $3 million toward electric scooter and bike safety: On the heels of Lime notifying the public about needing to recall some of its scooters due to fire concerns, Lime is putting $3 million toward a new safety initiative called “Respect the… https://t.co/sCZFB4lUaZ https://t.co/cZ68vzpYWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer – Cloud (NetApp): Role Profile Within the role of Focal Engineer (Cloud), you will act as a technical lead within your nominated customer account for both internal and external requirements. You will act as an internal technical… https://t.co/bv63m3Ysvn https://t.co/EC92NuXYV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Manager: An SEO Manager is sought for an established eCommerce retailer based in South Devon. Candidates with upwards of two years SEO experience shall be considered. Benefits Package is excellent so send me your CV now. You will be responsible for… https://t.co/1Jxa6BUEVc https://t.co/kCW5RAcAyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: This is an opportunity for a Data Analyst looking to take the next step in their career with this up and coming e-commerce business. Your New Company: An up and coming e-commerce Company who with a 4 Star rating by current employees are… https://t.co/p0BlUKwHEG https://t.co/5DZnJx8DI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Karma acquires Noddle from TransUnion and expands to the UK: Credit Karma, the US startup with 85 million users that offers credit reports and a platform to browse and buy other financial services, has made an acquisition to help it kick-start its… https://t.co/OszI395PX7 https://t.co/QNlfBNJCdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Line Infrastructure Support Analyst: 3rd Line Infrastructure Support | Competitive Salary + benefits Hertfordshire| FMCG My client, one of the UKs largest pharmaceutical companies, is currently looking for a senior 3rd Line Infrastructure Support… https://t.co/LVSBpNjGif https://t.co/lbxYKJmTdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst Programmer – VB6/.Net/Oracle/SQL: Analyst Programmer – VB6/.Net/Oracle/SQL We have an exciting opportunity for an experienced Analyst Programmer looking for a challenging and interesting development role. As an Analyst Programmer you will develop… https://t.co/4CvHuxGMMg https://t.co/gEuVGxTnxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Korean AI startup Skelter Labs lands strategic investment to expand to Southeast Asia: Korean AI startup Skelter Labs is expanding to Southeast Asia after it pulled in undisclosed funding from Singapore-based VC firm Golden Gate Ventures. Skelter Labs… https://t.co/I1iAERgE4d https://t.co/5quR5DcgeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Rob: Systems Architect – IT Architect – London – Contract We are currently looking for a Systems Architect to work for a very reputable consultancy on a project in the financial services sector. Candidates will need to have experience: *… https://t.co/3iCG6pE6op https://t.co/poKiYRxSlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Delivery Manager : Agile: Gerrard White is currently seeking a Delivery Manager / Project Manager to manage the delivery of multiple software application development projects for a leading insurance group through the full lifecycle from initial… https://t.co/Qa6gd0wu8y https://t.co/Ecm0POSILu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Service Engineer: Field Service Engineer (Dental &amp; IT systems) – covering installations, support &amp; repair work, inspections / planned maintenance – for this highly successful dental systems provider. The role has come about due to an engineer… https://t.co/CmJCPOue8K https://t.co/rSoYqGPLZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer, Azure, Windows, Linux, Powershell, Bash: DevOps Engineer, Azure, Windows, Linux, Powershell, Bash (Tech stack: DevOps Engineer, Azure, Windows, Linux, Unbuntu, Powershell, bash, OpenStack, Kubernetes, SQL Server, MySQL, SCCM, Puppet,… https://t.co/yMHijviLV7 https://t.co/VmKEyRTSN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: We're delighted to be working with a fantastic start-up who are developing innovative BI &amp; analytics solutions for the pharmaceutical industry. This is an exciting opportunity to join a business with a growing client base that… https://t.co/yzEzXPC2po https://t.co/C6IjZCmkko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Coordinator: Who are we: aap3 are accredited providers of IT Managed Services and Solutions, Project based support and resource augmentation providing our clients and partners with innovative capability solutions. aap3 is transforming the future… https://t.co/mpByjY7wdF https://t.co/euo2aBdGrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reportedly in ‘advanced talks’ to open HQ2 in Virginia: These sorts of major decision no doubt take some time. And, of course, Amazon is clearly milking the decision making process for all it’s worth as cities across the States roll out the red… https://t.co/z49u0MgLr3 https://t.co/sEp2Quvxzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Blockchain and Crypto): Software Developer (Blockchain and Crypto) My client enable businesses to realise the full potential of Blockchain. They are currently delivering solutions and innovations that are scalable, secure and… https://t.co/9LhnPVQR23 https://t.co/uWlbOCDkvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patisserie Valerie chairman waives salary https://t.co/uCCyqsIowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer An award winning fin-tech brand are looking for a SQL Developer to be work within a complex Business Intelligence Solutions and Data Warehousing environment. They have a reputation for quality work and are currently… https://t.co/yXSlLFPwyv https://t.co/0MJMTkfyOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Engagement Consultant (Sales): This dynamic startup loves out of the box thinking. The company prides itself on empowering it's employees to deliver truly revolutionary mobile experiences. They are seeking an exceptionally creative and innovative… https://t.co/PK4EQLUmO8 https://t.co/LICrFYJeNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Accountant (SunSystems): An international consultancy practice, specialising in, enterprise asset management software solutions and financial accounting systems is seeking an Accountant to join its rapidly expanding team in London. As a Systems… https://t.co/Xnblf6wpYo https://t.co/M6lL7GuTyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Architect – DV Cleared: SOLUTION LEAD/ARCHITECT -SECURITY The primary responsibility of a Solution Lead is to assist the delivery of a viable, management and fit-for-purpose solution that meets the needs of the client and is capable of… https://t.co/938M5e7Oua https://t.co/SvRnzVSftY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Account Manager Bulgaria: We are currently recruiting for a number of clients based in Bulgaria and we are urgently seeking experienced candidates with an excellent command of the English language and possessing first class communication skills – both… https://t.co/NrmaIdvbXa https://t.co/3NQL5ulW8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Western Railway workers in fresh strike over guards dispute https://t.co/NT4XFcgTxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glenrath Farms wins Peebles chicken shed appeal https://t.co/gTqevZz8zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Video Technology Company – Warrington: NET Developer – Video Technology Company – Warrington (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/nzWEdvqDSY MVC 5, MongoDB, RavenDB, Scrum/Agile, SQL Server 2016, Angular, .NET Developer, Urgent) Our… https://t.co/02Aar4WL7B https://t.co/fxIhBFO983]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Our client is an International life sciences company who, due to growing success is currently expanding their team. This is an exciting for an organised, ambitious IT professional to take the next step in their career with a global… https://t.co/xWVdg2MHBB https://t.co/jBevsnvica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon is letting users choose the day packages are delivered: Amazon Day looks like one of those options you’ll wonder how you ever managed to live without. The new feature, which is currently being tested for select Prime users, offers up a choice of… https://t.co/oHd8A9z5Pl https://t.co/SEDkUcIEUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAFM first line support/administration: CAFM support Our client, an FM services provider has identified a requirement for a CAFM administrator. This is a great opportunity to become part of their Software Solutions Team which will aims to deliver and… https://t.co/pKoBMBZUZP https://t.co/qXsGK1d4Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Assistant: IT Assistant required to work for an industrial company based near Wombwell, Barnsley You will report to the IT Manager to assist the office with Microsoft Office 365, printer, photocopier and any other IT issues You will also be required… https://t.co/mIgB2GCqvx https://t.co/i3cNrDaPpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: MultiValue/Unidata Lead Developer Salary: Competitive Location: Oxfordshire Our Client is an Oxfordshire based Software house and they have an exciting opportunity for a Lead Developer to be part of their Mobile Development Team. you will… https://t.co/Txu60O9uQZ https://t.co/kp9FT4CqTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blockchain firm bought asteroid mining company Planetary Resources: Here’s a match made in…I don’t know, somewhere on the blockchain, I guess. Pioneering space startup Planetary Resources was acquired by, of all things, a blockchain firm this week.… https://t.co/tbWrUHP1pq https://t.co/YdhCKaGstk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Java Programmer – Java Engineer: Excitining Opportunity! We are on the outlook for an exceptional Java Developer to work for a major EU Organisation. This is a long-term contract role with real possibilities of renewal. The successful… https://t.co/lqXuuLqWY0 https://t.co/VsPEuTX15Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber security consultant: As this is a short gig this would be ideal as a portfolio builder for a contractor looking for UK Gov experience. Job description The security of our website and applications is of paramount importance to business continuity… https://t.co/CIzpy60FHk https://t.co/ctiT8022Wg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scala Developer – Sports Streaming: Brilliant opportunity for a Scala Developer to work on a truly revolutionary platform that will boast millions of users – you’ll be coming in at a stage where you’ll enjoy input and influence into the design of the… https://t.co/LEfTg3pP8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPhone is reportedly getting 5G in 2020: The first 5G phones are set to start arriving next year. Motorola plans to bring next-gen connectivity via a Mod for the Z3, and companies like LG and OnePlus have promised to deliver the tech baked into… https://t.co/DKwSEGNs9b https://t.co/DyARvf6OvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of Hours Service Desk Analyst: Company Description We are part of Link Group, a leading global provider of financial administration solutions. As one of Europe’s leading asset servicing platforms, Link Asset Services interacts with almost 6m… https://t.co/J7cZeH5sui https://t.co/aOEdabuBI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programme Manager: Programme Manager- SW London Description:  This role has end-to-end accountability for the successful delivery and deployment of the Central Finance function operating Model change – managing schedule / plans; scope, resources and… https://t.co/prJ6G9bE1X https://t.co/sOxGTiSdW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a court filing, Edward Snowden says a report critical to an NSA lawsuit is authentic: An unexpected declaration by whistleblower Edward Snowden filed in court this week adds a new twist in a long-running lawsuit against the National Security Agency’s… https://t.co/4SOUXDxKiK https://t.co/TLDYpFvIzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Business Analyst: A European role for a Business Analyst to deliver and roll out tools to the wider business, creating dashboards, project managing, excellent communication skills, training(Tableau/Power BI)European Languages preffered not… https://t.co/ufFolfO45G https://t.co/1MomemwB2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior BI Developer: Senior Business Intelligence Developer / BI Developer A BI Developer is required for an innovative organisation in central London who are genuinely making a difference to the world in positive way. The successful BI developer will… https://t.co/ax4QdRdqrt https://t.co/3M5OVmdsJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A long and winding road to new copyright legislation: Dave Davis Contributor Dave Davis joined Copyright Clearance Center in 1994 and currently serves as a research analyst. He previously held directorships in both public libraries and corporate… https://t.co/IYP5kVfY7x https://t.co/t9aIFRU4Yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Field Engineer (Hardware and Software Break Fix): We are SCC – Specialist Computer Centres – the leading IT services provider in Europe. Our business is expanding creating a great opportunity for a talented Field Engineer to join our organisation to… https://t.co/24U26paKpk https://t.co/PT7hdFIVCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish border problem is a 'red herring', says DUP MP https://t.co/iJWSSX6iGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back – End Python Developer: Back – End Python Developer – Competitive Salary – London * Are you an experienced Back –end Python Developer? * Do you have strong knowledge of SQL? * Have you got experience mentoring junior members of staff? To find out… https://t.co/RdgpLVSeql https://t.co/L4Cv68VmVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant MI Manager: Assistant MI Manager Location – Stoke-on-Trent Salary – £35,000 to £40,000 A market leading company is looking for an Assistant MI manager to join there expanding Data management team. Your main responsibility is to provide insights… https://t.co/RIjnsflBQo https://t.co/POMHa05hus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumble drops its $400M lawsuit against Match, but this battle isn’t over: Bumble and Match’s ongoing legal battles are continuing today. According to a statement released by Match Group this morning, Bumble is dropping its $400 million lawsuit against… https://t.co/oMbNSPYDZm https://t.co/bh9y3QugzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Field Engineer (Hardware and Software Breakfix): We are SCC – Specialist Computer Centres – the leading IT services provider in Europe. Our business is expanding creating a great opportunity for a talented Field Engineer to join our organisation to… https://t.co/9TnSlH3dFV https://t.co/kwrnxlk1Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd/3rd Line Infrastructure Engineer – Central London: 2nd/3rd Line Infrastructure Engineer – Central London – Permanent – £40,000 DOE I am currently recruiting for a 2nd/3rd Line Infrastructure Engineer to join an exciting business who work in the… https://t.co/B4dzvmz8aw https://t.co/DHT8okoml3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamic Yield, which builds Amazon-like personalisation for the rest of us, raises $38M: Amazon, one of the world’s largest companies, has transformed the face of commerce in part because it has managed at once to be “The Everything Store” but still with… https://t.co/HErVjCwNQn https://t.co/5pWaIL7OUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer: Are you a JavaScript, HTML and CSS expert? Do you have experience working in a fast-paced, dynamic and agile environment? Would you like to work for the UK’s largest specialist wine retailer? If you have answered yes to these… https://t.co/CQ9UyBpyb7 https://t.co/sOal5vL4Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dev Ops Engineer – 100% AWS, 100% Infrastructure as Code: Exciting Marketing Company with global reach is looking for a DevOps or Platform Engineer to take responsibility for their AWS environment. Currently running at 100% AWS and 100% Infrastructure as… https://t.co/WNovWpeTQI https://t.co/EhGBIE6uHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lloyds replacing some debit cards after cyber-attacks https://t.co/RKEq5YxpOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How real is Trump's jobs 'miracle'? https://t.co/YgAJDHKoQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer (Contractor): £300 – £425pd Bristol City 3-6 Months Greenfield Project One of Capita’s growing business partners are looking for a skilled, enthusiastic developer to work with the in-house team on a single, large-scale greenfield project… https://t.co/ox4boqQyZM https://t.co/bvz4yk5rBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final season of House of Cards is out now: The ultimate chapter of the political drama House of Cards is officially out. The Netflix original series is in its sixth and final season, and without a new lead. Following sexual misconduct allegations… https://t.co/rPwb2nUHh1 https://t.co/ClBAViuxee]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>