<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/Xh0YXhRbdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/zF4yCUIEFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/IL3wrHopob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/C2InXe3ckV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/KT5s7qUwJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/CvuLkfUAdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/HNQAVnAf1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge : " Your wife charges that you haven't spoken to her in  5 years. Why is that?" Defendant: "I didn't dare interrupt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/c0q2O0aBWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/e5ZUAgD5FD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/eLARNlxgWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/RtTnndqTw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/MA0V0rRXqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/AcuRU6RVRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/pkq6v16wJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/RfEVkOjC9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/tTEInKwGvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/m93QerV61g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/aIZBZ1Xj5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/11UUGgez8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/X70ZgRPWQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/qPcSluX8kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/CZNDgDNCWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/CvkqA1y8gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/bP68ELRj5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget how fast you did a job - but they remember how well you did it. - Howard Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/eBwEBngo1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/pdE76JODgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/YdJQwgG6Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/aT5jsZp9qT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/xYvg1JEYJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/1OSuzEXROf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/Ht1MLCz2gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/EfenmFX5Sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/fSUbuvcWQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/LFMDPicFpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/REPopegBr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/dwRi9QjEYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/ndOC15W577]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/s6k3wa72yN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/WaSXabrogQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/Ncnbh5fme8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/ULzffyxvk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/cgGLNbvOP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/sxF7BFLAie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoes are special shoes for discerning feet. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/A5YauXtEmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/6O078VhHdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/UzxxpWzKFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/NeGcBSBbSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/ZNmAXlTkIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/BU2kCcfSwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/4IUgw2LrPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/7VxMzIluLl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>