<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can
do."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll do more GOOD if you aim to SERVE more than you aim to PLEASE. - Chris Edmonds #quote #leadership #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss this little person! 

#grandaughter #love @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/MNHfARFauX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Education is what remains after one has forgotten
everything he learned in school.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight against something and we focus on the thing we hate. Fight for something and we focus on the thing we love. - Simon Sinek #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first and the best victory is to conquer self.”
- Plato #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Debbie and Patty! We celebrated at the Jeremy Camp concert! A little taste of… https://t.co/Olo1itGsSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I myself am made entirely of flaws, stitched together with good intentions. - Augusten Burroughs #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matrixblogg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bad news: nothing is permanent. The good news: nothing is permanent. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The real opportunity for success lies within the person and
not in the job"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a limit to how many steps you'll be able to take today. Make sure they're all in the right direction. - Jeff Sheehan #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude is a little thing that makes a big difference. - Winston Churchill #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassment lasts a moment, regrets last a lifetime. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up what you want most, for what you want now. - Zig Ziglar #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend in Italy sent this to me! I thought it was pretty cool!

#tattoo #awesome @ Historic… https://t.co/pvxQPGyH5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every exit is an entry somewhere else. -Tom Stoppard #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so busy I don't know whether I found a rope or lost my horse. - Mark Schaefer #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none. - Shakespeare #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to success is doing the stuff other people won't do &amp; doing it for a really long time. - John Jantsch #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Obviously, there is little you can learn from doing nothing"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't judge me by my past. I don't live there anymore. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you treat yourself sets the standard for how others will treat you. - Steve Maraboli #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline is just choosing between what you want now and what you want most. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you are thankful for something God has blessed you with today! https://t.co/MqRicMEIbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest glory is, not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.
 Ancient Proverb #failure  #succeed  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9
“The power of imagination makes us infinite.”
- John Muir #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of fear is to raise your awareness, not to stop your progress. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Happy are those who dream dreams and are ready to pay
the price to make them come true.”
- Leon J. Suenes #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people say they'd like to be in your shoes, it's usually after the difficult journey is finished. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the character of someone is not clear to you, look at their friends. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in Christianity as I believe that the sun has risen: not only because I see it, but because by it I see everything else.C.S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mind is your prison when you focus on your fear. - Tim Fargo #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't live a perfect day with doing something for
someone who will never be able to repay you."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others. - Gandhi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the character of someone is not clear to you, look at their friends. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The soil says, "Don’t bring me your need. Bring me your
seed."
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest mistake you can make is listening to people who've given up on their dreams telling you to give up on yours. - Umair Hague #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s not what happens to you that determines how far you
will go in life; it is how you handle what happens to you"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving is important. Thriving is elegant. - Maya Angelou #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll do more GOOD if you aim to SERVE more than you aim to PLEASE. - Chris Edmonds #quote #leadership #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't appreciate what you bring to the table.. then let them eat alone. - Unknown #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others. - Gandhi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If winning isn't everything, why do they keep score?"
- Vince Lombardi #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you choose today will determine who you are tomorrow. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassment lasts a moment, regrets last a lifetime. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must learn to translate wisdom and strong feelings into
labour"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like photography. You need the negatives to develop. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we don't start, it's certain we can't arrive"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't judge me by my past. I don't live there anymore. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as a minor lapse of integrity. - Tom Peters #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My mentor said, 'Let's go do it,' not 'You go do it.' How
powerful it is when someone says, 'Lets!’"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes life takes an unexpected wrong turn in the right direction. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know of only one duty, and that is to love. - Albert Camus #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up what you want most, for what you want now. - Zig Ziglar #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to success is doing the stuff other people won't do &amp; doing it for a really long time. - John Jantsch #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you would create something, you must first become
something.”
- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people say they'd like to be in your shoes, it's usually after the difficult journey is finished. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will work unless you do.”
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating the mind without educating the heart is no education at all.- Aristotle #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss these two little people! Grandpa and grandma love you!

#grandson #granddaughter #love @… https://t.co/lABObwpDLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mind is your prison when you focus on your fear. - Tim Fargo #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing more expensive than education is ignorance."
- Benjamin Franklin #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't make the world go round; love is what makes the ride worthwhile. - Elizabeth Barrett Browning #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability is a poor man's wealth."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ask God to guide your footsteps if you're not willing to move your feet. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are some giants you are fighting right now? Health, finances, relationships?

Check out my latest blog==&gt;https://t.co/ZICsjFF0QH https://t.co/FaqeHJ3zL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your goals in front of you and your fears behind you. - Tony Robbins #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us never negotiate out of fear. But let us never fear to negotiate. - John F. Kennedy #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is the end result of all true learning.- Leo Buscaglia #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will prepare and some day my chance will come. - Abraham Lincoln #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone started at the beginning!

#newstarts #freshstarts #beginner @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/YRjcYiqjYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd buy that for a dollar! What can you buy for a dollar? Check it out here on my latest blog==&gt;https://t.co/IQ8BgZ5bfZ

#makemoneyfromhome #workfromhome #beyourownboss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating small victories!

#celebrate #godisgood #amen @ Rogue Ales &amp; Spirits https://t.co/EqzDhbw965]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd buy that for a dollar! What can you buy for a dollar? Check it out here on my latest blog==&gt;https://t.co/IQ8BgZ5bfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The miracle is this, the more we share, the more we have. - Leonard Nimoy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Positive thinking will let you use the abilities, training and
experience you have"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistently investigate what gives other people energy. Be the fan that fuels it. - Darren Rowse #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The athlete who says that something cannot be done should
never interrupt the one who is doing it."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything from your past does not belong in your present. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom begins with owning your flaws and disowning your fears. - Umair Hague #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth obtained by fraud will dwindle, but whoever earns it through labor will multiply it" Proverbs 13:11 (HCSB). #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't appreciate what you bring to the table.. then let them eat alone. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you get by reaching your destination is not nearly as
important as what you will become by reaching your
destination"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to let school get in the way of my child's education. - Mitch Joel #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so freakin' cool!

#awesome #cool #ferriswheel @ Leavenworth, Washington https://t.co/VhOFikUZPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging in Leavenworth for our anniversary!

#love #40thanniversary #bff @ Leavenworth, Washington https://t.co/XgQRsy6Fie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 40th anniversary Debbie Lynn!

#anniversary #love #40thanniversary #bestfriend @… https://t.co/7HJZhPxQXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you made some progress today? What did you learn today?

#progress #grow… https://t.co/ecY9vzTMsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people will never accomplish the long term great because they settle for the short term good. – Reg Saddler #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10
"Your attitude is an expression of your values, beliefs and
expectations"
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ultimately comes down to trust.- Marcus Sheridan #quote #socialmedia #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Resolve to pay any price or make any sacrifice to get into the
top ten percent of your field. That payoff is incredible!”
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest glory is, not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.
 Ancient Proverb #failure  #succeed  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Optimism is the one quality more associated with success
and happiness than any other”
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every exit is an entry somewhere else. -Tom Stoppard #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream big dreams! Imagine that you have no limitations,
and then decide what's right before you decide what's
possible"
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy, that makes happiness. - Charles Spurgeon #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>