<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/7i3AV3r3hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/fwx9pRIJpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/8C4QVvFyVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/2utSxrBS60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/CqkHMQB9cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/0NQ7jFVbaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/qtYCmZdqdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/joUX0KUayo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/xuvVI0gIJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/Jw8EciK98k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/K02JbhRDQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/eZtw6WWAPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/Q76JLIprKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/k1qkt0jPhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/y6ClcbTjAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/HjrMHyd3Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/ZVcYWjdbwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/XQeAEhdfBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/YUj3oZ354I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/f6XXV4Rp6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/5AsoMwmGWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/GIQGS0kDUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/HlPFhbeAiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/plEVENCF4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/C0IC50PdZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/tUNEzMIpv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/SeKTSlQdgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/DsVaN29ZOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/hO48m7ig5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/vs9jqcvoRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/VzrBoJWLJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/wFuUbNNGw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/IUsDkI5OI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/lMuTHS1HQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/AeVCjICFk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SJkbrmeChV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/E8zObTRvin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/fWbqjkZIa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/uMali8f6e6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/oh1ePo0yMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/ZBFaaDb72T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/DiHFGtUU0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/6mFOJalNlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/bIIBWMPzIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/JOz398hFwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/K4b2r14vh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/nyIByrd7Bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Jtb6zuoplL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/8ID1EpetJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/vLWpd2IMmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>