<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer: Principal Systems Engineer Princeton, NJ As part of SRI’s Integrated Systems and Solutions Division, the Senior Principal Scientist/Engineer leads multi-disciplinary teams in the innovation, development and deployment of… https://t.co/EDwgWO7rZC https://t.co/kYQ0cZSvKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration and Test Engineer: 109224BR Senior Integration and Test Engineer CO – Aurora 109224BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving… https://t.co/Xpq7L4aX67 https://t.co/slzrl0VqoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Success Manager: Redwood City, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Customer Success Manager with a knack for creating an engaging customer experience, please read on! Based in Redwood City, CA, we are a rapidly growing startup… https://t.co/u2ZW8R1ns9 https://t.co/RZtLiHLtgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: We’re looking for an experienced Rails developer to join our team. Build great products while contributing to our community with open source, writing, speaking, events, and more. Requirements thoughtbot web developers are able to rapidly… https://t.co/IxllyjTWml https://t.co/9ra1qW6f5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Software Engineer: Flight Software Engineer Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture – History –… https://t.co/oicyPjxOgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actuarial Analyst – Programmer: – Location: Chicago, Illinois, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: May 5, 2018 – Position Title:Actuarial Analyst – Programmer – Company Name:AON – Job Function:Risk Management/Loss Control/Investigations About AON… https://t.co/HWNEMR7UGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guidance, Navigation and Control Manager: Req ID : 434591BR Job Code/Title : L2335:Guidance, Nav &amp; Ctrl Mgr Job Description : Manages a team responsible for the design, development, implementation, verification and testing of algorithms to perform… https://t.co/IHJJug2lMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Architect: Job ID: JR-******* Description: As the health care industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable health care for our… https://t.co/fxvQCL8LG7 https://t.co/QPpB5kb8qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presales Senior Solution Consultant (SAP Ariba): Presales Senior Solution Consultant (SAP Ariba) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/TiyIhjsCQP https://t.co/bLeSFuKYjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Architect | Houston Sr. Consultant: About the role As a client-facing UX designer, you will deliver primary and secondary research and client interviews to ensure that all projects are driven by user needs and business outcomes. Youll facilitate and… https://t.co/cfktIepWzT https://t.co/whx0CkmR0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Fremont, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/01/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview ETL Developer/Programmer Terms: 12 months (12 months potential extension) Location: Fremont CA 94538… https://t.co/4LYOk4I6EC https://t.co/mBY9FjZgou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Automation Software Designer: We believe in the power of people. We are a network strategy and technology company that is motivated by making a difference in people’s lives – their productivity, their creativity, their health and comfort. That’s… https://t.co/YkWMvb3T89 https://t.co/AAB47ptAux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/oKCNI40h5H https://t.co/KsLw4l4MMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/E1SFddGpzD https://t.co/8511JA6qOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/ltU90II2X9 https://t.co/WJshjoSkfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/ufSpEPb45J https://t.co/9MOZfoXKu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/RvkRDlFN2U https://t.co/ZTKCNPKHJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/buQZwnyTE1 https://t.co/msR1t5dTKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/O4Mz1ckQNi https://t.co/JbdtQomDIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Sales Director – Primary Care: Overview Salix Pharmaceuticals is one of the largest specialty pharmaceutical companies in the world. Founded in 1989, Salix is committed to the prevention and treatment of gastrointestinal (GI) diseases. Salix’s… https://t.co/Q7wKz9Z97n https://t.co/j7g5QwMBKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avionics Software Engineer, Associate: Applicant Home Job Description – Ball Corporation Job Title: Avionics Software Engineer, Associate – ****** Job ID: ****** Location: OH – Dayton (Fairborn) Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Return… https://t.co/F4iw243TZD https://t.co/9OBM3u3e6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Automation Specialist: Company Description: Crown Equipment Corporation is a leading innovator in world-class forklift and material handling equipment and technology. As one of the world’s largest lift truck manufacturers, we are committed to… https://t.co/gzai6v9XSZ https://t.co/HV8mXVvpF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Position Description As an Associate Software Engineer at Scientific Games you will work on the frontlines of a game development team. You will implement, debug, modify and generally support in-game features, development and… https://t.co/MCZK7XT8SK https://t.co/8zXE1NjiYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Algorithm Developer – Engineer: We are looking for an experienced algorithm developer to come on board to lead development of technology that will play an important role in how people will find jobs in the future. Our international team gets along very… https://t.co/Saxh420tUL https://t.co/I6GWE2GWao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Financial Developer: Senior C++ Financial Developer McLean, VA Join a team of Financial Engineers responsible for the C++ Library that implements the major market and credit risk models for a trillion-dollar balance sheet of mortgages and… https://t.co/fK9tb4ovjt https://t.co/Q1ljD9iqKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Apps Programmer: Our direct client located in Mayfield Village, OH is looking for a mobile application developer to work on one of their delivery teams. The ideal candidate will have experience creating, maintaining and testing iOS and/or… https://t.co/MMQ5pzWgRN https://t.co/AZDnTBnkJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant – Requisition code: XGGS18FC0518COS1: Requisition code: XGGS18FC0518COS1 Consultant Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Consultant in Costa Mesa, CA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Facilitate… https://t.co/n9R0A4y23B https://t.co/zrmKa7MwoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Working for Trunk Club When you join Trunk Club, you join the Nordstrom family. Our fast-paced and entrepreneurial environment is paired with the strong history and experience of a retail legacy. We have access to some of the… https://t.co/1gO6YqF0XW https://t.co/Qod0uRFkNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Solutions Architects, interested in joining our team in Kearneysville, WV, and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Serve as .Net Developer… https://t.co/iWN8SRPMPq https://t.co/zMi2eikHB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Advisor: COMPUTER/IT Industry Value Sr. Advisor for SAP America, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to lead effrt for hgh tch &amp; telco indstrs glblly by wrkng w/ diff. teams wthn Cstmr Engagmnt &amp; Cmmrce &amp; Indstry Bus. Units, incl mrkting &amp; fld orgnztns wthn SAP.… https://t.co/S7Gwf2dyTD https://t.co/q2pqxhhAHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Specialist #80236P: Information Technology Services at Iowa State University is seeking qualified applicants for a Data Center Specialist. The Data Center Specialist will be responsible for supporting ISU’s data center infrastructure, and… https://t.co/rBKQ1UqAIt https://t.co/0vMZHVvAv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer: Allergan plc (NYSE: AGN) is a bold, global pharmaceutical company and a leader in a new industry model – Growth Pharma. Allergan is focused on developing, manufacturing and commercializing branded pharmaceutical, device,… https://t.co/TCL5fke669 https://t.co/tFDPGrm7i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Product Designer (User Experience) – Digital Aviation Analytics: Senior Digital Product Designer (User Experience) – Digital Aviation &amp; Analytics Jobs in Tukwila at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree –… https://t.co/FodZiWS4k3 https://t.co/7rKc9CB39Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Windows VM Engineer: *Position requires local travel to client sites in the Chicagoland area* Prestigious Microsoft Gold Partner Firm is currently seeking a permanent Cisco Networking and Windows/VM Engineer, any SCCM, and/or Citrix experience… https://t.co/iiEk7497Sf https://t.co/K8FvfWB3JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Analyst – Washington, DC: Sales Operations Analyst – Washington, DC Company Overview Cogent Communications is a multinational, Tier 1 facilities-based ISP, consistently ranked as one of the top five networks in the world and is publicly… https://t.co/UT4vaEQvyh https://t.co/z7t82hLmsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, PMO and IT Client Services: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Englewood, CO, US Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/13/2018 Job Description TTEC, formerly Teletech, is seeking a Director, PMO… https://t.co/hA7qIbPJ1I https://t.co/1AgKp8mlkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer: For BNY Mellon Senior Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking –… https://t.co/dUrfdOwf6R https://t.co/FhA6VcYs2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry Value Sr. Advisor for SAP America: Industry Value Sr. Advisor for SAP America, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to lead effrt for hgh tch &amp; telco indstrs glblly by wrkng w/ diff. teams wthn Cstmr Engagmnt &amp; Cmmrce &amp; Indstry Bus. Units, incl mrkting &amp; fld… https://t.co/cgY7V4yFlY https://t.co/B1PQ9s36p8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: ENGINEER: PLM (Product Lifestyle Management) Research, design, evaluate, install, operate or maintain systems &amp; processes used to ensure mechanical products &amp; equipment meet requirements. MS in Mechanical Eng or equiv. field. 2 yrs exp as PLM… https://t.co/aZVy00DHi8 https://t.co/TsCuatTOTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer: Description *CANDIDATES MUST COMPLETE A BACKGROUND CHECK UPON OFFER* Job Purpose/Role The Performance Test Engineer will plan, design and execute performance tests for all applications across enterprise participating in a particular… https://t.co/vrKjDjfCD7 https://t.co/jkAmbPOr78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesys Developer: Genesys Developer Ref No.: 18-20534 Location: Monterey Park, California 5+ years experience Ability to analyze, design, and program complex routing strategies using Genesys IRD 8.x Proficiency with Communications Manager and/or Genesys… https://t.co/oR6fyYKPnL https://t.co/1F4PfpUR2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Center (NOC) Analyst: Network Operations Center (NOC) Analyst – WHO WE ARE – Businesses – Life @ Bechtel – PROFESSIONALS – Business &amp; Corporate Services – Procurement &amp; Contracts – Construction Engineering &amp; Supervision – Engineering –… https://t.co/YV8gDuSBmD https://t.co/sSFxA7voyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Bridge/Structures Design: Job Description – Project Manager II – Bridge/Structures Design Job LocationUS-FL-Lake MaryJob ID0418-18377 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager II – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time… https://t.co/5GhO4Noqrb https://t.co/vH31ynfJzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS: SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS: Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: Develop, create, install, implement &amp; modify comp apps sware. Design, customize, upgrade &amp; migrate sware for client use with an aim of optimizing… https://t.co/txAmMnqNrr https://t.co/ep1ZHm8AdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Finance Implementation Technical Analyst: Peoplesoft Finance Implementation Technical Analyst: Washington State Board for Community and Technical Colleges, 1300 Quince Street SE, Olympia, WA 98504- Administer implement and enhancement of… https://t.co/NVacJYEkrP https://t.co/XOOq2mT5bI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant, Technology: TECHNOLOGY Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Consultant, Technology, Deloitte Digital in San Jose, CA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to function as integrator between business needs… https://t.co/0Z66b06ANr https://t.co/9AxPOJ4rvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Safety Engineer: Engineer Rockwell Collins, Inc., manufacturer of avionics parts &amp; systems in Irvine, CA seeks Senior System Safety Engineer for Supporting the development of innovative aviation electro-mechanical solutions for the world’s… https://t.co/JyyDsw3kuY https://t.co/RQOG5kgBnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Systems Administrator, Oracle Database Administrator, Software Developers: The New York State Unified Court System, Division of Technology, has the following positions available in its Troy, NY office. Windows Systems Administrator The successful… https://t.co/v6YGu8b1Bu https://t.co/O3rjQNrB7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and… https://t.co/J8b6ZPBPlP https://t.co/n9Eu1QhGaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM SCCD Consultant :::: Georgia Locals Only: Title: IBM SCCD Consultant Location: Atlanta, Georgia 30303 Duration: 8 Months Description: Candidate must possess 3+ year of experience with IBM SCCD suite including, Asset Management, Knowledge Base,… https://t.co/BfGmjFpCdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Engineer – Cloud Platform Infrastructure: Join our team and experience Workday! It’s fun to work in a company where people truly believe in what they’re doing. At Workday, we’re committed to bringing passion and customer focus to… https://t.co/PB1N1db6V2 https://t.co/7wYVZ9mpcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: The position of Relay Engineer II is focused on the automation of planogram creation using C# and the AMP API that is built on the .Net stack. This position requires working with clients to determine business requirements, and working… https://t.co/4cqoMI2hCq https://t.co/GanliC4PCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cyber Security Engineer: This position is located in Aurora, CO. What We Do: The CERT Risk and Resilience group works with government customers to help them protect and defend their networks. We pioneer innovative ways to monitor and safeguard… https://t.co/t5norkx02P https://t.co/c6umYdbbo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Strong experience in Agile Project Management Experience in managing projects from Project Planning through UAT Testing Experience managing large scale projects with timelines over 1 year. Any experience with JIRA, MS Project,… https://t.co/V59Af01hWi https://t.co/HCIkYhv43O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Developer: Title: Sr UI Developer Location: Princeton NJ Duration: 2 + year Interview Type: Phone + in Person Primary Skills: OO JavaScript, Angular 2/4, JQuery, HTML5 , CSS. Secondary Skills: Java. – Good communication skills – Strong experience… https://t.co/6v1JFx3Ypi https://t.co/aClmYUOtAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers and Architects: Job Description Senior Software Engineers and Architects Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you are helping to create a better world. Your day-to-day management will touch the lives of… https://t.co/xoLsAMkJv6 https://t.co/SdnQtFzfIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – Technical Business Development Software &amp; AI: Job Summary Serve as subject matter expert at Koito and NAL for automation related hardware and software solutions. The team will rely on you for market intelligence which includes software and… https://t.co/59XYcYuWYd https://t.co/CdIBmIn9hR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across more than… https://t.co/wnekv2fcbL https://t.co/nC1E7xubsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Engineer: About Us: Mercury Protocol is the future of communications, powered by blockchain. We are a well funded, early-stage startup with a world-class team that is backed by Mark Cuban. Based in Los Angeles, we are a passionate team… https://t.co/Ff7PUCN25n https://t.co/Qmwk6cpcZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Service Manager: Company Overview Fortune 2000 clients rely on Onshore Outsourcing as their U.S. co-sourcing IT partner because of our dependability, scalability and cost efficiency. We deliver tailored IT services and resources,… https://t.co/T3ecbIdFPV https://t.co/cJxY2SlTkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer with Salesforce – Mid Level: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Software Developer with Salesforce Mid level for our Plano, TX facility Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software… https://t.co/gQkK2gOTrV https://t.co/Jvaq7jJ2l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Engineer: Position: Security Engineer Location: Chicago Loop About Raise Raise, a leading retail payments company and the worlds largest gift card marketplace, connects consumers to buy discounted gift cards or sell their unwanted cards for… https://t.co/uhWGtIxaHU https://t.co/ZxEH01yg2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager: The Advertising Cloud is the first end-to-end independent advertising and data management solution that spans traditional TV and digital formats, simplifying what has been a complex and fragmented process for the world’s… https://t.co/Gl9kgNYsu3 https://t.co/NO76caL2ET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure System Oversight Engineer: Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems that make the world a safer place and help to secure our… https://t.co/PFkT2ueyw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/OThiBBcYbg https://t.co/pjULGqiCde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Full Time Position Job Description: Software engineers who will be responsible for the design, development and integration of device drivers and software on Intel mobile platforms for Windows client devices. Engineers… https://t.co/7YL6riNirD https://t.co/eGayyLXNfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Developer: Were looking for a Full Stack developer who will take a key role on our team. Our Full Stack developer must have knowledge in all stages of software development. Youll be working alongside other engineers and developers,… https://t.co/5EPHiUmDTQ https://t.co/vhTMaPCK2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Science Test Developer, Alternate Assessment: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10742 Job Location United States Alternate locations Washington, D.C. Category Test Development/Content Overview AIR Assessment is one of America’s leading K -12… https://t.co/ESFPVPIQol https://t.co/dlOiT7AlxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer (Integration): Python Developer (Integration) Ref No.: 18-21334 Location: Sunnyvale, California Job title: Python Developer (Integration) Location: Sunnyvale, CA Duration: 12 months Basic Qualifications: – BS in Computer Science or… https://t.co/1lxgW2YBka https://t.co/dhj7fER3kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) wrk in crss-fnctnl dvlpmnt or tstng team w/ focus on QA &amp; tst rltd tasks w/in prdct creatn prcss. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd &amp; 5 yrs exp req’d or alt… https://t.co/Le1aLnS0Ya https://t.co/tgj2aWwUcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Barrington): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/EBcu0Bhnjz https://t.co/Jh7GqETL6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! * Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/Q45E8IwoMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FPGA Development Engineer Staff Member: Req ID : 416921BR Job Code/Title : E2524:ASIC &amp; FPGA Design Eng Stf Job Description : Lockheed Martin in Colorado is seeking a Staff Embedded Software and FPGA Engineer to work on a cutting-edge team developing… https://t.co/G86JuEVJaz https://t.co/ehOTiAS8wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: As a Developer, you’ll be contributing to the successful delivery of digital products. You articulate the objective rationale behind your coding decisions, working with your teammates to ensure those align with business and audience… https://t.co/CZ4cATLA2T https://t.co/7uKXjkQYz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Missile Defense Systems Engineer / Relocation opportunity to beautiful Orlando, Florida: Req ID : 433010BR_32 Job Code/Title : E1463:Systems Engineer Sr Job Description : Lockheed Martin is looking for experienced systems engineers with a… https://t.co/e0RIsYeJ7i https://t.co/oZ8wlW4um1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Product Designer (User Experience) – Digital Aviation Analytics: Senior Digital Product Designer (User Experience) – Digital Aviation &amp; Analytics Jobs in Tukwila at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree –… https://t.co/W7btnzuzeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer &amp; Network Repair Technician: Innovative Technology Consulting is looking for a new member of our team to do both remote and onsite computer and network repair. We have been providing computer, network, and technology support services to over a… https://t.co/sMT4BmyKoS https://t.co/pf583rPEBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Trust Engineer: Atlassian, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks: 1) Principal Trust Engineers to collaborate and craft deliverables as part of technology team working to build infrastructure and scale that drives technical direction and… https://t.co/M6bukgSv0m https://t.co/pGaPx9J4vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Berkley): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/Zyvj00POZV https://t.co/pIatKbjPq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Looking for a strong RedHat Systems Administrator. Ideal candidates have experience with the following: -Cisco and similar network device experience. Know how to configure switches and assign ports to vlans and troubleshoot… https://t.co/mfYcd4S3HQ https://t.co/n7M7nMMYBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Systems 2/3:   Job Description – Engineer Systems 2/3 (18008217) Engineer Systems 2/3 Requisition ID : 18008217 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/AhjW3YMSDx https://t.co/dp4vyLoAIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION Job Title: Application Developer Supervisor: IT Manager Position Summary: This position is responsible for maintaining and developing code for in-house applications using industry coding standards and best… https://t.co/h1k9k5v2L6 https://t.co/fzvu4pDGdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media… https://t.co/io7mPz2iyw https://t.co/remEy1CQ93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title UX Engineer: Job Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 19 hours ago(5/7/2018 1:42 PM) Requisition ID 2018-3305 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development company headquartered in Cambridge, MA. The 1,700… https://t.co/vGimrbV11k https://t.co/ieYAlcNJUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer / Software Development Engineer: Workday Inc. is accepting resumes for the following positions at various levels in San Mateo, CA: Software Engineer / Software Development Engineer (P3/4-SESDESM 4/29) – Analyzes, designs, programs,… https://t.co/kD9AEAkGBd https://t.co/2W6TeWNCSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Adobe Systems Incorporated is accepting resumes for the following positions in San Jose, CA: Software Engineer (Ref.# SJSE106): Work closely with engineering teams and product management to deliver great compelling features for the… https://t.co/8ZKHUr0CJW https://t.co/2tjT1f9uAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electrical Energy Systems Engineer – Los Angeles, California: Our Los Angeles office is currently seeking an experienced Senior Electrical Energy Systems Engineer with superior design and analysis skills, to evaluate, plan and design electrical… https://t.co/nr9yHlhouA https://t.co/hCBlwuH9ls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wastewater Process Technologist – Toronto, ON: CH2M is now Jacobs. Support Civil Water/Wastewater Projects and have a hand in transforming tomorrow. As a Wastewater Process Technologist, you’ll have the chance to work with our global water/wastewater… https://t.co/D2FNyA5uY1 https://t.co/T8ejOW3UOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required:   Job Description – Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required (17027927) Cyber Security Analyst 2/3 – Targeter – TS/SCI w/poly required Requisition ID : 17027927… https://t.co/S030qsgaSd https://t.co/fCgFiXrCjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Data Analyst: Our Pharmaceutical client has engaged us to provide a Data Analyst contractor to support operational data analysis and support. The ideal candidate: * Provides support to the organization in regards to the processing and… https://t.co/c4JH0xfXYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer I – CORE: CLIENT REFERENCE CODE: ****** JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Engineering team is responsible for the implementation of approved network… https://t.co/k84KXGDUQn https://t.co/0wMFlWlonV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Administrator: DESCRIPTION: The Defense &amp; Intelligence Group of Employer has an immediate opening for aSr. Systems Administratorat the Pentagon. The Sr. Systems Administratorwill support the G2 Army MI Enterprise program which provides IT… https://t.co/VjP97SQ8WG https://t.co/NLgC9rLpgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Learning Support Specialist #HV-NTP-909: Applications are being accepted for the following vacancy on the Non-Teaching Professional staff of Hudson Valley Community College, 80 Vandenburgh Avenue, Troy, New York. Online Learning Support Specialist… https://t.co/aFVyTUH2az https://t.co/vPi4fkgjjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Cherry Valley): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and… https://t.co/WP3mDVaZ6F https://t.co/u5qNlOf0Gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer I, Service (Northern Michigan): Find a Better Way… …to use your skills and experience. This is the time to let your talent come to life. To maximize your knowledge and use it for the greater good. To work with the best professionals using… https://t.co/aDi74xl8pL https://t.co/tA2GA0LCfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Execution Analyst/Systems Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Aurora, CO Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/18/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/t0UMT0Dlzf https://t.co/JIobZbkrJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Looking for Android Developers Salary: $70k to $85k Location: Irving, TX Looking for a candidate with 2 plus years Android Development and Mobile Applications Developer The Application Developers will be responsible for the… https://t.co/4sYRQ6U0yh https://t.co/e1gaPXCiFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer, Android Digital and Mobile Product Development: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind – making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone… https://t.co/I8Lj4bvbgq https://t.co/ktxjYFlsED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst: Business Unit: Global Operations and Client Services Department: All Job Family: Global Operations Job Title: Operations Analyst Corporate Title: Analyst FLSA Code (US Only): Non-Exempt Business Unit Description: The Global… https://t.co/3XvUx6pzYg https://t.co/zz9id2llAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Automation Engineer: Intralinks External Website Advertisement Principal Automation Engineer (Intralinks, Inc.; Waltham, Massachusetts): Will be a member of the Tools and Automation team responsible for on-time delivery of high-quality software… https://t.co/DwHq2kdb0v https://t.co/N8ayCt6dEW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>