<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A coven of poets join forces to defeat a Greek god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archaeologist is climbing up the side of a giant thighbone. It has been her childhood dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A silent showgirl falls in love with regret.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poppy that can destroy prime numbers grows in a Burmese garden. A homeless person searches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By touching a particular face located in Wales, you can reach another world. It is ruled by a dental hygienist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ambitious Young Adult writer falls into a river filled with words. A schoolmistress tries to save her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hazel tree celebrates the Fourth of July.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A necromancer steals metaphors and hides them inside a lighthouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nurse is walking from Miami to an elm tree in Alexandria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A princess believes it is her destiny to kill letters of the alphabet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prime minister hears of a lagoon filled with honey, and wishes to sail her warship across it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, a beauty therapist in Illinois turns into a concert hall during her lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen is singing in a crystal forest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Russia is a desert in which every grain of sand is a volcano.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twelve software developers are on a secret mission. Their aim is to steal a gigantic emerald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess owns an illuminated manuscript which depicts every tsar's sigh by a schoolteacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 16th century textbook describes a universe entirely filled with late capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An emerald library whispers to a game show host: "I wish I was a geiger counter."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Colorado there is a cypress tree which used to be a Welsh congressman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Catalan nun is sentenced to death by a vice president for writing a book about free will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On All Hallow's Eve you suddenly become as wise as Wittgenstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A software developer slowly turns into a shopping trolley. Nobody notices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A caliph marries the International Space Station. They have one child: A daughter who is made of infinity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A doctoral student is found dead in a cinema. Beside the body is a toenail and a puddle of Jell-O. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A party of lake monsters are going on a quest. Their aim is to reach the 16th century.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nihilistic solicitor falls in love with management consulting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A naturopath suddenly appears in Red Square during the Russian Revolution. She feels out of place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lawyer is standing perfectly still at the bottom of the Marianas Trench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful stonemason plays a game of dominoes with a pyramid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forty-nine archivists devise a world where everything is oysters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A geisha steals everyone whose name begins with the letter M and hides them inside a crystal chapel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A PhD thesis causes anyone who reads it to believe they are a tortoise shell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Anatolian political action committee seeks donations from sapphires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen receives an unusual gift from her cat: A candle that can compose operas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congresswoman wants to steal every Fabergé egg in Hawaii.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A caliph wishes to catalogue every duck egg in Baltimore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A novelist has a rare gift: He can understand the language of sea serpents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Marxist finds a leather-bound book containing instructions for building a staircase out of cathedrals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a creature in Sicily that is half caterpillar and half dragon. It has the mind of a 10th century sheik.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Madagascan philosopher dies while writing a novel about women named Diane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor of English literature is dancing in a hospital. She is thinking about starlight. There is a lobster standing right behind her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pope waltzes with a frying pan inside a haunted waterfall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A porcelain aircraft carrier is sailing on a sea of Britney Spears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Vietnamese steering committee convenes a meeting about quinces that lasts for 8,500 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A unicorn appears in a sexual health clinic. Then tiny bats begin raining from the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten children play a game in which the aim is to become a rhinoceros.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Italian courtesan discovers a pair of spectacles which let her see every act of forgiveness happening around the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kenyan necromancer passes a law against puppets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By concentrating on a lump of coal, a Canadian tsar is able to destroy music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mechanical library appears over Borneo. A sociologist is talking to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Florida there is a window which is driving the kids to soccer practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen owns a painting by Michelangelo which depicts every fart that has ever happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Venice there is a chrysanthemum that smells like snakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bisexual French necromancer buys a tiny glass sphere that lets her sense the presence of Attention Deficit Disorder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders has a girlfriend. The girlfriend is https://t.co/h18x4x1NBo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an army major in Switzerland with a wardrobe instead of a liver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A travel agent is turning into potatoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pear tree as beautiful as the North Star grows in a Sicilian garden. A novelist writes a manuscript about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A book collector hears of a toilet that can destroy the stars, and devotes his life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pharmacist in Seattle is falling in love with men whose name begins with the letter S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baroness discovers that science fiction does not exist, and is relieved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cocktail waitress invents a better version of capitalism: Snoring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Norwegian grandmother listens to a xylophone that plays every song ever heard in Prague.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An American high school teacher sees a cloud in the shape of a cathedral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A movie producer is being chased by a fireplace in a Sudanese desert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ancient order of professors come together to worship Star Wars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congressman is masturbating in the belly of an eel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ethiopian politician is building a hospital that is filled with Santa Claus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A desert suddenly falls from the sky in the East Village.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kangaroo sleeps in a terracotta rainforest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorceress turns into every labyrinth in Milwaukee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A penniless chef makes a milkshake flavored with social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A butler counts to ten. In that time, he lives for twelve years as a 16th century novelist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dictator hears of a chestnut tree made of chocolate creams, and yearns to eat it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A swan kidnaps a queen. It demands a ransom of 7,700 cities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Czechoslovakian innkeeper plants a seed which grows into a waterlily made of Moonlight Sonata.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An electric guitar is elected Governor of Utah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Siberia, onions start raining from the sky. An elf is responsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman owns an essay by Spinoza on the subject of the Moon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In San Diego there is a book that is made of angels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a tornado in Dar es Salaam. It sucks up croissants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toilet whispers to a girl: "I feel so handsome."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anthropologist finds an opal which allows him to turn everything into arrogance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ash tree appears before Judas Iscariot. It says: "Don't be worried."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baby is born in Finland with Bruegel's Fall of Icarus painted on its face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Scottish book describes a way of having sexual intercourse that turns you into a pine tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl discovers that everything is being masterminded by Wikipedia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Algerian countess invents a machine that will let her have sexual intercourse with sexual frustration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congressman is writing a list. It has three items: A grand piano, a clock, and an exclamation mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Spanish vice president passes a law that everyone must drink clam juice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ostrich lays an egg. A rattlesnake is inside it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An army officer sets out on a journey to a marble city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A planet is thinking about ears in a railway station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher meets a spider with wigs instead of legs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mother tells you that you are a tsarina in a 12th century Californian city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dingo is eating a rectangle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Instagram celebrity suddenly turns into an Olympic stadium. His lover is secretly pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 14-year-old duchess hatches a plan to poison pretentiousness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Barcelona is a juniper tree whose every leaf is a gold mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An eagle made of candy canes is born in Sydney.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>