<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS! https://t.co/428Awj0LCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack's new obsession: how will the baby get out of Mommy's tummy?  #notreadyforthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Sunday will be one of the best times this year to invite a non-Christian friend to Restoration City!  https://t.co/wZkRj8rNKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for @GuMS_Principal and her team at the start of a new school year.  We're with you and so grateful for all you do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City, don't ever forget we exist for the glory of Christ and the good of this city!  https://t.co/MlwUHI5Zze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God wants our time with Him to be RELATIONAL.  Not FUNCTIONAL or TRANSACTIONAL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved everything about this morning at Restoration City!  Thank You, Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace is the gift that makes the most sense when we least deserve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure tomorrow morning at Restoration City will be the highlight of my Labor Day weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServeDC isn't just something we do. It's an expression of who we are.  https://t.co/FGhpUbaw3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Souls nourished by Scripture are less distracted by the temptations of sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't settle for internet outrage. The gospel calls us to make a real difference in the real world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: Give yourself some extra time to get to church this morning with the Army Ten Miler. Check out road closures here: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't come to church wondering if God will show up.  Come expecting He will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayshelt welcome back! we've missed you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuing our series in Esther tomorrow at Restoration City.  Praying our lives would be marked by risky faith!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer works far better when we come to God with open hands rather than a list of demands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gave you a vision.  Communicate it in your voice, using your own words.  Don't sell yourself short by copying someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you able to spot trouble in your own heart before you and others get hurt?https://t.co/DpJN9vboVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Watch over your heart with all diligence, for from it flow the springs of life." - Proverbs 4:23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self care isn't a frivolous luxury.  It's an absolute necessity. https://t.co/gZtihqnuAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How healthy are you as a leader?  You need a personal leadership dashboard to find out.  https://t.co/a0UPCSD1W3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Behold, how good and pleasant it is when brothers dwell in unity!" (Ps. 133:1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a world ravaged by the destruction of sin.  Remembering that doesn't disappoint me but forgetting it does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll never be able to influence people who don't know us or don't like us.  Be salt and light!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stress and worry don't have to rob you of sleep! https://t.co/srU5x5XDoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[55 people have already signed up for #ServeDC.  Have you? Take 3 minutes to do it now! https://t.co/I1Uw3o3ncL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I trust leaders who limp a lot more than those who swagger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great things happening through Community Group Open Houses this week. Still time to find a group.  Full list here: https://t.co/bKg89Gtkfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stress and worry keeping you up at night? King Ahasuerus can help. https://t.co/Cmb1DiEZRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SummitNetwork: 17/18 Church planting residency applications are now open! Learn more at https://t.co/bhhFsGc6Lc. https://t.co/ZZfxMgNwLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the best possible day to get signed up for #ServeDC.  Oct. 27-30th.  https://t.co/sk8wRHmsBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life gets really good when we learn to put more confidence in God's promises than in our abilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More enjoying the moment.  Less capturing the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a church starts developing leaders, it shifts from an organization to a movement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worship is the overflow of a heart convinced of its need for grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't say enough about how God used this in my life.  Strongly encourage any potential planters to consider this! https://t.co/Offo8rxKjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikekelsey you're right down the road!  Come and say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of our Community Groups are hosting Open Houses next week. Don't just attend RCC, get connected!  https://t.co/b2L9GEpYFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are few things worse than believing your best days are behind you.  Strain forward to what lies ahead. (Phil.3:13)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easiest way to get connected at Restoration City?  Starting Point! This Sunday right after our gathering. https://t.co/MMNwRM0z8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastoremase: Being discipled by someone means that you must be willing to make major life adjustments to be discipled by them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bible has a lot to say about making social media work for you: https://t.co/ahlqO5zBUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay focused on what God has asked you to carry today and free of everything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is often doing His deepest work when He seems most hidden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday night tired is the best kind of tired!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community group isn't just for grown-ups. Love that my kids will grow up knowing the blessings… https://t.co/Ct2yywgq3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting a series in Esther tomorrow that's going to be a game changer for a lot of us.  Love to… https://t.co/D4W3y8L0TB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't see your time as valuable, no one else will either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the positivity gospel as the prosperity gospel's younger, more emotional cousin: https://t.co/OO1Rtwh23R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day isn't going to be AH-MAZING.  And that's totally okay: https://t.co/kiS4OCctEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's Word pours inexhaustible grace into exhausted souls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jdgreear: Praying for justice &amp; peace in CLT and for the many believers working there as peacemakers. Only in the gospel are the resour…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[684 volunteer hours through ServeDC all aimed at one goal: the glory of Christ and the good of our city: https://t.co/4ScZwshQDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oldest &amp; Youngest https://t.co/WC4ZuZ4Gl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hope of the gospel turns our churches into beacons of hope for our communities: https://t.co/QfsxfuHQOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulTripp: Feeling overwhelmed? Remember, your Lord not only rules your circumstances, but is with you, for you, and in you every step…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still celebrating everything God did through ServeDC this weekend. Here's a recap: https://t.co/Oku2GsuAzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll either cheer or envy the success of others.  One expands your world and the other shrinks it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Christ, you aren't superior or inferior to anyone." Great message from Allan McCullough this… https://t.co/ATRtOuukyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never love this church more than on ServeDC weekends! https://t.co/3crroY6b0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Let your light shine before others, so that they may see your good works and give glory to your Father who is in heaven.”(Mt 5:16) #servedc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole 3 kids thing is no joke...especially when they are all 3 and younger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calendars and checkbooks show our priorities.  True for individuals and churches! https://t.co/XerVbTj4dS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved seeing the three of them together! https://t.co/3jF6YaT83N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Restoration City, we measure success by how much we give away - in time and money! https://t.co/FERRd0f0rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less trying to get God on my agenda. More trying to get me on His.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found the most unforgettable way to celebrate my birthday yesterday - by sharing it with this… https://t.co/kVpAcjj2IX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: Although this story is best told with numbers, it's about the faithfulness of God and generosity of His people. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City - let's be a church that's known for our generosity! https://t.co/UjnJmj2cFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved @AllanMcC's message this morning.  Hard to image a better start to our Distinct series at @RCChurchDC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day with family. Just waiting for baby sister to join the party! https://t.co/847raIJGIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait!  Going to be a powerful 7 weeks for our church!! https://t.co/aYBp0NlijF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to wrestle control of our lives away from God is a battle we can't and don't want to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sin tears down.  Jesus rebuilds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest friends simultaneously accept us and remind us of Jesus’ ability to transform us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need you to sign-up for ServeDC by this Sunday.  Why not just do it today! https://t.co/P6tbugdSFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our God is in the heavens; He does all that He pleases." (Ps. 115:3) Build your life on His will, not man's whims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transparency opens the door for love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one will ever be able to love the real you until you let them see the real you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being known is the precursor to being loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ's love liberates us from a self focused, loveless life.  https://t.co/VPG631TlTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't confuse the fruit of the Spirit with personality traits.  https://t.co/xHTWAc9IRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love isn't a personality trait.  It's evidence that God is working in our hearts.  https://t.co/wKSqFb9ImK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Jesus, our judgment day was moved from the future to the past." - @scottsauls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel doesn't simply call us to an upside down life.  It strengthens us for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for tomorrow at Restoration City: final "Risky Faith" talk &amp; communion. Just need Laura to not go into labor between now and then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect Saturday for these two little firefighters! https://t.co/ZIGqaZ4kOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear is the weapon of cowards. Faith, hope and love take tremendous courage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deepen your awe of God like your ministry depends on it.  Because it does! https://t.co/QzfcFB4vsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping our hearts focused on God and shaped by the gospel is our highest priority as leaders. https://t.co/FyoHmMG050]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a self focused or a God focused leader?   https://t.co/bpR71JoUqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weakness is a gift that deepens our thirst for grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abraham Lincoln's 1863 #Thanksgiving proclamation is stunningly relevant for America today.  https://t.co/GEwqOye8XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love one another so fiercely that Jesus becomes visible to a watching world. https://t.co/aH34ZEx03I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish all parents of newborns could receive the kind of love and support we have from @RCChurchDC - beyond grateful! https://t.co/SqtMHwon1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impossible to express my gratitude for the love you've shown my family this past month @RCChurchDC but I had to try! https://t.co/G7vBrlBf5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much you pray is heavily influenced by how you pray.: https://t.co/XjQjtwOg0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of the gospel isn’t that we pray, it’s what we pray. https://t.co/oOOSNFZBsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer is an impossibility apart from Christ. https://t.co/qt7std1Upt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>