<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/RxoywBvQ3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/JNIIkzxaYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/pjDXaUsXlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/VLHzXBNIUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/aerWQJqxv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/cwPEsfDNIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/IXdAw04JEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/Icj5tBHoQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/5pZ0bqkkYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/cbm3YEfdrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/Hd0XV3SLve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/Ud14jKOB34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/hnVZSqpRP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/pBujkYqLPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/yWpRRjsYlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/URxuv6WZWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/iv8poybniu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/pr9ErpOXtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Cicerone Beer?  http://t.co/Td5CPw2VFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/5ej59XWjul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/2PmWAA55HO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/Aimn1Wz0xM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/glOmBOjkEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/mvkpbMq19n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/EmplPXOLPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/4F7AYInhYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/FundBIwUjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/OvZmE870Kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/HmZwdJJmWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/caanSRtox3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/KfcAzLzBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/WoLAfLGR5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/SYLsJloucT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/4xNTlphXgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/EPz82C2hES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/7X5iKda1Uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/oQTHGgC1Tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/r8IOI9PAU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/awnpxJwVPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/396mn5z8nr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/YC7Y9ulupl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/fdcfKSo2R6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/ZM1NCIP8mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/jLhhq5wZue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/oPyUGGs58K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/Qaw9Fxc5Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/muAY3Ojj3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/sIrebw35Eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>