<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget, each broken heart is one step closer to finding the very person you were meant to be with...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words can break someone. But they can also put someone back together :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You re always gonna have that one person, would of, could of, should of, but it just never worked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss having someone that cares about what I did yesterday, what I'm doing right now and what I'm going to do tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like everytime I take a step away from you, something is pulling me back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when two hearts become one. True love is when two souls become one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#relationshipkillers Love is a thing for two, but there's always a slut that doesn't know how to count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you end your relationship over a petty argument, that means somebody wasn t in love. Never let an argument end your relationship!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with guys is, they pretend to like you when they don t. The problem with girls is, they pretend they don t like you when they do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anatidaephobia- the fear that somehow, somewhere, a duck is watching you. ~ I would like to meet a person with this fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are multiple sides to all of us. Who we are - and who we might be if we follow our dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how many lips you have kissed, how many shoulders you have embraced.. all i care is not to be your first but to be your last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because it s not happening right now, doesn t mean it never will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A relationship with NO TRUST is like a car with no gasoline. You can stay in it all you want but it won't go anywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving up is always an option but never my choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to meet new people to realize how much the old ones matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I should die before I wake, it's because you took my breath away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever just sat there thinking about that one person and then realize that you're smiling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When jokes are carried too far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiter : "Would you like your coffee black" Customer : "What other colors do you have"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me selfish but I don't want anyone else to realize how amazing you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You broke my heart. But I still love you with all the pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because no matter how badly a thing is hurting us, sometimes, letting it go, hurts even worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid - I'm right behind you...using you as a shield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Together. The perfect way to spend a lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grudges are a waste of perfect happiness. Laugh when you can, apologize when you should, and let go of what you can t change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will hate you, rate you, shake you, and break you. How strong you stand is what makes you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don t think myself as better than anyone else, but perhaps I would categorize myself as limited edition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry I missed your call... LOL jk I ignored that shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feelings fade, promises don't last forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've been hurt, you're so scared to get attached you've got this fear that everyone you start to fall for will break your heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you asked me how many times you have crossed my mind I would say once because you never really left...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When things aren t working out as you wish, be patient. Stop trying to move ahead of God. His timing is perfect. Trust him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hate those days when twitter doesn't work properly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority don't know what's wrong with this tweet. RT if you are one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 Of The Ugliest Celebrities==&gt; http://t.co/f0aQbKNe36 - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some teens want drugs, some teens want alcohol and some want sex..... I just want more sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing You confess, could make me love you less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he shall die, cut him up into little stars. So that all the world be in love with night.~Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be absolutely ridiculous than to be absolutely boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to let go of people who are important to you, but twice harder to see them fine as you let them go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not funny. I'm just really mean and people think I'm joking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something about you is so addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like you want to do it, but you're afraid that people won't accept it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because I m not speaking to you, Doesn t mean I don t miss you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting behind a door to scare someone, then leaving because they're taking too long to come out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before I go to sleep, I start imagining stuff that I would like to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you finally decide on something after a long hesitation, everything will seem much clearer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile is the best way to keep your lips in shape for the kiss that might follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All a girl needs is that ONE guy who proves to her that they aren't all the same...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you like tacos :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must be a snowflake, 'cuz I've fallen for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am actually not afraid to love; I am just afraid to not be loved back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought that was just a dream and it wouldn't come true, but that dream became reality when I met you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want you to look at me like you've never looked at anyone else. I want you to look at me like I have something other girls don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many people miss seeing the silver lining because they're expecting gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you wish, it's like you're throwing something in the air, and it or not come back down. It's in your hands, then it's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can live without you, but without you I'll be miserable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The annoying moment when you cannot find the long side of the blanket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened One day you love me like I'm the only one that matters to you &amp; the next, you can't even stutter a "Hello"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you believe everything that is told to you...then ANYONE can fool you, rule you, and control you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage doesn't always roar, sometimes it's that quiet voice at the end of the day that says "I will try again tomorrow".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you realized you screwed up on a tweet but people have already retweeted it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know I'll always love you, but right now I just don't like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are not meant for you to love, but meant for you to learn from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kiss can be a comma, a question mark or an exclamation point. That s basic spelling that every woman ought to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have a heart without a smile than to have a smile without a heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end everyone will hurt you... it's up to you to decide who is worth the pain. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the best way to get their attention is to stop giving them yours...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't make promises you can't keep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I get a picture of you so that I can show Santa what I want for Christmas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To old friends: "Let's meet up soon!" Never happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know how to differentiate between the right and wrong, but I just lack self-discipline, because my parents are always around to nag. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want something you ve never had, You sometimes have to do something you ve never done...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admit it, everytime you undergo a relationship you think that you'll last forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I saved all the tears I cried for you so I could fucking drown you in them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the things in common that make relationships enjoyable, but it's the little differences that make them interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear heart, Thank you for being so strong, I promise I won't make the same mistake. Sincerely, heartbroken person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[baby, you light up my world like nobody else ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather waste my life pretending, then have to forget you for one whole minute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to music is sometimes a distraction from work when your favourite song starts playing. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last thing I want to be is "just friends" because I don't wanna look into your eyes everyday and see a miracle I can't have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sad when people you know become people you knew, When you can walk right past me like I was never a big part of your life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do you go when you have no place to run to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to self: stop expecting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don t want a perfect relationship. I just want someone who I can act silly with, someone who treats me well and loves being with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all those who wander are lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always wondered what you're thinking when you stare at me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when you're on the computer looking for love quotes, while you're listening to love songs on iTunes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The perfect guy isn't gonna walk right into your life just like that... you've gotta meet him halfway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If raindrops were kisses,I d send you showers.If hugs were seas, I d send you oceans. If love was a person, I d send you me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how often we see each other. What matters most is how much we think about each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We used to spend the whole day thinking about that one person, but now they hardly ever cross our mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stupidly smile at my phone when i see your name on the screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it funny how they want to be your friend right after they break your heart Yeah, not happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words are like bullets: when well aimed, they have a pretty hard effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is good when you can see it from the right perspective. If you don't feel so, you just need to change your view.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would hit you B**ch. But that would be animal abuse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate it when you're around me and you frown, cause I wanna be the girl who can always make you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I pretend to be asleep when my mom checks my room.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>