<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer or Senior Java Developer: The Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland is part of the nation’s central bank. We’ve provided many opportunities for professional growth during our history. For eighteen years in a row, we’ve been named “One of… https://t.co/cFydyr1QGe https://t.co/2iW1YgCUnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PHP / JavaScript Developer: Are you a developer who loves building new things? Do you ensure what you build is scalable? Are you creative and not afraid to think outside the box to come up with creative solutions that pushes the boundaries? How do… https://t.co/ZyxH5O6q4M https://t.co/Y79IgbcJpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap's new Spectacles offer better quality for more money: As rumored, Snap has unveiled a new set of Spectacles with new colors and better specs that address user complaints with the first model. To better aid in their spring break beach appeal, the new… https://t.co/Mq6ZrvxY4q https://t.co/KNCkEiBsXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers grill EPA chief Scott Pruitt: 'You are unfit to hold public office': Scott Pruitt's controversial spending and travel decisions were the subject of a blistering congressional hearing Thursday, where the embattled administrator of the… https://t.co/ofzUe05qfR https://t.co/iPO9Qw6OUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Java Engineer – Provo, Utah: Revature has partnered with a Fortune 500 company to find and develop a strong team of 20 Entry Level Software Engineers to work on next gen software solutions. This is an excellent opportunity for an ambitious… https://t.co/InniIXtBy6 https://t.co/gtBaPD6PO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System/Software Developer – Java/Big Data: 30390BR System/Software Developer – Java/Big Data Washington District Of Columbia United States Senior Software Developer Java/Big Data This senior level position is ideal for a software engineer that enjoys… https://t.co/IG4ToUr9Vw https://t.co/dO76CYRnmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Denver, CO Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment working… https://t.co/o3xMUwnLOw https://t.co/HJmqUOBwfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She invented Spanx. Now she's a billionaire https://t.co/lYVaIhXVXB https://t.co/1YpXcUkUzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Javascript Engineer: We’re looking for a Senior Front-End Engineer to join our team. Mastery of JavaScript and client-side web browser technologies is key in this role as you’ll be responsible for enhancing the engine that powers our ad… https://t.co/aFYnEGsomb https://t.co/p9rGYyZaYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. JAVA Developer: Corporate IT Position Summary The Senior Java Developer will be responsible for the development of new software solutions as well as the maintenance of and enhancements to existing software solutions. The Senior Java Developer will… https://t.co/Q03HAqTHxr https://t.co/p09KqhqynO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LaVar Ball pulls his sons from European team, reports say https://t.co/QRZ0YfXK0g https://t.co/Tz9cUrXwaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance:   Job Description – Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance (18006409) Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance Requisition ID : 18006409 Location : United States-Virginia-Herndon US… https://t.co/egbgJkLJth https://t.co/E4RXAPFh7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java Developer: TCG is an award-winning Government IT solutions provider. We are seeking a Mid-Level Java Developer, who currently resides in the Washington DC metropolitan area, to join the TCG team at a major Federal agency. US Citizenship… https://t.co/eRU6e4ODpW https://t.co/zXbss4cXRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – https://t.co/6m4pXZO33Q, JavaScript, Apex: Plano, TX Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Solution Architect with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful Plano, TX. We are an energetic, innovative, and… https://t.co/KLs7hSdsgF https://t.co/QuNWSf7rAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mainstream electric car we've been waiting for https://t.co/RfW9CC4CR9 https://t.co/JlRckLfgcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – PHP, JavaScript, Node.js: Are you tired of being just another developer working on some corporate system that you don’t care about? Are you stuck in a dead-end job doing the same boring thing for the past three years? Is that where… https://t.co/cUigpI20Vo https://t.co/Vffeey9Bc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Job Title: Java Architect Location: Mt. Laurel, NJ Job Type: Contract Main duties and responsibilities: * We need a Manager tech level person who has retail banking experience. * We are looking at that person as the lead solution designer… https://t.co/7A0ozfChfg https://t.co/k5pwSY8KcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer 2 (ETL/Java): Software Developer 2 (ETL/Java) =============================== Req #: ******Location: Tysons, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job… https://t.co/9Wj0pHXoqf https://t.co/WKizKbBxKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java full stack: Java full stack irving, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 04/12/18, Posted Date – 04/12/18 Primary Skillsjava full stackTax TermsC2COverviewclient skype ! Currently seeking 5-10 Full stack Java Developers with AWS, development tying… https://t.co/v12YhCVOyW https://t.co/qng2XJCFAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack JavaScript Web Developer: Web Developer Job Responsibilities: The role is responsible for designing, coding and modifying current features and/or potential new features for FP Assistance’s (FPA) Web-Application, from layout to function and… https://t.co/jT4AwqXKMg https://t.co/ORjgbeUWVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- J2EE/Struts: POSITION DESCRIPTION: Java Developer with extensive experience on enterprise solutions. The candidate must have strong solution design skills and the ability to document, communicate, and implement the designs patterns… https://t.co/Sd3LoQwFED https://t.co/wymDmiqDlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Join our team of Java Developers and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Application Technologies: Spring,… https://t.co/eCpsd9yKEm https://t.co/IQJVvOJWYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full-Stack Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems. This position will be responsible for design and… https://t.co/Th47qpuJKc https://t.co/lJFdeUYJ9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump brushes 'dandruff' off Macron: President Donald Trump said his "special relationship" with French President Emmanuel Macron is not fake news. https://t.co/7oKon8mGw5 https://t.co/XpmxxnZtuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 3/4 (Mid.-Sr.) TS/SCI with the ability to obtain Poly:   Job Description – Java Developer 3/4 (Mid.-Sr.) TS/SCI with the ability to obtain Poly (18000974) Java Developer 3/4 (Mid.-Sr.) TS/SCI with the ability to obtain Poly Requisition ID… https://t.co/UQauYlAVYj https://t.co/bcot4v9iup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer, Secret Cleared (Req# 00019): SENIOR JAVA ENGINEER Title: Senior Java Engineer Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified applicants MUST have an ACTIVE DOD issued SECRET security clearance, and by virtue… https://t.co/uZld5yQ1zl https://t.co/p2c5WsPH47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Computer Methods International Corp. (CMiC) is a Software Development firm specializing in enterprise financial and cost management systems designed for the Construction and Engineering industries. About CMiC CMiC is the leading provider… https://t.co/ENGbmc90C3 https://t.co/qAnZqHrjcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verne Troyer's family mentions suicide in announcing his death: Verne Troyer, who played Mini-Me in two of the Austin Powers comedy films, has died at the age of 49, according to statements posted to his social media accounts Saturday. https://t.co/lxikKmkRdx https://t.co/ukcJ7dc9Ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Full Stack Developer (Java, Spring, Angular, DB): Sr Full Stack Developer (Java, Spring, Angular, DB) DESCRIPTION: The Business Partner Technology Group is in the middle of building out a new enterprise regulatory reporting system. The system is an… https://t.co/KHARQCebUS https://t.co/qPkim5Nf9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead Full Stack Java: Responsibilities * Partner with Product Owners and Scrum Masters to optimize implementation of agile practices on client projects * Serve as the primary technical point of contact for multiple full stack development teams *… https://t.co/gTnMMyN6bT https://t.co/m2kR5nfXbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins performs the first total penis and scrotum transplant: The first US penis transplant was successfully performed in 2016. Last year, a uterus transplant recipient gave birth for the first time in the US, too. Now, doctors at Johns Hopkins… https://t.co/qv4aJqRn40 https://t.co/xfHdOTacAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: I'm a legislator and a mom. Tammy Duckworth is my hero: On Thursday, Senator Tammy Duckworth and her newborn daughter Maile made history for working parents everywhere when they entered the Senate floor together for mom to cast a vote. https://t.co/xETc8YTzv7 https://t.co/G6mIL9Gaon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead/Senior Software Engineer – Java/J2EE: Join one of the fastest growing security companies in the industry as a Technical Lead or Senior Software Engineer. You will help build the next-generation Identity Governance product and will… https://t.co/NVzRbvmksE https://t.co/Mbn9ubHkYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment… https://t.co/ZaHCRMfxIg https://t.co/Dj417ZQLcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite JavaScript Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for JavaScript Developers to join one of our projects in Allen Park or downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location… https://t.co/qU33an9ggZ https://t.co/XPfOcx2iG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr – Web Development, Java: Req ID : 427980BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : This is an exciting software development position within the growing Space Security initiatives within Mission Solutions. The… https://t.co/qfuC0BtfQH https://t.co/qGd0oRk3cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This snowy park is home to the Wizard of Winter https://t.co/gCrdiB1DHN https://t.co/xdNPBxD3ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (REST API, Spring MVC): San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $150k Posted Today Based in San Francisco, CA we are a innovative FinTech company purely focused on streamlining the home buying experience for consumers. We've developed a… https://t.co/JZyW9BPSMA https://t.co/r8aTurcjuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java): We are looking for an experienced Java Software Engineer who will work as part of our team to develop back-end services to support accessos Passport suite. This may include development and maintenance of a custom Java framework,… https://t.co/p34SIyT53k https://t.co/vT9jyrUHrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's most delicious drinks https://t.co/IHG50oYLsw https://t.co/O65xITSea5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FullStack Agile Java Developer [USC Only]: Infostellar, Inc is a VA based company, dedicated to providing agile development and dev ops services to the Government and Commercial clients. We offer fun, learning, and challenging environment to our team… https://t.co/H9FsABhWYi https://t.co/BUHjsU414o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Job ID  2017-11566 Primary Location  Michigan, Ann Arbor Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  .. Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this job To all recruitment agencies: TD Ameritrade… https://t.co/NxlaNtzYqj https://t.co/1IwvUCCGsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Big Data: 30392BR Java Developer – Big Data Washington District Of Columbia United States This position is ideal for a software engineer that enjoys supporting legacy and new systems development and continuous improvement of mission… https://t.co/qr6eWklHnc https://t.co/URODRrIsVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer for Blockchain Startup!: New York City, NY Full-time $130k – $160k Posted 01/21/2018 If you are a Java Engineer with experience, please read on! If you follow FinTech, you know that blockchain and distributed ledger goes much further than… https://t.co/W8QXEvAwDk https://t.co/WlsFERK0QP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Object Oriented/Java Developer: Req ID 92613BR Business Title Object Oriented/Java Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed Top Secret Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is seeking… https://t.co/L5xABgESzf https://t.co/LWQKOrsj2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: Glendale, CA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a JavaScript Developer with 4+ years experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 1. Based in Glendale, we are digital data collection company that is setting a… https://t.co/wsg1l4qmff https://t.co/Osu9vzKUJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python &amp; JavaScript]: JOB DESCRIPTION Our clients product team is expanding and seeking top-tier senior engineers (Full Stack and Back End Engineers). Theyre looking for independent thinkers that want to take ownership of parts… https://t.co/9Nhc1If0Mh https://t.co/MJ4dQlG2xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Java/AWS Developer: Job Description Duties and Responsibilities: Design, develop, document, integrate, test and deliver scripts, code and other services employing agile DevOps project life-cycle methodologies, processes procedures, in a cloud… https://t.co/Z9ukhASq80 https://t.co/hy5nQyk4fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS ENGINEER – JAVA: Job Description DUTIES and RESPONSIBILITIES: Develops and manages software tools in support of Enterprise Management. Formulates and defines specifications for software applications or modifies and maintains existing… https://t.co/hGmELveoaU https://t.co/xZdIfd8hYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer, Secret Cleared (Req# 00002): SENIOR JAVA ENGINEER Title: Senior Java Engineer Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified applicants MUST have an ACTIVE DOD issued SECRET security clearance, and by virtue… https://t.co/dUl0l2T5wd https://t.co/96etF5YNQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's meeting with Kim will lead to an awful hangover: If their goal is to eliminate North Korea's nuclear weapons threat, the planned talks between Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un are doomed before they even begin. https://t.co/nVhZKYqc06 https://t.co/nhP0PT8QM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18007388) Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18007388 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/c6cipLyvQP https://t.co/TnNJj015k2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Denver, CO Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment working… https://t.co/FK3O5Gxm6H https://t.co/GDIa1auLbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 (18005436) Mid Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18005436 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton… https://t.co/2EUz3VDzEn https://t.co/xfj2vWwfDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Hybris/Java Developer: Job ID 21817BR Job Posting Title Senior Hybris/Java Developer Job Description As a global semiconductor company operating in 35 countries, Texas Instruments (TI) is first and foremost a reflection of its people. From the… https://t.co/IBYM0mLwBD https://t.co/6VeWohelCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer Date: Apr 17, 2018 Location:Waltham, MA, US Company: Ericsson Ericsson Overview Ericsson is a world-leading provider of telecommunications equipment &amp; services to mobile &amp; fixed network operators. Over 1,000… https://t.co/Ep8eotsHKm https://t.co/NVtpolrTQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer – JavaScript, Middleware Java, jquery, bootstrap: Belay Tech is seeking a UI Developer with solid JavaScript and Middleware Java experience. Experience with jquery, bootstrap, MySql or ElasticSearch is a bonus. You must hold an active DoD… https://t.co/JAFsGbbQbc https://t.co/goCqWJ3WfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer-Back End: Req ID 96690BR Business Title Java Developer-Back End Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Alexandria Clearance Level Needed None Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is seeking an experience Java… https://t.co/ccQYJSPSTp https://t.co/Ww3hJ5j7GO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- Partial Remote: Irvine, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Java Developer with experience, please read on! Are you a Senior Java developer that is looking for something new and exciting? Do you want the… https://t.co/KdvyyCX6G5 https://t.co/sZlVAJg43T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer System Analyst ( Java Developer): Internal_Careers | Marvel Technologies Inc Skip to main content – – – – Call :+1 ************ – ********************* – Employee Login Main navigation – Home – Company – About – Our Team – Recognitions – Careers… https://t.co/LKnSa2mSQD https://t.co/krigcfSzv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting to work could soon be a lot easier https://t.co/SaOnOldQuI https://t.co/SAzNNlStei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully * Position Title –… https://t.co/0pmVcjDgCE https://t.co/Q3jnlzn8GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead – Java – US: We are The Mobile Bank. Our vision is to build a bank the world loves to use. Technology and design empower everything we do. N26 is Europes first Mobile Bank with a full European banking license. We redesigned the banking… https://t.co/5XRRvSrgd4 https://t.co/KRdja7kLj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apps Dev Intermed Java Prgmr Analyst: * Primary Location: United States,Texas,Irving * Other Location: United States,Florida,Jacksonville * Education: Bachelor’s Degree * Job Function: Technology * Schedule: Full-time * Shift: Day Job * Employee Status:… https://t.co/kySk00anxV https://t.co/Gd7DMsWjVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Optomi, in partnership with an industry leading, Fortune 100 insurance solutions provider, is seeking talented Full Stack Java Developers to lead the charge in developing innovative digital products, service APIs, and component services… https://t.co/P721Zn9LqH https://t.co/qC8IaM7siq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Full Stack Java Developer- Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Mid Full Stack Java Developer- Engineer Software 3 (18004992) Mid Full Stack Java Developer- Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18004992 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/FdRxZoI23E https://t.co/d2RW5iBhnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of Web based applications for the Retail Trading/Brokerage Systems. Strong JAVA/NGA based technologies experience is required. This job requires very… https://t.co/cUBJm5Hlzx https://t.co/30Io7ctyxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMOTE Sr. Full Stack Engineer (Java): Redwood City, CA Full-time $120k – $140k Posted Today If you are a skilled Full Stack Engineer that is looking for an interesting/comprehensive platform to dive into, please read on!!! **THIS WILL BE A 100% REMOTE… https://t.co/Ci7s1iQGHz https://t.co/zkA4UG6SJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/Bd4Dj4FwpI https://t.co/aiPvswiAA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer (REST API, Spring MVC): San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today Based in San Francisco, CA we are a innovative FinTech company purely focused on streamlining the home buying experience for consumers. We've developed a… https://t.co/XOPBslciPM https://t.co/yduTyDlJ9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Big Data: 30392BR Java Developer – Big Data Washington District Of Columbia United States This position is ideal for a software engineer that enjoys supporting legacy and new systems development and continuous improvement of mission… https://t.co/uHybj73KKI https://t.co/q0RUDqlbwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- Innovative Company!: Irvine, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Java Developer with experience, please read on! Are you a Senior Java developer that is looking for something new and exciting? Do you want… https://t.co/9fMRO9VNak https://t.co/rJqZdwO8py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Sail taps VR to help online students feel less isolated: Taking online classes is an easy way to fit college into your schedule without the need to physically be on campus. But, there are drawbacks. Full Sail University hopes that implementing… https://t.co/WlCdC9y6wy https://t.co/D3TSBXLOPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surging oil prices rattle Trump https://t.co/UBnfDUW9oD https://t.co/tczkbTstuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer: Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking a Java Application Developer. Candidate will develop application and system code, participate in code reviews and module testing, and support ongoing maintenance. Candidate… https://t.co/Ej6aGNanbz https://t.co/OPtN96JNfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/SDzdcJO0ZZ https://t.co/V0GZZQhiHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Agile Developer: We are the Company Development team. We bring to market innovative services and solutions for Company by partnering with IT developers across the company leveraging the Agile XP methodology and the Pivotal Cloud Foundry… https://t.co/7K6gPljy6q https://t.co/5AX3AttAKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/EtNHNp3ibl https://t.co/mYHvSGxQRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technology Architect – US – Java, J2EE, Microservices: Infosys Engineering Services – Senior Technology Architect – US – Java, J2EE, Full-stack, Architecture Are you looking for a change? Do you want to collaborate with some of the best talent in… https://t.co/55B8Xnwp9s https://t.co/rp0SgKtHJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Front end: Java Swing. End-user facing trading platform.Back end: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multi-threaded/high throughput. XML.QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/Ph.D. a… https://t.co/al4Ri55SnW https://t.co/inG2g10f9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Application &amp; UX Fabric (Java &amp; Javascript): Description OVERVIEW: Intuit continues to push the boundaries of technology by investing in individuals and leaders who passionately believe in the potential of innovative technologies… https://t.co/L2EdTltigT https://t.co/BVErTlKjdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lava gushes from Kilauea https://t.co/79OK8hmicO https://t.co/3LIur82JYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – Java/JavaScript – APS: Sr. Specialist Developer-&gt;&gt; Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for… https://t.co/IlVOC1b7rh https://t.co/givUu3bgQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer, Senior: Java Developer, SENIOR JOB RESPONSIBILITIES * Understand Business needs and processes; identify solutions, present and guide project team/sponsors in identifying best solution. * Participate in Requirements Analysis; design… https://t.co/7YlUhO9vn7 https://t.co/OLPEPwzKaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer, IT Data Integration – Java preferred: Careers Center | Associate Developer, IT Data Integration – Java preferred Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of… https://t.co/4v14sFvqbh https://t.co/H2dXXeMXRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Open your eyes, pro-life feminists are everywhere: Politics -- read "political parties and fundraisers" -- largely refuse to make room for pro-life feminism or what it stands for. https://t.co/ZFa22PJzzA https://t.co/8CvbefUpNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer – USC/Green Card: Need Asap :: Java Developer (Devops Exp.) * Only US Citizen/Green Card can apply. * Local candidates preferred. * Experience: 10+ yrs. * Experience with good understanding of Devops/Cloud a plus The candidates… https://t.co/h4WO8DrdgV https://t.co/IY1SnoDXhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla settles class action suit over Autopilot issues: Tesla has agreed a class action lawsuit settlement with Model S and Model X owners who claimed the Autopilot feature was "dangerous" and "essentially unusable." The settlement, which was filed at San… https://t.co/TVyxUErgLj https://t.co/r410QrBPQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was slavery a choice? A conversation beyond Kanye: The black community was up in arms over Kanye West's remarks about slavery -- for 400 years -- being a choice. https://t.co/XXc4DThY7C https://t.co/C0wWFYECbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions): IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions) Job Number: 1600620 Description This position is responsible for providing leadership and technical deliverables in the design, development, testing, documentation, and… https://t.co/N0aADlRsn3 https://t.co/JjQJkgenqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer — TS/SCI Required (Java): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Sr. Software Engineer with TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. This person will be… https://t.co/Bvz1akuMT6 https://t.co/GTLtXlqwSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right away.Your… https://t.co/NCLHNdZoZz https://t.co/eFcxcWu7ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-09051 Location: Jacksonville, FL, Florida Start Date: 05/16/2018 JOB Discription : Job TitleJava Websphere Portal Relevant Experience 8+ years of experience in Java Development Technical/Functional Skills… https://t.co/B2VNih30Cq https://t.co/HCAyrHuP1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-18939 Location: San Jose, California Position : Core Java Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : San Jose, CA Description: Required Skills: Core Java, Linux, Cloud, Virtualization Responsibilities:… https://t.co/MEMn4I65Nz https://t.co/wvy4jTvo0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat now lets you 'send and request' location info with friends (updated): Snapchat has started rolling out a new "Send and Request" location-sharing feature, according to TechCrunch. From its introduction, you could broadcast your location to all… https://t.co/g5ThNube5m https://t.co/3HL4K0dDyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer – JAVA The Senior Software Engineer primary focus of this position is to develop server based highly available JAVA solutions for the cloud using Java application servers with Spring Boot and web… https://t.co/ZDUA1OIc9r https://t.co/tbMCe93Ygi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Kardashians vs. Wests on 'Family Feud': Does Kanye West have an advantage on "Family Feud" since he has a way with words? https://t.co/QfI6WpIXm3 https://t.co/MqWQLsj6s8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Development Engineer, XP Agile: Job Description The Java Development Engineer will research, design, test, implement and educate delivery area teams on the latest open source software, technologies and methodologies as well as understand challenges… https://t.co/hAwxpDYXn6 https://t.co/gNHxhHWs3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer: Core Java Developer Ref No.: 18-18976 Location: San Jose, California Position : Core Java Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : San Jose, CA Description: Required Skills: Core Java, Linux, Cloud, Virtualization… https://t.co/Cd0Qyve9gq https://t.co/7Nk4usRVes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- J2EE/Struts: POSITION DESCRIPTION: Java Developer with extensive experience on enterprise solutions. The candidate must have strong solution design skills and the ability to document, communicate, and implement the designs patterns… https://t.co/EzJGhgkpey https://t.co/xsp7BpZhXV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>