<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie @AmnestyIreland @SIPOC Still waiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonTonyD @WrestlingSoup Good segment on White Moose. I should point out that the hotel would be considered an average price for Dublin. It's 124 euro (154 USD) per night. I was at the cafe last year after similar viral stuff. They are brilliant at getting free publicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dodging the question. https://t.co/i6VGj2zd2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup @jon7687 @DonTonyD @whitemoosecafe Excellent! I look forward to the segment. That hotel/cafe is infamous for not putting up with BSers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup @jon7687 @DonTonyD Hey Mish I look forward to hearing that segment. If you weren't aware, The hotel is called Charleville Lodge. Twitter account: @whitemoosecafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie @AmnestyIreland @SIPOC Awaiting your answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie @AmnestyIreland @SIPOC "Love Both". Are the donors published? You can't accuse without having your own house in order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pro-L*fe bots are suddenly out in force. Somebody is paying for this. Pathetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie @AmnestyIreland @SIPOC I'm asking you about your funds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacifistIreland @Office_Zombie You're going to have to prove this. Where does your campaign publish its donors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbucsfan https://t.co/6rhuHXmcri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ButlersChocs Who are their owners Conor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely nothing wrong with this. https://t.co/8P4ZynXU0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc What's your opinion Kate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realised the Oireachtas was a codeword for Kim Jong-Un. https://t.co/fAQzo6HJx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn off the TV. It will be the worst kind of car crash "debate" between the extreme on both sides. https://t.co/ciuYBhktkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*punches air* https://t.co/TQ2jLnBptX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using very young children in campaigning is deranged. https://t.co/GJiUMmoFQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This so deserves the Curb Your Enthusiasm theme. https://t.co/0QwpznHENr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 But again, suggesting violence ain't an answer. Ridicule with evidence is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 I sometimes agree with him on other topics but if this was a ruse to depict people as fascists that is beyond low. That can get people sacked and lives damaged. Horrendous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @BoxBurgerBray @eatyard So that's what went in beside the Bernard Shaw!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EimzT He's such a wind up merchant. I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas @WrestlingSoup @iamjondraper If ye do a live show in NYC for next year's WM I'd nearly considering travelling over from Ireland. I am a Soup Mark. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colliniho @threeredkings @EimzT I imagine they'll give Bill a deal. Dave is definitely gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBarnesRugby Beef or Salmon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robocopey All the best Robin. I have great memories of your demon like performance against NZ Maori. Man possessed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colliniho @threeredkings @EimzT Sherry, Johnston x2, Grobler, Loughman (short-term) remain unsigned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Strawmen. Low. https://t.co/0QwpznHENr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @aisghair Fake merch is very common. Munster Rugby had one a while back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Oh I totally understand. Better perhaps then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper It could be worse Jon. At least it's not T*isha P*ytas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 I'm torn on involving the Gardai. As bad as this is, are we feeding the trolls by making them martyrs? Tricky situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenFarmer81 @MonaghanRFC @duffyowen1 @fintyk @PaulFinlay11 @dickclerkin8 Ah no worries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenFarmer81 @MonaghanRFC @duffyowen1 @fintyk @PaulFinlay11 @dickclerkin8 Any bids yet? I'll go €120.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People can't have nice things. https://t.co/Mk2TC2j8HP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @Revolution_IRL I assume you didn't get an answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 A spell inside will do fine. What do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lidl_ireland: So err... anyone do anything nice over the weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoid. If you come across it, ignore. Calling Gardai only grants attention. That's the goal. https://t.co/JLvqMBCt8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cianaf: Had surgery this day last year, wrote about it then, figured I'd write about it now and the other places my brain has been late…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath Put em away for a nice stretch. They made themselves scumbags. Classist language is appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawl. https://t.co/MNssRNlWy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pjgallagher: @faslj19 Nah people are making out like it’s some “classist” shite. Like using the word scumbag is aimed at Tallaght. It’s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage Well said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 Well credit to the Gardai on this case. Plenty arrests made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They dehumanised themselves. https://t.co/6WSrmKbBrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Gets me every time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eoin_OF "Stupidity" is putting criminal damage and dystopian behaviour very mildly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 https://t.co/iIyti19qxB
It's a poor attempt at humour. You don't solve anything by attacking people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 FWIW the Noel Rock tweet was pathetic. I'm no fan of Paul Murphy but associating him with this thuggery is classless.
Accounts like Revolution could learn that people that disagree with you are not automatically on the 'other side' of everything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Ah I appreciate you going to bat for me but it's fine, really. If what I said causes me to get blocked then I'm happier to be blocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Otherwise your ideas never get questioned and you never learn/change your mind about things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Ah not to worry. I don't agree with a lot of your stuff but twitter shouldn't be a vacuum of accounts you completely agree with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 I questioned his tweet that bankers/DoB/media were to blame for the Lidl incident. I raised some points. Then I was blocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Revolution_IRL sadly blocked me when I dared question his earlier tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution_IRL Correct me if I'm wrong please: Destroying property and costing jobs does not put people with no connection to that business in jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution_IRL And what does stealing and destroying property do to solve this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't envy @IrishRail workers right now. Passed the DART line earlier. A river of snow. Good luck to them tonight/tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution_IRL Bad behaviour doesn't justify more bad behaviour. That's essentially what you're saying. I can't agree with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution_IRL This is called moving the goalposts. Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution_IRL The young lads just wanted to destroy and loot. Simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VoteHollandSF: The #Lidl looting isn't a case of beleagured proletariat turning against a mighty corporation, it's a small number of sc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy As have others I'm sure. 
Wonder why he couldn't get an agent....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy The toerag deleted that tweet....too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PTHosford: Lidl employs 4,500 people in Ireland, mostly in working class areas, pays them the Living Wage and sells food cheaper than m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Excellent! Thanks. Good effort from ye today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignore/Block. Simple. https://t.co/Y7JOKcCuad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Hi. I am booked on 8am Dub-Cork tomorrow but want to travel on 9am (have a semi-flexible ticket). How can I ensure I don't get a refund automatically as 8am is not running. I have not printed the ticket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Dictated by landlord? Wasn't aware. I know the difference in price...robbery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Don't get payg meters then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath Hotels will be open Vicki. They are obliged to be I think?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBridge1859 @Davens05 May call in....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davens05 @TheBridge1859 Just drink I assume? Saw an earlier tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do yourselves a favour. Do to this RugbyL*D account and block it immediately. A scumbag site. https://t.co/bOCmH3lw06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give @threeredkings money. Just do it people. https://t.co/XlqXyAFrqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same for me too! https://t.co/pvvC0gs0e1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBridge1859 @Davens05 Opening soon by any chance? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This can't be real. https://t.co/PNLGRs0zNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup @JoeNumbas @iamjondraper  Getting a taste of Murica right now in Ireland....blizzzzard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrAndrewCotter: After much consideration this remains my favourite moment from Murrayfield on Saturday. https://t.co/0GLfVmeLnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh Ignore clickbait Niamh. Unfortunately that site is plagued with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly21 @phog6189 @threeredkings Absolutely. MOD performed that role for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 And Keeeeeeeeeet. I love Keet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robin Copeland seems to perform in these dirrtracker games. Keep him around? @phog6189 @threeredkings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @ormondlad @IrishRugby I get that cost wise for IRL and visiting teams Donnybrook may make sense but games really should be moved around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @IrishRugby Clashing with Leinster wasn't great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Good night? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Raids today by CAB...not just rickshaws they are after!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I click hashtag armourteachers it's all bots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloyjh As someone else said, I'd love to be the teacher with the gun in my head when the SWAT team arrive and blast the "adult with the gun".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeejayOV2 I'm dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoconnorbl Cheers for the link. One to read later!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EimzT I thought so. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EimzT I couldn't agree more. Though I wonder would the same happen in a case based in RoI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic! You can abuse the players in person! https://t.co/CkTyOw7Pf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OliverNorgrove: I'm worried by Leaver attacks on the Good Friday Agreement. This sort of discourse follows the pathetic anti-Irish sent…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland -9 as a spread is pretty crazy considering that Wales lineup. I'll be shocked if it's more than a one score game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDunc123 I was wondering had you lost it there for a sec when you just retweeted him. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbucsfan Jesus wrote the second amendment.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>