<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["When it rains, why don't sheep shrink?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a parsley farmer is sued, can they garnish his wages?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the cops arrest a mime, do they tell him he has the right to remain silent?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a stealth bomber crashes in a forest, will it make a sound?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When companies ship styrofoam, what do they pack it in?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're cross-eyed and have dyslexia, can you read all right?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a book about failures doesn't sell, is it a success?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a shame his parents didn't get divorced thirty years ago. He could've been normal." - Jerry, about George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These pretzels are making me thirsty!" -Kramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is it possible to be totally partial?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did you know that the original title for War and Peace was War, What Is It Good For?" - Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Can you be a closet claustrophobic?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would drape myself in velvet if it were socially acceptable." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "Why do they make the condom packets so hard to open?" Jerry: "Probably to give the woman a chance to change her mind."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do they call it a "building"? It looks like they're finished. Why isn't it a "built?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry : "I'll tell you what the big advantage of homosexuality is. If you're going out with someone your size, you double your wardrobe."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who read the tabloids deserve to be lied to."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "Look at that, a lesbian sighting. They're so fascinating. Why is that? Because they don't want us. You gotta respect that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did you ever notice when you blow in a dog's face he gets mad at you? But when you take him in a car he sticks his head out the window."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You want a Christmas card? You want a Christmas card? Here's your Christmas card!!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "If Relationship George walks through this door, he will kill Independent George. A George, divided against itself, cannot stand!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A bookstore is one of the only pieces of evidence we have that people are still thinking."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is it illegal to park in a handicapped parking space but okay to go the bathroom in a handicapped stall?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you open a bag of cotton balls, is the top one meant to be thrown away?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: I know a guy who took a vacation on his change. Jerry: Yeah, Where'd he go, an arcade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine: "Perhaps, there's more to Newman than meets the eye." Jerry: "No. there's less."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to stay in shape. My grandmother started walking five miles a day when she was 60. She's 97 today and we don't know where she is."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do they call it a "building"? It looks like they're finished. Why isn't it a "built?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes the road less traveled is less traveled for a reason"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's the true spirit of Christmas; people being helped by people other than me"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is there another word for synonym?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The big advantage of a book is it's very easy to rewind. Close it and you're right back at the beginning."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't return fruit. Fruit is a gamble. I know that going in." -Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Isn't it weird that we drink milk, stuff designed to nourish baby cows? How did that happen? Did some cattleman once say, "Oh, man, I can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fireman: "How do you live with yourself?" George: "It's not easy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "Yeah. I figured since I was lying about my income for a couple of years, I could afford a fake house in the Hamptons."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Can fat people go skinny-dipping?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do hungry crows have ravenous appetites?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "Who buys an umbrella anyway? You can get them for free at the coffee shop in those metal cans."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The reason most people play golf is to wear clothes they would not be caught dead in otherwise."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're cross-eyed and have dyslexia, can you read all right?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Men don't care what's on TV. They only care what else is on TV."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "I'm speechless. Speechless! I have no speech."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who read the tabloids deserve to be lied to."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do they call it a "building"? It looks like they're finished. Why isn't it a "built?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes the road less traveled is less traveled for a reason"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't like the opera. What are they singing for? Who sings? You got something to say, say it"  -Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kramer: I love the name 'isosceles'. If I had a kid, I would name him Isosceles. Isosceles Kramer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know, if you take everything I've done in my entire life and condense it down into one day, it looks decent." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I always wanted to be somebody, but I should have been more specific."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "She's got a little Marissa Tomei thing goin' on." Jerry: "Ah, too bad you've got a little George Costanza thing goin' on."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm still trying to figure out why kamikaze pilots wore helmets."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is the word abbreviation so long?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: "Looking at cleavage is like looking at the sun. You don't stare at it. You get a sense of it and you look away."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: "My father was a quitter, my grandfather was a quitter, I was raised to give up. It's one of the few things I do well."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just remember, it's not a lie if you believe it." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["what's so great about a mom and pop store? let me tell ya something, if my mom and pop ran a store, i wouldnt shop there"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm much more comfortable criticizing people behind their backs." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a parsley farmer is sued, can they garnish his wages?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How come you have to pay someone to rotate your tires? Isn't that the basic idea behind the wheel? Don't they rotate on their own?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine: "You'd really like him." Jerry: "Why do people always say that? I hate everyone, why would I like him?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anytime four New Yorkers get into a cab together without arguing,a bank robbery has just taken place."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: "Broccoli? Newman, you wouldn't eat broccoli even if it was deep fried in chocolate sauce."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Well, it all sounds pretty glamourous, but it's business as usual at Kramerica."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a mute swears, does his mother wash his hands with soap?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Isn't it a bit unnerving that doctors call what they do "practice?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Instead of talking to your plants, if you yelled at them would they still grow? Only to be troubled and insecure?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: "Do the people that work in those little shops at the airport have any idea what the prices are, everywhere else in the world?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love a good nap. Sometimes it's the only thing getting me out of bed in the morning." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry will be performing this Friday the 26th in Newark, NJ! Check future tour dates and tickets here! http://t.co/pAZf0n256v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why do they report power outages on TV?" #Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never tasted a cough medicine I didn't love." -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'll tell you what I like about Chinese people... they're stickin' with the chopsticks."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When it rains, why don't sheep shrink?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the cops arrest a mime, do they tell him he has the right to remain silent?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Because I'm like ice, buddy. When I don't like you, you've got problems"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The story is the foundation of all entertainment. You must have a good story otherwise it's just masturbation" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George: I think I can sum up the show for you with one word: Nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry the card says "Moops"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine: My father thinks George is gay. Jerry: Because of all the singing? Elaine: No, he pretty much thinks everyone is gay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I can’t be blind, Jerry. The blind are courageous” -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every woman on the face of the Earth has complete control of my life and yet, I want them all. Is that irony?" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A leg man? Why would I be a leg man? I don’t need legs. I have legs” — Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel like I've had two lives. My pre-mousse, and now I begin my post-mousse" -Kramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I was the best man at the wedding. If I’m the best man, why is she marrying him?” -Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ve driven women to lesbianism before but never to a mental institution” -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If you don’t have anything bad to say about a relationship, don’t say anything at all!” -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One hundred percent cotton-Dockers. If they're not Dockers, they're just pants" -Kramer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A relationship is an organism. You created this thing and then you starved it, so it turned against you. Same thing happened to the Blob"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: He's a doctor. You gotta pay what he says. George: Oh, no, no, no. I pay what I say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm lactose intolerant. I have no tolerance for lactose and I won't stand for it!" -Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know, when you read Moby Dick the second time Ahab and the whale become good friends" -Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Instead of doing a wash I just keep buying underwear. My goal is to have over 360 pair. That way I only have to do wash once a year"-George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I lie every second of the day. My whole life is a sham" -George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't turn down money! It's what separates us from the animals" -Jerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two bedrooms? Why do I need two bedrooms? I got enough trouble maintaining activity in one -Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Kramer Poster! http://t.co/HYkOTXmAhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry: But the question is, are you still master of your domain? Elaine: I'm queen of the castle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jpRniFAFdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/h6Svjil5EX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>