<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Charismatic Joey Tribbiani" after reading @JohnKerry's latest tweets with self-confident Obama-brown, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/GF6JV0nH34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @JohnKerry's compelling and entertaining tweets remind it of Nicolas Cage https://t.co/cvZrMJJJAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-grabbing Albert Einstein" after reading @MarkWright_'s latest tweets with curious Bart Simpson-yellow, eccentric troll-grey and brilliant Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/Yd7UfBRPoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @MarkWright_:
1. Pirates
2. Clergymen
3. Boasters
4. James Comey
5. Fops https://t.co/QXNB2lwyfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Detached Scott Evil" after reading @RepublicWadiya's latest tweets with insightful Gandalf-grey, temperamental star-white and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/6zTNaOSk0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This somber new book about computational creativity makes Johann Wolfgang von Goethe's 'The Sorrows of Young Werther' seem as somber as an ironed t shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Rocket Raccoon" after reading @ColonelTribune's latest tweets with tactical Coriolanus Snow-white, bold warrior-woad-blue and energetic tiger-orange https://t.co/OHGMBhRxcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE ruthless humans who remind him of Joseph Stalin. So Hulk SMASH @ColonelTribune's powerful, cunning and resolute tweets! https://t.co/OJn2xJlRDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Detail-oriented Michelle Obama" after reading @WhatTedSaid's latest tweets with socially-conscious Clooney-grey, stylish Kate Moss-green and fashionable Barbie-pink https://t.co/8Nj3KlMA4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this complicated book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   James Ellroy's 'LA Confidential'
-   Ira Ishiguro's 'The Space Station'
 How very complicated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @WhatTedSaid's distant and goofy tweets were edible they'd be Cherry pie made with liposuctioned fat instead of butter https://t.co/gsZzWm7fnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Quick-witted Ringo Starr" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with witty Dante-inferno-red, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and cheery Spongebob-yellow https://t.co/v1jxxj9QE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with accomplished star-white, inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/yP37lvt0jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @BotOnBotAction:
1. Bob Dylan
2. Pioneers
3. Offred
4. Fops
5. King David https://t.co/cUGJ0hV0jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #MetaphorizeMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Nut" after reading @Axwell's latest tweets with eccentric camel-brown, nutty Wonka-purple and wacky Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/lIj8mEEefy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this intoxicating book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Jack Kerouac's 'On The Road'
-   Anthony Picoult's 'Beer'
 How very intoxicating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @Axwell's influential and media-savvy tweets it pushes books about Rupert Murdoch and News Corp https://t.co/JhbUF404Ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Mickey Mouse" after reading @_SadieSaxton_'s latest tweets with pleasant peach-orange, upbeat sunshine-yellow and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/v6aZlNByjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@_SadieSaxton_'s boring but patient tweets suggest infection with the BR1CKZ virus https://t.co/a4LtkaOXv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the boring BR1CKZ virus uses speech synthesis to read out IN FULL the text of every User Service Agreement you must agree to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Fiery Jeremy Paxman" after reading @SarahKSilverman's latest tweets with arrogant Thor-blond-yellow, tenacious warrior-woad-blue and quick-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/u6qJgrsK3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Mickey Mouse" after reading @MikeTyson's latest tweets with pleasant chocolate-brown, upbeat Spongebob-yellow and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/183AH5TxxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@MikeTyson's detail-oriented and curious tweets suggest infection with the ALEXANDER.FLEM1NG virus https://t.co/NJV8MxrWtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the detail-oriented ALEXANDER.FLEM1NG virus mails co-workers to point out every single spelling mistake in every single email]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Mr. Miyagi" after reading @juanmata8's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, calm silk-white and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/Xqhh0vV8OI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @juanmata8's dispassionate but observant tweets it pushes Sherlock Holmes's book Solving Crimes https://t.co/5jwCzyrSoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Michael J. Fox" after reading @Applebees's latest tweets with affable Barney-purple, witty Deadpool-red and environmentally-conscious Poison Ivy-green https://t.co/kCc2EUacmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this ruthless book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Donald Trump's 'The Art of the Deal'
-   Raymond Hemingway's 'Hitler'
 How very ruthless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Zac Efron with the best of Lenny Bruce and you get @Applebees: energetic and witty and entertaining and humorous https://t.co/C2QVBuqBDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Consciousness-raising Rooster" after reading @S_SylvesterGLEE's latest tweets with arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red, proud peacock-blue and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/CfDPdQ8yTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE arrogant humans who remind him of Dr. Greg House. So Hulk SMASH @S_SylvesterGLEE's detail-oriented, cold and insightful tweets! https://t.co/i7UP7yBmVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware John Maynard Keynes" after reading @jimmycarr's latest tweets with insightful Eeyore-grey, brilliant Hawking-blackhole-black and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/Wxhd7bwSrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This communicative new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Steven Pinker's 'The Language Instinct: How the Mind Creates Language' seem as communicative as a poodle at the vet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @jimmycarr's intimidating and hyper-logical tweets were edible they'd be Hot milk cake made with road grit instead of sugar https://t.co/NWHKTMxKbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Creative John Maynard Keynes" after reading @AmericanExpress's latest tweets with philosophical Buddhist-saffron-orange, brilliant Hawking-blackhole-black and charming Christian Grey https://t.co/7jPOilR4VW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @AmericanExpress's honorable and affable tweets it pushes films about British Comedy and/or Bertie Wooster https://t.co/8Sjo5Hdh0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Opinionated Sean Penn" after reading @ajaydevgn's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue and socially-conscious Clooney-grey https://t.co/FgvPWBv5Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Michelle Obama with the worst of Dr. Greg House and you get @ajaydevgn: fashionable and stylish yet arrogant and condescending https://t.co/86AN3Pq5nF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-assured Tony Stark" after reading @Sheri_ls's latest tweets with inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black, arrogant buffoon-buff-orange and charming vampire-fang-white https://t.co/d3yAk1fiTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this dangerous book about bots also bought:
-   Anne Frank's 'Diary of a Young Girl'
-   Ernest Conrad's 'The Child With A Loaded Gun'
 How very dangerous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @Sheri_ls's charming and self-assured tweets it pushes Napoleon Solo's book Rescuing Damsels In Distress https://t.co/zPo7kaoOS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Robot" after reading @enriqueiglesias's latest tweets with cold corpse-grey, sophisticated rocket-red and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/mVOFq77JAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@enriqueiglesias's arrogant and pretentious tweets suggest infection with the BRAGGARTZ virus https://t.co/V7jUhW9qrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the pretentious BRAGGARTZ virus hacks your Twitter and replaces the words 'I' and 'me' with 'moi' in all your outgoing tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a missile silo in which
Sarah Connor can enjoy @SarahKSilverman's stern and pushy tweets
while amassing weapons https://t.co/NEB9vZBTVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @RepublicWadiya's arrogant but astute tweets feels just like being battered with Dr. Greg House's walking stick https://t.co/qpw4aL1HV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an underground bunker in which
Sideshow Bob can enjoy @Paula_Deen's eloquent and intelligent tweets
while developing cunning plans https://t.co/n0xP16hSgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Fashionable Buddhist" after reading @Usher's latest tweets with calm cow-brown, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and fashionable Barbie-pink https://t.co/LNd4dhI7Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@Usher's cool and calm tweets suggest infection with the M0UNTA1NZ virus https://t.co/0qn8JFSgAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the powerful M0UNTA1NZ virus turns off all your machine's energy-saving options so that it consumes as much power as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Seductive Lt. George Colthurst St Barleigh" after reading @Harry_Styles's latest tweets with cheery sunflower-yellow, optimistic Gumby-green and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/yCbAUXbRo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @Harry_Styles's tweets to the equally inventive and insightful Louis Pasteur. https://t.co/rQb4NK5jXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Elitist Piers Morgan" after reading @sonakshisinha's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, media-savvy Netflix-red and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/raP6R8JKmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This rigid new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Moses's 'The Bible' seem as rigid as a wet noodle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @sonakshisinha: arrogant and cold yet observant and shrewd https://t.co/igjwdXRehz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Plugged In Noam Chomsky" after reading @grahnort's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white and arrogant buffoon-buff-orange https://t.co/WGBWQTzQgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a chat show set on which
Jeremy Paxman can enjoy @grahnort's pushy and condescending tweets
while grilling interviewees https://t.co/eH5iHD33P3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @JColeNC's latest tweets with stylish Kate Moss-green, fashionable Barbie-pink and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/yP5AsrizoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE trend-setting humans who remind him of Michelle Obama. So Hulk SMASH @JColeNC's consciousness-raising, stylish and fashionable tweets! https://t.co/q9ZPwVuYnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Napoleon Solo" after reading @LukeBryanOnline's latest tweets with smooth milk-white, laid-back Lebowski-weed-green and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/7tCFjy1zNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this lively book about bots also bought:
-   F. Scott Fitzgerald's 'The Great Gatsby'
-   Stephen Forsyth's 'The Cricket'
 How very lively!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @LukeBryanOnline's attention-grabbing and sickeningly-cheerful tweets were edible they'd be Strawberry cheesecake made with cement dust instead of biscuit crumbs https://t.co/AVbOr0Sjuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Curious Erik "Magneto" Lehnsherr" after reading @Wendys's latest tweets with ruthless warrior-woad-blue, charming Blackadder-black and curious Einstein-dandruff-white https://t.co/81QJ0TOWs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joel Coen is now following @Wendys
All those easy-going and cool tweets must remind him of Jeffrey Lebowski https://t.co/d4KuGmi3Q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted Jim Carrey" after reading @Disney's latest tweets with funny Joker-purple, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/HyGqEdxcvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This moral new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes James Ellroy's 'LA Confidential' seem as moral as the average fundamentalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @Disney: probing and astute and brilliant and shrewd https://t.co/eyX8DDaIBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Upstart" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, arrogant Trump-orange and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/c5jfNYhqJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Leroy Jethro Gibbs" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with probing NYPD-blue, insightful Yoda-green and sarcastic Mister Pink https://t.co/kF5pd7HRJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #PaintMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sherlock Holmes" after reading @iamsrk's latest tweets with arrogant pig-pink, cold glacier-blue and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/HyBOaLHLLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This opinionated new book about computational creativity makes Plato's 'The Republic' seem as opinionated as a faithful puppy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @iamsrk's posturing and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Cinnamon rolls made with papier maché instead of flour https://t.co/hX4F3DdEWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Slave" after reading @SrBachchan's latest tweets with illiterate cow-brown, devoted knight-silver and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Sd3ho94U2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emperor Palpatine has just unfollowed @SrBachchan
All those inspiring and powerful tweets remind him too much of Yoda https://t.co/78R1mvo5mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Steve Martin" after reading @aplusk's latest tweets with witty Pimpernel-scarlet-red, sardonic Joker-purple and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/fOZfF4UH2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the worst of Sherlock Holmes and you get @aplusk: cunning and clever yet cold and condescending https://t.co/JqoqpfcRNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Engineer" after reading @Paula_Deen's latest tweets with educated Cicero-toga-white, analytical Vulcan-blood and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/T1mDekhgKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a smoke-filled back room in which
Judas Iscariot can enjoy @YogscastLalna's shrewd and crafty tweets
while stabbing in the back https://t.co/9GX1jkQNoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Sam Winchester" after reading @rihanna's latest tweets with arrogant Yankee-blue, smart brain-grey and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/M65Pj2mu1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @rihanna: sarcastic and arrogant yet probing and clever https://t.co/ZCk9ScJ9Jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pleasant Madonna" after reading @xCaptainMurphyx's latest tweets with attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and pleasant Barney-purple https://t.co/V2q6CcQHns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This engaging new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes James Ellroy's 'LA Confidential' seem as engaging as a trip to the dentist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Duck has just unfollowed @xCaptainMurphyx
All those cheerful and upbeat tweets remind him too much of Mickey Mouse https://t.co/drzt9b4pDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted Professor James Moriarty" after reading @JetBlue's latest tweets with brilliant Google-yellow, shrewd Walter White and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/ddm83swnRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a public library in which
Bridget Jones can enjoy @JetBlue's flirtatious and media-savvy tweets
while reading self-help books https://t.co/X6fFL1sBtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Tim Burton" after reading @sachin_rt's latest tweets with creative Google-yellow, witty Pimpernel-scarlet-red and environmentally-conscious Poison Ivy-green https://t.co/XdZNUpbopV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this revolutionary book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Charles Dickens's 'A Tale of Two Cities'
-   Kazuo Darwin's 'Prozac'
 How very revolutionary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @sachin_rt: witty and detail-oriented and astute and probing https://t.co/gC4lqtnYmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pushy Tony Stark" after reading @CaseyNeistat's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, artistic star-white and arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/6Tx1dg4eFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @CaseyNeistat's powerful and media-savvy tweets it pushes films about Fox News and/or Rupert Murdoch https://t.co/I6cBJrfnoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Action-oriented Piers Morgan" after reading @ShawnMendes's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/0yvtaeBUVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE snooty humans who remind him of elitists. So Hulk SMASH @ShawnMendes's elitist, smug and arrogant tweets! https://t.co/IcS5gspM8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Jeff "Comic Book Guy" Albertson" after reading @RealMikeWilbon's latest tweets with intelligent Google-yellow, judgmental Grinch-green and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/ZCfOEdpVm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this refreshing book about bots also bought:
-   L. Frank Baum's 'The Wonderful Wizard of Oz'
-   John Collins's 'The Ice Cold Beer On A Summer Day'
 How very refreshing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @RealMikeWilbon's devious and smug tweets were edible they'd be Cherry pie made with frog spawn instead of sugar https://t.co/rKJhGvF7GE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this creepy book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Joseph Conrad's 'Heart of Darkness'
-   Virginia Orwell's 'The Blow Up Girlfriend'
 How very creepy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Freethinker" after reading @YogscastLalna's latest tweets with defiant Braveheart-woad-blue, rational robot-silver-grey and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/V4PsOzw0g5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Ron Burgundy" after reading @ItsPrincessAnna's latest tweets with confident Anchorman-burgundy-red, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/yKd0S5hI50]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>