<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer: For BNY Mellon Sr. Specialist Developer job – Information Technology – Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers –… https://t.co/9eTZepnoZg https://t.co/UVROMmmqiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domestic Truck (Port and Rail) Dispatcher – ROAR: Domestic Truck (Port and Rail) Dispatcher – ROAR Job Start Date: Apr 27, 2018 Location: Burlingame, CA, NY, US, 94010 Company: Rich Products Corporation Rich’s has been able to pull off something rare in… https://t.co/TLaOzeaK7L https://t.co/i1WhN3S8uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineer – Singapore: Data Centre experience Electrical Engineer to support the long term growth in Singapore and Asia Pacific. Serve as Electrical design discipline lead for the preparation of the design of HV/LV power systems, lighting and… https://t.co/HyfspkrEMP https://t.co/SLUnDBfayX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interim Service Owner – Voice: Interim Service Owner – VoiceVITA91557511*Chester, VA*Oversight of the client’s Telecommunications Services.  The Service Owner – Voice and Video functions as the business owner for delivery of Voice and Video strategies,… https://t.co/1bFeBnaAoP https://t.co/fnVRRHZzt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAD technician-Structural Design-Corvallis OR: Support our water clients and have a hand in transforming tomorrow As a CAD technician, you’ll have the chance to work on water projects that help provide safe, sustainable water solutions for our clients… https://t.co/iAK1nWeBk4 https://t.co/StSyjErmXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager III: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Product Manager within PNC’s Debit,… https://t.co/WEXJAjadcR https://t.co/n64fFLqjTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared: DescriptionMID-LEVEL JAVA API DEVELOPER (Java, Rest API, JS) Title: Mid-Level Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance:… https://t.co/Mn4YJNM8kI https://t.co/DYTr9Tukt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimization &amp; Innovation Intern: At Kepler Group, youll be front and center in the data-driven, digital marketing revolution. Since our 2012 start, weve grown to service over 15 of the worlds leading brands. Our teams harness data and technology to… https://t.co/yA5IqiIvYk https://t.co/7GVDalVc7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer: Web Designer * Duration: 6 month * Location: Tallahassee, FL * Pay rate: W2 Hourly About the Job Our Client is seeking qualified candidates for the position of .Net Developer in Tallahassee, FL area for the contract opportunity. Purpose:… https://t.co/fBrxYHBKNL https://t.co/xTNm2LIh7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title Entry Level Avionics Software Engineer: Job Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 2 hours ago(4/25/2018 8:10 AM) Requisition ID 2018-3281 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development company headquartered in… https://t.co/PPoR20cZUC https://t.co/nixv9Jblkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Associate: Service Desk Associate Business Stores – Kmart Hourly Job Description Provides "World Class" Member Service by surprising and delighting our members every day. Performs daily responsibilities including, but not limited to:… https://t.co/5EdpNG8kv3 https://t.co/B5iST6WAnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer – Big Data: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/GJ9VIB43D3 https://t.co/WXCuRbyhGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Supervisor: CalPortland – “EXPECT MORE… WE DELIVER!”This is us…– Best-in-Class, industry leader with a rich 126-year history– Largest building materials contributor to some of the West’s biggest construction projects including:• Los Angeles… https://t.co/7eABzEOEJL https://t.co/OirttnjQ8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity &amp; Privacy – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us… https://t.co/1Cn3sgO35A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Abington): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/iIpC4Cm4r5 https://t.co/qlduVbJYZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Westwood): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/Nh4n7JkiYv https://t.co/VaBtcOuSwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Services People &amp; Org Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/QHwqywNpFC https://t.co/U3I0gh1gFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React.JS / Node.JS Developer (Immediate Opening): We are seeking a strong React.JS / Node.JS Developer &amp; React.JS Architect for our clients project in Wayne, NJ. We are looking to close this role this week. Duration: 6+ Months Client Domain: Ecommerce… https://t.co/jttJ2B09Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Consultant/ IT Support Specialist: We have full time work from home positions. IT Support Specialist Our support team is broken down into two main groups. The first group are our first responders, tasked with receiving all support requests and… https://t.co/MTDAnTy5zF https://t.co/hnK3UT8zxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low Observable Specialist II:   Job Description – Low Observable Specialist II (17023677) Low Observable Specialist II Requisition ID : 17023677 Location : United States-California-Edwards AFB US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/0mRFXifOiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineering Project Manager: Tacoma, WA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Electrical Engineer with PM experience in the Tacoma, WA area and you're looking for your next great career opportunity with a leading manufacturer of… https://t.co/OmA4IC2kdw https://t.co/aQ118t764V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect/Designer Digital Fabrication Project Manager: Job Description Timbur LLC Architect/Designer | Digital Fabrication Project Manager We are looking for an experienced, highly motivated individual for a Design Development and Project Management… https://t.co/uZctfScH5R https://t.co/s9EaE3JBUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: This Trump answer on Russian collusion is a real doozy: On Friday morning, President Donald Trump and German Chancellor Angela Merkel were huddled in the Oval Office. Reporters were allowed in for a few photos and some shouted questions. Fox… https://t.co/t0rPAYPBJs https://t.co/60ktcT8wRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Engineer – San Antonio, TX: Revature has partnered with a Fortune 500 company to find and develop a strong team of 20 Entry Level Software Engineers to work on next gen software solutions. This is an excellent opportunity for an… https://t.co/xpUudOAFpw https://t.co/qdtyR64Fk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/M2FKctoQJk https://t.co/V5n2c2c3N1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the New Snap Spectacles Matter: Want to see the future? Try squinting through Spectacles. https://t.co/vq7Le3eor6 https://t.co/46U6NKQc3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike 'The Situation' Sorrentino is engaged https://t.co/TxW0bKaMXc https://t.co/9an8i0WtPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The week in 22 photos: Take a look at 22 photos of the week from April 20 through April 27. https://t.co/Bvk0yOTkz4 https://t.co/u11CkxaKe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Somerset): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/Gf0Ss8z6Au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tulsa, First Class-Unlimited Stationary Engineer 3rd Shift: JOB SUMMARY Position requires a Tulsa 1st Class-Unlimited Stationary Engineer license. Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings,… https://t.co/QvaVLaJWp3 https://t.co/BWh96QbvIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RF Engineer Staff Member for Satellite Communications: Req ID : 398076BR_2 Job Code/Title : E1684:RF Engineer Stf Job Description : Digital Communications System Designer: Lockheed Martin Space Systems Company is looking for top talent to design… https://t.co/OaKyoadKbU https://t.co/MrtSRKoQmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: We are looking for a Java Developer with experience in building high-performing, scalable, enterprise-grade applications. You will be part of a talented software team that works on mission-critical applications. Java developer… https://t.co/Bnnqzf1rA9 https://t.co/XuwkUcTx9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems Engineer 3 or 4-Dev Ops – Secret clearance required:   Job Description – Cyber Systems Engineer 3 or 4-Dev Ops – Secret clearance required (18006056) Cyber Systems Engineer 3 or 4-Dev Ops – Secret clearance required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/TsfpqvMrDa https://t.co/HPDhFoN2S4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Automation Engineer (#3662BK042018): COMPANY DESCRIPTION * Specializes in chemical processing equipment and supplies * Has over 30 years of industry experience * Values social and environmental corporate responsibility JOB DESCRIPTION * Program… https://t.co/ADdmH1vO8b https://t.co/30pGXOJYWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Computer/IT Software Developer: Design and develop code in middle tier and backend mostly, have code reviews, mentor development team, hold test sessions, responsible for technical operations including emergencies, finance and client… https://t.co/BYlS2uuIY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's bringing Kim Jong Un to the table: North Korea's relationship with the world seems to be changing for the better. But how did we get here? https://t.co/vKHL4aqFkN https://t.co/MIl05YQkIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer #R10001338: IT: Senior Developer job open at Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA. Job # R10001338 Job Description: Senior Developer sought by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA to utilize… https://t.co/Vp5FQvdemG https://t.co/5SXeEyJNNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: So, Scott Pruitt totally lied about raises for his employees: Something amazing happened Thursday morning on Capitol Hill. https://t.co/4ksKbzhJUW https://t.co/uebE7pqTXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Solution Architect: Infrastructure Solution Architect VDOT87558914*Fairfax, VA*  North VA Client desires systems administration duties to be performed for the TOC.  The majority of these duties shall be conducted on-site.  Work space will… https://t.co/rQZgRyeFtm https://t.co/qba5W21sl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Description We are currently seeking a PHP Developer to join our team of software engineers.  Candidate will work both collaboratively to help maintain and modernize our company’s multi-platform transactional databases and systems.  This… https://t.co/TO53KOvMQa https://t.co/4jOc2N3vVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/iXxmSHOoN0 https://t.co/SqrN1Po7l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advocates offer Facebook Live sex ed: In one video, a bearded young man sits with an inflatable penis on a shelf behind him and talks frankly about sexually transmitted infections. In another, a young Muslim woman comfortably delves into steps and… https://t.co/z7gfmxe9nR https://t.co/I1tiEXtKiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (North Attleboro): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes… https://t.co/k6HJD3wi5r https://t.co/3gVTPvpEe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/ecuakuYZ3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title – Senior Solutions Architect, Job Code CT207: Senior Solutions Architect, Job Code CT207 (CitiusTech, Princeton, NJ) Onsite Coordinator and Scrum Master. Facilitate collaboration between the Scrum team and client. Ensuring quality delivery on… https://t.co/DDZnb1GPld https://t.co/1DR4NYRlb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania stuns in her state dinner gown: First Lady Melania Trump is known for her fashion sense. These are some of her most talked about outfits. https://t.co/PjZ7An056r https://t.co/2Z6qPEJxYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portfolio Test Manager- Data Services (ESP): Job ID: TR-******* Description: As the healthcare industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable… https://t.co/BLggMPHpkP https://t.co/pU3Ha3dwqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Systems Analyst: Controls Systems Analyst City (or Nearest City) Denver Job Description Summary Analyst oversees and participates in the maintenance and modification of existing building controls systems (AAM, Modicon, TAC, Optimum Energy (OE),… https://t.co/5lRpMLkpHn https://t.co/1bKJ0iuSXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Tasks: Hands On With Google's New To-Do List App: The newest Google app is a simple and easy to-do list named Tasks. https://t.co/18EiPOphzB https://t.co/m5D6TSrnAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Design Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Development Engineer (Req#9UJRYF) Dsgn &amp; dev systms for spatial data ingestion, normalization, anlysis, format intrchnge &amp; publshing. Engineering Program… https://t.co/0m60WPika9 https://t.co/xqz6j1i6FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Direct Support Professional-PT-Fargo: CHI CORE JOB COMPETENCIES   Core CHI Behaviors:  The following behaviors have been identified as critical to all leadership roles at CHI. Integrity &amp; Character – exhibits high standards of personal conduct by… https://t.co/1npZGqboSv https://t.co/QfJ5AKhKK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Modeler: Does your dream job include the following? * Friendly and respectful work environment. * Open, supportive, collaborative, team focused environment. * Opportunities to grow within your job and grow with the company. * Recognition for… https://t.co/0tKpGikE46 https://t.co/KPElKQCQEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Security – Mgr Systems Engineering 2:   Job Description – System Security – Mgr Systems Engineering 2 (18006552) System Security – Mgr Systems Engineering 2 Requisition ID : 18006552 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship… https://t.co/BxxNwIABh6 https://t.co/KgaxPE8Smn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Looking for the next step in your career? Enjoy a challenge? Do you have an ambition for innovation? Want to make a difference? If you join our growing global team, you ll be working for an industry leader with offices across five… https://t.co/RzCJjHz6MH https://t.co/ZEkgmx4SlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump just effectively killed Ronny Jackson's nomination: During his joint news conference with French President Emmanuel Macron on Tuesday, President Donald Trump wanted to make two things very clear in regard to his embattled Veteran Affairs… https://t.co/3u8BsCEcDC https://t.co/nezxPDRveA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Begala: Sean Hannity is a welfare queen: Sean Hannity is a welfare queen. https://t.co/T5S9uNonIe https://t.co/wjgf9ryRPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipboard's Answer to Fake News: More Human Curation: The news aggregator is focusing on human curation at a time when people distrust the news. https://t.co/QiBc8Qk085 https://t.co/dFnh7wvYoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Specialist #XGGS18FC0318RIC4: Technology Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application Management Services (AMS) in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites… https://t.co/NUNjpV0iK8 https://t.co/0tvfr4nXkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama makes Melania smile: Twitter erupts after former President Barack Obama makes Melania Trump smile. CNN's Jeanne Moos says it is not what it's cracked up to be. https://t.co/Srk6xs1zEE https://t.co/UdysxiHB3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Najanaja Ltd Flower Mound, TX. recblid g5a0n0dmtph3zl9xdzjogrjx7okyvw https://t.co/c3Dx1eakGi https://t.co/jmdfchZIF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Developer: Overview Ralis Services has an immediate opening for a Sr. UI Developer to join our Web Development team. In this role, the Sr. UI Developer will work with Marketing, Business, and Development teams to code multiple brand UI… https://t.co/L5qJZUJ8ux https://t.co/dT8Y1ksWeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Hi , Greetings from Macropace Technologies. We have a job opening with suits for you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested for this position. Software Developer Bellevue, WA Fulltime position… https://t.co/cSRkXAlOMf https://t.co/HYLSwvMQlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2:   Job Description – Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2 (18001342) Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18001342 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder US Citizenship… https://t.co/Pea4USsRa7 https://t.co/G7peIYfSDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican women wonder when they'll get a female speaker of the House: In the days since House Speaker Paul Ryan announced his retirement, the jockeying for the speaker's gavel has centered on three names. https://t.co/hi1k0llElp https://t.co/R2aTWMwTmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Senior: Req ID : 427314BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : We are seeking a Software Engineer to join the dynamic SBIRS Software Development Team! The selected candidate will design, develop, and test… https://t.co/5vTbHCpbpk https://t.co/7eydaChVQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Software Engineer: IT Software Engineer This position is responsible for the delivery of technical components within Allegion s Americas Region. The Software Engineer will work on projects primarily delivered to (but not limited to the) the Americas… https://t.co/UeWMQtKLCw https://t.co/ZBpe8uClHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Data Analyst: Financial Data Analyst – Spalding Consulting, Inc. ************** *************** – Home – About – Solutions – Careers – Contracts – Contact – My Account Job Openings &gt;&gt; Financial Data Analyst Financial Data Analyst Summary… https://t.co/rb9QvzSQXh https://t.co/cBBAt1bazJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows fraternity mocking disabilities: Syracuse University has expelled a fraternity after videos surfaced showing members exhibiting inappropriate behavior, according to the university's chancellor. https://t.co/PKMXmwKUnJ https://t.co/2kEkqXz9pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer Application Software: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV… https://t.co/utyWM0EOQw https://t.co/oUKHHnhjlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5 yrs of… https://t.co/c00RGcj7oL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 presidents come together for Barbara Bush: A touching photograph of several generations of presidents paying tribute to the late Barbara Bush is being warmly and widely circulated on social media. https://t.co/Yny9OXVgFp https://t.co/nGx6KbpaJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Manager: COMPUTER/IT: ANSYS, Inc. Sr Manager, Software Development to work in San Jose, CA. Driv innovatn in semicondctr dsgn &amp; manuf to enabl smallr devic archictr w/ hghr perfrmnc &amp; enrgy efficncy for pow-rng the smart prdct revolutn. Degree &amp;… https://t.co/Vau68ME1oU https://t.co/ElYffTXu3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Technician / Engineer: Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment… https://t.co/taAkDFcp9v https://t.co/smCKyxmd4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Operations Security Support Job: Date: Apr 11, 2018 Location:Herndon, VA, US Company: SAIC Mission Operations Security Support (Job Number:426268) Description: Introduction The position provides oversight and direction for the network of… https://t.co/OCTavLrkbn https://t.co/cs4WYZZ4cC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine Regional Sales Manager, Channel Sales: Marine Regional Sales Manager, Channel Sales Location: US – Remote ID: 9182 Time Type: Regular # of Openings: 1 Description Trimble is recruiting for a Marine Regional Sales Manager (MRSM). Job Summary The… https://t.co/yneJ3G22Er https://t.co/HzScjo8L7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Integration and Test Engineer: 109247BR Sr Integration and Test Engineer CO – Aurora 109247BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems… https://t.co/DOKA5P7rDY https://t.co/X3nvct8Qfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLBer collapses with brain hemorrhage https://t.co/MhbYeIxzuc https://t.co/lX6ZOJwjhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager/Senior Scrum Master:   Job Description – Program Manager/Senior Scrum Master (00001OG6) Job Description Program Manager/Senior Scrum Master – 00001OG6  Are you looking to make a difference in a patient’s life? At AmerisourceBergen, you… https://t.co/ZH7zGBf9ap https://t.co/IlGTERZRWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faculty Developer/Instructional Designer – SE1324: Valencia College is now hiring Faculty Developer/Instructional Designers. Change lives, starting with your own. There are plenty of places to find employment, but at Valencia College, you’ll find… https://t.co/6V9pQfbjOh https://t.co/TpYaEgEYg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Englewood ETS ERP Account Executive CS: JOB REQUISITION Englewood ETS ERP Account Executive CS LOCATION ENGLEWOOD JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary As an Account Executive, your responsibilities will include: * Business development: Develop and grow your own… https://t.co/hzEphiIQHw https://t.co/P2sbLFjSQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ATM heist caught on camera: Police are investigating the fourth ATM heist in a month at Houston-area courthouses. https://t.co/J272cg6c0q https://t.co/tN5pbAlDJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Planner Consumer Research: Job Overview We are seeking a Project Manager – Consumer Research for our Greenfield, IN site.  Reporting to the Senior Manager, Project Planning, this position is primarily responsible for creating and designing the… https://t.co/fwS49Myz9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids ride to surgery in style at this hospital: An Oklahoma City hospital is using remote-controlled cars when they send kids to surgery. https://t.co/M3ScUf7GAg https://t.co/0UpAfO9xhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Product Specialist, Technical Underwriter: Zurich North America is currently looking for an experienced Cyber Product Specialist for our Technical Underwriting team. This role will provide technical underwriting expertise and guidance to Business… https://t.co/QhkpIhP2Mb https://t.co/7fobPFnkwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security SME / Project Manager: Req ID 92557BR Business Title Cyber Security SME / Project Manager Group MCIS Location USA NEW JERSEY Jersey City Clearance Level Needed None Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Help prepare documentation… https://t.co/NTeNPI2gcA https://t.co/XwJZbMRA2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold Fusion/.NET Developer Job: Date: Apr 13, 2018 Location:Houston, TX, US Company: SAIC Cold Fusion/.NET Developer (Job Number:433986) Description: SAIC has an opening for a .Net Developer to work with our team in Houston, Texas. The individual will… https://t.co/DJnQIKsSps https://t.co/aNJTD4RWFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A surprising victim of the opioid crisis https://t.co/lJwx7Rc4z4 https://t.co/xTiHc2Wo8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Customer Liason – Aberdeen, MD: Req ID : 429298BR Job Code/Title : E5544:Program/Customer Rep Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary &amp; Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest… https://t.co/TWNOEfqNCW https://t.co/cfZY90Ab5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch what husband did after wife's stroke: A man went to a salon and learned to do his wife's hair after she suffered a stroke and was unable to style it herself. https://t.co/29xlenzsTB https://t.co/sieCqxrZ6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: The Business Analyst is a critical role within the organization, and is primarily responsible for successfully collecting complete and accurate business requirements from clients, recommending solutions, and providing the necessary… https://t.co/XjeLdk4aAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer ( Shopify/ Liquid / E-Commerce ): Title: Web Developer ( Shopify/ Liquid / E-Commerce ) Rate: Best Possible Duration: 5 months Work Location: Hoboken, NJ Client Location – Chelmsford, MA Requirements Our client is looking to assemble a… https://t.co/LlWiqxQHqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US sails warships past disputed islands in South China Sea: The United States has sailed two warships past a handful of disputed islands in the South China Sea for the first time, a move that drew the ire of Beijing. https://t.co/PZOiTUDqbZ https://t.co/7o0Na8b3qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Municipal Assistant Project Manager: Discipline Municipal Job Location(s) US-NJ-Mt. Arlington Type Regular Full-Time Use your browser ‘Back’ button to return to job listings Responsibilities * Site Investigation &amp; Due Diligence includes the review of… https://t.co/ypIT5OFkaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani says Mueller team 'giving us the material' to undermine investigation: President Donald Trump's lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, defended the President's political attacks against special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into the Trump campaign,… https://t.co/NJfakcgh1l https://t.co/gIXUofrfYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and how… https://t.co/dQiH8NFhjx https://t.co/PJ3N3R5cTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/MgMvHoj01i https://t.co/mvsc5sszSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and how… https://t.co/GBRn5MDzgS https://t.co/Q8L9cF0H7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/p5XsutPAKQ https://t.co/7zgjXP2QrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/nTjNSmLzMB https://t.co/vFMM42KhPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/iF7B5YRZsN https://t.co/ugh7QXqTy5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>