<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer: Job Title UI Designer Requisition # 7375 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Product Development Education Bachelor’s Degree… https://t.co/1YqNfYQnTv https://t.co/2NOzq9OszA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Controls and Autonomous Systems Manager: Req ID : 433751BR Job Code/Title : L1075:Software Engineering Mgr Job Description : Sikorsky Aircraft, a Lockheed Martin company, is the world leader in the design, manufacture and service of advanced… https://t.co/Vt2D4TnDTt https://t.co/1KXkvPP50j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Manage projects from the receipt of purchase order through completion. Be the point of contact for the customer. Assure our customers expectations are met and our obligations are fulfilled Responsibilities * Clarification of… https://t.co/lGpzthBVTu https://t.co/EP8bDgbWF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversion – EE Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since5/2/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2501 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/YStOF6APqf https://t.co/j7g2hv8nhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Sr. Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies is seeking an Experienced Software Developer to grow our back office cloud development team. The candidate will be working… https://t.co/5lwntVwwWO https://t.co/YBS0KMyVkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Java Architect with Akka Play Framework | Stamford, CT | 6+ months: Title: Java Architect w/ Play Akka Framework Location: Stamford, CT Duration: 6+ Months Years of experience: 10+ years Requirements Java Architect with recent years of experience in… https://t.co/Vv42RBth0r https://t.co/qF7YMjYXpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IA (Intelligent Automation) SW Developer: Senior IA (Intelligent Automation) SW Developer, #15616BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations… https://t.co/pP53M9zFzu https://t.co/uXdt0vUlXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test Platform QA: Job Title Software Engineer in Test – Platform QA Requisition # 8219 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/SL157jZLPU https://t.co/uHCKBUcvNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qlikview Developer: Qlikview Developer Ref No.: 18-27501 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Hi, Hope you are doing great!! I would like to check your availability and interest for this position. Job Overview: POSITION: Qlikview Developer LOCATION: Hartford,… https://t.co/ZU6nJZCuLO https://t.co/dxJK49Vc5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Assoc. Software Engineer Summary: Assists in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and peripheral equipment from prototype to production.… https://t.co/ogkQS6BugU https://t.co/4Q8XIStnge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Tracking Code 5202-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the world that will… https://t.co/v6wzqBOe6J https://t.co/KP6GoDFU4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Financial Operations Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The Financial and Operations Analyst will develop and provide management based reporting and analysis to support daily operations and projects for Prospect Physician Enterprise (PPE), a national… https://t.co/kTC87IWGkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Laboratory Automation: Software Engineer – Laboratory Automation The Software Engineer — Laboratory Automation will develop applications for laboratory automation systems, including user interface development. These applications are… https://t.co/1v3Xs5VObM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Systems Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The IT Clinical Analyst works at resolving production problems and is accountable for the development of basic application/system specifications, systems testing, code changes and the implementation of… https://t.co/QMO7UeSa2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Associate – Java Selenium: Sr. Associate – Java Selenium in Hartford, US-CT, USA | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us –… https://t.co/PVwoLK3HCq https://t.co/hUuqnDPAcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Business Manager (ABM): Req ID : 422495BR Job Code/Title : E4172:Proposal Analyst Job Description : The Associate Business Manager (ABM) leads business office activity for prospective helicopter and associated sales, including the management… https://t.co/X1Z5X0hS96 https://t.co/Td5jzBZeZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Project Manager (Design Group): Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, systems integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other industrial… https://t.co/9916HiDiv5 https://t.co/60fVSDwDcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xamarin Developer: Xamarin Developer Location: Windsor, CT Duration: 6 months contract Experience with Xamarin Experience developing and publishing enterprise mobile applications Familiar with the end to end life cycle process for mobile apps:… https://t.co/usINJUVZhd https://t.co/263Y8IZL2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager – Engineering (Client Service Leader): Job Description – Sr Project Manager – Engineering (Client Service Leader) Job LocationUS-CT-Rocky HillJob ID0318-18047 HNTB Job TitleSr Project Manager – Engineering Position TypeRegular… https://t.co/s9CwJ4EFA3 https://t.co/xGrFPV2Niz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Anlyst Sr: Req ID : 415391BR Job Code/Title : E5433:Business Process Anlyst Sr Job Description : Sikorsky Aircraft, a division of Rotary Mission Systems at Lockheed Martin, is looking for a Business Analyst/System Administrator.… https://t.co/1qoJjbzdr2 https://t.co/HhgtIQH7zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – IT Communication Collaboration: Henkel operates worldwide with leading brands and technologies in three exciting business areas: Laundry &amp; Home Care, Beauty Care and Adhesive Technologies. Our success is built on constant innovation and people… https://t.co/gde8Ak8UNj https://t.co/B5IHpfcUMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Analyst: Direct-hire opportunity available for a Desktop Support Analyst in the North Haven area! We are searching for a Desktop Support Analyst who enjoys being busy and has experience providing a wide range of computer support… https://t.co/lJT7s373yM https://t.co/MoZ77iOI0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Lead, Java:   Job Description – Senior Application Lead, Java (00019908) Job Description  Senior Application Lead, Java – (00019908) Description   Gartner is looking for a Sr Application Lead who will direct a multi-disciplinary… https://t.co/gxoKKgk1Xz https://t.co/ju7pPNxP9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Lead: Senior Test Lead Ref No.: 18-28051 Location: Wilton, Connecticut Experience: – Over 5 years SAP project experience as Test Lead/expert – Proven experience with large SAP programs – At least two IT Expert roles scope SAP ECC mid-size /… https://t.co/FFPThRyiVl https://t.co/hS4J61XkDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Cloud Procurement SME (FT Consulting with 75-100% travel): Oracle Cloud Procurement SME Full Time * We are seeking an Cloud Financial consultant for an implementation project of Procurement module * Modules implemented – PO, Procurement, contracts… https://t.co/3LgFL1U2UA https://t.co/gdcdF2r2O5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET- Software Development Engineer in Test: SDET- Software Development Engineer in Test Ref No.: 18-01455 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 06/25/2018 to 08/06/2020 Role &amp; Responsibilities – Scrum team… https://t.co/NdsLiBeDXV https://t.co/TLAGqyQRDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Business Intelligence Analyst: Job Title Lead Business Intelligence Analyst Requisition # 9026 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category… https://t.co/Np5zRTfxps https://t.co/TCoj4ac9oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Web Development: Hello Professional, Hope you are doing great !! Please respond with your updated resume if you are interested in below job position. SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WEB DEVELOPMENT * NEED ENGINEERING OR SCIENCE DEGREE… https://t.co/9LmIBeK1SL https://t.co/vRj4UCfUHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/11/2018 Functional areaProject Management BackgroundElectronics Referencereq1781 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most… https://t.co/6Wh4Q5zh8j https://t.co/ooJ5EW1JKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager for Aviation Engineering and Planning: Project Manager for Aviation Engineering and Planning Gale is seeking an established Civil Engineer/Project Manager for airport engineering projects. Job Requirements * Professional Engineer (P.E.)… https://t.co/lIIams1jjb https://t.co/sBrCchppqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. PROJECT MANAGER AMBULATORY: Job ID 67594 Department FACILITIES DESIGN CONSTRUCTION Category SERVICE/TRADES – MAIN &amp; FACIL Position Type Full Time Benefits Eligible Scheduled Hours 40 Work Schedule DAYS Work Days MON-FRI Work Hours 0800-1630 Work… https://t.co/aUa3UWFC0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer – Avon, CT: Corporate Overview Hubbell Incorporated was founded in 1888 and has grown into an international manufacturer of quality electrical, lighting and power solutions with more than 75 brands used and recognized… https://t.co/MDhplkKC2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Global experts in shopper behavior, we help brands, retailers and government organisations to make the right decisions. At Kantar Worldpanel, we turn purchase behavior into competitive advantages through continuous monitoring, advanced… https://t.co/zZ5X6jGjHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Assoc. Software Engineer Summary: Assists in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and peripheral equipment from prototype to production.… https://t.co/tW68feanuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION AND RESPONSIBILITIES Interactive Brokers Group is seeking a Web Applications Developer for our Tax and Web Development Groups to participate in all phases of the development cycle for our customer-facing… https://t.co/QvgfgVhJqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/IAkwVd3hCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Integrated Product Team Lead: Req ID : 430273BR Job Code/Title : E1953:Project Engineer Sr Job Description : The TUHP PSI engineering team has an immediate opening for a highly motivated technical lead with 5+ years in the role of developing and… https://t.co/jnSuE6rIpE https://t.co/8aUthedDdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contracts Manager: Req ID : 422775BR Job Code/Title : L4155:Contracts Negotiation Mgr Job Description : Manages the negotiation, administration, extension, termination, and renegotiations of all standard and nonstandard contracts, including major… https://t.co/uqC2f7Aw7h https://t.co/YV77LCueRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 414651BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Turkish Utility Helicopter Software Supplier Management position to oversee software supplier activities. The applicable candidate will reside… https://t.co/bgrVDn02xm https://t.co/23GmOkBaDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotus Notes Developer/BA: Lotus Notes Developer/BA Ref No.:18-01175 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Position Type:FullTime This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers… https://t.co/IB930xqnXg https://t.co/FoDrMPSDc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathology Application Specialist: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and… https://t.co/86EgJsoOUS https://t.co/VfJPz7m8t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Systems Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The IT Clinical Analyst works at resolving production problems and is accountable for the development of basic application/system specifications, systems testing, code changes and the implementation of… https://t.co/tEDtBSnAWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION AND RESPONSIBILITIES Interactive Brokers Group is seeking a Web Applications Developer for our Tax and Web Development Groups to participate in all phases of the development cycle for our customer-facing… https://t.co/6XZkJbh3pK https://t.co/lPQqi37Wik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Administrator (WebLogic Application Server Support ): * POSITION :SR. SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR (WEBLOGIC APPLICATION SERVER SUPPORT ) * LOCATION : REMOTE * DURATION : 6 MONTHS + * * THIS IS REMOTE POSITION * * 10 years of strong industry… https://t.co/FLltb8ByvQ https://t.co/3ZzZ0jFg9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Project Manager: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2/15/2018 Functional area Project Management, System Engineering, Design Engineering Background System Integration, Other- Technical… https://t.co/MlDPTZhFyQ https://t.co/GWp4pxM5Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Director, Application Development, Flexible NA Location, Gartner Research:   Job Description – Research Director, Application Development, Flexible NA Location, Gartner Research (00018667) Job Description  Research Director, Application… https://t.co/sTKHoRDpFa https://t.co/pEw2KQ8pTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety Plainville, CT Office: Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc. (Loureiro) has an immediate opening for a Project Manager/Environmental… https://t.co/TQIyWmFHyj https://t.co/kB1EfrOsy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst Newington, CT: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports the usage of business… https://t.co/bNyPnAkC6x https://t.co/gJZXywWcS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: As part of our team, you will be part of a fast-paced, innovative and collaborative environment, working with closely with subject matter experts and colleagues. You formulate and define solution scope and objectives. You will work with… https://t.co/bsBTpFBQbY https://t.co/xugT0Srptu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation tester/SDET: Automation tester/SDET in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home –… https://t.co/CTyknVy6Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Norwalk: Job Title Software Engineer – Norwalk Requisition # 7558 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Entry Level Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description FactSet is… https://t.co/nif1u8kRDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dot net developer: Dot net developer Ref No.: 18-27536 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Position: ******* Developer Location: HARTFORD, CT Duration: FULL TIME (Permanent Position) JOB DESCRIPTION: Qualifications: Comprehensive understanding and hands-on… https://t.co/Dbg0yMUyDr https://t.co/LvbnARyDj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Norwalk: Job Title Software Engineer – Norwalk Requisition # 7558 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Entry Level Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description FactSet is… https://t.co/NfKsapL7rL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services:   Job Description – Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services (00015163) Job Description  Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services – (00015163) Description   Conduct… https://t.co/qZ8pZzjnv0 https://t.co/OOkrJn99PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost &amp; Productivity Engineer: Req ID : 424188BR Job Code/Title : E2033:Value Engineer Sr Job Description : Provide project management, cost estimating and business analysis for Management, Engineering, Programs, Purchasing and Proposals throughout the… https://t.co/Lh1N2aC6Xe https://t.co/GGPXuNBUyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 1/31/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering Background Optics, Other- Technical Reference req5 Introduction ASML is… https://t.co/480BzTPq0F https://t.co/2u5SLrpDGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Jr.: Functional Area:IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): No Travel Relocation Provided: No American General Life Insurance Company Software Developer Jr. Your future team Our technology teams collaborate with… https://t.co/E8BBmElnhU https://t.co/1DNU0FlX2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-Software Engineer: Hello Professional, Hope youare doing great !! SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER ATHARTFORD, CT * NEED ENGINEERING DEGREE OR AT LEAST 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE. * GC OR CITIZENS ONLY * GREAT COMMUNICATION SKILLS * SHOULD BE ABLE TO LOCATE NEAR… https://t.co/d1fMAxQdRv https://t.co/P2wbmG862V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular JS Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: * Would be responsible for building a web application, delivering a complete front-end application and ensuring high performance across platforms. * Experience in writing tested, idiomatic, and documented… https://t.co/ndOb44WYyX https://t.co/vpD8oHsZ1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test Platform QA: Job Title Software Engineer in Test – Platform QA Requisition # 8219 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/OslVaWS8JK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Financial Operations Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The Financial and Operations Analyst will develop and provide management based reporting and analysis to support daily operations and projects for Prospect Physician Enterprise (PPE), a national… https://t.co/pV9uXMFsEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java with Spring boot Maven: Java, J2EE with Spring boot Maven in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home –… https://t.co/MMYjFgbPnh https://t.co/N7q738MUjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer VueJS: Must Have: * A Masters degree * Functional knowledge or experience with REST Web Services * Functional knowledge or experience withVueJS * Experience Level:3 years * Masters degree or Bachelors degree in Computer Science,… https://t.co/X6evBYKZFm https://t.co/2P9Ny63NTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. GIS Consultant: Sr. GIS Consultant Cyient Location: East Hartford, Connecticut Website: ********************************************************************** Category: GIS Developer , GIS Technician Duties: Perform Software Integration including… https://t.co/b45vb8KQi2 https://t.co/JhFBnVdIQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C#: Job Title Software Engineer – C# Requisition # 7649 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description… https://t.co/0cxaLqG8BJ https://t.co/vtQef7TnHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 5/9/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2880 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop… https://t.co/zyMvUNZxrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Architect Technical Lead: – Systems Architect – Technical Lead Job Locations US-CT-Stamford Req. # 2017-2560Division Global Information Business Solutions Position Type Regular Position Overview Legg Mason is seeking an experienced Senior… https://t.co/MHQQDIvl73 https://t.co/9CAYIIBKRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Data Scientist, Emerging Technology: Lead Data Scientist, Emerging Technology, #16009BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced… https://t.co/P7XCmjghDL https://t.co/OQmZtnMqX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-Software Engineer: Hello Professional, Hope youare doing great !! SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER ATHARTFORD, CT * NEED ENGINEERING DEGREE OR AT LEAST 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE. * GC OR CITIZENS ONLY * GREAT COMMUNICATION SKILLS * SHOULD BE ABLE TO LOCATE NEAR… https://t.co/pLgNHTtVvm https://t.co/TrwPf8znQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Title Project Manager Requisition # 8836 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Temporary/Contract Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Project Management Education… https://t.co/2WXQRPE2WO https://t.co/3FahNz1aQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Norwalk: Job Title Software Engineer – Norwalk Requisition # 7558 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Entry Level Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description FactSet… https://t.co/7lahXMBUTk https://t.co/pjxL5YIKJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Project Analyst/Engineer: Lead Project Analyst/Engineer at LABORATORY CORP OF AMERICA HOLDINGS Skip Navigation Menu – Why LabCorp – Career Areas – Military Professionals – Phlebotomy – Cytogenetics – Join Our Talent Community Improve Health and… https://t.co/C9mAHrUlst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Embedded – Avon, CT: There’s an evolution happening in Avon, CT. iDevices, a preeminent brand in the smart home industry, is building ‘The Silicon Valley in the Farmington Valley’. With a comprehensive product line of both… https://t.co/ZWlWR1JWjL https://t.co/d4LmD1v8lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/cWGvpHAJ5U https://t.co/yLTMm2Waxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claim UAT Lead: Claim UAT Lead, #15846BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk Control Sales… https://t.co/EVgd7p1zy1 https://t.co/GrHT0lY7uY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Engineer/LabVIEW Developer: Country: United States Work Location: Cromwell State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary: The Controls Engineer/LabVIEW Developer will… https://t.co/ye6z3p8vlu https://t.co/rOWIHYnahW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Design – Design Intern: Job Title User Experience Design – Design Intern Requisition # 8875 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Internship Career Level Student (Undergraduate/Graduate) Category Marketing Education… https://t.co/XWr6aleKYY https://t.co/GbU3PVQIlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer In Test: Job Title Software Engineer In Test Requisition # 8985 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description… https://t.co/lOJHGxW2v8 https://t.co/UVYRXVtqW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety Plainville, CT Office: Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc. (Loureiro) has an immediate opening for a Project Manager/Environmental… https://t.co/lgKx6CeQfB https://t.co/H7YTRRpF0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop lithography machines that are key to producing faster, cheaper, more energy-efficient microchips. We design, develop, integrate,… https://t.co/9am6YFcQ6o https://t.co/8Q6oSAtVKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Job Title Senior Network Engineer Requisition # 7531 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/v8YFFYNkPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Project Manager: Agile Project Manager, #15688BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk Control… https://t.co/qxvtmYxwEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Assoc. Software Engineer Summary: Assists in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and peripheral equipment from prototype to production.… https://t.co/FtZ8PGqpVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer C#: Job Title Software Engineer – C# Requisition # 7649 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description… https://t.co/OEcWGduFbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Data Scientist: Job ID: ********-11227-MS Company Name: ISO Description: Verisk Analytics has an amazing story to tell. In 2016, Forbes magazine named Verisk Analytics to its World’s Most Innovative Companies list and to its America’s Best Large… https://t.co/M54impUnaE https://t.co/kTwzco9kQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager- Interiors: Building and Land Technology Building and Land Technology Construction Project Manager- Interiors Stamford, CT 06902 Building and Land Technology (BLT) is a privately held, vertically integrated, mixed use real… https://t.co/WUy2i8Z79E https://t.co/kKxMxQQQiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Electronics Development: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since3/14/2018 Functional areaElectrical Engineering, Design Engineering, Research &amp; Development BackgroundElectronics, Other-… https://t.co/paM9Uj01RM https://t.co/7MOWBpa6GE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversion EE Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since5/2/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2501 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/TyG8wiBQaC https://t.co/L2WcgqKRh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst Newington, CT: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports the usage of business… https://t.co/UymFmPczs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Biology, modeling: Responsibilities: – Apply mathematical modeling principles to current drug development to bring insight to biological mechanism of action investigations for drug development studies. – Develop biological systems models… https://t.co/jF5QwTXy4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Front end: Java Swing. End-user facing trading platform.Back end: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multi-threaded/high throughput. XML.QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/Ph.D. a… https://t.co/u3K8453MYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager IT Communication Collaboration: Henkel operates worldwide with leading brands and technologies in three exciting business areas: Laundry &amp; Home Care, Beauty Care and Adhesive Technologies. Our success is built on constant innovation and people… https://t.co/ivgunag4En https://t.co/v7KDajqO2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 5/9/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2880 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop… https://t.co/BtI48vVHjK https://t.co/iRtOaBH4me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Project Analyst/Engineer: Lead Project Analyst/Engineer at LABORATORY CORP OF AMERICA HOLDINGS Skip Navigation Menu – Why LabCorp – Career Areas – Military Professionals – Phlebotomy – Cytogenetics – Join Our Talent Community Improve Health and… https://t.co/IGst6bfcjr https://t.co/kJRa4tnhs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Title Software Engineer Requisition # 8825 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description FactSet is a… https://t.co/OhAEpmSXjd https://t.co/RT2dTA7XDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Analytics Reporting and APIs: Job Title Senior Software Engineer – Analytics Reporting and APIs Requisition # 8693 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level… https://t.co/uDnh4JFh7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/Smc5i4HdIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trading Platform Software Engineer (C++/Linux): We create and operate securities exchanges to reduce friction in trading. Our core product, IntelligentCross ATS, is a new US equities venue that uses machine learning to minimize market impact the key… https://t.co/VhdNNmBNsC https://t.co/Id7WlZRUjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Ref No.: 18-26582 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Title:: Business Analyst Location :: Hartford, CT Type :: Full time Visa :: USC/GC Job Description: The ideal candidate will have previous experience working as a… https://t.co/iMy3pGLTRB https://t.co/xNkBlWRZQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test Platform QA: Job Title Software Engineer in Test – Platform QA Requisition # 8219 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/c9J8NvY2PN https://t.co/vh3Ua2XOZm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>