<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist / Engineer: Dialexa is expanding its Data Science practice and is looking for great talent to join us building intelligent, next generation platforms. Are you tired of just pushing out ones and zeros and you yearn to solve hard problems?… https://t.co/yZU65FlUYv https://t.co/2GGS6HP2M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior NLP Data Scientist: Are you looking to apply your Senior-Level NLP Data Science skills to a fast-growing startup specializing in the area of automated user interaction? We are looking for someone to join our team and help take us to the next level… https://t.co/1tGxQ64iug https://t.co/2ncSnWeNAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/Python) Job: Software Engineer (C++/Python) (Job Number:434869) Description: SAIC has an exciting opportunity in the growing field of robotics. In this position you will be using and modifying a web based multi robot control unit… https://t.co/cyPBk70PXd https://t.co/nN38wRsvfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/W4KcYit32l https://t.co/Y6D8vxC4kU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/bgWfD77dA0 https://t.co/hfYJFAMMZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Developer Engineer: We are looking for a brilliant mind to join our team, working on solving very real and important problems. You will take a leadership role in our algorithm team to develop machine learning and behavior… https://t.co/Iz49wngLF8 https://t.co/ovrNK2KvsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist ($150-180k) – Python and MATLAB: San Francisco, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today Job Title: Financial Controller Job Location: San Francisco, CA Salary: ($150-180k) Based in San Francisco, CA, we are an exciting medical… https://t.co/Qg4LDXsnuB https://t.co/Pp14btqEQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer, Autonomous Technologies: At Lyft, community is what we are and its what we do. Its what makes us different. To create the best ride for all, we start in our own community by creating an open, inclusive, and diverse organization where… https://t.co/GKoKHF5wB7 https://t.co/AnNuxYcz2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: 605 is looking for experienced devops engineers who can help us build a devops culture, with infrastructure automation owned by the whole engineering team. Our work is in optimizing advertising and programming for the television… https://t.co/jy0IQxzazy https://t.co/bVBdIhmwFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Analyst: Category: Development/Engineering City: Lafayette, Louisiana, United States Position ID: J0118-2154 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals Build a Career that Matters at CGI’s Lafayette Center Position Description: Position… https://t.co/9ogyVln2h4 https://t.co/ihAUwsx70n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator: Job Description Radiance Technologies is an employee-owned company with benefits unmatched by most companies in the Gulf Coast area. Employee ownership, generous 401K and profit sharing, health/dental/ life/vision insurance… https://t.co/BGAex9ozCZ https://t.co/f2biEgceKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA – alexabostonjobs@amazon.com: Job Description DESCRIPTION Java/Python Software Development Engineer – Amazon Alexa – Cambridge, MA.. Candidates with or without Machine Learning experience are invited to… https://t.co/sYT5U78BG4 https://t.co/wqbFQYWgJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/Nu0AID3Unt https://t.co/rLuVU2ObTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python and… https://t.co/qbEtmhnDix https://t.co/KbcMkoILef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Architect: UI Architect We are hiring a UI Architect to make our customers dreams a reality by utilizing the best-in-practice architecture, tools, and design patterns in web development. You will work closely with Reciprocitys global product and… https://t.co/iIuMQAGv5S https://t.co/bD9d6nlTdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ground Software Engineer: Tyvak Nano-Satellite Systems Inc., a Terran Orbital company, is seeking a motivated Ground Software Engineer at our Irvine, CA location. Tyvak is a leading worldwide provider of nanosatellite and microsatellite vehicles,… https://t.co/LvR4PG0OGw https://t.co/XO2q7U4tIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/CwZhB271NC https://t.co/2csCIZlTwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer (C /C++ /Python): Req ID : 403146BR Job Code/Title : E2551:Cyber Intel Analyst Asc Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are impossible? If you… https://t.co/F2dkc3Ie12 https://t.co/uGvxWtudcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/Bwyhsgoz1E https://t.co/AD48jQBelr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator approves SpaceX plan for broadband satellite services: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The top U.S. telecommunications regulator on Thursday gave formal approval to a plan by Elon Musk's SpaceX to build a global broadband network using satellites. https://t.co/5GElpOb5ti https://t.co/mnuvJoolbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – Automation Engineer: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US QA Automation Engineerfor Medical Devices Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/wlpO4TyX0Z https://t.co/8nV6boAou7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/skZZJmaHHo https://t.co/1IMz2XdMPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/RpiG7zhzWn https://t.co/hPdqCjo3wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/FZqhuJedTI https://t.co/HWwKLDMyep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/AEijm9YXum https://t.co/X5XFdJK6n3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/WW1yVMI6U5 https://t.co/QxJeVTFyDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data #SSE228SU: PeopleConnect, Inc. has an opening for a Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data (Ref# SSE228SU). Work Location:  1501 4th Ave. Suite 400, Seattle, WA  98101. Job Duties:  Build large-scale backend systems, develop… https://t.co/TbFHx7Nqs0 https://t.co/D6gsdFhPha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/eBSvGtFvIO https://t.co/axcNCEkYuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/6JPNagZmwG https://t.co/GhEenJ0o6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Developer: SENIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER Los Angeles. Full-time. As soon as possible. inShare ‘" style="border: none; padding: 0px; height: 20px; visibility: visible; width: 67px; background: transparent;" height="20" width="67"&gt; YOUR… https://t.co/VueSfzQAOG https://t.co/fRHlMgMFcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/KseGkhwHSv https://t.co/uNQ7HTHyKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Engineer: For over 20 years, Symphony Corporation has been providing technology solutions and managed services to leading healthcare organizations to help them achieve their operational goals. Symphony has implemented and integrated ERP… https://t.co/nb1zt49Rh0 https://t.co/WEQACfK8yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geofields – Project GIS Analyst: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global… https://t.co/0uFbu45Zu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer: Req ID 96679BR Business Title CNO Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Performs as the technical subject matter expert.Designs new capabilities… https://t.co/FD34J3bFxA https://t.co/enBmoWiQAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quickbase Developer: Role &amp; Responsibilities : * Develop, configure, enhance, and administer a variety of Quickbase applications * Provide end-user support by debugging issues, answering questions about system functionality, and responding to enhancement… https://t.co/abIrdjlxF9 https://t.co/5ui8ZwTGmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/gdFqeWrzSK https://t.co/JTQdKDqBQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/2koIJxJPue https://t.co/V3x1r3Azrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/LKTlOryNCY https://t.co/aiqUtozSpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer: I KNOW NOTHING We are transforming the fashion industry through a radical approach to building brands, an advanced process that integrates all aspect of product creation from raw materials to customer doorstep, and… https://t.co/fDAZqYdVJm https://t.co/y3nW3ywgdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/B7DhepD2Ms https://t.co/zrEG7yMWc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Cyber Security Analyst – Reverse Engineering &amp; Python: What We Do: The CMU/SEI Forensic Operations and Investigations team is a cutting edge analytical resource focusing on critical U.S. Government (USG) needs. For the past 10 years, we have… https://t.co/4CHiP0YIxw https://t.co/ys5xKk8Ybx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares dive again, stung by fatal crash, credit downgrade: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Tesla Inc shares fell sharply again on Wednesday, reeling from a credit downgrade of the electric car maker by Moody's Investors Service, federal probes of a fatal… https://t.co/oiW72svSLA https://t.co/a53Yz7KmBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused – employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team of… https://t.co/B1nZ6DCkxP https://t.co/y3M6tretdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software applications. Master’s in Computer… https://t.co/FWJHyZcv9l https://t.co/WuzKrHFBiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Security Engineer (Cloud Security): As the Sr. Application Security Engineer (Product / Cloud Security) for GAP, Inc., you will work closely with technical peers across all of GapTech. You will ensure that our platforms and technologies… https://t.co/ySltux7Rm0 https://t.co/M0xe2C5byp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/5KEuUEN7gv https://t.co/j2inWlmzqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/MJSCa40O9z https://t.co/iR7X0KIv0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/Django Developer: Zipari is a technology start-up company based in DUMBO, Brooklyn, NY. Our mission is to disrupt the insurance industry by introducing consumer-centric solutions powered by data analytics. We are looking for individuals who want… https://t.co/IB14ajFpSl https://t.co/JN8h2Y8wWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/KY6KDWI0Sj https://t.co/Z6xIJZWJcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/TbR6sPAwK1 https://t.co/57SoQO6E45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Software Engineer: ## This Position is available either in our San Francisco, CA Office or Bellevue, WA Office. Welcome to Planet. We believe in using space to help life on Earth. Planet’s mission is to image the whole world every day and make global… https://t.co/hY9V4I0Oml https://t.co/xFqVoAcdNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: Treeline Interactive is searching for a Web Developer to join our growing Development Team. You will be responsible for developing key features for a web application dealing with location based data.… https://t.co/pi71o0jVX8 https://t.co/tqrR8xWH0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIM Programmer: American Achievement Corporation has a long and successful history, providing products that mark special moments and achievements in peoples lives. From our start in 1913 to today, the company has grown and evolved in many ways but the… https://t.co/0l2Nuhyll0 https://t.co/BckCgeuHFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/Y4cXB07Uyp https://t.co/cxFFJauoOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Oracle Architect: Key Required Skills: Visionary, Able to define and lead to future state. Excellent Communications, Expert level Oracle DBA MUST be US Citizen or green card holder POSITION DESCRIPTION: Looking for a candidate with exception… https://t.co/craUeW9rMP https://t.co/bm4kMD8mwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pega Lead System Architect: Category: Architecture City: Princeton, New Jersey, United States Position ID: J0218-1735 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A company committed to clients Position Description: CGI is seeking candidates… https://t.co/F9cJwnj0YO https://t.co/tVEA7x6wld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: We are looking for a Mid Level Python Developer for a full-time direct-hire role with our client in North Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Operate and develop within enterprise data environment hosted on AWS. Preferred experience/skills:… https://t.co/DLKrczp4Tq https://t.co/ow24G6XssN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/8qZ2ktxIlU https://t.co/4jmzYeoD7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Analyst 4 – Policy Violations: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/BsllYhgWui https://t.co/AyGCH7pUj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users… https://t.co/dkbjF4PnUI https://t.co/r5U0GpGy8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/7DPOra9cnx https://t.co/0TjFHl1Mm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Lead: Sprinklr is 1,500 employees strong, valued at $1.8 billion, and positioned at the forefront of the customer experience management industry. At a time when consumers are connected and empowered like never before, Sprinklr is helping the… https://t.co/xE6a4KFAvP https://t.co/m82Mgr79Od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/F9UaaUddAa https://t.co/ycl4SwPTZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: VIDEO ENGINEER Tremendous opportunity for a passionate Python developer to join a leading organization and take your experience to the next level. You will be joining a high profile team and will be responsible for spending time… https://t.co/MRkPo0YoO2 https://t.co/ufDv2TDkCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber’s use of fewer safety sensors prompts questions after Arizona crash: TEMPE, Ariz./PITTSBURGH (Reuters) - When Uber decided in 2016 to retire its fleet of self-driving Ford Fusion cars in favor of Volvo sport utility vehicles, it also chose to scale… https://t.co/BWgwe6i9yw https://t.co/Lq64RgIebA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer: At Two Bulls we look at the landscape of emerging technology and create innovative products which become tomorrow’s solutions. We are a band of roughly 80 people with offices in Melbourne, New York and Berlin. We ship early and… https://t.co/6mnvCl70d4 https://t.co/kbB6sbWzBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/OmxUaVs8cU https://t.co/EPPaofzvty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python and… https://t.co/uCOqiGtoTX https://t.co/F9JrTm7dRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/UfTkuQHFOW https://t.co/mQlCIdpTMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Python, R, SaaS): Redwood City, CA Full-time $140k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Due to massive growth and demand for our services, we are currently… https://t.co/d9buHpochO https://t.co/I21zLSlCjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/nGFR84vByA https://t.co/DxFrDB01Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/iefxNQF2uv https://t.co/PePwamY29o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinetic Weapons Effects Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Kinetic Weapons Effects Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission… https://t.co/C9se5bUtFl https://t.co/lxssj36MrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/U0vHpBWbg2 https://t.co/u3IywHlWlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer – High Assurance Software Protection: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can… https://t.co/r5dgXW2CKF https://t.co/iOEpnzocII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer downtown Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsPython DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD from IT Serve Phone – Skype 5 month project in downtown Chicago. Please… https://t.co/gPUDHKBKvV https://t.co/1G78hNlYI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x programming Strong Design and Development… https://t.co/aWjKonBqh4 https://t.co/X9YlHKZwR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Arlington, VA and Barranquilla, Colombia. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small startups to large enterprises, and… https://t.co/hnCBBOJt7B https://t.co/s6xYwGKRO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Node API Development: Since 1938, new parents in Finland have been sent home from the hospital with one unique, yet simple gift: A cardboard box. Filled with newborn essentials, the boxes are also designed to be a babys first bed.… https://t.co/p1qmgSV1Eh https://t.co/I3XkzctFK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/EI3QfG3AGo https://t.co/XKjQl2qW7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tools Programmer: Looking to work on a globally known game franchise? Join our exceptional development team as a Senior Tools Programmer on an unannounced AAA title. The job will include writing plugins for common art production tools, adding… https://t.co/uEQOvBROVX https://t.co/1tJYpfOWAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist: Job Description: * Develop advanced algorithms that solve problems of large dimensionality in a computationally efficient and statistically effective manner; * Execute and teach application of statistical and data mining techniques… https://t.co/3QMWejtgxJ https://t.co/5zrd4oZ4vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x programming Strong Design and Development… https://t.co/WpIZwsl9Y0 https://t.co/CsymOw0stZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer – High Assurance Software Protection: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can… https://t.co/fbYawdHjXw https://t.co/NGv2eDINRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer, Optical Test: Responsibilities: Ownership of architecting and implementing test and validation systems (including software, hardware, and database) for DWDM optical transceiver module production, characterization, and development.… https://t.co/MSD1dDXetG https://t.co/hY0R35I9W2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/3nom5xcleW https://t.co/emBs3ctx0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr Python Developer: Following established written procedures, guidelines and techniques, develops, enhances, modifies and/or maintains applications that support business units or support functions in the Global Markets environment. Software developers… https://t.co/hFFLJ33oQZ https://t.co/pPNuCZACie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Hey, we’re Article. We’re a digital-first furniture brand that’s re-engineering the furniture experience one sofa at a time. We don’t have brick and mortar stores, so we’re able to deliver remarkable value on beautiful,… https://t.co/45s6CPJ22u https://t.co/HXcAjo6iWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta still grappling with widespread computer hack: officials: (Reuters) - Atlanta is still struggling with its ability to collect online payments of bills and fees, officials said on Monday, four days after a ransomware attack snarled the computer… https://t.co/TmQyYEdsU8 https://t.co/GtfCBP1ONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/cGTwfPeQve https://t.co/q3X06T3Q8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer: Position Summary: As a member of CERT’s Workforce Development program, the candidate will work with other team members in developing cyber-security training exercises and simulations, primarily for US military/government… https://t.co/0WHDma5VmV https://t.co/duGM57lxZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain Developer – Hyperledger Expertise: At Blockgram, our knowledge and expertise help us ensure that we recruit only the best possible Blockchain and FinTech talent for our clients. We are laser-focused on offering a unique depth of understanding… https://t.co/6akDPktQMB https://t.co/SS68NHOaWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr DevOps Engineer: Qualifications: Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science or related field is required, advanced degree preferred. At least 7-10 years of relevant work experience in a senior technical position responsible for managing… https://t.co/wMJOXKmc0T https://t.co/FQBqCNZx3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer, FireEye: Support the FireEye ecosystem including patching, and administering configs with a FireEye AX, CM, EX, FX, HX, NX environment Test FireEye HX Agent configs prior to upgrades and testing FireEye Appliances and validate… https://t.co/xj5C7WFBPq https://t.co/ZoMn08Guxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/QHk89LxEvt https://t.co/KFVEWEG7XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/NIOPjoffEP https://t.co/gwsQHfEwlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: Understanding of PC Platform and mother board architecture Good understanding of different power states of system and devices (ACPI S-states,… https://t.co/HvD3vbEGXz https://t.co/T5mAxTclJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: What We Do: The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement. The SEI works closely with defense and government… https://t.co/NiDXaAy09h https://t.co/s6arKgSDkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CX – Software Engineer – Full Stack: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered… https://t.co/zP4oVFK8sy https://t.co/fbOnQJNKtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/unKESEtcuK https://t.co/zz38x4tBeS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>