<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect #80259P: IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking applicants for a Security Architect. This position will help define, architect and oversee implementation of security of campus systems including network and endpoint devices. This… https://t.co/oesWYdqRtM https://t.co/PU8ArpLHVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Expert Development: Ariba, Inc. seeks a Project Expert Development at our Palo Alto, CA location responsible for complex and large-scale development projects of high volume or high risk and/or exceptional challenges in project structure. Bach dgr… https://t.co/dvPPNrHUG0 https://t.co/ZerZ0nmCyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst III: We are looking for a business analyst to join our IT -NAST application development team. This role requires a highly motivated person looking for a challenging and rewarding environment that has an entrepreneurial culture that… https://t.co/JmjhyxEj0u https://t.co/5pytLAFOJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer/Engineer: Our Company Informatica Corporation is the worlds number one independent provider of data integration software. Thousands of enterprises worldwide depend on Informatica data integration, data quality, and big data… https://t.co/AV3uYNYvJg https://t.co/zn9TAqCqME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Posting Title Mission-Critical Software Developer for GNC Systems: Job Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 2 months ago(2/26/2018 5:01 PM) Requisition ID 2017-3052 Overview Draper is an independent, nonprofit research and development company… https://t.co/a81q8Z7PiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FIORI Consultant: SAP FIORI Consultant Ref No.: 18-20413 Location: Atlanta, Georgia At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our… https://t.co/Qt4i97SDh8 https://t.co/HlUgfwY1hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer | PowerCenter (design, development, performance tuning, monitoring and support): ETL Developer | PowerCenter (design, development, performance tuning, monitoring and support) Columbus, OH 05-14-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18… https://t.co/kJ4jQvdbeo https://t.co/oUmd43Agtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java SDK: Software Engineer – Java SDK | Joyent – Why Triton – Products – Multi-Cloud Kubernetes – Private Regions – Node.js Support – Compute – Storage – Converged Analytics – Services – Cloud Networking &amp; Security – Load Balancing –… https://t.co/GDoFuMVf3s https://t.co/ScxkZ4pENZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President: Advisory Senior Consultant for Deloitte Transactions and Business Analytics LLP in Costa Mesa, CA to assist clients in solving complex bus. &amp; transaction issues, including analyzing alternatives &amp; recommending solutions. Requires:… https://t.co/TFFlJTc4ct https://t.co/MGqBxaYjGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Management Analyst 2:   Job Description – Business Management Analyst 2 (18009721) Business Management Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18009721 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/YBQhinbQj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Tech Lead: Salesforce Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-20658 Location: Naperville, Illinois Salesforce Tech Lead " – Strong understanding of SFDC sales cloud – Strong experience in SFDC integration with other systems using ETL, SOAP/REST – Be able to… https://t.co/trdfIZtqc0 https://t.co/x005prqnCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System QA Engineer – Media Engineering: Job Description Overview The job of the Senior System QA Engineer includes developing system level test plans, creating and enhancing automated system tests written in Perl/Python, executing automated and… https://t.co/2xNcJRZsvY https://t.co/se1an9CRk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Support Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The selected candidates will demonstrate experience in absence and tardiness control plans with working knowledge of scheduling, resource and capacity management. The candidate will be… https://t.co/KBG4XutrHo https://t.co/ntcw571lAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Engineer: ENGINEERING: Software Development Engineer (LogMeIn USA, Inc. Mountain View, CA) Develop, test, troubleshoot, maintain &amp; debug components for existing &amp; new applications software products throughout software engineering lifecycle.… https://t.co/ZbeiNnv4gm https://t.co/aFMgEVdRBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design &amp; implement Oracle database environments to ensure the highest level of performance &amp; availability. Administer all relevant databases, including Oracle, MS SQL… https://t.co/RZBmuOzvcz https://t.co/e8CyOVNbPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: The Company Founded nearly 20 years ago, our client is a leading provider of online marketing to the healthcare industry. Their goal is to keep professionals and physicians up to date with the latest news in the healthcare industry and… https://t.co/Ge0PMfiqox https://t.co/rkUVWrfLAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/Fl9OT6ae9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Instructor: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Omaha, NE Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/16/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/72qKjvnDt7 https://t.co/LB5QPDlL7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Marketing Tech: About Houzz Join Houzz in revolutionizing the home and remodeling industry and have an impact on over 40 million homeowners and 1.5 million professionals around the world. Frequently ranked as one of the top 10 most… https://t.co/alUlYkYOgH https://t.co/ytjkFvhfEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multi Unit Sales Director: Company: FreshPoint Home Team Location: US-FL-Maitland Zip Code: 32751 Minimum Level of Education: Bachelor’s Degree Minimum Years of Experience: 1 Position Type: Travel Percentage: Up to 50% More information about this job:… https://t.co/eUCmDTVw0E https://t.co/MXrpFZQG2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Software Engineer: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is our global vision and the common… https://t.co/ME7mmrcPZq https://t.co/ZXyL2yBj75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Engineer: The Company Were a tech company thats changing how people bank and think about their finances. We value empathy, curiosity, craft and efficacy. Our mission is to help people feel confident with their money. We do that by bringing… https://t.co/vUNBaELPhs https://t.co/FkIBgEQ5zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Full Stack): The eCommerce team at C.H. Robinson is transforming the logistics industry. Our team is comprised of UX, web, API and data science engineers who are passionate about delivering world class products. We are looking for a… https://t.co/s8LoqBDV5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solution Architect: Senior Solution Architect (71403) Ref No.:18-00084 Location: Rancho Cordova, California Skill Type:Service Delivery NWN is recognized as one of the top 16 Cisco partners in the U.S. and a leader in the IT services industry with… https://t.co/nYgE02uhw4 https://t.co/6HGkb4aOiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer I: Job TitleProgrammer I – ID:31701 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsProgramming LocationSalem, OR Date Posted05/10/2018 Our client, a leading provider of computing, applications management, IT procurement, network, and… https://t.co/bEye2CBa1m https://t.co/0jkwNnKdW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Systems Integration Engineer: This Systems Engineering position supports the F/A-18E/F Super Hornet and EA-18G Growler programs. These programs are fast-paced and cutting-edge with new capabilities planned for development and introduction… https://t.co/4yZ2hiUc6j https://t.co/eoapVbiiRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Architect: Adobe Data Platform team is looking for an exceptional Cloud-first data architect to work with multiple engineering teams across Digital Marketing business units to define, architect and build data platform integration… https://t.co/P2WWQ2uT6Y https://t.co/7Ctv1JRHy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working JavaScript Development Lead: Job Category: Information Technology JavaScript Security Clearance: Secret (or willing to obtain) Clearance Status: Must Be Current Citizenship: Must be a US Citizen IT Partners is seeking a working JavaScript… https://t.co/FmHPqz0IJ2 https://t.co/AHOK1Nc81l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (North Reading): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and… https://t.co/XOAD42wkhB https://t.co/EyNfQRWzTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/eWHF3wC7Ao https://t.co/UUgI4tAvzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Network Analyst: Req ID : 424232BR Job Code/Title : E1193:Sys Integration Analyst Sr Job Description : As a team member in the Enterprise Business Service DV2 organization, this position successfully applies technology to meet service… https://t.co/1dqfUZuBzb https://t.co/Ro5zoCCTRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Electrical Engr: 111897BR Sr Principal Electrical Engr CA – Anaheim Hills, CA – Fullerton, CA – Goleta 111897BR This position requires a U.S. person or the ability to obtain an Export Authorization from the appropriate government agency for… https://t.co/HEn3TjM0Ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer with Angular 2 Exp: Net Developer with Angular 2 Exp Ref No.: 18-20261 Location: Centennial, Colorado Position: .Net Developer with Angular 2 Exp. Location: Centennial, CO 5+ Experience in Dot Net.Required Qualifications 3+ years of… https://t.co/GkORCSNd6j https://t.co/e865ZuBwjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java Developer: java Developer Ref No.: 18-21417 Location: McLean, Virginia Role: Java/J2EE Developer Location:McLean, VA Duration: FTE Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills – 1+ years experience with Java , J2EE technologies – Experience with Spring… https://t.co/Dz2c30YDee https://t.co/32NDlKawDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehousing Engineer: Computer: United BioSource LLC has opportunities in Blue Bell, PA for a Sr Data Warehouse Engineer (Ref #BLUMCH); Software Development Engineer may work in Blue Bell, PA or reside anywhere in the US &amp; work remotely from home,… https://t.co/ZtgfcJcl5O https://t.co/bWfK2sSZTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Providence): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/e7calPsuAi https://t.co/pwRLGCRdZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/vJQk7Vrtgb https://t.co/5IHKdfCHxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Security Engineer – CSI: Principal Security Engineer REQ# 18000036 Position Overview: Cygnacom Solutions is currently looking for motivated and technology-oriented associates to join our security and information technology consulting team at… https://t.co/rOdT4MIgD5 https://t.co/q5yOCItiRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: At Mediavo we are quickly staking our claim as one of the premier digital marketing companies in the world. With offices around the globe we keep our finger on the pulse of the online market 24/7. As masters of innovation and technology,… https://t.co/ffy7PH1RyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Systems) TS/SCI w/Poly: Software Developer (Systems) TS/SCI w/Poly in Herndon, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | –… https://t.co/QPjQpiW2pX https://t.co/MRFRQAPH88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineering Project Manager: New Product Introduction: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 4/11/2018 Functional area Manufacturing, Mechanical Engineering Background Other- Technical Reference… https://t.co/mSfwAia8KO https://t.co/HqJOSP0Hqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Ashby): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/0armMPOGvz https://t.co/5wHNZxkvFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/ Engineer: Job Description Join BAEs Intelligence and Security division and be a part of the team of men and women who solve some of the worlds most complex technical challenges. The Intelligence and Security division is searching for… https://t.co/0q6fcjXsPE https://t.co/9nvM8Kcah3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT Network Software Engineer: Job Details – Benchmark Electronics, Inc. Careers Home/Search for JobsRegisterContact Us [ Log In ] [ Create account ] Job Title IoT Network Software Engineer Job ID(Requisition ID): 3518 Job Summary General duties for this… https://t.co/1W7RH9w4Tp https://t.co/JrTA4KJ2iL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise. Agilent… https://t.co/CIPhZp2Wkv https://t.co/HvHMQG61jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Developer: Big Data Developer Ref No.: 18-20816 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Hello, My name is Anuradha and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc.I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available… https://t.co/uaVYQYaJF0 https://t.co/VrgHBIUtdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analytics Specialist: BNSF Railway seeks multiple Senior Data Analytics Specialist in Fort Worth to use object-oriented &amp; non-object-oriented data-manipulation languages &amp; predictive-analytics tools to provide statistical insights &amp; design,… https://t.co/ULfHV9ixN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mechanical Engineer / Tunnel Ventilation – New York, New York: At Arup, our innovative spirit compels us to express our ingenuity in unique ways — engineering, planning, designing, and consulting on many of the most renowned projects in the built… https://t.co/hijSsuRZrv https://t.co/muO17zLb8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAD Tech-Instrumentation and Controls-Corvallis, OR: CH2M is now Jacobs. Support our water clients across the U.S. and have a hand in transforming tomorrow As the CAD Technician on our Water and Wastewater Program, you will have the chance to work on… https://t.co/SkmUBdWbeA https://t.co/QmZGNOIQW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Publications Coordinator: Req ID : 426127BR Job Code/Title : E5482:Publications Coordinatr Job Description : The Publications Coordinator (PC) trains and works with experienced publishers to support Space Systems Company proposal and program needs for… https://t.co/zdTVapE0HZ https://t.co/YKmSbl9bs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VR QA Tester/Analyst: Responsible for running manual functions and stress testing of VR applications and specified hardware. Run standardized tests provided by client Run ad hoc user scenarios using the applications Install and remove software on phones… https://t.co/ptqI8DRYKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Companion Diagnostics: Date Posted: 17/Apr/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: Project Manager, Companion Diagnostics Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science,… https://t.co/bEYmBqtEE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Developer: IOS Developer Plano, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 04/25/18, Posted Date – 04/25/18 Primary SkillsIOSTax TermsC2COverview POSITION #5 IOS Developer Any Visa from IT Serve Skype to HIre Location Plano, TX Strong in iOS/iOS native… https://t.co/6DHanT1u73 https://t.co/5Wqqj9jzwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Software Engineer: Junior Software Engineer job in Roy, Utah, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp;… https://t.co/fN6pXKSmID https://t.co/ERDUVzH0QE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHMSM Operational Medicine Project Manager: DESCRIPTION: Employer’s Military &amp; Veterans Health Solutions Group is seeking an Operational Medicine Project Manager to work on the DHMSM contract in Vienna, VA. Provide leadership and oversight to design,… https://t.co/Q0r8vWbIhX https://t.co/u2I9eJ0rAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management Analyst Principal Job: Project Management Analyst Principal (Job Number:424024) Description: SAIC has 6 openings for a Senior Project Management Analyst Principals who will: – Facilitate integration across a range of programmatic,… https://t.co/EeWRVscHFk https://t.co/SdEvwfDgov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer II: A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Data Engineer II, Job Code AZJM03: Identify, design, develop, implement, test, document, and operate large-scale, high-volume, high-performance data structures,… https://t.co/x1NaVTizPT https://t.co/02kuJAUFFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much Sex, Violence and Hate Speech Is on Facebook?: Facebook issued its first report on objectionable content, showing the prevalence of graphic violence is rising, as is Facebook’s ability to detect it. https://t.co/hzqJHllVn4 https://t.co/J4TVSuiqkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Bridgewater): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/REZ3NTpxlw https://t.co/QoAyTplBhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II- CORE: Client Reference Code: 216189 JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Engineering team is responsible for the implementation of approved network… https://t.co/pPNQ95nGPP https://t.co/XaRe61qOG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hybris Technical Architect: Job Description Job Purpose: Responsible for translating the client s business requirements into high value services solutions by applying practice offerings knowledge and architectural expertise. Designs and formulates the… https://t.co/UDkU1JqZnm https://t.co/6wKOEcbwPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FMV Instructor/ Developer: FMV Instructor/ Developer job in McLean, Virginia, United States | Intelligence jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp;… https://t.co/tDsOICpUXp https://t.co/yXrrihESA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Mobile Developer: Permanent Full time role Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking an iOS Developer. Candidate Candidate will be responsible for the development, testing, and implementation of innovative customer-facing mobile… https://t.co/R0wB56snKr https://t.co/prrJmuDi0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance/Cyber Security System Engineer: Department:Space &amp; Missile Systems Office:EL Segundo Location:El Segundo, CA START YOUR APPLICATION Millennium Engineering and Integration (MEI) has an immediate need for an Information Assurance (IA)… https://t.co/F6u9ZSqOuW https://t.co/sekg3Tql5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Infrastructure Engineer, Cloud Applications Build Delivery: DevOps Infrastructure Engineer, Cloud Applications Build &amp; Delivery Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers… https://t.co/sAex4s0rRc https://t.co/P6iCH5t1gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: About the Opportunity: The Senior Software Engineer will build tools and applications that support the ReachLocal Media Organization by leveraging a full stack across HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Spring and MySQL. We are looking… https://t.co/pYPSmiIpI2 https://t.co/wRxgiZTQvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Business Manager: Sr Business Manager sought by Zillow, Inc. for Irvine ofc. Monitor sales, churn &amp; MRR performance for assigned sales regions. 30% employer paid travel reqd. Reqs: Master’s, or foreign eq, in Business Admin or rltd +3 yrs of data… https://t.co/g5lua2ZIq7 https://t.co/cAuKBYv3q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Tool Developer: Atlassian, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks: 1) Principal Trust Engineers to collaborate and craft deliverables as part of technology team working to build infrastructure and scale that drives technical direction and implementation… https://t.co/ZLQdNsUVYA https://t.co/H9pn8856M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer – ePharmaSolutions, LLC (Plymouth Meeting, PA): Responsible for the design, development, configuration and implementation of custom software solutions and enhancements to existing systems and new product… https://t.co/pRpSyAUT7N https://t.co/uz2vp35dHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers: Software Engineers (Santa Ana, CA):Identify and document requirements for computer architecture and systems to facilitate automation and streamlined business process. Integrate existing systems and making changes to configuration to… https://t.co/UG5KzZWSQ6 https://t.co/aL9Bw11Xhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Positions: COMPUTER Sr. Systems Administrator (Sacramento): Responsible for managing all service delivery resilience, efficiency, and audit programs as well as ensuring engineering standards and products are integrated across the ESX estate.… https://t.co/4SYLF22F2v https://t.co/gZos2gvuQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/Services Designer (Full Stack): About Healthwise Healthwise is a global provider of health information, decision support tools, behavior change assistance, and personal care planning for the top health plans, care management companies, hospitals, and… https://t.co/uXPVGoEv3u https://t.co/s61Wn5vM4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science/IT Systems Team Lead: GreenZone Solutions, Inc. is currently seeking a Data Science/IT Systems Team Lead to provide guidance and support for both new and existing projects. Responsibilities: * Leveraging a deep understanding of Data Science… https://t.co/X3T5YvZMoB https://t.co/QRyUemtZjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AUTOMATION TEST LEAD: AUTOMATION TEST LEAD Ref No.: 18-18701 Location: PLANO, Texas (1) 12+ years of Automation testing with 5+ years working as Automation Test Lead at client side (2) Prior hands on experience of defining Automation framework… https://t.co/HR3BjcCKSd https://t.co/CBNKegx4Zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electronics Hardware Engineer – Rail Automation: For Siemens Senior Electronics Hardware Engineer – Rail Automation job – Research &amp; Development – Munhall, Pennsylvania Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/WF6GMraS0R https://t.co/ISPHiuUXqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Sharepoint System Administrator: DESCRIPTION: The Civil Health Operation is seeking a Junior Sharepoint System Administrator in Bethesda, MD. Duties: Provides SharePoint farm and infrastructure administration services. Daily monitoring of all… https://t.co/wKSeYJw2KG https://t.co/Nj4jiZ4Rcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Web Developer: OVERVIEW OF THE POSITION: Our client, an independent, employee owned, diversified financial services firm recently partnered with TeamBradley to find an accomplished Salesforce Web Developer. RESPONSIBILITIES: * In a nutshell,… https://t.co/P7L8X87hpO https://t.co/T4InBR0kUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Ozmo is seeking a full-stack software engineer who is smart, curious and loves the challenge of solving problems that improve people’s lives. Our intelligent device support solutions use the latest software stacks and cloud… https://t.co/iwYfQwbbqG https://t.co/2mv5RVwj4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Information Security Architecture: Requisition Title Manager, Information Security Architecture Part Time? No Department Corporate Security City Louisville State KY Description Position Summary: Support all ongoing activities that serve to… https://t.co/fJ3PmurRMO https://t.co/JKbsTg4bo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Intern: The role of the Database Intern is to help develop and maintain Microsoft SQL databases, SQL Server 2000 and SQL Server 2012. Some specific tasks include monitoring and setting up replication jobs between databases located on… https://t.co/bdbyHRVlD4 https://t.co/QiOfMseDr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Applications: TECHNOLOGY Software Engineer, Applications New York, NY, USA Apply Job Description Software Engineer Applications needed in New York, NY and various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S. to design, develop, test,… https://t.co/MWJpToJE7J https://t.co/7N1leGd4Uy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect: Architect Job Summary ​The Architect makes recommendations regarding technology adoption and purchase, develops, analyzes, and specifies quality of service requirements, and determines architectures, techniques, designs, software, and tools… https://t.co/P208YHrROb https://t.co/IsIManwAhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Engineer: About BlueJeans: At BlueJeans, we’re transforming the way people meet by creating a human connection in every experience. Together, we’re bringing video to everyone, regardless of location or device, including mobile, desktop, or room… https://t.co/39lKtMQtkg https://t.co/6bRBOJLtb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sourcing Manager: Huawei is a leading global information and communications technology (ICT) solutions provider. Through our dedication to customer-centric innovation and strong partnerships, we have established end-to-end advantages in telecom… https://t.co/wuzbnZxB8W https://t.co/FB9IwoItO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Enterprise Java Engineer 100% TELECOMMUTE: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $300k Posted Today We currently have offices in San Fran, Santa Monica and Miami but are open to hiring telecommute people if you are a strong match. We need 2 – 3… https://t.co/StncPhWnLO https://t.co/NRWRuYdo1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radar Programs – Deputy Program Manager Engineering: Radar Programs – Deputy Program Manager Engineering Posted Date 10 hours ago(4/19/2018 5:32 PM) ID 2018-31022 Job Location USA-VA-Fairfax Required Clearance Top Secret Category Engineering-Systems… https://t.co/DxNmRyqlyv https://t.co/PhzpHMTgY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Tester: Quality Assurance Tester for healthcare industry web applications. You will work as a full time employee for a software development studio near Princeton, NJ, testing web applications and mobile software. Your role will include creating test… https://t.co/91LFS1SXEc https://t.co/bjffnP1JVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst VI – ACH: Business Systems Analyst VI – ACH Baltimore, MD THE OPPORTUNITY: Facilitates complex technical projects requiring system changes from proposal through post-implementation. Consults with internal application owners to… https://t.co/oIbvbhnD8G https://t.co/urvXBv9HGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cyber Intelligence Analyst: Description:Leidos Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center has an immediate opening for a Senior Cyber Intelligence Analyst in Gaithersburg – MD.   As a Senior Cyber Intelligence Analyst, you will be focused on… https://t.co/jJkwlqG0Uq https://t.co/7tTTCJWTqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Sequencing Research Systems: Other Locations:US- CA- San Diego Description Celgene is a global biopharmaceutical company leading the way in medical innovation to help patients live longer, better lives. Our purpose as a company is to… https://t.co/j1VikKMwzm https://t.co/nsBpEVHlvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certified EPIC HIM Document Imaging Analyst: Are you a Certified EPIC HIM Document Imaging Analyst who is ready to take on new challenges, propel your career and join a prestigious and reputable non profit hospital in beautiful Central Coast of… https://t.co/OBNLRnNEV4 https://t.co/NsdvULr4RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN ED III – CPT, Varied: Pay Scale: $34.34 – $52.53   Shift: Casual Part Time, Varied   Job Summary:   Under the direction of the Emergency Department Clinical Coordinator, the Emergency Department RN III performs duties by applying professional nursing… https://t.co/wuHfSAT9zS https://t.co/IC8AdIpWDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Fayville): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/w4urK9WCjb https://t.co/jamGbuZcA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we… https://t.co/lvtr6zNpeN https://t.co/kZww9Dz34t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[devops engineer: Nutanix, a leader in enterprise cloud, is looking to hire a DevOps Engineer to spearhead the launch of new products in application/infrastructure performance monitoring and security analytics space. The new products incorporate… https://t.co/nvGDPbthAa https://t.co/qcdc0gAKYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Technology Architect – US: Role Senior Principal Technology Architect – US Auto req ID 28698BR Domain Analytics Skillset Grid Computing Platforms , HADOOP Country USA State / Region / Province California Illinois New York Texas Work… https://t.co/073PTmhfZ3 https://t.co/C33C8rLc70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F35 Affordability Operations Management Process Manager – Individual Contributor: Req ID : 431401BR Job Code/Title : E1753:Prj Mgt &amp; Plng Opns Rep Sr Job Description : The candidate selected for this position will report to the F35 Affordability Ops… https://t.co/AwxcKwqH7t https://t.co/V2nVx7kzjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data / Cloud Architect Senior Associate – Consumer Market: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/XzkqQFeFex https://t.co/FbPPiclzPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL DeveloperDSS86528656*Richmond, VA*ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very important. … https://t.co/hGMpC1SAgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Automation Engineer: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/RUpk7rixIE https://t.co/G1A68p6TyJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>