<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/WfGned00v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/QIYA6fXkE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/OKqp5Q1bLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/y36fSnTG0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/5IK4vDgP5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/JDwr95P8to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/zfWNRoob8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/abqLjwKexX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/QIYA6fXkE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/I2O0d08g41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/Q88cLhQWUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/tqoxRNvvEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/hrXuiJIXx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/sNFCFibVYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/Z7uDMMmsaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/LPJMqgysJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/0yiIQknn1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/isipex9s22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/yUdmr6q5ww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/RIoxVh9lM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/r3YTIUl3YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/B72IXJuQAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/qs3RN3Di7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/UZj3HYopyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/Tcxk40ya2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/MVhuW4z2lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/be9Di8Cli5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/YhHNzlqSgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/tVcDf4mfjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/vgD5CKPXBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/Qk3kdleODX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/fQVZWYWFKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/vTQ1g0aIos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/aLeaXQNyv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/V9Tc7zJjX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/abARLtYOCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/KFuMT1fcUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/vO5rt5o9lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/7j7Oftdsu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/1qdY9B5ZhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/Te5e6p7Foo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/29Qr09cotN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/QGRyL9Er63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>