<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai @MeganBatoon Shes just pweerfect!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrity crush on @MeganBatoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yomyomf replied to one of my tweets!! #FanBoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yomyomf: @decaiman67 Like the way you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chachigonzales: "Reminder: nothing ever works out the way you expect it to. Reason: God is a much better poet than you."
~m.k.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai @yomyomf Yeaaaah buuuddy!! Gotta love Internet Icon. #Season1 #Season2 #Represent #Hashtags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having an Internet Icon Season 2 marathon! Gotta catch up on all those videos I missed. @yomyomf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Rocky Point in Coquitlam. This is probably one of my favourite photo sets I have taken. http://t.co/w0Flxx7Kxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Mundy Park in Coquitlam. http://t.co/DKDgERfSOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear and follow @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud https://t.co/XnNTSJ4CG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if im excited to see the new batch of grade nines...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: Let the light shine in you and let Him be glorified #Jesus http://t.co/nDj3ojLeoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my latest song! Shoutout to Shauna for the awesome cover art! https://t.co/xxeiZGIhVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Dark Into Light’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/rP6fxdR36Q #music #suspense #electronic #dubstep #electro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its about time I learn a new song on the piano.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wanna start using Logic Pro! Someone give me a Mac so I can use this DAW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CapitalKingsUSA: Remix our next single "I Feel So Alive" for a chance to win a custom pair of CK Nike shoes! http://t.co/dir4lvKMLT htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @MatthewParker2 for winning Round 1 of @CapitalKingsUSA remix contest!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CapitalKingsUSA: Congrats to @matthewparker2 http://t.co/NSWmiuYWnd on winning Round 1 of our #URemix contest! Show him some love y'all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalKingsUSA What DAW/Music production software do you guys use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalKingsUSA Can you come to Vancouver, Canada?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winner gets announced today! I wonder who it is.... #CapitalKings #Remix #contest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Photos of some flowers in the Rose Garden. Portland, Oregon. http://t.co/nHcFBVHnTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Some pictures I took at Portland, Oregon. Beautiful place! http://t.co/eKIjEM3yTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Dark Into Light http://t.co/Uglrl6bETd on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early morning workout with the guuuuys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the hotel noaaw!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exporting the song right now. While my bro plays le guitar in de background. http://t.co/Q3OeOuYmq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The song is going to be released late 'cause the NEW cover art isn't done yet. Exporting it now in case I upload it while I'm on vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo... THis is my 3000th tweet.... Thats a lot.... Well time to celebrate this milestone... WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My next door neighbor is such a good piano player. All I did was take the garbage out and I end up listening for a few minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should check up on Shauna tomorrow... I need the stuff pre' soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Pacific Rim... By myself... #ForeverAlone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovationHelp Is it possible to use the Novation A Station without a keyboard (but using a piano roll in a DAW instead)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Jesus Christ is the same yesterday and today and forever. -Hebrews 13:8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you listened to my music yet? Releasing a new song this week as well as some new cover art from Shauna! http://t.co/Ac4cx7YJuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a good talk with mah Unicorn Buddy. Missin' ya! Ya better come back soon!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on this new track. Really enjoying on this one. Releasing it sometime this week! http://t.co/ghcB0Q15RF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunna upload a new song sometime this week. Stay tuned 'cause this one is probs one of my favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have a new idea for a song! Gunna revive one of my old beats? Gotta work with Shauna again. Leggo do this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai probably complete. Im broke so yeaaaah. Once I actually know how to skate, then Ill get a custom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Im actually checking out prices for skateboards right now. This is how bad I wanna learn. =P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im guna have the hardest decision when I get enough money. Skateboard or music equipment.This is what happens when i have too many interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to get a skateboard so I can have my skate lesson from @TheManlySamurai already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of sleeping early today... Or should I wait til 3am again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karaoke all night cause were Filipino that way. Singing with duuuh brooos and sistaaas! #2ndFam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I just checked out my overall grades and im surprised that out of all my core subjects, English was the highest #ImNotGoodInEnglishTho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What your favourite DAW? #producers #music #electronic #hiphop #daw #share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your favorite plugin? #producers #music #electronic #HipHop #share #DAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lil' sis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Christiann_Teen: My father... http://t.co/GZUPDujvsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had fun at the park with some friends. It was great to see Josh again. Come visit soon and have a safe flight back bro!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you producers start a track? #producer #electronic #hiphop #music #producertips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many possible ways to produce a song, but its so hard to choose just one. #producerproblems #electronic #hiphop #music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are some ways you transition? #producer #electronic #music #electro #house #trance #ProducerTips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rereading my lil' sis' post just made my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant wait to see Legend Of Darkhorse County. Main reason why I wanna see it is 'cause @chachigonzales is in it. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gideonscx Thanks broo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of doing HipHop beats... I really need to find my own style of music already. I'm everywhere. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristnDubstep: Lord, make me an instrument of your peace. Amen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the things I learn involving music production are self taught.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Havent checked it out yet? http://t.co/zjtTWynQF7 #Remix #Electronic #CapitalKings #AllTheWay #Music #Share #retweet #Producer #help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished stringing one guitar. Now I have one more to do later!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need my new guitar strings..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuhhJohn what's moombahton? I've never heard of that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuhhJohn Im just trying out a variety of styles until I find one I like. But house or trance is something im interested in producing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuhhJohn Im trying to get into electronic but I still have much to learn. Heres song things I have atm https://t.co/G1cyAUyulP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I has a new profile pic! RED &amp; BLACK!! Gotta take a selfie once in a while ;) #selfie #self #pic… http://t.co/XnkbaXt2Q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausting day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View of Coquitlam. #photography #photo #pics #pictures #view #camera #sight #clouds #sunset #coquitlam… http://t.co/jZO83wbG2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I don't have studio monitors yet, I gotta rely on this baby! AKG K77 HEADPHONES!! Loooooove… http://t.co/D6tW6fWBRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MatthewParker2: @decaiman67 Storytime? :D I use Reason. And it doesn't use plugins. The End. ;) No, but I love Reason. It works great i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal before 2014: Write, compose and produce my own song. I really wanna start getting into songwriting &amp; expressing God's love thru lyrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logic Pro is still a DAW that I'm wanting to try out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewParker2 what DAW do you use? And what are your favorite plugins? #share #StoryTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm gunna go back with FL Studio. Sorry Ableton but I just have a hard time working with you. #BreakUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally decided to learn my favorite Tenth Avenue North song on guitar. YOU ARE MORE!! Hopefully I can… http://t.co/kk8t18htLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Christiann_Teen: Sometimes enough is enough and at that point you have to just hand it all over to God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @louiegiglio: If Jesus is not the prize we are running the wrong race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im having writers block... but for music.... I need to do something else...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate those times when I dont know how I should start a song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MatthewParker2: @decaiman67 Do I actually have that much already? :D Sweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One hour of @MatthewParker2 's dubstep! Leggo doo this!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calvary__Tweets: "That moment when you realize that God is enough."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djofficialdj: I'm waiting for the Christian remake "Locked Into Heaven (Forever....Forever....ever....ever....Forever....ever....ever..…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School is in a week and I should be fixing my sleeping schedule, but what am I doing? Staying up of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to use this photo as my profile pic on Facebook once again. Not sure why but I really like… http://t.co/BCEQThxrEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My drivers license finally came in the mail!!! YAAAY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a new profile pic... I think its time to start taking selfies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremiah 29:11 #keep #calm #God #Jesus #Plan #promise #future http://t.co/bi4NTxKlNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RighteousMen: Everybody wants the blessing, but nobody wants the test that precedes it. We pass this test by remaining patient and fait…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Don't make the choice of going back to where you came from. God has bigger plans for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 32GB iPod is almost full. Most of it is full of songs and random jailbreak stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm thinking of restoring my iPod and removing its jailbreak... It's going to be a sad time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that im in grade 11 now still shocks me #TimeFlies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My comment was featured on @shamamrema 's video, Coming Home Ep. 5! #Fanboymoment #shocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wish that @EmazingLights had a store in Vancouver, Canada. I really wanna get a set. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just doing scat solos... No big deal! ;)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>