<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Set your DVRs!  I'll be on CBS Sunday Morning this Sunday @CBSSunday https://t.co/x7mMx60Gbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating (and smart). Investors want companies to release info about culture that they can include in valuations. https://t.co/4pyc8Xx3xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improving work-life balance and creating better opportunities (not paying more) are the best strategies at solving this problem. https://t.co/fnoKwcyIGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies are using retirement benefits to makeup for low raises, but does it drive talent outcomes? https://t.co/Jz9LTD0wcg #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes a baseball team better than the individual abilities of all of the players? Chemistry. https://t.co/0FAwOamNqy #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can AI reduce bias in recruiting and performance mgmt? https://t.co/UOJt5yH3ns #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the law will allow companies to lower wages is anybody willing to take the PR hit to do so? Doubtful.  https://t.co/uUsnQllacG #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done @olark. This is how CEOs should treat employees. https://t.co/jzdGLSpZVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Rule Requiring CEO Pay Ratio Reporting Looks Likely to Hold https://t.co/Cjy1BZScX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A digital employee considers automating their own job and not telling https://t.co/JARMGd49jQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the great conversation @conorknighton @CBSSunday.  Looking forward to the piece on #summerfridays airing on 7/30 https://t.co/VAoUWYMUpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting idea that Gen Z in the workplace will look more like previous generations rather than millennials  https://t.co/eEyIKaoETT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The video games today are better than asteroids and space invaders.... https://t.co/T0fswTEgZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get workplace flexibility make it a right not a request https://t.co/ukrRssRv5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix redefined its corporate culture: What to do if this happens to you https://t.co/UIqsBdLaZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the best roundup on the argument for summer Fridays and the plan to make it work @fastcompany https://t.co/yHH00WoEvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you get early?  My daughter can't wait! @benhatke https://t.co/3NcfvLzRsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flattening of organizations has led to employees putting in less effort at work https://t.co/aYJx0nkmkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broader debates within society have made companies feel compelled to share pay data, regardless of regulations https://t.co/wNx6zi0B4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI hiring algorithms might be just as biased as your hiring managers https://t.co/F2UZ9c5MzO #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...putting in a budget line item to manage culture ... makes accountability for it a 'high stakes' proposition." https://t.co/ttYOzt3cre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing momentum in employment and profitability buoys Aussie workers' confidence https://t.co/BTL9zi63nd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If companies plan to cut bonuses, yet employees are expecting a bigger bonus, the two could be at odds in 2018 https://t.co/isnIdHk5Bz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R E S PE C T: find out what employees need https://t.co/Qhooyq4lyn #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employees expect bonuses to ^ by 1% YoY, but employers are planning on cuts --&gt; disengaged core performers https://t.co/n0rEVuYdgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing: Less Than 9,000 UK Parents Took shared parental leave last year https://t.co/Bv7zxbZsER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Deloitte's decision to eliminate ERGs might not work https://t.co/EhI61hyYMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next frontier in exec recruiting?  Crowdsource it via execthread.  Interesting and different take. https://t.co/SOonwjPGeC #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Older employees value meaningful jobs, just like everbody else https://t.co/SuPklWBegh #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No.  Millennials are experience hoppers -- companies need to offer different experiences to keep them from hopping. https://t.co/R78d3djNnW https://t.co/jge6azZOq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEOs have increased the amount they talk about talent during earnings calls by 20% https://t.co/PDDkxdMI0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting unmeasured but impactful impact of opioid crisis -- fewer workers for companies. https://t.co/crwVu3ntyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-onboarding programs like these make a dramatic difference, well done @IBM https://t.co/h9voojdUhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to kick off!  Exciting conversations and examples of what the future of performance management looks like. https://t.co/Bq7iOr534r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 things we just talked about in london on how HR must change to thrive in a digital world https://t.co/2gFtiGwmVJ #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progressive companies have a corporate culture budget line item https://t.co/bRJ8RbTpBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will companies talk about DACA or take a stand on DACA #HRasPR https://t.co/AgsBnCWof3 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating stories from @iRowan: e.g. startup creating wine without using grapes https://t.co/djyfIVAU5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changing expectations that parental for fathers is becoming a right to have not just a benefit to get https://t.co/TThXjjGmZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illinois Governor Vetoes Ban on Salary, but look to it being overturned @alexiaer  https://t.co/K3qo6b40J4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bumble (via BumbleBizz) creating a networking platform for women as powerful as the dating app they made @bumble_app https://t.co/MzDQh5f8EH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How should CHROs manage during a disaster like Harvey? https://t.co/MxT45LkSiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4% of fathers opt to be stay-at-home, should be higher, but better than the 1% in 1970.  Progress is too slow. https://t.co/3KF9Wda860 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform companies competing against Amazon based on treating their "employees" better #HRasPR https://t.co/24lhz8LGAB #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent benchmarks not aligned against strategy don't mean very much @TalentEcon https://t.co/koYu9L6K7p #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook continues push into the recruiting space with new job listings functionality https://t.co/rvHl7AS4bZ #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employees increasingly making the decision about how companies should respond to current environment https://t.co/MNFAtGLKBz @aimeepicchi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @McDonalds and @benandjerrys supporting their employees and their pursuit of higher education https://t.co/AshZqSTOvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More support that increased vacation (and actually not working) leads to more productive employees in the long run https://t.co/u3iuEljnhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And not but a couple of hours later the CEOs make a decision that they should not stay on the President's Councils https://t.co/LU4pLPRFn1 https://t.co/djKOfc1zq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great insights by @lnichols928 on what CEOs should be doing in response to Charlottesville https://t.co/njzU2L1z1u #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the judges have ruled in favor of hiQ over LinkedIn.  https://t.co/dSPCqm4W3L https://t.co/0i884gEWAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really big deal for all the companies using LinkedIn data https://t.co/7LdbZQ6QH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In managing company culture, HR must go beyond talking the talk: https://t.co/rSjuHH24Li #talentdaily https://t.co/fOaWIXxUBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workplace monitoring technologies are advancing faster than HR ability to turn the information coming out of it into insight.  CHROs must catch up and be willing to experiment in the new world @oliviasolon  https://t.co/HtHfi3i8n2 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know what a 6 year old girl is going to get from Santa this year @ElaineKTurville https://t.co/oxfM1UkzD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point.  Smart companies do. Eg Hire an actuary and train them into a data scientist.  However it takes time to make that happen. https://t.co/TdKE8sbVin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to HR executives, the biggest issue they face is not enough candidates with the right skills, if they can find them they are willing to pay for it @crampell https://t.co/5AB4lMep7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most HR tech capabilities focus on automating existing processes, rather than leveraging tech to re-imagine  HR https://t.co/zqMsvl0ww0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool and valuable new insights on the state of vet hiring https://t.co/FjacSD2AZY well done @ZipRecruiter @Dan4vets @CallofDuty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the great conversation @ebnnews on what HR execs need to think about before making tech buys https://t.co/gZazz9dvWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for coming!  Dates for next year out shortly! @michelleMsmith9 #reimaginehr https://t.co/N9w22DndZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thoughts from @jepassy on whether on latest immigration debate and whether or not it will help/hurt job growth https://t.co/R2mD3h4TQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[employees who work for 52 minutes, take a break for 17 are the most productive https://t.co/WybPTKrMEn @desktimeapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barclays supports diverse job seekers and turns them into customers.  Smart.  @Barclays @talentdaily https://t.co/eT3THWJhD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thank you @NellieBor  for joining last week at #reimagineHR -- great insights shared @elainekturville
https://t.co/I1Fnnq3CXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @NAVSOinc @dan4vets @hireherosusa for helping HR execs better engage vets to help them find jobs #reimagineHR https://t.co/lAjT1A8X9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While important to think about leaders, agile processes more important for leadership dev than HR realizes https://t.co/woLO67eBml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad you enjoyed it.  Can’t wait to see everyone for #reimaginehr 2018! @michelleMsmith9 https://t.co/IyIiwBME3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHROs must determine if they work for the CEO or the Board to ensure good corp governance @talentdaily #ReimagineHR https://t.co/D1G4lvxFcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every co should read this playbook to learn how to hire people with intellectual disabilities @bankfofamerica @SpecialOlympics  #reimaginehr https://t.co/rZoKpUxw0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stories of @SpecialOlympics athletes give inspiration for all of us. True leadership.  #ReimagineHR https://t.co/1pgmcgr1bL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real question is how do you get from this culture to what you need — about building the processes to make it happen @micHR15 https://t.co/3olb4bGzyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are in HR are you helping your CEO tell the culture story or are they doing it on their own? @michellemsmith9 https://t.co/GCm6gxVhs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR executives connecting with veterans to #ReimagineHR https://t.co/gVLdlqOmuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 70% of CEOs are talking about talent on earnings calls.  Is yours? @lyssmyers https://t.co/WgbIlrkP98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Teddy Roosevelt ever #ReimagineHR ?  Yes, yes he did. https://t.co/b8WMgLgSI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NellieBor thank you for sharing great insights on our i&amp;d panel earlier today! #ReimagineHR https://t.co/op0VjY4vhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR can help their CEOs build accountability this way @CaraCapretta #ReimagineHR https://t.co/6rllTkeCKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to budget for your culture just like any other business priority #ReimagineHR https://t.co/lpCevmzQu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready to #ReimagineHR https://t.co/77kNw6jd7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing you in a few days #ReimagineHR https://t.co/99Xtcqa9yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When communicating the ceo-pay ratio you are telling half of your employees they are paid below average https://t.co/BSfiYGSmsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As recruiting technology evolves, the idea of a cover letter will soon feel as quaint as a business card feels now https://t.co/vPeTyzbdE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AI might help find talent faster, but risks bias by replicating what we have rather than finding what is next https://t.co/F2UZ9c5MzO https://t.co/MEloARfEwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showing pay ratios tells half your employees they are paid below average https://t.co/xUuGac4ZYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to go Falls Church! @ElaineKTurville can't wait to get the kids out to play at it. https://t.co/jFWuzTtPyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. #military &amp; #veterans, register for our Veteran
Employment Seminar w/ #ReimagineHR! 19 October from 1:00 – 6:30 PM at @GaylordNational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love living in the matrix?
Pretty much everybody. https://t.co/pRjkh1LszV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR is moving past traditional boundaries to help employees with all the facets of their life, nor just their work https://t.co/CVTY3Gq2Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One result when companies push down wages --&gt;  they also push down effort @ceb_hr https://t.co/eVEKtaqdup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies that conspire to suppress wages end up shooting themselves in the foot by discouraging their employees from doing their best work: https://t.co/eVEKtaqdup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify's new holiday policy is a movable feast: https://t.co/72QsENwq1R #talentdaily https://t.co/ttv0fj9Ddc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you would think it is the manager, but you would be wrong.  nowadays the top reason is career opportunities. https://t.co/NtWWsJbIiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much a company pays is the number one reason someone chooses one job over another https://t.co/UmNIbE3AQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise for @target employees --&gt; better retention and net cost savings @Zlatimeyer https://t.co/lspJCIcg8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[benefit to @target of min wage increase will be improved retention @DPAQreport    https://t.co/ErnxYXTuTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn-hiQ lawsuit could determine future of internet scrapping technology   https://t.co/CvLdueZ43Q #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for having me on @cheddar @lisahopeking @timsteno the closing bell show. More from global talent monitor https://t.co/P0YeLK8OvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to go live on cheddar TV! #CheddarLIVE https://t.co/GaKsWQoWnO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>