<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@_nofi @colossalblue Jesus Christ. This is it. This is the end times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s also the day I realised some fucking rogue app has permission to post to my timeline. Hang on, I’ll be right back. https://t.co/K0ZospvmkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #MyTwitterAnniversary! I have been on Twitter for 11 years (since 29 Aug 2007).
And you? https://t.co/0u9sjPOAil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jemalexander I saw the announcement and I didn't even read it. I went straight to your profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HD image taken by NASA of the three types of aerosols in the atmosphere. Red is black carbon from combustion. Purple is dust. And blue is sea salt spray. (Shit’s on fire, yo) https://t.co/lhX8x5QAD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Omac_brother 33.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No milk for Nathan’s porridge this morning. If he had the number for The Hague he’d be screaming down a phone right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vacation next week so today starts the “head down don’t make eye contact no I don’t want to head out for coffee” focus time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cartychristine I have a foam roller from when I did lots of long runs. I’ve been rolling my hoop and it seems to be helping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This evening we created the characters for our upcoming Midnight campaign. Everyone in the group is a former BioWare designer. Except me. No pressure. #deeplystupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conquered a 10B at climbing today. I appreciate that’s like a scientist announcing they quarked the Hadron today. For context, there’s one jump on the route right out of Die Hard 4.0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jim_hargreaves Jesus. There’s bleak and then there’s British Bleak™️.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 I don’t know what broke me more: the religious chicanery or the odious grammar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianlelas Yeah, I have one of them from my marathon days. Off climbing this morning, too, so that will likely loosen up my arse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Combat_Cow Ah, the direct approach and only a marginal chance of arrest. I like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianlelas “Me glutes are fooked.” Got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfbarry Yeah pretty sure masseuses specifically stay away from the crack. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched Mute. I can see why it polarises people. Tonally schizophrenic, plodding at times, and ludicrous to the extreme. But damn it does look and sound good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed I’ll make sure to point frantically and do the dance of my people. Works a charm when buying goods down the local Bulk Barn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed This is so not hip or lower back. This is ass. This is ass all day long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the etiquette for asking a masseuse to massage your arse? Asking for a broken arsed friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you go for BBQ and you run into your son’s baseball coach eating brisket. We have reached peak New World.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art Ambulatoire just pulled up. They’re trying to save a tinfoil man. Montréal you cray-cray. https://t.co/GuZCikn5Ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It disappoints me how many times I have to convince Apple that bollocks is a real word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wrossmck Shockingly none. This wasn’t a personal goal. The “Eat my way out of a Brie Helmet” one is still painfully intact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed Our floor now. Muwahahhaha. All the oils are ours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colossalblue Wouldn’t happen in Canada. Yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed So wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenmanRooke Let’s just say I got to present to someone you may have heard of. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenuinePanic Surprisingly close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another career related bucket list item checked that I can’t talk about. #vague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonJ_McD Did you eat any knots? Might be it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Braxifen @brianlelas The numbers, Mason, what do they mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I received a really nice compliment yesterday for something I wrote but because it directly relates to the game we’re making I can’t talk about it. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 Double 0 Notions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed You should check her desk. It’s a shrine. And she wants dogs in the office. Like NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed Have you met Jenni’s Wilson?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Debekay Healing up quite well, thanks for asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AlexCalvin @PCGamesInsider Ha! Carry on. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big fan of this batshit timeline we’re in. Fucking amazing. https://t.co/6bB13ZxEtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PCGamesInsider Not sure why these last three tweets were directed at Futurlab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwillfixit Living the dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed Same. Wait. What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 Try not to fall asleep this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 Gowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 They still know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 You couldn’t just point them at the logging system? Now they know you as the guy who logs tickets for them. Congrats, you played yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 Because it’s not out yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 I heard accountants are quite resourceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Braxifen This still blows my mind. https://t.co/F7iVw3ngaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 But why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed @tibermoon @netflix The good to bad ratio of content to actually watch is shockingly out of whack now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 There was a plot in Sharknado 5?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrowadat A Portman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinDYoung My favourite part is when actual licenced properties (like the movies) call her Laura. It’s fucking Lara, McNulty. It’s not fucking hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I am banging on about banjos and I haven’t caught up with my feed. Apologies if I’ve missed something important today. Like Trump supplexed an aide through a table five hours ago or something similar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banjo Speedball 2 is also seriously impressive. https://t.co/uMHOeSXEGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @daveconcannon has finally outdone himself with sending me amazing/weird shit. Knight Rider theme on banjo. https://t.co/j1MsxcsGwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tibermoon Everyone gets a free ability called “Deeply Stupid”. Covers things like sticking your head into a furnace where you’ve just seen eerie green smoke, and locking friends in cursed basements “for shits and giggles”. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An idiot of a man, who couldn’t figure out how to buy a ticket for the metro (it happens) and refused to step aside to let others purchase their own tickets (dick move), then tried to jump the turnstile and promptly fell on his dumb face. Karmalicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A giant bear of a man dressed in leather blew me a kiss at the Pride parade today. Still got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed @myownfairytale We’re downtown. Near the end of the parade. Anyone still about? #FierteMontreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipCostigan But is he a nobody? Or did he just have a poor game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @myownfairytale: Getting ready to go! @EA @UbisoftMTL @WBGamesMTL @EidosMontreal @SquareEnixMtl #OurMotive #NotreMotive
#prideMTL  #fier…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipCostigan Fred is a nobody? Ouch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed Friends are great. Nearly as great as dogs. Nearly. https://t.co/as7uujJi6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliejoypanic The day after is my son’s 6th birthday. He loves dragons. Are you thinking what I’m thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonJ_McD I’m curious what net code they’re using. Which is to say I might have my name in the credits of this one, too ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcporter21 @SenSanders Japan’s population is ~130 million. If your point is it can’t be done on a grand scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Omac_brother popcorn.gif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed I haven’t actually spent much time over there but I have an account. Twitter really has become a dumpster fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Omac_brother The fact that you had that mistake in a tweet about being typo free is scrumptiously delicious. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toby is 2 today. To mark this momentous event he came into my bedroom this morning and howled like a wolf. Just like the prophecy foretold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed I created a Mastodon account. Let’s all leave together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grumpyrocker @StephNunneley Do not become addicted to cha, it will take hold of you and you will resent its absence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogueSNRadvisor “Its” terrible glory. Good thread but that just sticks out like a sore thumb. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveconcannon sends me the weirdest (and greatest) shit. https://t.co/JsyqfEQqxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 The three bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david4482 I am in Canada. That would be a prodigious display of astral projection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s also this amazing “loophole” in Irish insurance law that states boilers are not covered. It’s like they know this really expensive thing is a veritable fucking time-bomb just waiting to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Revenue: “Drunk on power, we overtaxed you in 2017. Here’s €1,500.” Nice!

In other news from Ireland: “The boiler in your house just exploded. That’ll be €3,000 in repairs.” Shit!

The Lord taketh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameDesignDan I feel like you need to move to Canada to cure your insomnia. At least you’ll be tweeting in an appropriate time zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveconcannon Nice try. This is just you in your shed putting on different voices, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tha_rami There can be only one shape. https://t.co/lbfcjCvKtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylancuthbert Some rare art there from “Dan’s Mum”. Might be worth a pretty penny. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliejoypanic I am tripping balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCarus You’re welcome. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On two separate occasions today I found a $2 coin just lying on the ground. Mad Canadian bastards just throwing money around these days. #merci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed You did good. https://t.co/Yz1n4jG6XM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally conquered the outside silo at climbing today. The actual moves were not hard but it’s a super long climb. I was knackered at the top. Great view of downtown Montréal, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonH1981 @JenuinePanic Check the JQL that drives the pie-chart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think Twitter has become a festering shithole of Nazis and cockwombles, do something about it. #blockparty500 https://t.co/fwN3XB6kts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Combat_Cow Too soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinDYoung Oh hai Mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed @MandyJacek The fact that you don’t have proportional representation is BANANAS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed When I say pro-French I answered that I felt it was very important for the government to protect and promote it. :)
https://t.co/W9FFI9lW40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed There were questions like “Do you trust [candidate name]?” for everyone on the ballot I believe. As I don’t know these charlatans I just said “I don’t know” for everyone. That probably skewed the results. :) 

Also, my answers on language were very much pro-French by the way. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autumnbreezed No excuses but I did race through it and messed up a few answers (the form on mobile is difficult to navigate) so this may not by a true indication of my political views. I got the QLP.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>