<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Health Law Means for the Latino Community: 

		Ed note: this was originally posted on the Healthcare.go... http://t.co/vM7D2r1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Makes the Case for the Buffett Rule: 

	President Obama was in Florida today to talk about our... http://t.co/wldn2xnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching Apps for Energy! Developers, Are You Ready?: 
	The Energy Department’s first ever Apps for Energy comp... http://t.co/SojVQ6qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time-Lapse Video: The 2012 White House Easter Egg Roll in 1:48: 
	Yesterday the President and First Lady hosted ... http://t.co/iIwo0ogr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Buffett Rule Asks the Wealthiest to Pay Their Fair Share: 
	Nearly one-quarter of all millionaires (about 55... http://t.co/Dre7HBzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Partnerships to Coordinate Care for Medicare Patients: 
	Ed note: this was originally posted on the Healthca... http://t.co/yTS0PUl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Report – The Buffett Rule: A Basic Principal of Tax Fairness: 
	Warren Buffett pays a lower tax rate... http://t.co/vsr8lJkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official Sources Agree: The Affordable Care Act Reduces the Deficit: 
	Today, we are reading about another brand... http://t.co/fWzPkgl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: The 2012 White House Easter Egg Roll: 

    President Barack Obama cheers on a young child a... http://t.co/Ttv5mFMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets with President Rousseff of Brazil: 

    President Barack Obama and President Dilma R... http://t.co/UDXMyFqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours:  The Buffett Rule: 
	In 2009, 1,470 people who made more than $1 million paid $0 in fe... http://t.co/odEvaaod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the White House Easter Egg Roll: 

    Reed Preston Lindsey, a nine-year-old attending Anderson El... http://t.co/yAVUUWyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Easter and Passover Greetings from President Obama: 
	President Obama offers his warmest greetin... http://t.co/2cY8gY59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Forum on Women and the Economy: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks at the “White Hou... http://t.co/LHTeWIrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: "Some Calm Before the Storm": 

	A quick look at this week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	North Ameri... http://t.co/hExWgjSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting at the Facts: 
	On Tuesday, the President gave a speech in which he contrasted his vision for our econom... http://t.co/gXmJqXWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Wants You to Know How Your Tax Dollars Are Spent: 

	On Wednesday, we released the updated Fed... http://t.co/W8CngsZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in March: 
	There is more work to be done, but today’s employment report provides furth... http://t.co/to72P0RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 4/6/2012 or "The Annual Spring Break Edition!": 

	This week, the President hosted a summit with... http://t.co/o5EqL1p1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The JOBS Act: Encouraging Startups, Supporting Small Businesses: 

    President Barack Obama signs the Jum... http://t.co/OpsiCtBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Two Years of Sorrow, A Reflection and a Promise: 
	Ed note: this post originally appeared on the Departmen... http://t.co/RuvWjqBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Drops By Personal Finance Online Summit: 
	President Obama dropped by a meeting at the White Hou... http://t.co/oPFlUrwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Passover Message from the Obama Family: 
	Starting tomorrow night, the Jewish community in the United States, ... http://t.co/XLGwNubq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch and Engage: White House Forum on Women and the Economy: 
	Today, more than ever before, women are a drivin... http://t.co/iDnivSYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Announces 15,000 Jobs for Military Spouses: 
	Earlier today, I joined with First Lady Michelle Obama,... http://t.co/le28nbaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AskVP: Vice President Biden Answers Your Questions on College Affordability: 
	In his first #AskVP chat on Twit... http://t.co/oiyjImpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $0: 

	In 2009, 1,470 people who made more than $1 million paid $0 in federal income tax. That... http://t.co/q4MUPK0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing in the Potential of the Next Generation: 

    Vice President Joe Biden holds an event on College... http://t.co/6W9HBNId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Millionaires Paid $0 in Taxes? Find Out for Yourself: 
	Today the White House launched the official Fed... http://t.co/VWEVQOem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad Math and the Affordable Care Act: 
	If you’ve followed the public discussion of the Affordable Care Act, you... http://t.co/ZuLd61ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Charts Illustrating Two Different Visions for Our Nation: 
	The President believes this is a make or break... http://t.co/ldWnipCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Combatting the Spread of HIV/AIDS Among Women and Girls: 
	There are approximately 1.2... http://t.co/rAQnqKac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valerie Jarrett Speaks at the National Forum on Youth Violence Prevention: 
	In 2009, a wave of youth violence s... http://t.co/8NO1nA9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Behind the Scenes as Google "Captures" the White House: 

	As part of President and Mrs. Obama's commitment... http://t.co/O5Y6ZZLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosting Economic Growth Throughout North America: 
	President Obama today hosted the leaders of Mexico and Cana... http://t.co/tDKtqPQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing the Summer Jobs+ Code Sprint: 
	Today we’re announcing the first ever White House Code Sprint. This i... http://t.co/16z5I2RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: The 1940 Census: 
	Ed. note: Once each decade, the Census Bureau releases the individual reco... http://t.co/DRwS9nOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MyrnaCare: Peace of Mind and Health Coverage for People with Pre-Existing Conditions: 
	Myrna Rodriguez Previte,... http://t.co/INu3H9LD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Commissions the USS Stratton: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama is escorted to the ... http://t.co/3PWXdeog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Passing the Buffett Rule So That Everyone Pays Their Fair Share: 
	President Obama calls on Cong... http://t.co/K1eQjcSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: “We Need to Keep at It”: 

	A quick look back at the week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	From Dartmou... http://t.co/HA6mUt8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let's Go, Let's Play, Let's Move!": Easter Egg Roll 2012: 
	Ed. note: This was cross-posted from the Let's Move... http://t.co/d4Pr9BDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing the White House Facebook Timeline: 
	We're excited to introduce the White House’s Facebook timeline,... http://t.co/35dGMn9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.2 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/DpNMWfSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gearing Up for the Second Annual National Summit on Preventing Youth Violence: 
	I am excited to announce that n... http://t.co/JjiQRgdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Wounded Warrior Embraces the New Normal: Part Three: 
	Editorial Note: This is the third in a three part part ... http://t.co/Uw01B82S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/30/2012 or "I've Got Seoul": 

	This week, the President traveled to the Republic of Korea to ... http://t.co/3zYjUf5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Vote to Block Student Loan Bill: 
	Today, Senate Republicans blocked legislation that would have pre... http://t.co/nLKy6G8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: A Few Facts about Manufacturing: 

		Ed. Note: This was originally posted on the blog for the U.S. ... http://t.co/LzuOL6fO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting Fraud and Making Medicare Stronger: 
	Fighting Medicare fraud has long been a top priority for Presiden... http://t.co/5gtB4UOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Joins Elected Officials and Student Leaders to Urge #DontDoubleMyRate: 
	This afternoon, Preside... http://t.co/EeAuCa2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait Update: Advancing Innovation in Health Care: 
	Ed note: this post was originally published on the ... http://t.co/Gx6STiz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Joins Elected Officials and Student Leaders to Urge #DontDoubleMyRate: 
	This afternoon, Preside... http://t.co/1vL8XwUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Teacher Appreciation Day: 
	Today is the start of National Teacher Appreciation Week, an oppo... http://t.co/6UIS4fW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 3,000: 
	Ed. note: Today at 3:30 pm EDT, Mary Wakefield, a Registered Nurse and Administrator of... http://t.co/FtGWiWHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: The White House LGBT Conference on Aging: 
	The White House LGBT Conference on Aging will meet today at t... http://t.co/XEIlsar0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: A New Chapter in Afghanistan: 
	After signing an agreement that details our future relationship ... http://t.co/3urCQh4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes the 2012 NCAA Champion Kentucky Wildcats: 

	Today, President Obama welcomed the Univ... http://t.co/WTT4xjvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Driving America Forward: 

	Here's a quick look at what happened this week on WhiteHouse.go... http://t.co/3uLS7scr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Continues Push Against Rate Increases for Student Loans: 

    President Barack Obama deliv... http://t.co/N7R249pV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart Steps on Natural Gas: 
	Since taking office, President Obama has supported an all-out, all-of-the-above st... http://t.co/MMUgzglv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Cecilia Munoz: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to w... http://t.co/u3jBVOde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Lew Speaks to the American Jewish Committee Global Forum: 
	Last night, White House Chief of Staff Jack Lew... http://t.co/ufJm4t5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in April: 

	Today’s employment report provides further evidence that the economy is... http://t.co/Q9L2OMTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 5/4/12 or "Out of Many, We are One.": 

	This week, the President traveled to Afghanistan to sig... http://t.co/MOyOZOGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait Update: Fighting Prescription Drug Shortages: 
	Editor’s Note: As part of the We Can’t Wait initia... http://t.co/kTy5957f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinco de Mayo at the White House: 
	Though Cinco de Mayo isn't officially celebrated until Saturday, today Presi... http://t.co/vWXtkR41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: 'Move Your Body' Flash Workout: 
	How do you get kids all around the country to get moving,  ... http://t.co/rh3y0p3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Jimmy Fallon: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to wo... http://t.co/34pBSEqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 23,000: 

	On Tuesday, President Obama made an unannounced trip to Afghanistan to sign the Str... http://t.co/Moi8cfF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: National Nurses Week: 
	This is National Nurses Week, when we recognize the significan... http://t.co/EvQZ4Zx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building on Efficiency: 
	Two administration-led, industry-driven efforts marked milestones today. The first wil... http://t.co/90K98EGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Secretary of Labor Hilda Solis: 

	Today, on the train up to Philadelphia for the announcement o... http://t.co/jZB6LKZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovative Summer Jobs+ Apps Announced: 
	Innovative Summer Jobs+ Apps Announced

	Four weeks ago we launched th... http://t.co/1L0dmbCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: President Obama Travels to Afghanistan: 
	On Tuesday, President Obama landed in Kabul to sign a s... http://t.co/GL6PdXpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama on Ending the War in Afghanistan: 

	Today, President Obama made a surprise visit to Afghan... http://t.co/YdaOy1pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Pays a Surprise Visit to U.S. Troops in Afghanistan: 
	President Obama made a surprise visit to ... http://t.co/sRnbFJYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: President Obama in Afghanistan at 7:30 PM ET: 
	President Obama is currently in Afghanistan, and tonight,... http://t.co/Tw4KIDGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Google+ Photowalk: Garden Tour: 
	For forty years, the White House has opened its doors and welcomed... http://t.co/JDW1nk5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama: “I am humbled and inspired”: 
	Yesterday, First Lady Michelle Obama and Gen. Martin D... http://t.co/FkFpIQzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reducing Red Tape: Regulatory Reform Goes International: 
	Over the past year, the Federal Government has been w... http://t.co/2d9lJgaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: The Death of Osama bin Laden: 
	On this day last year, President Barack Obama made a historic... http://t.co/fwbw1jmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Report: Health Care Law Makes Community Health Centers Stronger: 
	The President's health care law gives har... http://t.co/aoBS0s8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets with Prime Minister Noda of Japan: 

    President Barack Obama and Prime Minister Yo... http://t.co/61rinqN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Makes an Argument for Rebuilding America: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks at ... http://t.co/KtlnBCQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: John Brennan on the President’s Counterterrorism Strategy: 
	One year after the raid that delivered ... http://t.co/3uRZoESL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: President Obama at the 2012 White House Correspondents’ Dinner: 
	On Saturday night, President Obama and ... http://t.co/ZHyrr8BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Helping our Veterans and Servicemembers Make Informed Decisions about Higher Education: 
	Presid... http://t.co/C8z5fBPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating a Year of Champions of Change – President Obama Meets with 12 Champions Who Are Making a Difference ... http://t.co/LEXP42da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers Matter: 

    2012 National Teacher of the Year Rebecca Mieliwocki, a 7th-grade English teacher at... http://t.co/IXLkOtCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screening "To Kill A Mockingbird" at the White House: 

	Art has helped create the America that we know and lo... http://t.co/kbcuGSei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 3: 

	The G.I. Bill was originally passed after World War II to help returning veterans transi... http://t.co/gPbOC5gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.2 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/xxURabLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Time For Old Political Battles: 
	On July 1, unless Congress acts, interest rates will double for more than 7... http://t.co/zHXA67i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs Executive Order Supporting Service Members, Veterans, Military Spouses, and Their Families... http://t.co/6d2LoIwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance Estimate of GDP for the First Quarter of 2012: 
	Today’s advance estimate indicates that the economy pos... http://t.co/sEVhkGDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 4/27/12 or "'Don't Double My Rate!'": 

	This week, the President hosted the Wounded Warrior Pro... http://t.co/s9iij5aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Marks Take Our Sons and Daughters to Work Day: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama answers question... http://t.co/G3F0uzsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Community Living: 
	For the first six years of his life, Quentin Hammond lived in a nursing home wher... http://t.co/6OFyA87F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Roundup – “You are the Economy”: 
	Yesterday, President Obama traveled to the University of Iowa where ... http://t.co/tqQedhTx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>