<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software https://t.co/vgkMCKZgHH-Web Services-OOP/OOD-Jenkins/Maven-Com. Design Patterns-CIO Org: Software **********************-Web Services-OOP/OOD-Jenkins/Maven-Com. Design Patterns-CIO Org Ref No.:18-08195 Location: Hillsboro, Oregon Position… https://t.co/nu3QqphMWp https://t.co/6DpS4bYL7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-09827 Location: Den Centennial, Colorado Title: Java Developer Location: Den Centennial, CO Responsibilities &amp; Deliverables: – Work with development team members and stakeholders to provide technical solutions… https://t.co/YZn0ZqpxD9 https://t.co/T3srjBHOCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Singaporean online marketplace startups raise fresh funds: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Singapore's Carousell, a classifieds marketplace, said on Monday that it raised $85 million in funds from investors including DBS Group Holdings Ltd, the city-state's… https://t.co/aA8MZydxSL https://t.co/1nIxpHYR7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Lightning Architect: We are looking for Salesforce Architect with Salesforce Lightning experience * 12+ years of overall experience working in Java, and other Java based open source technologies like Apache foundation. * Extensive experience… https://t.co/Fl38XFWMH5 https://t.co/JtGyWSDPtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla executive Schwall leaves for Alphabet's Waymo: WSJ: (Reuters) - Tesla Inc's main technical contact with U.S. safety investigators, Matthew Schwall, has left the electric carmaker for Alphabet Inc's self-driving unit Waymo, the Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/Fs8NTbNSjU https://t.co/bxA2FBPujf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satellite Installer: Digital Reception Services (DRS) is a regional service provider for DISH Network and is looking to hire entry level Satellite TV Technician/Installers throughout Florida. While no satellite experience is required we are looking for… https://t.co/PnDGoomIio https://t.co/h5f7A0tGVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst: Position Description * Creates and delivers presentations on application solutions to diverse audiences (for example, suppliers, technical staff) * Demonstrates up-to-date expertise and applies this to the development,… https://t.co/tGG8HgZShD https://t.co/7osJAlVbqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber SME Senior Principal: Req ID 95839BR Business Title Cyber SME Senior Principal Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Be a part of the solution in solving the most… https://t.co/ILBUFIlyHj https://t.co/oPuzN92CqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPT Advanced Development Engineer, Fuel System Specific Controls: Cummins is a place big enough to coach and develop a global workforce and create the world’s leading clean, engine and power technology. We’re also small enough for you to find your fit… https://t.co/LoUjcB62Ui https://t.co/Pe0eCMdxf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump working with Chinese president to help China's ZTE 'get back into business': WASHINGTON () - U.S. President Donald Trump said on Sunday that he and Chinese President Xi Jinping are working to give Chinese telecom company ZTE Corp "a way to get back… https://t.co/RXdG0de5wa https://t.co/gENAPKHOfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Engineer: About Us: Mercury Protocol is the future of communications, powered by blockchain. We are a well funded, early-stage startup with a world-class team that is backed by Mark Cuban. Based in Los Angeles, we are a passionate team… https://t.co/zg6T4XGjDB https://t.co/VSLxEsKXGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technologist-CT: Job ID: 249878 Technologist-CT Nashville, Tennessee Regular / Weekends Additional Job Information Title: Technologist-CT City, State:  Nashville,TN Location:  St Thomas Midtown Hospital Department:   Computerized Tomography CT Additional… https://t.co/gpGLJrk7Fm https://t.co/ftubTpAFCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire Protection Designer: Ahern, one of the leading mechanical and fire protection contractors in the United States, has an exciting opportunity for a Fire Protection Designer within our St. Louis, Missouri regional office. Building a first class… https://t.co/37e745CkB7 https://t.co/KNFrhSnQjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simulation Analyst, Special Operations Forces Job: Date: Mar 31, 2018 Location:Quantico, VA, US Company: SAIC Simulation Analyst, Special Operations Forces (Job Number:432904) Description: SAIC is seeking a Simulation Analyst to support Training at our… https://t.co/VnE5RB2UGg https://t.co/b3jIPUpBOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Production Specialist: 110433BR Media Production Specialist VA – Herndon 110433BR Job Description: Raytheon is currently searching for a highly-skilled Media Production Specialist to join a talented and creative digital media team in Northern… https://t.co/Qm0NYEKhQs https://t.co/HJ47gTbkX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: JOB SUMMARY Technical Support Engineers at GCS are expected to have and maintain a high level of technical competence over a very large range of products. They will be expected to learn new products and technologies quickly… https://t.co/77hpos1fDY https://t.co/jK0CtFvIO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Engineer: The Role:33Across is seeking an experienced software quality assurance engineer in our New York office, to join our team to help launch new products and test new features for our publisher platform and our consumer products… https://t.co/Szru5owd65 https://t.co/tuhugY7jGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place… https://t.co/9GXh6AsgoA https://t.co/rAyLxoFPYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= AWS Solutions Architect Cloud Computing Stafford, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a AWS Solutions Architect that is passionate about developing and executing… https://t.co/p1pVwUpgqt https://t.co/jkGw0MYhWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AZURE Cloud Architect: Description: The Defense &amp; Intelligence group at Leidos has an opening for an AZURE Cloud Architect. This group is migrating to the Cloud. They are standing up a new Cloud environment and looking for the expertise to migrate and… https://t.co/DHouBpN9wh https://t.co/y8oIo6wT1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Release Train Engineer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   We are seeking a… https://t.co/C17pAtW5bm https://t.co/cwpU8lHRwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Enterprise Technologies: Overview The Manager of Enterprise Architecture (EA) is responsible for managing the overall IT architecture, engineering and data governance by developing and maintaining a holistic, long term view of all enterprise… https://t.co/YGJLpIAqPf https://t.co/zTRpTFWfw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoC Performance Modeling Engineer: Description: Leidos has an excellent opportunity for a System-on-a-Chip (SoC) Performance Modeling Engineer located in our San Diego, CA office.   The successful candidate will participate in an SoC computer processor… https://t.co/ZoX8H5xxZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer: MORE THAN JUST A JOB! THE ENERGY HERE IS CONTAGIOUS! ____________________________________________ Title: Application Developer Report To: VP Information Technology Position Summary: As an Application Developer you will be… https://t.co/mFs3Jz1olV https://t.co/rmsGzKemwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Superintendent: Jacksonville, FL Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent with experience, please read on. What You Will Be Doing Responsible for the day-to-day execution of large commercial / industrial construction… https://t.co/gFdMV7lfyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Operations Manager: Manufacturing Operations Manager Posted Date 2 days ago(4/13/2018 3:05 AM) ID 2018-30905 Job Location USA-MA-Quincy Category Manufacturing Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company Bluefin Basic Qualifications Bachelor's… https://t.co/syYic8kgl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Manager Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/ARrg6pSDSD https://t.co/79excdUPgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity &amp; Privacy – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us… https://t.co/or4nQGKIaR https://t.co/36l49WNIVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory FS- RPA (Robotics)- Digital Tech Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/evqEydVn4u https://t.co/M7hbqnXXlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Digital Technology Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/iC3tEEChcY https://t.co/gU0uHwI8qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Commercial Lending Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/ftOCUXXojF https://t.co/dXJa1mmgqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VMware CFO likely to turn down Uber finance chief job: WSJ: (Reuters) - VMware Inc's Chief Financial Officer Zane Rowe has indicated he will turn down the offer to be become Uber Technologies Inc's [UBER.UL] finance chief, the Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/y8VGgbcFWY https://t.co/c8ySumPdeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/PnFa5PTIPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics AX Functional Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/0Ysyy2ox7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Cyber Privacy Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/aCh9xG0AUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's HSBC joins the fintech fray with multi-account app: LONDON (Reuters) - HSBC's Connected Money app, providing a single platform for users to see their accounts with a range of providers, registered 13,000 downloads within a day of its launch,… https://t.co/GOUH6xU7VV https://t.co/MwFA7D0jbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executive Director, Capture: Req ID 93894BR Business Title Executive Director, Capture Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Programs &amp; Operations Job Duties and Responsibilities  ManTech is currently seeking a… https://t.co/H2zXb0gM41 https://t.co/SHPsowSqJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didi says to halt ride-sharing in China for a week for driver checks: BEIJING (Reuters) - China's biggest ride-sharing company Didi Chuxing said on Friday it would halt its business in China for one week following the death of a passenger that has raised… https://t.co/9otz9s65ml https://t.co/enfkchvf7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Risk Management: job detailsJob Number:1199571Job Title:Manager, IT Risk ManagementJob Type:Full-timeLocation:Hoboken, NJHours:Post Date:Aug 24 2017Salary:$140K-$150KDetailed Job Description: Large financial services firm is looking for a… https://t.co/8wsHNsw87r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GXP Software Engineer: 29616BR GXP Software Engineer Rome New York United States GXP is seeking a motivated candidate to join its software engineering team as a full time software engineer. In this exciting opportunity you'll be responsible for… https://t.co/MMNkQv9KAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (mid career) – Software Defined Radio: Req ID : 402433BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : As a software engineer, Lockheed Martin invites you to create “new realities,” enabling solutions that have never… https://t.co/ASMuKihG9s https://t.co/QI6skeAipT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Manager: Req ID 96862BR Business Title Incident Manager Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Bethesda Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Engineering &amp; Support Services Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is seeking a motivated,… https://t.co/5RymisTjxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Manager: Zipari is a technology start-up company based in DUMBO, Brooklyn, NY. Our mission is to disrupt the insurance industry by introducing consumer-centric solutions powered by data analytics. We are looking for individuals who want to build a… https://t.co/9afqdCzs3Z https://t.co/fwyb0uNIil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Phantom is the leading Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage company… https://t.co/e9K9JBeovw https://t.co/4k8xwpBeW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: ABOUT THE COMPANY RobustWealth… https://t.co/z7N5QIwG7e https://t.co/P3g98GD9EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: As a Software Developer, you will be delivering software releases, which includes development of web applications, Windows thick client applications, Windows services, and Administrator clients for web and windows. This is an on-site… https://t.co/BVXD9bsYaP https://t.co/Y98EJORB8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn announces North American headquarters in Wisconsin: SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Taiwanese electronics manufacturer Foxconn said it would establish its North American corporate headquarters in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, following the purchase of a building in… https://t.co/XNbTZZY2j7 https://t.co/faggZHAI93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer: Panoply is a rapidly growing company with a highly visible brand, bringing millions of listeners the smartest conversations that podcasting has to offer through top tier partnerships with publishers like the Wall Street Journal, Vulture,… https://t.co/Dpww00lnBC https://t.co/GSrLVZABaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spark Software Developer: – Analyzes and determines data integration needs – Evaluates and plans software designs, test results and technical manuals using Big Data (Hadoop) ecosystem – Reviews literature, current practices relevant to the solution of… https://t.co/Qz9eDJBeNF https://t.co/vNBGkQKuKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: – Software Engineer (HID4032) &gt; Software Engineer (HID4032) Full-timeHID Global 2018-06-04Region: North America Long Beach, CA North AmericaUSLong Beach, CA HID Global powers the trusted identities of the world’s people, places and… https://t.co/8N5YtwGl3b https://t.co/EdgyLRZitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lustre/Infiniband Engineer: 30011BR Lustre/Infiniband Engineer Annapolis junction Maryland United States BAE Systems is looking for candidates who have worked extensively with Lustre and Infiniband Networks and who have the ability to create and… https://t.co/F9OfiPDu8J https://t.co/kGykcQ2ypO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer – Billing Platform: Test Engineer – Billing Platform at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA or Mountain View, CA About the Job: This role is focused on raising the bar for software quality on the realtime fire-hose of Twilio's billing… https://t.co/hkVsl0T767 https://t.co/iqNzOgvFfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Engineer: ENGINEERING/TECH Sage Intacct, Inc. is seeking a qualified applicant for the position of Sr. Quality Assurance Engineer to design, develop, validate, and execute software test plans and test cases according to the… https://t.co/WDeRU0pH1o https://t.co/aG49waEECg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple poaches senior self-driving engineer from Waymo: (Reuters) - Apple Inc has hired a senior self-driving car engineer from Alphabet Inc's Waymo unit, Apple said on Friday, a sign that the iPhone maker maintains autonomous vehicle ambitions. https://t.co/dQUYOsK2cQ https://t.co/TMnEPAoWKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: RM &amp; CM Technical Lead Elevate Credit Service, LLC Addison, TX Position requires related degree, experience, and skills. The position will supervise and lead 3 RM &amp; CM Engineers. Requires travel to Fort Worth, TX 1-2 times per month for… https://t.co/bnXOrRWJvJ https://t.co/Q8zwhZimwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sets $50 billion in China tariffs with Beijing ready to strike back: WASHINGTON/BEIJING (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump announced hefty tariffs on $50 billion of Chinese imports on Friday as Beijing threatened to respond in kind, in a move… https://t.co/PQjAPTgE7R https://t.co/91Ch9zKNaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZTE's shares slide on trade war jitters, lost 30 percent of market value this week: HONG KONG (Reuters) - Shares of ZTE Corp plummeted on Friday on renewed worries of a trade war and the Chinese telecommunications giant has now lost 30 percent of its… https://t.co/WVm1aun2jc https://t.co/HSLJAOxgpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Analyst Supporting Audit: Recruiter Visa Location California California United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 23 May 2018 Job role Audit Sector Accounting and public practice Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need… https://t.co/A74Gsuv0sQ https://t.co/mvlzJE0XEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Analyst – JDE Financials: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location US-Chicago-IL, United States Posted By Aegion Corporation Date Posted 36 minutes ago Expires 03 Jul 2018 Qualifications None Sr Systems Analyst – JDE Financials in US-Chicago-IL,… https://t.co/AEOLIMEIta https://t.co/ST132q8qX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T closes $85 billion deal for Time Warner: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - AT&amp;T Inc, the No. 2 wireless carrier, on Thursday closed its $85 billion deal to acquire media company Time Warner Inc after it reached an agreement with U.S. antitrust regulators. https://t.co/GZ7tPR0yRW https://t.co/dh7RiCbGbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's chief of communications, policy to step down: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Thursday that Elliot Schrage, who as head of communications and public policy has led the social network's response to scandals about privacy and… https://t.co/h32LrzbzWn https://t.co/G4zLdchkrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robots Luise, Renate join Airbus A320 production line in Hamburg: HAMBURG (Reuters) - European planemaker Airbus inaugurated a new production line for its best-selling A320 jet with robots Luise and Renate joining human workers as it turns to new… https://t.co/3TF6X5q7Eb https://t.co/p8v7ytyDYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: We are expanding our web development team and looking for someone that has experience in full-life cycle development of web based applications using Node.js, React, Backbone, or Angular. The ideal candidate should be… https://t.co/Z4jUwPWZnf https://t.co/4V00ahbeXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Analyst: We are looking to hire an IT support analyst who is responsible in performing a variety of support activities including but not limited to the remediation of desktop computer issues, the installation of desktop computers, and support… https://t.co/bc7NlN9Z7H https://t.co/t2ySQAzIq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: UNION is a digital-first agency that partners with ambitious and progressively-minded clients to deliver powerful digital brand experiences. Our work whether its a fully-enabled corporate platform, branded connected-device experience,… https://t.co/WjK8YthncB https://t.co/0mIojB9t4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a Mid-level Java Developer to analyze, design, develop, implement, and support code; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/mjdr8rmEDy https://t.co/CdvbOiP3To]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Developer: Job Description What is the opportunity? As part of an expanding development API practice in Raleigh, NC, you will assist to transform and accelerate our software delivery pipelines by building and supporting Java REST and SOAP based APIs… https://t.co/KJr0DghOSH https://t.co/sE5ryD6pjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Microsoft takes aim at Amazon with push for checkout-free retail: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Microsoft Corp is working on technology that would eliminate cashiers and checkout lines from stores, in a nascent challenge to https://t.co/s2foRsMat5… https://t.co/uo44f6zAsy https://t.co/ikl8LOpsfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Android Developer – B2E| Daimler &gt; Karriere &gt; Jobsuche &gt; Stellenausschreibungen Wonach suchen Sie? Android Developer – B2E Mai 2018 Mercedes-Benz Financial Services USA LLC Android Developer – B2E Aufgaben About Us: Mercedes-Benz… https://t.co/HbJ3peSYbb https://t.co/1AKmOaqanC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Analyst: EMPLOYER EXPECT MORE WE DELIVER! This is us – Best-in-Class, industry leader with a rich 126-year history – Largest building materials contributor to some of the Wests biggest construction projects including: Los Angeles… https://t.co/Bxj2o70BMV https://t.co/wK7i8ic9z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: * Business Intelligence Analyst (Requisition#A44URZ) Manage Data &amp; Logistics system that drive &amp; support the operations for Apple in the Americas region. *… https://t.co/6a3PiuVW2Z https://t.co/wAoEgKZGLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook used less for news as youngsters turn to WhatsApp: Reuters Institute: LONDON (Reuters) - The use of social media networks such as Facebook to consume news has started to fall in the United States as many young people turn toward messaging apps… https://t.co/HqJ9yZm5Rw https://t.co/jw8WGh4Goi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Sr. Consultant: Technology Sr. Consultant for SuccessFactors, Inc (South San Francisco, CA) wthn bth Delivery &amp; Operation orgs, dvlp &amp; prvd systms, apps, prdcts, &amp; srvs to optmze, atmte bus processes, imprv wrk effcncy, &amp; prvd exprt spprt in… https://t.co/hYvi78uwOD https://t.co/IBwI2t3s7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Specialist #80236P: Information Technology Services at Iowa State University is seeking qualified applicants for a Data Center Specialist. The Data Center Specialist will be responsible for supporting ISU’s data center infrastructure, and… https://t.co/Dq2ZCgnDpO https://t.co/3FHvpG4i4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks unlikely to process payments with distributed ledgers for now, says Ripple: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Banks are unlikely to use distributed ledgers to process cross-border payments for now because of scalability and privacy issues, according to Ripple,… https://t.co/AQANBJD1vj https://t.co/9oIvhgluzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T slips after Time Warner buyout gets approval: (Reuters) - Shares of AT&amp;T Inc fell 2 percent on Wednesday after a federal judge approved the telecom company's $85 billion buyout of Time Warner Inc, clearing the path for more deals in a rapidly… https://t.co/OQDyC1Dh19 https://t.co/HsvmSy1Q4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VMware Virtualization Electronics Engineer 3:   Job Description – VMware Virtualization Electronics Engineer 3 (18008941) VMware Virtualization Electronics Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18008941 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship… https://t.co/nWnfXZvaWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba unveils $6.3 billion share buyback after completing massive chip deal: TOKYO (Reuters) - Toshiba Corp announced a planned share buyback of around 700 billion yen ($6.33 billion), following up on a pledge to share the windfall from an $18 billion… https://t.co/psoksDEhEe https://t.co/p0wfqXeOuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Front end: Java Swing. End-user facing trading platform.Back end: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multi-threaded/high throughput. XML.QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/Ph.D. a… https://t.co/XpLWy0RqYv https://t.co/FbI5NkdICG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – General: UST an IT Corp., Aliso Viejo (Orange County), CA. has an opening for a Systems Analyst-General (Job No 0001A): Will collect; review, analyze &amp; recommend technology &amp; tools; Use independent judgment &amp; discretion to analyze… https://t.co/mcULR8Bj8e https://t.co/Nl21MtDXM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliveroo steps up Just Eat battle, letting restaurants use own riders: LONDON (Reuters) - Deliveroo will allow restaurants to use their own riders for orders placed through its takeaway food app, in a move which will boost the number of available… https://t.co/cCUiiIRSMa https://t.co/SrgKx7taMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASIC Design Engineer: Technology: Apple Inc. has multiple positions open for the following in Austin, TX: ASIC Design Engineer (Requisition #9TTUZJ) Design &amp; debug system level test automation programs &amp; Hardware for debugging, characterization,… https://t.co/3GxqnzV8El https://t.co/r89WP8BWPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing Director: MANAGING DIRECTOR Managing Director for HealthNOW Medical Center, Inc. d/b/a Root Cause Medical Clinic in Saratoga, CA. Manage financ. ops. re: budget, financ. proced./prgms. &amp; factors affect. rev. /exp. &amp; act to improve effic./profit.… https://t.co/aqghvtV52p https://t.co/ijdH9BuRQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Site Reliability Engineer: ENGINEERING/TECH Sage Intacct, Inc. seeks a qualified candidate for the position of Senior Site Reliability Engineer for our San Jose, California office to design and develop solutions to complex applications problems,… https://t.co/E3bbx06h3j https://t.co/5zkoBLw4z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Daddy founder Parsons buys revamped Arizona center for $133 million: NEW YORK (Reuters) - A real estate concern of Bob Parsons, founder of web hosting company Go Daddy, said on Tuesday it agreed to pay $133 million for a revamped retail center in a… https://t.co/X44ZlVjo6H https://t.co/45ZDd0dPRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: ENGINEER: PLM (Product Lifestyle Management) Research, design, evaluate, install, operate or maintain systems &amp; processes used to ensure mechanical products &amp; equipment meet requirements. MS in Mechanical Eng or equiv. field. 2 yrs exp as PLM… https://t.co/DgHAQSAcYT https://t.co/LsaPvpiquU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer: XCast Labs Inc. needs a Computer Programmer (BS in Computer Science with knowledge in Java).  recblid day4pl2xmnefjv1zqqqnbu3w9x9ir1 https://t.co/2aU1tPnGBj https://t.co/IIdpWCXSwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0518MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies; Manager, Site Reliability (6597.1170) Oversee a team of… https://t.co/ZnNxJXS8DK https://t.co/iaA5vE4Scg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – About Us – Our Benefits – Our Culture – Featured Categories – Administrative and Operations – Technology –… https://t.co/9Jc7Y0Cikc https://t.co/0wuhEY4xB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Manager Job: Date: Mar 22, 2018 Location:Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC Configuration Manager (Job Number:425143) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: – Responsible for administration and management of configuration management processes and… https://t.co/eDU9gpAm9Z https://t.co/1D8wv4oN98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thales and Microsoft partner on cloud system for armed forces: (Reuters) - French defense electronics group Thales is partnering with Microsoft to jointly develop a common defense cloud solution for armed forces, the companies said on Tuesday. https://t.co/i8Why5A1Qs https://t.co/MuJ85igJbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Superintendent- High Rise: Miami, FL Full-time $85k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Construction Superintendent with High Rise experience, please read on! We are one of the nation's top construction management and GC firms that has been… https://t.co/TZFvKqcWwP https://t.co/r2vEGEwvT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineering Manager: 15929BR Systems Engineering Manager General Atomics San Diego California General Atomics (GA), and its affiliated companies, is one of the world’s leading resources for high-technology systems development ranging from the… https://t.co/n251OpdrB4 https://t.co/1Xd2rja5qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst II: Scientific Research Corporation is an advanced information technology engineering company that provides innovative products and services to government and private industry, as well as independent institutions. At the core of our… https://t.co/jLoJHqRd26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Security Engineer: Defend Periscope And The Data Of Our Customers: Customers trust us with their most important data. They use Periscope to query everything from revenue metrics to the personally identifiable information of their users. You will… https://t.co/cRs24eaZ1m https://t.co/qdDqmy4HLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Design Oracle data marts for d/warehouse. Support existing ETL, Informatica, Kettle (PDI) feeds. Use Oracle, SQL, PL-SQL,AWR reports, Elasticsearch (Kibana); Agile, Waterfall, code review, Git, Jira, Jenkins, etc.… https://t.co/qcpfprg5tL https://t.co/iFzWCVuDSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T leads telecom stocks higher ahead of Time Warner ruling: ** S&amp;P 500 telecom sector higher, led by AT&amp;T Inc , a day ahead of court decision on whether or not it can go through with its proposed purchase of Time Warner https://t.co/DPKAmxkjQI https://t.co/0ONP6cegd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Specialist II: Electronics Specialist II Colorado Department of Corrections, Limon. Starts at $4558/month. The mission of the Colorado Department of Corrections is “To protect the citizens of Colorado by holding offenders accountable and… https://t.co/ASwOt5bFm5 https://t.co/EKsO6H8oS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Lead Engineer: QA Lead Engineer (Private National Mortgage Acceptance Company, LLC- Ft. Worth, Texas) Utilize minimum requirements to perform automated software testing of web based and database applications. Will guide and mentor offshore QA analyst… https://t.co/F7wLbQMgTR https://t.co/48cJ0SyioC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Assistant #2769: Morris Area School District #2769 has an opening for a full time, year round, Technology Assistant. Job responsibilities include PC setup, troubleshooting and repair as well as providing technical support to district students… https://t.co/uUrUzYpTt6 https://t.co/HiX70QeVZ3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>