<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you want to read a book about boats, a book that you can read about boats is The Shipping Man, by Matthew McCleery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there are two possible views of the problem of tax inversions: That is, you can blame the tax code, or you can blame the companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the debate will continue where it left off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple entertainment strikes me as a plausible (partial) explanation for the same phenomenon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gives unicorn a powerful immediacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't want to subscribe, but you want the data, so you steal my password when I'm not looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and demand (higher property prices make buying harder). Apple is apparently planning to sell bonds, "possibly at least partly in euros."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hedge fund donors did a decent job of backing winning candidates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet the sprawling U.S. rule and the slim European one get to not that different a place, at least with regard to proprietary trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, boy, he was mad at me. So then he came back, and he said, "Do you happen to work on Fridays?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a Greek Orthodox priest in New Hampshire who runs a $20 million hedge fund called Amvona Fund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there are rules governing their manufacture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From a certain angle, the life cycle of a GE Capital looks like: An obvious question is: Will this catch on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They aren't even "investors." They are "donors."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that this argument doesn't run in reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We will blanket the United States,” Levine says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "It’s welcome news to hedge funds that have trailed the market almost every year since the global financial crisis."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honest, we didn't make these up," says Fortune, but I feel like I made up "quinquagintacorn"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that arrange, underwrite, or distribute leveraged loans are considered originators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is: Nasdaq is a big company with lots of big computers on which it processes stock trades for public companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which, I mean. You can see why "nonono my boss made $276 million; I only made $9.4 million" would not be a super-sympathetic argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like this linkwrap, why not try my Bloomberg View colleague Katie Benner's tech news roundup (most recent here)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Izzy Kaminska mentions the ice bucket challenge. A Voxplanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still elsewhere, a Fannie/Freddie lawsuit will continue, and Mel Watt of the Federal Housing Finance Agency got yelled at by Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would this press release significantly change a "reasonable investor's" view of Tesla?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Dell wasn't thinking about buying EMC until it read in the paper that it was, and then said, hey, why not, let's do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're keeping the headline anyway because "blood wolframite" doesn't have the same ring to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a little late to this, but this article about sales jobs is really interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies don't like paying taxes. So they move to Ireland or Switzerland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trader R was coming to London and his priority was figuring out what to wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For one thing, it sounds ... really client unfriendly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission is having a grand old time busting penny-stock scams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops. Those bonds are Japanese yen exchange bonds, and their prospectus is easily available on Bloomberg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like obviously the client is expecting an un-marked-up price, and so thwarting his expectations seems straightforwardly dishonest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then he told his dad, who told him "don't ever mention this again" and "we never talked," and, of course, traded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lending Club steps into the bank's shoes and really is your lender, in a way that I am not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the IRS wants to change the rules to prevent those hot-dog-stand deals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of this is probably better thought of not as a matter of gaming but as a matter of incentives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess this one has no involvement? Besides Fidelity, this one has lined up BlackRock, T. Rowe Price ... hmm wait a minute JPMorgan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But "I was addicted to money and it was a terrible affliction" is apparently a successful hook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-- but the shareholder thing is reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was apparently wrong of him? Though it is also kind of ... the job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, equity markets go up, and they go down. In the future they will certainly do some of each.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortunately, that claim seems not to be true, though that probably just means that the real number was higher. Vox explains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Investors are fleeing from a business they see as confidence-based, and therefore prone to unravel at speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This is not particularly true of mutual funds.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[has agreed to acknowledge that it never found evidence supporting its accusations of retaliation."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Regulators are seeking information about the trading of specific securities," which is usually how subpoenas work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We talked the other day about how Nasdaq's Linq blockchain can replace Microsoft Excel as a way to keep corporate cap tables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don’t mourn the unicorn," says Gideon Lichfield; "there are more interesting animals in Silicon Valley." Hippogriffs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can read a lot of obituaries for Bill Gross's bond-picking skills; here are Megan McArdle and Gillian Tett, for instance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, conversely, punishes you for being dumb or sleeping on your rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Carol Loomis is great, but that seems like a terrible legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously this is not how mind reading works; he recorded the video and made his guess before you watched it, come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about stock buybacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Facebook buying Oculus? This is why, realistically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That it is impossible to know for certain that you are obeying the law?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being involved in a crime seems like a pretty minimal standard of criminal liability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer databases have existed for a long time; the question is not "could this securities thing be better with a database?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But some of what I write elsewhere is CEOing advice. (Unlike legal advice, which it never is.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moody's put Valeant's credit rating on review for a downgrade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's a guy who promised not to shave his beard until the stock market fell by 10 percent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or, if you don't buy that, how 'bout this one: Will anyone make the default day of rest Sunday rather than Saturday? Or what about Tuesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem for Men's Wearhouse, and the market, is that Men's Wearhouse's tender offer remains mostly fictitious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect that something like what happened to the notion of "hedge funds" is happening to the notion of "activism."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It turns out that Zuckerberg's personal control of Facebook's voting stock is worth billions of dollars to other investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you can either vote for the current board to stay in office, or you can not do that, but you can't vote for anyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you believe that, then this paper understates the cost of bank capital -- perhaps by a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you turn Twitter into Facebook, it won't be Twitter, and Twitter is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish independence.

It will apparently be bad for banks, but good for lawyers, which seems appropriate for the times we're living in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lake does “such a good job, that I’ve become unnecessary to be on all of them, and I can obviously go do other things.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except 14e-3 insider trading! A whole 'nother kettle of fish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though there is the issue of, how do you claw back a bonus if it's already been spent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But probably some of them aren't! Also probably like 90 percent of what you read on the Internet today will be false!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wouldn't, is the answer that is well established by history, though people keep trying to start them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational risk is just made up to reflect a best guess as to how much a bank is likely to, oh, you know, pay in fines, mostly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you like to see pictures of a New Guinea flatworm eating a snail? No, is the answer, trust me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those investors have to do something with that money, if they want to keep calling themselves investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Con: If you grind the banks down to nothing then you don't have banks any more, and didn't you want banks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[presumably don't. Their fees are laid out in an underwriting agreement that Twitter will sign the night they price the deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or maybe "people are coining weird new unicorn words."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope not. But if you do, Kevin Roose has a conspiracy theory, and Clive Horwood has some gossip about the account's author (one of them?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine It is statistically certain to happen to somebody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Incidentally there is some empirical evidence against this proposition.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope he patiently explained to them that their funds were taking a much-needed breather after getting a little too bubbly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it does seem like Williams wants to enforce the merger agreement by, you know, completing the merger?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently he now plans to lower the price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh by the way it's worth noticing (?) that this argument doesn't run in reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting one as a joke is amazing. The fake letter is a pretty glorious piece of work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not strictly "on Wall Street" but you probably drink coffee, and anyway, it's my linkwrap so I'm linking to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whatever you call it. In a larger sense, though, what sort of "success" is it to play rock-paper-scissors against a computer 20 times?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is much harder to follow than actual Twitter. Even worse is this Moment about the Nobel Prize in Physics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In other words, Trump knows a U.S. government default is inevitable."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On top of that there’s the housing allowance – $25,000 a month in Singapore, he stressed – and a car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why is it so important for Twitter that it attract that Macquarie analyst's mother? Why can't she be happy with Facebook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually find it kind of weird that Mercuria agreed a dollar price for the business without negotiating whether Masters comes with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not understand the thing where Ralph Nader has now devoted himself to protecting the rights of shareholders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price system: Sometimes it's good. Third, though, consider Uber's model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was S&amp;P self-evidently worse than Moody's?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>