<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopia and Eritrea will meet in a football friendly next month, another move marking the swift end to their 20-year state of war https://t.co/46SoHuoRvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Margaret Thatcher warned Mugabe that British mercenaries were about to mount a raid in Harare 'imminently' from South Africa. https://t.co/nj5gtPjklY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LesothoJohn: If you are interested in #Lesotho or in Arron Banks's #diamond #mine there (that is closing), you need to watch this Chann…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nthakoana: Arron Banks admits paying £107,000 (under LSL2million) to #Lesotho Minister of Communications and his party BNP but both den…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cautious optimism about the Zimbabwe election but attacks on women candidates worrying https://t.co/FEe4POsRVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salvaging ships in Massawa, 1943 – after the liberation of Eritrea from Italy https://t.co/8s3NNFoHhK https://t.co/rwLnq1zY0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Eritrean Liberation Front captured a train https://t.co/zHXV3yADOd https://t.co/Yq6nC8tG2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Smith_JeffreyT: It’s now less than a week until polls open in #Zimbabwe. The actions taken by the government of Emmerson #Mnangagwa hav…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MARTIN PLAUT: How former enemies Ethiopia and Eritrea are talking after two decades of conflict https://t.co/8V5mg9W4cG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mauritania ignores slavery, but jails those who protest against it https://t.co/ZCLv0FYtLI via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ibiriti https://t.co/inwGNKQSHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UAE together with the USA brokered the reconciliation. Now appear to be working to bed it in. https://t.co/SDnsWPE9mS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest batch of recruits to Eritrea’s national service have been told it will last no longer than 18 months
 https://t.co/ItD5Tfvvy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: Meeting between Crown Prince Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed, President Isaias Afwerki &amp; Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed is taking place i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: President Isaias Afwerki and Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed have been presented with the highest Abu Dhabi honour, "the Zayed Award…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Margaret Thatcher rode to Robert Mugabe’s rescue https://t.co/LVJ32a4Eae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel considers deporting asylum seekers to Eritrea and Sudan - again
https://t.co/uggRCbm3Mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Djibouti border dispute with Eritrea could derail Horn peace moves
https://t.co/kdQCtfCwpj via @dailynation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been told there have already been threats against opposition supporters https://t.co/pmvaajaWBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @helenzille: It is truly frightening to think of how Russia's state-sponsored Troll Farms have run deliberate campaigns to polarise peop…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieFick: Eritrean conscripts told unlimited national service will end: sources https://t.co/CVFISQInxq @ReutersAfrica @AaronMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa narrowly averted a mutiny by soldiers loyal to Jacob Zuma in February https://t.co/LoCcSCggBC https://t.co/cje0vIwFtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @willintune: Ethiopia's PM Abiy Ahmed says there is no option except multiparty democracy with strong institutions that respect human ri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieFick: Another political earthquake in Ethiopia: PM says country has no option but to adopt multi-party democracy. @reutersafrica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another taxi war? https://t.co/9mI9ZDrCJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa’s really Unsung heroes: Steve Biko, Robert Sobukwe, Helen Suzman and Rick Turner https://t.co/3OzvoS61L3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Africa_Conf: Critics calling on #Malawi's President Peter Mutharika to resign after a leaked report by the Anti-Corruption Bureau alleg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary lessons for ANC about Venezuela-style land grab plans https://t.co/NNodmnFzIU https://t.co/x3RXEvnvtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @labour_first: Over 1,000 signatures already today on our petition asking the NEC to reverse its refusal to adopt the whole IHRA definit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incoherent rant against the EU by the Eritrean government.  https://t.co/lcjfj1Ava7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Smith_JeffreyT: That an election is somehow “good enough” in #Zimbabwe or elsewhere in Africa, despite glaring problems, is disrespectf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly Theresa May does not know how the system she is suggesting we introduce on taxes at the UK's borders will work. This is her own system! Bonkers. https://t.co/xoamqWNbsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: Interesting statement on the dire human rights situation in #Eritrea by government spokesperson. Now ‘walk the walk’ to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopia or Eritrea? Border community fears split https://t.co/hyY9NHGCCV https://t.co/Nwg273ycDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrean diaspora watches Ethiopia thaw with hope, mistrust https://t.co/GjgVyUPlSp https://t.co/3W3iad6C7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffreyyork: New poll shows a tightening election race in Zimbabwe. Soldiers have been deployed in villages. Will it be a fair electio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libya rejects EU plan for refugee and migrant centres https://t.co/4SEJqCBKDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Smith_JeffreyT: We've been saying this and raising the alarms for the past year--&gt; "#Cameroon’s military has been accused of burning vi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isaias out of character: Why Eritreans are getting nervous https://t.co/V5lwYgiP8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnshelPfeffer: Viktor Orban and Jeremy Corbyn are the only leaders of major European parties to reject the Jewish community's definitio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fergalkeane47: #DRC so Kabila still won’t say if he plans to stand in elections. The uncertainty ensures he keeps the momentum. Opposit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VOAAfrica: Homeland Security to Decide Legal Protections for 500 Somalis in US https://t.co/j5Ey3a52Uk https://t.co/AOWQSMCYow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If confirmed this is a huge step forward  https://t.co/Kv6wQbCo44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ferialhaffajee: So, unfollow or ignore me if you you disagree with this. I am:
*unapologetically and impermeably non-racial - an adhere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea 'pulls out troops from Ethiopia border' https://t.co/k1QiEcN3qa via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What peace will mean for Eritrea – Africa’s ‘North Korea’ https://t.co/4KLpcdMskL https://t.co/rmb6ar2aiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What peace will mean for Eritrea -- Africa's 'North Korea' https://t.co/M9i7vEes8e via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Eritrea confirms that the number of religious prisoners released yesterday was 30 following 5 on Tuesday 11 women and 24 men. They were from a group that signed their agreement to stop being members of banned churches over 4 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redwan Hussien, formerly Ethiopian ambassador to Ireland, had become Addis Ababa’s representative in Asmara. Says report  https://t.co/Xpgcv6c1iV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note: this is a report from media - it has not yet been confirmed. https://t.co/6dHHwZVTOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea still holds hundreds of Prisoners incarcerated for their Religious Faith  https://t.co/QZ4ODkmmdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndianExpress: Djibouti is asking UN to help peacefully resolve a border dispute with Eritrea.

https://t.co/WxFtHYt0ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: Unilever - where is your #humanrights leadership? The company's tea pickers killed or subjected to gang-rape in #Kenya deserve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: Release of prisoners from Adi Abeito in #Eritrea is surely welcomed - these are likely people who had escaped National…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: Release Eritrea has confirmed that this morning around 30 prisoners who were imprisoned for their Christian faith have been rel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BDliveSA: Taiwantese ship detained in Cape Town under new UN labour rules
https://t.co/fgfKSVDlN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @meronina: This is the kind of gesture I want to hear, Radio Erena reports  400  religious prisoners released. #Eritrea https://t.co/XZY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea: Radio Erena's breaking news: 400 prisoners from May Sirwa prison released today.  All are said to be Christian evangelicals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea-Ethiopia Peace Deal Offers Hope for Reform – Human Rights Watch https://t.co/o0mSz1PHki https://t.co/rELfRQfmug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/j7sE9BzGdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: #UNHCR ought to keep in mind the failed negotiations over repatriation of some 300,000 Eritrean refugees from East Suda…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natberh: There is no directive from #Eritrea|n Government or Embassy in #Ethiopia that says refugees must sign 'regret' form &amp; go home.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to watch President Obama give the Mandela lecture live? Watch here
https://t.co/ypXium8pWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What now for 200,000 Eritrean refugees in Ethiopia? https://t.co/2n57maBAmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words - if the Lib Dems had been in Parliament and voted then Mrs May and the Tory government would have been defeated. https://t.co/GRSl2ffAGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adrianblomfield: The Rwandan Movement for Democratic Change, formed in Brussels last year, and co-led by Paul Rusesabagina, who shelter…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want lasting Eritrean – Ethiopia peace? Find ways of resolving local disputes now! https://t.co/mF3ALrM1fT https://t.co/OstJvq85lj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Radio Erena, Eritrean refugees in Ethiopia are being told to sign the regret form at the new Eritrean embassy and to go back home.  What is UNHCR doing? This is refoulment and against international law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK finds ‘no improvement’ in Eritrean human rights – accuses regime of ‘modern slavery’ https://t.co/p7QHRIOzj5 https://t.co/hCHbCTJLX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frozen in time: Inside Eritrea's embassy - BBC News https://t.co/lYHNDFjrRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: Mining giant ERG (formerly ENRC) ignored a UK govt report on rights abuses at its mines in #DRC and now it ignores a request f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZEugc4O6M7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AFPAfrica: Hundreds of Nigerian troops missing after Boko Haram attack on base https://t.co/ljpDMj6173 https://t.co/2Y25EINNbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: The million dollar question: will the #Eritrea - #Ethiopia peace rapproachment lead to demobilisation, liberalisation,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrantTucker: Literally no one said this. https://t.co/MlYlXlrEhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/u7oKV2XP3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrean leader arrives in Ethiopia for first time in two decades as uncertain peace deal advances
https://t.co/Wh08NE4es8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regrets, recipes for herbal tea and dreams of Winnie dancing ... Mandela’s letters from Robben Island  https://t.co/ogWvFZ8qAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkTJones500: Has anyone seen HE Rowan James Laxton the British High Commisioner to Cameroon? He appears to have gone missing. Whilst…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeahHardingAJE: Not fake news. @amnesty says the video of two women and two children being executed in #Cameroon is real, and that the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAfrica: The story of Ghanaian warrior queen Yaa Asantewaa and the fight for the Golden Stool - the first in our 8-part series about…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Errr...No Mr Trump...it’s called Scotland. Still part of the U.K. https://t.co/pIjzYlpiD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lair, lair your pants are on fire...
President Trump says US/UK trade could QUADRUPLE
https://t.co/d69Yy0HkXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let peace by accompanied by freedom and democracy https://t.co/7b9YGVXoAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea: Peace with Ethiopia must be catalyst for human rights change https://t.co/kUK3KY0lTf https://t.co/w33YtJlWEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tewerwari_1: !! #AddisAbaba, #Ethiopia,...are getting ready to warmly receive #Eritrea|n president Isaias Afeworki.

!! It is easy to n…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdriaanBasson: “For the first time in 97 years there will be a South African in a Wimbledon final.” Goosebumps. We have a new hero and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Like a dream’: Families separated for decades by Ethiopia-Eritrea conflict celebrate peace deal https://t.co/Ra7IHNfYSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa’s Anderson in Wimbledon final! Amazing match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HurstPublishers: As Eritrea and Ethiopia reach a peace accord after years of conflict, @martinplaut, author of ‘Understanding Eritrea’,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the BBC Lost the Plot on Brexit https://t.co/zLbl2dbymw https://t.co/y8pBqljYMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: #Eritrea: As announced in his keynote address in Sawa,  President Isaias Afwerki will lead a delegation and pay official visit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another African dinosaur hangs grimly onto power https://t.co/1S7MjYG2Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrean President Isaias Afwerki to Addis Saturday Morning https://t.co/xKJ9zQLyKy https://t.co/Uzn3UHKOeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrean military service no grounds for asylum, rules Swiss court https://t.co/WuXhWCq4vS https://t.co/1fnMRCUYTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nmj323: https://t.co/nv1mmAJXpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natberh: Breaking News :- Though #Ethiopia|n government declines to confirm, it's very likely that #Eritrea|n president Isayas Afeworki…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea-Ethiopia: what’s on the cards now?  Note: this has been updated.  https://t.co/gf3H2HTBEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the month since Italy prevented Mediterranean rescue ships run by SOS MEDITERRANEE and Médecins Sans Frontières from operating, over 600 men, women and children have drowned - MSF. "EU decisions have had deadly consequences" - Karline Kleijer, MSF head of emergencies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ethiopia-Eritrea peace deal: what’s on the cards? https://t.co/gf3H2HC0Nm https://t.co/wDpzV0m8Mm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>