<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Every grandfather in Jerusalem is giving birth to camels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a cobra in Bethlehem that is 35 times more lonely than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ambassador blinks his eye. In that time, he lives a whole other life as an undertaker from Wichita.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An arrogant exotic dancer has a sixth sense: She can understand the language of panda bears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor of English literature is writing a list of people she plans to kill: A girl, a philosopher and a movie producer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gold mine in Australia is made of artistic integrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A schoolmaster plays a game of marbles with a golden five-star hotel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At dusk every kaleidoscope in the world is replaced by cathedrals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scholar finds a 14th century book containing instructions for building a tower out of potatoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The body of a psychiatrist is found in a city. Next to it is a placenta and a broken harp. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 99-year-old president falls into a swimming pool filled with Microsoft Word. She drowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a hurricane in Constantinople. It is made of bed bugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your father tells you that you are made of mother-of-pearl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prime minister passes a law against dieting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An HR manager finds out that Donald Duck is controlling her destiny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Texan vice president introduces a law that everyone must be mauve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A secret society of monks plan to create a world where everything is lobsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A secretary switches bodies with a yew tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man discovers that Friday the 13th does not exist, and is driven insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A deeply depressed sex worker has an unusual ability: She can smell laughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a volcano in Nepal. It spews out seahorses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Athenian teenager remembers a gigantic koala.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A circus performer invents a new type of horror based on the movement of clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cathedral floats above the Forbidden City. It is controlled by a bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful man with orange eyes knocks at your door. You answer it, and he hands you an astronomer's mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drunk accountant discovers a crystal ball that lets him see, hear, smell, touch and taste Mothers Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Kansas there is a carnation which has petals in the shape of candy bars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a supermarket in Paris. Instead of groceries, it sells clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Polish duke constructs a swimming pool that is filled with the fast food industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess rebuilds the Golden Gate Bridge out of supernovae.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guilt-stricken child spends all his time writing an essay about despair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A staircase in Melbourne is made of artificial insemination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bureaucrat discovers that the Fijian economy is secretly being controlled by a glass prince.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Danish notebook describes a way of tying a knot that kills everyone who is itchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time traveller from medieval Florence appears before you. She gives you a square and says: "I am your biggest fan."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One hundred university professors do battle against a Coliseum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archangel aims to befriend every recursive algorithm in Hollywood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mixtape causes anyone who hears it to turn into a clock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scholar is vomiting in a little boy's mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A monster is born in Cairo with the head of a crocodile and the body of a dragon. It feels sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theologian is sailing a dinghy to King Arthur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine tunafish are setting out on an adventure. Their aim is to find the lost king of Rome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A church is haunted by the ghost of a boy. He keeps repeating one word: "Big Macs."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Scientologist is reading a notebook by Hegel on the subject of syphilis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 12th century treatise describes a bath filled with tongues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In San Francisco there is an island which is in love with a supermarket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A zeppelin floats into a lighthouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Portland there is a rubber duck which is getting married in a silver crypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An embittered sheik goes for a walk in a forest and discovers an oak tree made of jazz music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mexican mermaid tells the story of a leopard with diamonds instead of spots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sun is singing in a laundromat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A busboy is found dead in a locked room. Next to her is an oak tree and a cynical demon. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every sculptor in Toronto is getting high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king catches his partner having sexual intercourse with optical illusions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a volcano in Bangkok that feels mysterious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bumble bee can move beehives with its mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prince crawls across a domino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sexually frustrated maharajah has a recurring dream about being chased by good luck. It eventually sends him mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pharmacist looks into a pair of spectacles and sees every sunrise that has taken place in Manhattan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Australian architect plants a seed. A palace grows from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A huntsman puts a hex on a pope. It makes him forget every philosophical treatise he has read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An opera singer is being followed by a huge turtle in a glass forest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A watchmaker writes a book that is made out of office Christmas parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hairdresser owns a pearl that allows her to kiss everyone in the western world at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sous chef is listening to a professor give a lecture on Aristotle. Suddenly, the lecturer turns into a the paintings turn into labyrinth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A porcelain ship sails across a sea of skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A trench coat has the power to enable fireflies to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Venezuelan admiral hears of a city located inside a forest, and devotes his life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are standing in a clockwork wheat field. Motor oil begins falling from the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drag queen in Cape Town writes a book on how to hug candles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a Swiss reality TV show in which the players must race against a wardrobe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up and realise that you are a lake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A necromancer imagines a pigeon that can destroy the sun, and dedicates his life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clerk finds out that a tennis racquet is controlling Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychologist is writing a shopping list. It has four items: A compass, a shooting star, a chess piece and a peacock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kurdish witch declares war on everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A soldier urinates breast milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A YouTube star is committed to an asylum located in a snail in Tennessee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An irritable man plays a game of rock, paper, scissors with a giant sequoia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An accountant buys a telescope which lets him see every humiliating defeat since the birth of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman gets married to moonlight inside a stained glass garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A witch sits on a swing in a termite mound. She is thinking about Kantian ethics. A fairy is painting behind her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Caribbean fashion stylist sees a stain on a carpet in the shape of an opium poppy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pope builds a giant cathedral and fills it with rabbits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Parisian duchess hears a fire alarm that sounds like clichés.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A violinist is poisoning the Middle Ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leaf emerges from a sea. A grandmother says: "That's a bad omen."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You suddenly turn into Seville.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher spends her life rewriting a book of poetry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hourglasses and ziggurats. That is all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Incan sailor appears at the base of the Eiffel Tower. A little boy knows why he has come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight, a little girl will appear and give you the meaning of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Japanese duke has a Siamese cat instead of a kidney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A candy apple made of Generation Y appears in Marrakech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By thinking of a piece of rose quartz, a Brazilian sultan is able to destroy the Milky Way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A piglet holds up a jewellery store. It steals 15 moonstones, a diamond and a magic ruby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king is assassinated. The killer turns out to be management consulting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anxious archduke makes a speech about birthdays that goes on for 3,100 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ninety-nine archivists invent a parallel universe where everything is wedding dresses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen plans to steal every barometer in Nashville.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>