<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/fI0wgjsplz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/LFOIiHuHEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/SoFDufW61N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/KSGulw4v0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/qJ3e3RMD8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/6RngZPGNYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/ERRF1Fempi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/IWDLcA304A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed in business, to reach the top, an individual must know all it is possible to know about that business. - J. Paul Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/6vTJIGvUx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/Kj5DZXNmIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/2AZ8WEeiWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/j2Q1U43o2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/gV3nFvXLm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/t3JPk3V4KT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/bULxZW5qnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/ZeYRD389fB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/CNHA8rwlFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/sEc0VedoYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/wlPOdCsMO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of The Hollywood Sign  http://t.co/5Vij0RjnVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/t27YIqHmgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/RceggQnozh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/rHoiLuWqVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/v0xufEbmjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell that you're in trouble when you feel the air on the back of your neck instead of in your face. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/jfXtbBZrIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/gNATUKxSsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/kDcchiG3lF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/0hI1IehvH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/UUQsWO5USq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/uHoDEey1uF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/I8xdUhgh3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/hXEeJeCNhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/avbjo7ezVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/ofnmiBrUJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/MmR3RSEsPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/3iDMl4L5vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/gV3nFvXLm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/WKP0rPHAml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/6h380efQQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/IL1vsCyiQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/urWYDs905w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/VidyYgSTrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/p2IpxnctOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to get thin is to re-establish a purpose in life. - Cyril Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/WRPOnIgdFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/VIQVLBmAyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/o6ACMrcTrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/dH9phFfU1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/GwjipoXC6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/Q8EXf1EWEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/uWrJSCm9Sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/LGUAFqKTEG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>