<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@FineArtNCustoms cool daddyo - ive got my studio if u want a big open space to collaborate in :) (very busy with stuff now, down teh road..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtisanMrkt604 thanks! it was a great, fun night!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryceBarfoot good man. my art career is really taking off and job is easy and relaxed. Lots of boarding/adventuring etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these pics from my opening on Thursday night!

http://t.co/fVD0ROlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a show I would love to go to if I wasn't so far away from it:

http://t.co/E68baOtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anybody help me [and my art] with a ride to Whistler either April 12 in the evening or April 13 in the daytime? I'll pay or trade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are in St. Catharines the end of April, I have animation screening as part of this festival: http://t.co/YsXUDvC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryceBarfoot hey man. hows it goin? seems like a lot of people migrated to proximity from mac toronto eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PAHomeBuilders thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDrewKennedy i know you! nice pic as background ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coachcomeback thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladeedy hey there - thanks for the follow!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart @aspiringmedia @adapia @philemonjung @society6 @jonshawpainting @aydengallery @decayfm thanks for mentioning buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart sweetness! I'm sure I will (unless it's An amazing night for them!!) haha. I'll also be doing plenty of summer markets with them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart one day only!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart may 16;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart yup for sure! they're gonna be for sale at the roundhouse on the 16th for that show, then ill sell leftovers after. $20 a pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart hAHAHAHA.well, u can certainly
See them as I make em then :) (or at the roundhouse show!) ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asapprintdepot best*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asapprintdepot I like deep
Yellows beat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the first 14 images of my 100 sushi painting project on my FB fan page:

http://t.co/9x9tV9Ow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[here is sushi painting #12. 88 more to go! http://t.co/3al0wwSD via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought a new tube of deep yellow. Oh colour excitement!! #art #Vancouver #paint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So long Rosie, I'll miss ya but you're goin to a good home :) http://t.co/JcB2OIaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart lol thx buddy! Just circumstance of the show we were at :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shut_up_n_paint fantastic! Deets closer to the date :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shut_up_n_paint fantastic! the show is 10-10 , and the reception is in the eve, 7-10. its a big group show, at the roundhouse :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart thx buddy! I'm pretty stoked :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shut_up_n_paint haha i will! my piece at the roundhouse will be on display for one day, may 16, if you are on this side that day/night.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shut_up_n_paint @jonshawpainting you got it budddday! ones in ambelside, its called harmony arts in august.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two new shows coming up later in the summer - Time to tackle West Van!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgbg hey man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c2mnet hello thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy hey there - thanks for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomebaseStudio hey there, thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KendalKendrick thanks for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy awesome turn out at state of the art final day yesterday. Thx everyone for your support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is much amazing work available from our recent design24 show - check these available prints:... http://t.co/pjjxYOgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final stage - this will be auctioned off next sunday, 29th at Squamish lillioet cultural centre http://t.co/4OJwx2CM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting stage 2 http://t.co/CLqnaVw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live painting progress shot #1 http://t.co/vybpSD55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling I most definitely will! Do u print shirts yourself? I've seen your other printing skills.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the final day of State of the Art. I'll be painting a 4 footer from 12-6pm :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling a printmaker friend, hand screens em: does a very good job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling thanks buddy! New explorations are fun :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart ended up choosing a bear eating a salmon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shirts are printed, here's the tester. Setting them up for sale next week. http://t.co/Y4XYCnwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 out of 100 sushi pieces drawn so far. http://t.co/JwaqveXq via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phoenicopterus roseus
24" x 24"
Ink and acrylic on canvas
2012 http://t.co/EBaTv4A3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ara spp
30" x 40"
Ink and acrylic on canvas
2012 http://t.co/EWwRjzzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cathartes aura
24" x 48"
Ink and acrylic on canvas
2012 http://t.co/CM417pR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my shirts. Wearing one to my live painting session at State of the Art tomorrow in Whistler :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart thanks! It should be fun! I still haven't decided on what I'm painting but I'm kinda leaning towards a whale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtProfiles hey there thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onehappyartist thx, I'm wanting it all tge time now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart haha thx buddy! Stoked about the early progress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart I'll be at the whistler conference center, all day tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is the beginning of my 100 sushi painting project, going on display May 16 at the Roundhouse Community Center! http://t.co/cPlFhMfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@utidur hey! thx for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - its neat to see Vancouver showing some effort towards the arts:

http://t.co/PF1lPTrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpperCutArtists hello - thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsyShark hey thanks for the follow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart was awesome - im going back this weekend for live painting on april 20th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart of course! we'll discuss once i get them, get pricing, online store, etc all set up :) (online first then shops)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T shirts are printed. Picking them up this week. Expect an online store to pop up shortly! http://t.co/ugkhENoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaBellEady hey - thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianPCosta hey there - thanks for the follow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart @jonshawpainting hmmm good call - would be a sweet image for sure - its on the list!! thanks bud :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to prepare a subject for this Friday's live painting session in Whistler. Any suggested imagery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CenterpointArt hey! thanks for the follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting my set up in whistler. Can't wait for the opening tonight! http://t.co/sNlOw3o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brentclowater hey man nice shots im seeing on here. how's the day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pieces are shipped to Whistler. Opening party for State of the Art is THIS Friday night, 8-12 PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how this colour blends and separates..and the yellow bits beside the red up top:. http://t.co/oRmuUQG1 via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue CRABBBB  http://t.co/JZ6x42qi via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going up on display this week!! http://t.co/YOJF81AX via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight I am hanging paintings at Cuppa Joy in Kitsilano, at 4th and Alma. New work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like the patch of colour on the right here - reminds me of fruit loops! http://t.co/jyAJ76km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a piece that ive slowly added to for two months. I now like it :) http://t.co/OJxLV5TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent most of today packing paintings for shows. In two days...the studio will be empty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato ya - i always just buy one or two sizes only, and the amount i use is ridiculous! im saving all the worn out ones for fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zanytomato i use a couple weights of fine marker pens. i use staedtler lumograph pens (Fine and Super Fine sizes) and a fat marker too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got this one started and in progress, just establishing a colour scheme of lime green and high key pink.... http://t.co/1wpZmq37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the current state of "B", one of three pieces in a set titled "RGB" http://t.co/TMZsx2Te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of three crabs. I may be titling them "R" "G" and "B" to correspond to digital colour space.... http://t.co/D4nVo5zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cybelenegris hey there - thanks for the follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Crab in progress, almost done! http://t.co/YWuaFVXK via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BUG! I'll have this one on display in a coffee shop in Kitsilano starting next week! http://t.co/0CZ82aFP via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Crab! Piece in progress, from a series of several crab works: http://t.co/SH6bwNNc via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the ball continues to roll on making my first run of t-shirts. Pretty stoked to see how this will turn out: http://t.co/wt94JmUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lineup for In The Soil announced - the venue for my animation is so sweet! (scroll to the bottom)... http://t.co/K9ATeBeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's becoming more and more clear that I'm going to be painting art directly onto my apartment walls soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/eoAjZ7qn Super cool. I love seeing awesome concept in art pieces like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so stoked that this is the venue for my work at State of the Art starting next Friday: http://t.co/eyaJTykW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are some pieces in progress http://t.co/Tie612LZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comin along. Gonna wrap this fella up shortly. More work on it tonight http://t.co/rDUxtaj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeanettebizdev1 hello - thanks for following me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeanettebizdev hello - thanks for the follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This work is hung and you can see it tomorrow at the roundhouse centre. Free food. http://t.co/tud0tYv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliesviews1 thanks for the follow! Where are you based?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>