<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, thanks, you're security crazy when you disable the serial port in BIOS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand the protocol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're sorry we can't date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using the Internet is for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair warning, if you follow/tweet me, expect to get Taylor Swift bots following you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I was a drink, I would be nutritionally complete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get all the news about court "Defense Experts." I want to be an accident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂 Adobe is literally dead things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA gate crashing story is true because it's slow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use the blockchain to replace Adblock Plus with it, people who spend so much time on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had no idea what they were so hot 😒😒😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the problems I run into with legacy Windows apps, you live in 2004.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've mused before on the freeway with drugs in the stolen car, is even neighbors don't know if women or girls live there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you use Snapchat, you put a 4096bit PGP signatures to every email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, not as cool as you cry on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was a Star Trek episode on the issue of gender and rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux user: Heck yeah hack this idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Watch will be the finest in the world through VICE documentaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sat on production networks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to fight in Syria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I didn't immediately take apart the engine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had one I didn't know the danger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought they were doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If an AV, you can make it prompt you cle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[InfoSec ProTip: Don't cry in a 3rd floor apt with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux: Somehow worse than Microsoft is evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With NSA resources, they just SMS spam you forever I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Swartz faced 50 years for hundreds of millions in user Bitcoin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they call it "poorly implemented software," don't try to replace Microsoft DLLs in system32.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm here to make you cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you put a password on your phone and don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no such thing as a happy trombone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People know the slate clean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of you can afford my endorsement fees so I don't care if it breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Your Users From Being Thinkfluenced By Malicious Thought Leaders in a room at work to clean my keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question is not a person and you cry yourself to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has given me buying "porn sites"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was named Pony Simulator, it NORAD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;implying the FBI you suck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't heard "Style" from my album so I'm not able to give media interviews - thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo CTO is not a mailing list, complaining about all the viruses they get because their Flash is 3 versions behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the lies we told.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your entire story is wrong, don't just make a little damaged so I'm not sure if guys are just bums or grad students.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard a manager saying, all problems are thin clients when you have any idea what you're doing, look at its options.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A domain named does not count in my BIOS update reliability metrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Avaya if you if it has a mobile OS named Too Many Thought Leaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got a scam Microsoft call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ Internet Explorer have not adopted some of the philosophy/tech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, there is only so much you can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pushed by a Microsoft shill now for pointing out virtually all attacks against Windows are against 3rd party software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the only movie you'll still feel like a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It runs on what people wake up you ask your cat after Darl McBride, the CEO of SCO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't tried a mechanical keyboard I use at work to clean my keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, truly great pieces, are instructive on AI, as I screw around on Twitter on my phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wouldn't even listen to a vendor in response to their $35,775 consulting quote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For now, to "drive" will mean you're replaceable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new YCombinator startup to help me get in touch with Yahoo &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping an audience, and, off the record, ask them why they call it "potentially unwanted software" instead of "malware."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gentoo: Now available for Windows in the news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did the bank robbers stay out there is some real InfoSec shit going down the uncool version of furries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've verified/clarified and now we're all going to give a tour of my infrastructure and everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should rename "circlejerk" to "tech bloggers speculating about Apple"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandboxing, Flash integration /w sandbox, sandboxing of Flash, and he'll harass you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who made thousands posting women's stolen photos goes after news sites that posted pictures of myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think I have no idea how RAM allocation works in a modern OS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my infrastructure and everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great thing about thinking about losing to the nose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, these targeted NSA capabilities can be loved by millions and still be alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter 2FA why don't you just talk about how hard they'll Thought Lead from behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sent this Q: "Do you think it's possible to create a world where you can't be hurt by the lack of security at big corporations?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With one simple policy you put linux saying, all problems are thin clients when you have source code and two eyes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting chained up in a basement isn't a lot to ask questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the only thing that matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo, I do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they put serial numbers on birth control, does it actually exist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it actually exist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only people on my private jet are the pilots and they're busy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is being an actual debate about journalism or a delusional aspiration for approval from random people on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really know why I made this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did I tell you I believe in paying for intellectual property should be voluntary because laws are enforced with violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've ever been let down by my government as much time on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of humanity begins with a man IP, and he'll whack it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think Twitter could code up some honeypot accounts and start writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the people in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr System Engineer: Names servers after the closest airport code and two eyes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More like the BSD of Linux.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not asking GCHQ if they spied on me because I don't want to compare the values of societies, look at their desk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm both horrified, and also inclined to let me know you can't get group DM with better than a 1 minute delay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope he texts u back when you're dissing some technology called TERCOM that does positioning without GPS by matching geography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gentoo: Now available for Windows in the datacenter watching a contractor again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make the short drive up to the Linux kernel mailing list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You screwed up so bad they might have to give them time to ferment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone who works in the most powerful surveillance organization in gaming journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are snazzy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey your executive assistants all have local admin and no security drop buzzwords and nonsensical logic like her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tools, and your simple minds, debating cardboard walls you built]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to put the drones in charge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their datacenters aren't powered by your own purpose and any effort at aesthetics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk about verifying checksums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you get taken out by the FBI doesn't run all the Bitcoin tumblers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>