<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["My persona's so real, people think it's fake." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born To Die: The Paradise Edition is now available on iTunes UK , purchase it here: http://t.co/DxxdSv9B — Support Lana!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to our Queen @LanaDelRey for winning 'Best Alternative' at the 2012 MTV EMAs! http://t.co/V5BP52he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She looks like an angel tonight! So gorgeous! http://t.co/KFvl45rG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for The Paradise Era! TOMORROW! #TeamLana http://t.co/kDZycgHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need nobody, 'cause we got each other. Or at least I pretend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck yeah, give it to me. This is heaven, what I truly want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This made my day. http://t.co/pc5GGFM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Lana Del Rey will be the big #MTVEMA winner! Tweet your pick at http://t.co/vTGNH6MZ #EMAWinLanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take another drag turn me to ashes. Ready for another lie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana &amp; Jaime. How cute they are. — http://t.co/7wyCbIFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think Lana Del Rey is Flawless! — http://t.co/OXmAPjx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, you and me are the lucky ones this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana The Queen Of Bel Air. http://t.co/Rny8DemV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana The Queen Of Bel Air cause she had a chameleon soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana The Queen Of Bel Air, and I have been waiting to meet her. — http://t.co/x3e6QOzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just you and me feelin' the heat even when the sun goes down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it trend! #EMAWinLanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eonline: Our favorite Bond Girl nominee from you guys: Lana Del Rey. Can totally see that! http://t.co/7H7cd8iu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep tweeting and keep using this hashtag guys! #EMAWinLanaDelRey — We can do it! #ThePowerOfTeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only seventeen, but she walks the streets so mean. — #EMAWinLanaDelRey http://t.co/SHrYN3zN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Angel RT @LanaDelRey: http://t.co/L8tKrFHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EMAWinLanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#iWillNeverUnderstand why people hate on Lana Del Rey. I'm sorry but they really have a problem with their eyes, hearing &amp; their mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby, nothing to lose and we get messed up for fun. We went too fast, too young.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LANA DEL GOD. http://t.co/5PaxyoK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one lives forever, but that's no reason to give up. Don't you wanna fall in love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hater: Lana Del Rey is so ugly! — Me: … http://t.co/PnMN1v56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keren ! RT @MariaParamithaa: By : Adinda Maharani @LanaDelRey @LanaQuote http://t.co/LtiMCLNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool ! RT @NadineManson: @LanaQuote 2 drawings I did of @LanaDelRey .... http://t.co/RlDrmJ43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She laughs like god, her mind's like a diamond. http://t.co/0rCXzvVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulation to @LanaDelRey for winning 'Best Pop Video' (International) at the 2012 UK Video Music Awards for "Born To Die" Video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it for the thrill of the rush, love you just a little too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is nominated for @AskMen #Top99Women of 2013. GO VOTE HERE: http://t.co/qw5hwdhg #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know what the boys want, I am not gonna play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no relief, I feel you in my sleep. And everybodys rushing me, but I can feel you touching me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YouTube: The latest video from Lana Del Rey is smoking hot … and maybe a little spooky. http://t.co/VK57VjQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the land of Gods and Monsters, I was an angel. Living in the garden of evil. http://t.co/rvYyITqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LETS TREND: Gods and Monsters. http://t.co/hIuXqvgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need you like a baby when I hold you. Like a druggy, like I told you. Yayo, yeah you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/mXGLZbD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bel Air Art Nouveau.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey presents: Bel Air Music Video! Watch it now: http://t.co/H1D5bvG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I know that it's Love. You make me happy and I never listen to anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark and lonely, I need somebody to hold me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their heavy words can't bring me down. Boy, I've been raised from the dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who runs the twitter? Team Lana! —  Lana Wore Blue Velvet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She wore blue velvet. Bluer than velvet were her eyes. Lana Wore Blue Velvet. http://t.co/45ZWWc3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LETS TREND: Lana Wore Blue Velvet. http://t.co/BHGG3X5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voice of Nirvana says come as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lana isn't a fanbase. We are FAMILY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[❒ Obama ❒ Romney ✔ Lana Del Rey — #VoteLana #TeamLana http://t.co/tWxDwrzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise you'll remember that you're mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretend I'm not hurt, I walk about the world like I'm having fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Building a world for yourself isn't as important as being a good member of society in the world that you actually live in." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the next music video! http://t.co/AXl7ibaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey has been nominated for 5 World Music Awards for Best Song, Album, Video, Best Female Artist &amp; Best Entertainer Of The Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there's no remedy for memory, your face is like melody. It won't leave my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be bad &amp; have fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I also fear the unknown after death, which is probably the number one fear for most people." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/YAcg1hgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were the one thing that kept me holding on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VOTE for Lana Del Rey as E!'s 2012 Celeb Of The Year, she's up against Lady Gaga in Round 3! — http://t.co/bBNr1w0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the land of gods &amp; monsters, I was an angel, living in the garden of evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I caught myself smiling for no reason. Then I realized I was thinking about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you forever, not maybe. You are my one true love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this our first trend guys? – (February 5th 2012) #TeamLana http://t.co/BQqHbnN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am usually always singing about the same god damn person so I'll love him forever, but you know, it's all good." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you RESPECT my idol, I will respect yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morgan_Rose_xx Every Man Gets His Wish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said, "I wanna buy you a classic white milkshake."
I said, "I'll serve you up a special side of heartbreak."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light of my life, fire of my loins. Be a good baby, do what I want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't sleep at night, what once was sleep is now taken over by thoughts of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the different ways my life could have taken me, I always knew I'd end up in your arms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't imagine doing anything else with my life except loving you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is better than you since you were born.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is strange, sometimes it makes you crazy, it can burn or break you down." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alvinreez97 https://t.co/Oaf9JTrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna be yours, like I always say, never let me go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Gangsters, No Riders, No Lanatics, or etc. We're Team Lana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey on her fan name. http://t.co/qdqKOV8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born to live fast die young. Leave a beautiful corpse, live my life on the run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Truth is like the sun. You can shut it out for a time, but it ain't goin' away." —Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DeleteYourTwitterIf you don't like Lana Del Rey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my parents. http://t.co/D2YLSYUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DJ's, Rockstar, Posers, we are the new politicans – but celebrity editions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I write my own songs, I made my own videos, I pick my producers. Nothing goes out without my permission. It's all authentic." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The fans of Lana Del Rey are called Gangster's." http://t.co/udJ2moOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're boring me to death and I'm already dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were the only friends I ever had. We got into trouble and when stuff got bad, I got sent away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blurring the lines, between real and the fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 1st Anniversary to http://t.co/ZRdzAbKu – @LanaDelReyWorld &amp; @LanaDelReyFan :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I felt I lived most of my life divided into two states of either fear or love." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that true? RT @EsztiDelRey: But why is Lana on the cover of a children's magazine? http://t.co/e0hRXA0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Text me when you get home safely, like you always did when we were first dating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep voting for Lana Del Rey as 'The Hottest Women in Music'. We're on the 1st place! — http://t.co/rXGKqqBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VOTE! https://t.co/V8y43TCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 days until 'Born To Die Video' 1st Birthday. http://t.co/Mgh4Jhtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had Lana Del Rey's voice I'd never shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Games will never get old. http://t.co/6XCAAdIg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>