<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it so that people feel they can come to you with any issue without fear of reprimand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: "That's the way it's always been" is never an adequate reason to continue doing something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Study history. The answers are there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Peace begins with the choice to reject your own anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's okay if your second in command has a different management style, as long as you both agree on the goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep up with new technologies. Today you get a holodeck, but tomorrow could bring a holographic doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Used sparingly, some light swearing can help emphasize your damn point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Get your own damn work done. Others will follow suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Have an opinion on one side of an issue. Stay out of the neutral zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a realistic understanding of what your ship can and cannot do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Say yes whenever possible, except when your tactical officer recommends attacking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your past successes are not assurances for the future. Remain vigilant against complacency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let a crew member's age blind you to their skill level, in either direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let upper management dismantle your team, nor your team members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard crisis tip: Even when the situation seems daunting, don't give up your determination to win the day. It's not over till it's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Fight for what you know is right. Only arrogant bullies think resistance is futile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know your audience. Display strength to Klingons, logic to Vulcans, and opportunity to Ferengi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In a strange new environment, be wary of making changes until you understand more about what's going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Don't assume your opponent will behave rationally. Plan for their emotional response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Decide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Admitting one's failures is a sign of confidence and strength. It reassures others that failing is okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Even if computers can talk now, remember how deeply stupid they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your sense of morality is the guiding light that people under your command will follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're on red alert every day, then red alert means nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: The enemy of my enemy is sometimes a dangerous sociopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Some of your decisions are going to be mistakes. You have to make them anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you make a mistake, apologize right away. Embrace humility over defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard emergency tip: When all else fails, route main power through the main deflector dish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Exercise makes you smarter. Don't just sit there thinking.

Get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Good crew members love what they do. Get off their backs and let them enjoy their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeSondow: going to bed with a headache and waking up without one https://t.co/nAQfxJJduY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Give your experts time for unstructured play. It makes them more creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Improve your vocabulary by reading books. Words can be your most powerful tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If your crew is afraid to talk to you, they won't always give you the information you need. Be approachable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your superiors are just as fallible as you are. It's okay to talk back to them. Just do it respectfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Treat your crew like adults. They aren't children… except the college intern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard exploration tip: Our galaxy has over eight billion habitable planets. Get to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard investigation tip: Magnify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Certain crew members are like walking encyclopedias. Remember to ask for their input.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard science tip: The universal translator is not the end of linguistics. The replicator is not the end of chemistry. Keep going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The crew needs to see you calm. If you're frustrated, complain to a confidante in private, then make a decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Finish what you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Half of leadership is acting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When a middle manager says one of his crew isn't fitting in, tell him to befriend the crewman and fix the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard responsibility tip: Don't leave known, wide-scale problems behind for the next generation to solve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Explain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There is always a non-obvious third option. When caught between a rock and a hard place, find a jackhammer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Passion is not an excuse for a tantrum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard social tip: You're not really a third wheel if one of the others is a hologram. https://t.co/Uw1Of1EOoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Regulations do not cover every situation. Sometimes you have to decide for yourself what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If a crew member needs to become more responsible, give them more responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep a log of your journey. You will understand better by writing it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There's no need to solve hard problems alone. Admit when you need help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: Don't fall in love with holograms, even if your friends do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: If reality gets altered, leaving you alone with your crush, it doesn't necessarily mean it's time to make your move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Statements should not sound like questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Use the metric system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be realistic about your project timelines. Romulus wasn't built in a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeSondow: For the first time, @jonathansfrakes replied to my @RikerGoogling account, and it was 🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/JKhezxtS2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard multiversal tip: Be careful; not even a Jedi or a Time Lord can withstand Vogon poetry. So say we all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you build up enough reputation, people will listen to any drivel you say. They'll even repeat it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you have the misfortune to acquire enemies, face them head on. They're just as afraid as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take some alone time. The crew will be fine without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Bathrooms are unseemly. Keep them out of sight and don't talk about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Pushy consultants make strange bedfellows. https://t.co/kSq7A9542k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Conducting an experiment with an unknown outcome is time well spent, even if the result disappoints you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Malfunctioning systems must be fixed right away. There is no excuse for delaying repairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't be afraid to use imperative verbs. They're called orders for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your knowledge is a wellspring from which to draw for others, not a treasure to hoard for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard beauty tip: Traveling for years at superluminal speeds greatly slows down the aging process. https://t.co/78AydCjdGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There is a time to follow a military hierarchy and there is a time to enjoy an informal community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your first impulse will often be wrong, but you have to start somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Everyone's a critic, but some criticisms are more correct than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard rationality tip: There is no such thing as a ghost or a devil. It's just an alien. It's always an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When crew members are unsuccessful, urge them to try again. Encouragement and persistence may be all they need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Become a symbol of stability for your crew. This takes time, but then they'll move mountains for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Expecting people to work long hours is short-sighted, counter-productive, and potentially dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it so the crew has real time monitoring of your enterprise's critical systems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: A polished appearance for your enterprise reassures your crew and intimidates your foes. https://t.co/X8XBI5oHPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Obedience never lasts long when it's based solely on punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard sociology tip: Those who rise to power by embracing ignorance and fear will only make their people more ignorant and afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When a crew member's behavior changes significantly, inquire and investigate. It could be important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard theology tip: Unproven gods are hypotheses waiting to be tested. Proven gods are aliens with better technology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Yes, the uniforms are tight, but please, eyes up here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a reputation for completing missions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Succeeding at the very last second is still succeeding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeSondow: every time i use webmd https://t.co/6OqDCIC5PF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: During a large-scale, life-threatening emergency, postpone all other priorities and focus on protecting your crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Withhold advice on matters you do not understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Make it a habit to try to gain new allies, not just new enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: If there is one truth, one constant that history shows us over and over, it is that resistance is never futile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard science tip: Investigate stellar phenomena whenever the opportunity arises. There is always more to learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard tactical tip: There is no shame in a wise retreat. The shame would be in risking one's crew because of selfish pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard leadership tip: The larger your audience and the higher your position, the greater the need to communicate with care and precision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you find yourself leading an unusually toxic crew, it may be necessary to remove more than one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard leadership tip: If everyone on your team quits, don't pretend you fired them. No one will believe you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard ethics tip: The fact that a conflict has many sides does not imply that every side has merit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard morality tip: The moment you consider yourself morally superior to someone due to your genetics is the moment you prove you are not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard social tip: A Vulcan can laugh. A Klingon can soothe. A Ferengi can give. Your preconceptions are not facts.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>