<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream no small dreams for they have no power to move the hearts of men.
- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the balance of nature decrees that a super-abundance of dreams is paid for by a growing potential for nightmares. -P Ustinov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He that will watch for providences, shall never be in want for providences. -Flavel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience will achieve more than force.
-Edmund Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discontent is the first step in the progress of a man or a nation. -Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities? They are all around us... There is power lying latent everywhere waiting for the observant eye to discover it. - Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is to know something nobody else knows. -Aristotle Onassis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this true? "The struggle alone pleases us, not the victory." -Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is much easier kept than recovered. -Thomas Paine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only true happiness comes from squandering ourselves for a purpose. -John Mason Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The successful person places more attention on doing the right thing rather than doing things right.
- Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-trust is the first secret to success. -Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Above all be of single aim; have a legitimate and useful purpose, and devote yourself unreservedly to it.
- James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is wonderful what may be done if we are always doing. -Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have made any valuable discoveries, it has been owing more to patient attention than to any other talent. -Sir Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry, perseverance, and frugality make fortune yield.
- Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you reach your goals, set new ones. That is how you grow and become a more powerful person. -Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sooner you make your first five thousand mistakes the sooner you will be able to correct them. -Kimon Nicolaides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be. -Kurt Vonnegut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We die daily. Happy those who daily come to life as well. -George MacDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expect to lose. Even when I'm the underdog, I still prepare a victory speech.
- H. Jackson Brown, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You play the way you practice. -Pop Warner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive Thinking If you care at all, you'll get some results. If you care enough, you'll get incredible results. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the nature of the strong heart, that like the palm tree it strives ever upwards when it is most burdened. -Philip Sidney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be discouraged. It's often the last key in the bunch that opens the lock. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how far you have gone on a wrong road, turn back. -Turkish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay. -Simone De Beauvoir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people struggle with life balance because they haven't paid the price to decide what's really important to them. -Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never complain. Never explain. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In every triumph there's a lot of try." -Frank Tyger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a great believer in luck, and I find the harder I work, the more I have of it. -Stephen Leacock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we think determines what happens to us, so if we want to change our lives, we need to stretch our minds. -Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is by surmounting difficulties, not by sinking under them that we discover our fortitude. -Hannah Webster Foster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conditions are never just right. People who delay action until all factors are favorable do nothing. -William Feather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so easy to learn as experience and nothing so hard to apply. -Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. -Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has never tasted what is bitter does not know what is sweet. -German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot rise higher than our thought of ourselves. -Orison Swett Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners must have two things: definite goals, and a burning desire to achieve them. -Brad Burden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without hope men are only half alive. With hope they dream and think and work. -Charles Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to be fast on your feet and adaptive or else a strategy is useless. -Lou Gerstner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are forgiven for your happiness and your successes only if you generously consent to share them. -Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conquering any difficulty always gives one a secret joy, for it means pushing back a boundary-line and adding to one's liberty. -Amiel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man should frame life so that at some future hour fact and his dreaming meet. -Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people follow their dreams, others hunt them down and beat them mercilessly into submission. -Neil Kendall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not doing more than the average is what keeps the average down. -William M. Winans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody ever forgets where he buried the hatchet.
- Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote It's not that I'm so smart, it's just that I stay with problems longer. -Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wisdom of the wise and the experience of ages may be preserved by quotation. -Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are all born for love. It is the principle of existence and its only end." -Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any person who contributes to prosperity must prosper in turn. -Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We judge ourselves by what we feel capable of doing, while others judge us by what we have already done. -Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luck is what you have left over after you give 100 percent. -Langston Coleman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intensity of your desire governs the power with which the force is directed. -John McDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE #5: my #facebook page is still stolen. Strange that no one from @facebook has contacted me yet.(???) 13 days of logging tickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend time every day listening to what your muse is trying to tell you. -Saint Bartholomew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is through cooperation, rather than conflict, that your greatest successes will be derived! -Ralph Charell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your life in your own hands and what happens? A terrible thing: no one is to blame. -Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a dream so BIG that you cannot achieve it until you grow into the person who can. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am looking for a lot of men who have an infinite capacity to not know what can't be done. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's going on in the inside shows on the outside.
- Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who admits ignorance shows it once; the one who tries to hide it shows it often. -Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful person is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks that others throw at him or her. -David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is often what you get when you were expecting something else. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can imagine no more comfortable frame of mind for the conduct of life than a humorous resignation. -W. Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had to live my life over again, I'd try to make more mistakes next time. -Nadine Stair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never become so much of an expert that you stop gaining expertise. View life as a continuous learning experience.
- Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though we travel the world over to find the beautiful, we must carry it with us or we find it not. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The soul without imagination is what an observatory would be without a telescope. -Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it. -George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nail is driven out by another nail. Habit is overcome by habit.
- Desiderius Erasmus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything comes if a man will only wait. -Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change the changeable, accept the unchangeable, and remove yourself from the unacceptable.
- Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never knew a man come to greatness or eminence who lay abed late in the morning. -Johnathan Swift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exceed expectations. We are not driven to do extraordinary things, but to do ordinary things extraordinarily well. -Bishop Gore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing about the school of experience is that it will repeat the lesson if you flunk the first time. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you'll not settle for anything less than your best, you will be amazed at what you can accomplish in your lives. -Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is going from failure to failure without losing enthusiasm.
- Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We grow great by dreams. All big men are dreamers. -Woodrow T. Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything comes too late for those who only wait." -Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you fear a foe, fear crushes your strength; and this weakness gives strength to your opponents. -William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who is shipwrecked the second time cannot lay the blame on Neptune. -English Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men stumble over pebbles, never over mountains. -Emilie Cady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything comes to him who hustles while he waits. -Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not look where you fell, but where you slipped. -African Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. -Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong beliefs win strong men, and then make them stronger. -Walter Bagehot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a man constantly aspires is he not elevated?
- Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success consists of getting up just one more time than you fall. -Oliver Goldsmith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have made a ceaseless effort not to ridicule, not to bewail, not to scorn human actions but to understand them." -Baruch Spinoza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life... It tends to respond to our outlook, to shape itself to meet our expectations. -Richard M. DeVos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people dream of success. To me success can only be achieved through repeated failure and introspection. -Soichiro Honda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first hour of the morning is the rudder of the day.
- Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No life ever grows great until it is focused, dedicated, disciplined. -Harry Emerson Fosdick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little more persistence, a little more effort, and what seemed hopeless failure may turn to glorious success. -Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance is a great element of success. If u only knock long enough and loud enough at the gate, u are sure to wake somebody. -Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profit is a by-product of work; happiness is its chief product. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality questions create a quality life. Successful people ask better questions, and as a result, they get better answers. -Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who has a strong enough why can bear almost any how. -Friedrich Nietzsche]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>