<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: ..."'til morning."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: Jerry, immediately, not yelling or aggro, wryly like yr h.s. math teacher: "No. Fuck you. You gotta stick around to hea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: audience applauds at the end. when the applause dies down to silence, a man in attendance immediately yells: "Morning D…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: they open with "He Was A Friend of Mine," utterly beautiful rendition, pretty bold opening choice: 11 minutes of liltin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: the scene: the Ark, 15 Lansdowne St., Boston, MA. the date: 4/23/69. a dude who saw them last night and got converted i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mountain_goats: ok I'm working while listening to live Grateful Dead in the headphones and I just heard my favorite stage banter of all…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waddya' think happen.when zoo goes work Zappen' https://t.co/ZjdC8T7pQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Line? He's playing Hopscotch ffs https://t.co/xBuEGFDO19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne Loved the column. Disappointed he felt need to apologize. The Appropriation Prize must be made real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: RT if you agree this writer must be fired. https://t.co/I1URHDeg23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJenNeale_PD Is he married?. Girlfriend ? Remind her how coLd it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Has the oldest national Paper figured out the youngest way to stay relevant https://t.co/vXT26kTCZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FanSince09 You must be a fan of Mitch Hedberg. That is some fine Mitch shit right there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Commentary at its wryist https://t.co/W2O3JvO9St]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie I like pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlse That's why patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mlse: The real angle exonerates Kadri! You’re all monsters for calling him a diver https://t.co/vGYMUurmwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jasondrums68 @yyzsportsmedia @b0undless What is the story. Why has something so good been ended by #HNIC AND OR #sportnet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jasondrums68: @yyzsportsmedia It was really terrible. What a mood killer. Taking away @b0undless intros was one of the worst decisions…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darrenrovell: The art of the troll. Savage move, @Bucks. https://t.co/2o5XI8oSHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rachel__Nichols: I feel like the settings on my dryer could also describe a large portion of the people I know... https://t.co/W1q11Yt9…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dellowhockey: Peak Corey Perry would be the guy holding the stick on the bench. https://t.co/T5oTHiPa0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davelozo: NHL referee as a doctor: "After reviewing your tests, in six weeks you will die...gest that gum you swallowed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wyshynski: Hello darkness my old friend https://t.co/cwaCSTPvai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Damn. I just realized I was sitting on this. Should have sent this hours ago. NO! No news on Happ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Just Stop all. I've watched so many season and have seen so many teams counted out early and  Whoa! Here they come. Roaring back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactjy ! https://t.co/FHufWe83Ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2008 is now haunting Canada Bundle, Uninsured for a reason = SUBPRIME?? https://t.co/KlPoTp0geF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Anyone else tired of former head of the Toronto police services board constantly crapping on Toronto police force? https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_j_roth: This is some Yogi Berra shit. https://t.co/EJ5djdtYYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne A chippy is also british slang for a girl on the side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kady Ha. You're the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronWherry @kady where are you. You are being outpaced here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP24 Why oh why couldn't they make it 23?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaHuseman @AaronNagler Both U.S. and CDN STYKES IF GVT Have this safety valve. It seems to work more quickly in U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessicaHuseman: A federal judge in Texas has ruled legislators wrote the 2011 voter ID law to be intentionally discriminatory. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elizabe86318411 @acoyne @kinsellawarren FCT CK Cnsrvtv, partial to responsible, accountable behaviour and reasoned, informed debate. Love animals, loathe ignorance and bad manners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theturner: "A fanatic is one who redoubles his effort when he has forgotten his aim" would serve well as Political Twitter's official m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey Sure there are - It's a Shit Storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JIMrichards1010 There are Canadian Artists. They are joining in for a song because they want to. Not being paid. Not displacing any Canadian Artists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JIMrichards1010 When did it become a bad idea to invite guests to a party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new hero! https://t.co/w0Q3uiOmHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should get out more https://t.co/Ym6kd6YyM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petridishes @ivortossell Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @odognine2: Jameson whiskey. Two shots. Happy birthday to my brother who would've been 45 today. One for you, one for me. https://t.co/k…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianNemett You guys are bullying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torquilcampbell I think it's all kinds of ok. We're having a party and like an guest wants to sing a tune. Doesn't matter where  they're from. join in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProudResister: Trump: I have tapes

Mueller: I have a team of 13 lawyers who prosecuted Watergate, Enron &amp; Mafia

Trump: I do not have…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @NBCSWarriors This is all kinds of brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace I will!  Tell me when is good I'm open next couple weekends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace Oh Oh! Ha. That was funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace Glad you smiled Ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just a little explicit. https://t.co/RroyxOxQKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgarland Now. RFN. We need the movie of Micheal Flynn. Charlie Kaufman will author.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DustinGiebel Now. RFN. We need the movie of Micheal Flynn. Charlie Kaufman will author.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now. RFN. We need the movie of Micheal Flynn. Charlie Kaufman will author.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@althiaraj When you finally realize there are no ethics it becomes so evident that your role is redundant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donlandrymedia Doobie Bros would be richly appropriate next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cboddy2727: @simmonssteve Not everyone can break hot dog stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Moment. He thinks to himself. I will run for the presidency and this is the type of president I will be #TRUMP https://t.co/49L6EXBdLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Great news! #MAGA https://t.co/pirHR7lAyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OR this https://t.co/NYsgSnEU6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronWherry Further proof of the axiom opposites attract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey Everything gets thrown off united. Fuel wouldn't give up its space for cheaper fuel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBarlow_ROB Agree See @acoyne  tweet re: the seeming disappointment in the @macleans article. #stormchasers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosieBarton @PnPCBC Nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLoneBellow: Our third album, Walk Into A Storm, comes out on Sept 15! Check out the first single and our new fall tour dates at http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_warmington @_scottreid @realDonaldTrump @Cabinet You were inspired by that? How do dead puppies make you feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_scottreid @scottfeschuk Zeppelin Trivia: DYK that the inner sleeve is a water colour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: Immortal: Election Night Special - Monty Python's Flying Circus https://t.co/kj0TRQzhfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne Seriously. Resonance of Churchill or Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne That is wit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: Then it’s unanimous. https://t.co/Hl21XkdLLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Ha! The winner says. But none the less I agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey It is the consequence of a break down in the structure of government. A step to anarchy is not far away. But not probable Hopefully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano This advice needs to be followed. This is how you become informed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alyssa_Milano: Tomorrow, let's not judge the Comey testimony by our own biased political ideology. Let's really listen and decide if it…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT @scottfeschuk @POTUS No. He has an idea that alarming to populace will make them susceptible to his extremist reactionary plans. And it will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @afhitcom: https://t.co/EstUXDiAVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See. This. This is the humanity the world seeks.  https://t.co/zvqrOUUx8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wyshynski: Jesus, Take The Whistle https://t.co/yIiSy29632]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to take the Bechdel Test. I can tell butter from margarine 10 outta 10 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: Toronto police invited to take part in NYC Pride March in uniform https://t.co/lqXTn95K8T https://t.co/doixiQtjLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne We all know how painful that can be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @halloates: We never liked you either! https://t.co/jikiqycEG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: Florida Keys residents debate merits of leaving vs. staying as #Irma churns towards Floridian coast https://t.co/NCHEep9K2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy Or maybe a Man who doesn't rest on protocol when the right thing needs to be said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ComfortablySmug: VIDEO: George HW Bush and Ronald Reagan in 1980 debate fighting over who would be more compassionate to children of un…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsDeanBlundell Yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne Nope. Jesus Complex. Or Liberal Patronizing Complex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlamwhite CIRCLE 9/28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AlgonquinPark  with my  DD guide. She taught me how to Portage, Cross Cut, C Sweep, perfect my J Stroke- Planned all  meals etc #3GRTDAYS https://t.co/PweU0p0zvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 I don't think so. But I know you can do a spot on Jerry Seinfeld.  Seriously and I know you've  heard this before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur Wait for it Wait for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primawesome It has to be a cannabisabilistic gang and things will go so much more smoothly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace You are a brilliant person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnneWallace If someone hands you " grapes from an old brown paper bag" make wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darth: "is this the line for nachos" https://t.co/4unqk4doRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darth @smell3roses It's gonna get longer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jilevin No. He is vulgar and disfunctional]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>