<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich people, old people, all got dreams. –Princess and the Frog May]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew it. Why did you lie to me? Did you think I was stupid that I wouldn't figure it out? –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is all my dreaming at an end? Or do you still wait for me, dreamgiver? –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope for a miracle. That's all we can do. –Jumba (Lilo &amp; Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only get a few good friends in this life who are devoted and true. –Piglet's Big Movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said to myself, "I'll put it away for him until he comes back. He's sure to come back". –Wendy (Peter Pan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realized that I miss you and I need you. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got a friend in me. If you got troubles, then I got them too. There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends follow you anywhere. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many of the things that seem impossible now will become realities tomorrow. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's still the same. There's just less in it. –Jack Sparrow (Pirates of the Caribbean)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some things were just meant to be, and that's you and me. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to stay close to you, no matter what, because I love you. –Naveen (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heal what has been hurt. Change the fates' design. Save what has been lost. Bring back what once was mine. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's magic if you close your eyes, so all you have to do is believe the impossible. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilo: "You think I can do it?" | Stitch: "We do together." –Lilo &amp; Stitch 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is the comfiest place to be. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing it takes to accomplish something is courage. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the story of you and me. From the very beginning, we were meant to be. –Tigger (Book of Pooh)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm afraid I can't explain myself, you see, because I'm not myself, you know. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you give love, you get love back. In other words, what goes around comes around. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When hearts are high, the time will fly. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one to tell us no, or where to go, or say we're only dreaming. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christopher Robin: "What do you like doing best in the world?" | Pooh: "What I like best is me going to visit you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you get scared, just be scarier than whatever's scaring you. –Thumper (Bambi II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought you were different. I thought you thought I was different. I thought. –Colette (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, the journey of a thousand miles begins with the first step. –Rafiki (The Lion King ½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only you could know the things I long to say. If only I could tell you what I wish I could convey. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Broadway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm like a shooting star, I've come so far. I can't go back to where I used to be. –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes bad things happen, and there's nothing you can do about it. So why worry? –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you lose someone you love, they never really leave you. They move into a special place in your heart. - Mrs.Frankenstein (Frankenweeni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To laugh yourself is to love yourself. - Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, there's one thing. They can't order me to stop dreaming. - Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A day without a friend is like a pot without a single drop of honey left inside. - Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if it's not everything I dreamed it would be? And what if it is? What do I do then? - Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can dream it, you can do it. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart has wings and I can fly. I'll touch every star in the sky. So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming of. - Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remember, I cannot be replaced. - Miss Piggy (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both of us will be forever you and me, forever and ever. - Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love is higher than the sky, deeper than the ocean, warmer than the sun shining down on me, quiet as a prayer. –Ariel's Beginning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without inspiration, we would perish. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tod: “We'll always be friends forever, won't we?” | Copper: “Yeah, forever.” –The Fox and the Hound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the difference between movies and real life. In real life, you don't always get a happy ending. –Jake (Hannah Montana)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ring, ring! Who's there? Destiny? I've been expecting your call. –Rhino (Bolt)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay to fight. Everybody fights now and then, especially best friends. But you got to make up fast. –Uncle Topolino (Cars 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just find a nice spot to rest, the sort of spot where thinking's done best. Now relax and put your mind to the test. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we take the time, time to understand each other, we can learn to make it right. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things aren't always what they seem. –Jafar (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you haven't found your talent yet, doesn't mean you don't have one. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just met you and I love you. –Dug (Up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we're together, clear skies are clear and I'll share them till where I'm less depressed. –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a friend, any day is an adventure. Any song becomes a symphony. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look inside yourself. You are more than what you have become. –Mufasa (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the clock reverse. Bring back what once was mine. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your eyes now before you get hurt. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your heart is in your dream, no request is too extreme. –Jiminy Cricket (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing up is such a barbarous business, full of inconvenience and pimples. –Captain Hook (Peter Pan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is gone. I must move on. –Pocahontas (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice’s mom: “You’re not properly dressed.” | Alice: “Who’s to say what is proper?” –Alice in Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love kindergarten. Best three years of my life. –Mike (Monster, Inc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughter is no enemy to learning. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/JZ6c9lIjNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow White: “And she fell in love” | Sneezy: “Was it hard to do?” | Snow White: “It was very easy.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer not only is a supplication for strength and guidance, but also becomes an affirmation of life. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curiosity often leads to trouble. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that time, never even knowing just how blind I've been. Now I'm here, blinking in the starlight. Now I'm here, suddenly I see. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we’re in each other’s dreams, we can be together all the time. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrayForKyleMassey http://t.co/SkL15yWrgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella remained ever gentle and kind, for with each dawn she found new hope that someday her dreams of happiness would come true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't leave me. I love you. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody has problems. Everybody has bad times. Do we sacrifice all the good times because of them? –Phoebe (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the morning comes and the sun begins to rise, I will lose you because it's just a dream. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love? Just a boy, meeting a girl under the right conditions. –The King (Cinderella)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could feel a love so strong and true. –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream is a wish your heart makes when you're fast asleep. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t stress over anything that you can’t change. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they win the weirdest family award: http://t.co/KoBmFUWyzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think you can just show up and tell me how to live my life? You don't even know what I've been through. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and me together, that's how it always should be. One without the other don't mean nothing to me. –Monsters, Inc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right things may seem wrong sometimes, or sometimes the wrong things may be right at the wrong time. –Jiminy Cricket (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sorry I bit you. And pulled your hair. And punched you in the face. –Lilo (Lilo and Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go and chase your dreams, you won't regret it. Anything can happen if you let it. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just I'm not sure I fit in here. There's no one I can really talk to. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's best to leave the past in the past. Do not look back. Only ahead. –Great Prince (Bambi II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world, too many people grow up. They forget. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never really know until you think, think, think. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen, and you can't do anything about it. –Timon (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always let your conscience be your guide. –The Blue Fairy (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends make any adventure better. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right things may seem wrong sometimes, or sometimes the wrong things may be right at the wrong time. –Jiminy Cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a world of my own, everything would be nonsense. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just I'm not sure I fit in here. There's no one I can really talk to. –Belle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's best to leave the past in the past. Do not look back. Only ahead. –Great Prince (Bambi II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world, too many people grow up. They forget. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never really know until you think, think, think. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen, and you can't do anything about it. –Timon (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always let your conscience be your guide. –The Blue Fairy (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is done cannot be undone, but what is left to be done should not be left undone. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i bet you didn't know this: http://t.co/IswZMl1vzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohana means family. Family means nobody gets left behind, or forgotten. –Stitch]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>