<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarolineCheese: They said it would never happen. But I am literally in the same pub as Graham Onions #cheeseandonions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New clubs purchased! #hackerscup http://t.co/o0IwJu8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[defoe #ahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets all laugh at #England !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart #Downing, ahahahahahahaahhahahaaaa!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Just hearing the Rebekah Brooks news. Neigh! Neigh! And thrice neigh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with @henrywinter, think that Paul Lambert would be a perfect fit for #villa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 Actually can we make it 1.30?. Don't want to get humped by traffic coming back in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 nice one. Say 2.30? Want a lift? Could be booking a time to have a new set of irons fitted. #oooph!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 real sweet! Whens your exam, fancy hitting range today? Might try to have a look at deer park as well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad about to let one go on the Montgomery course, Dubai  http://t.co/pwehzKei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to have been on the plane and missed unbelievable scenes. #sarcasm. Twitter feed a great read tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: The new Statham film perhaps lacks the subtlety of his earlier work but includes a back story and character development!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GaryJanetti: How come people who don't own a TV are always so fucking desperate to tell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballAid big Vaughan had an incredible game last year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Skiingmag: 7 Reasons to Ski in Jeans. http://t.co/sjrRBQO9 --- they way forward #ski #skiing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casual fish tank in the atlantis http://t.co/sIWLdSRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo http://t.co/ueQYTDb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Negredo is showing absolutely nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah @aspy87 Nah. Spain too strong for me. Hope I'm wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charltonbrooker: Just saw a bit of Geordie Shore. They all look like characters from Tekken. I don't understand this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bored of my 'professional' look in profile pic, I have successfully reverted back to #bluesteel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sethmorrison1: A must read, http://t.co/jzawNTW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLNews: Tune in now to listen MENA CEO Alan Robertson representing #JLL at the  "UAE Real Estate Debate"  http://t.co/cvXQXxq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah went to this bike shop in stockbridge last week. You need to see it. #paradise http://t.co/o21WP84e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: I have a sneaky feeling we're going to see John Terry lifting this trophy, whether England reach the final or not
#Eur ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah like climbing the rope in gym class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah Georgie T on #8outof10cats tonight. Just breathe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickjfrost Bet you would give anything for the #bbc back now! #euro2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: Pic I just found from training in chile last sept. Leg burner gs.  http://t.co/EcD8Rf2m http://t.co/SlUhikV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 aye they are shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 nah was at luffness with dad. horrific rough! wedges out only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 internship going okay, done fuck all diss tho. yeah still heading down the road. played worst golf of my life last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 They did for sure. but have a look at this. ships soon http://t.co/myihpttD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Bendtner fined €100,000 for ad on his pants. Porto fined €20,000 for fans racist abuse of Balotelli. Uefa need to open  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae maybe without the burden of lawrenson. he's pish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished 'racing through the dark' by @millarmind. Phenomenal read. Best of luck to him in olympics and tdf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pkelso: Brilliant interview with David Millar by @ianchad_tele. Note the comments on 'white knights' Redgrave &amp; Hoy http://t.co/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unreal finish #euro2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha #euro2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: Andy Caroll attacked that ball like it was a defenceless woman in a carpark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GoCardless: Supporters of St Mirren Football Club have been using us in order to buy their club for the fans through @10000hourslive ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @roryr1: Only 25 miles left to go after 975 miles done and £140 short of £3,000 for York Against Cancer. Please donate http://t.co/vO ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#passionateaboutpirlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a player Andrea #pirlo is. Was immense against Spain last week, class free kick to give #Italy the lead now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAnnaT: Lots of chat saying Andy Schleck is out of Tour de France with serious back injury... he's called a news conference for We ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zachbraff: If Steve Jobs looked like Ashton Kutcher he probably wouldn't have been hanging out in a garage with Steve Wozniak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@brewdog: Oh, did you see the BrewDog Graduate Scheme? http://t.co/GbADMhns” --- dream job for somebody!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoingBoing: Giant NES Zelda map wall-hanging: http://t.co/sxHE17qH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: A wee look back on the Altitude Festival, what a happy wee week that was
http://t.co/atnx5XJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonnyP77: #allezlesbleus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for a team that considers itself tough to beat, #Ireland's defending is appauling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GusTheFox: Giving a crow a Chinese burn behind a leisure centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wesley Sneijder || Amazing Training Ground Goal with slow motion || HD: http://t.co/1cg7rJ5U via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 #lollapalooza. I'm going to BBQ at Petes- u r all welcome. Reckon Im just going to drive back same nite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: Scotland is introducing gay marriage. We’ve never had anything against gay people in Scotland. Unless by gay you mean  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Whoever screwed up the North and South Korean flags must surely now do pennants...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae actually, I am in your home town and it's pretty bleak at the moment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a total #shitemare of a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 oooohhhh jimmmeeehhhh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 that is absolute genius!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLNews: Watch Alan Robertson, JLL MENA CEO talking about the Dubai Office Sector   http://t.co/qhIRJCCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nedboulting: Back home after the Tour, and another publicity caravan comes blaring down the end of my road. It's the torch relay. Bu ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @TeamSky, unbelievable performance over 3 weeks. #chapeau @thejensie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English commentary team on #TdF manage to get '1966' in there. #wankers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@millarmind: Ok, so this is a mad tribute: http://t.co/6ovnJprZ Thank you @CPbike.”---- this is awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkCavendish: Absolutely lost for words to describe the honour I've just received from L'EQUIPE as the best sprinter in #TourdeFran ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philmcnulty: Finally read the superb "A Life Too Short". Ronald Reng's book on Robert Enke. Moving, informative, sensitively written ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: Rangers fixtures for next season look like the itinerary of a beleagured 12th Century warrior attempting to unite the  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrazYoung: @brober87 @ThisisMannah Changed brake pads on bike tonight, reminded me of @u01naf6 making sure his were well oiled. #hed ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic, well done @millarmind !!! #chapeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a real job today #yaldi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbmcommercial: [Startup Blog] New post by @domdunnett - 8 things to consider when you incorporate your business http://t.co/NCsDnTuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HibernianFCClub: TRIBUTE: Club's tribute to Joe McBride http://t.co/Ihsg7yAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just lost a major interview for my interview from my fucking phone. #facepalm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thejensie: Ok that officially a very hard day, gotta admit. More than once i yelled at my legs" shut up legs" believe on that on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TetonGravity: Alright kids! Here it is: the trailer for our 2012 ski and snowboard movie The Dream Factory #tgrdreamfactory http://t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thejensie: A 1 liter bottle of chocolade milk, i really dig that stuff, its great for my soul and my head. And hey- a happy rider is ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thejensie: And hey- to give the diet experts among us a heartattacke,on our 200km transfer to hotel we stopped for petrol and guess  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeamSky: That pushes Wiggins' race lead out to 1' 53" over Cadel Evans while Froomey vaults up to third overall! What a performance! ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wiggins is absolutely destroying this TT... #tdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkCavendish: 41km TimeTrial done &amp; dusted. I can't TimeTrial very well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brewdog: So... Email from Heineken = they want us to stock their beer in our bars. Discussion = what our reply should be...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@BBCSport: Queens Park Rangers agree deal to sign Park Ji-sung from Man Utd for a fee in the region of £5m, --- NOOOOOOOOO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Puppy164: Oh dear. http://t.co/5pt80Sje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: We’re losing the war against drugs. Maybe it’s time to switch sides and join them in their glorious fight against hide ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 did you see DP is closed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCSport: Arsenal striker Robin van Persie announces he will not be signing a new deal at the club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 nah I didnae get it but booked a ticket for u anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 sorry pal can't tomorrow night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@u01naf6 nicely done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCNews: Lynsey Sharp selected for women's 800m at #London2012, ahead of Jenny Meadows, Marilyn Okoro, Emma Jackson http://t.co/OsSv ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLNews: Rio is one of the 30 cities recommended to have RE investment in the world. Find the reason in JLL conference,July 25http:/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrishoy: New lab record today for peak torque. More than a Ferrari Enzo. And I reckon I can carry more luggage that it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @k44rve: Check it out! This is what British Ski Racing has come to...
http://t.co/gtoWYLkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkCavendish you absolute beauty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iniesta deserves #Euro2012 player award. Best Spanish player by an absolute mile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paddypower: Morning! Huge day at Wimbledon today. Will Britain's Andy Murray win or Scotland's Andy Murray lose??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@aspy87: #aleover”. This]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J-League player scores from distance, celebrates by doing the Balotelli flex http://t.co/SxmfuRpt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>