<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I can lie to myself&amp; convince myself that there's an excuse for what you did, but that doesn't change the truth. I let you in&amp; you broke me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst thing about being lied to is knowing you weren't worth the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only when you hurt someone do they realize they truly love you, I guess that's why we fall in love with the people who break our hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know how to differentiate between the right and wrong, but I just lack self-discipline, because my parents are always around to nag. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A second chance doesn't mean anything if you haven't learned from your first mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about trusting your feelings, taking chances, losing and finding happiness, learning from the past, and realizing people change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the most significant moments in your life happen without you even knowing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The higher you build the walls around your heart, the harder you fall when someone tears them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was little I would autotune my voice by singing into the fan while it was on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it really worth loving someone who doesn t return back that love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone try to impress you it means he or she is already impressed by you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to let go of your ex to receive your next... you can t embrace the future while clinging to the past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we first met, I honestly had no idea that you would be so important to me. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love for you was bulletproof but you're the one who shot me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guy and a girl can be friends. But sooner or later one will fall for the other. Maybe too early, maybe too late, but maybe....forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To change the future, change your choices. Keep giving the same, keep getting the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't make a someone jealous if they never cared in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day you wait is another day you won't get back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge someone, make sure you look into the mirror, it's not like you're perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are worth every tear that I will cry and all the heartache I may feel. Loving you isn't easy, but you are worth having in my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to be contented, then you will start to cherish and eventually appreciate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even at midnight the sun was still bright, all because you kissed me goodnight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still standing here for one stupid reason. Call it love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels right to love you, yet the world says it's wrong for us to be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It crushes me so much to know that I tried my hardest to be perfect for you, and I still lost you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The things we find most valuable to our soul are the ones that are so far out of reach, it only appears in our dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday I think of you, every night I dream of you; No matter the time of day you're always on my mind...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hershey's Chocolate Company makes millions of kisses a day. I only ask for one from you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twinkle, twinkle little slut, name one guy you haven't fucked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's pathetic but I check my phone every few seconds... hoping you'll call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I want to talk to you, it is still pointless if I am the only one keeping up with the conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Facebook users, It says "What's on your mind" not "Dear diary..." Sincerely, why do you want to share that with + people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though it was never meant to be, it never hurts to smile at the memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone wants to do well, but not everybody have the determination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go a day without someone you can t stop thinking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought syrup was thick, until I saw your make up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate is easy. Now love, that's something that takes courage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never will I let someone take advantage of me and never will I change myself to satisfy others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never play leap frog with a unicorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading all these things about love makes me think of you, every single time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minute you stop caring what others think is the minute you start being yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you love someone you say their name different. Like its safe inside your mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't hate me 'cause I'm beautiful"...um we don't hate you 'cause you're beautiful, we hate you 'cause you're a cocky bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's at the end of the day while im laying in bed thinking of you, that it hurts the most, because you're not thinking of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[need a hotel? this site has great rates==&gt; http://t.co/ZZQW53qbQP - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it s over let it be over! Don t waste time thinking about the past, instead prepare for the future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've used up all my sick days so im calling in dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fighting back feelings I've never fought back before, because I'm not supposed to be with you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, I talk to other guys but I don't talk to them like the way I talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money can't mend a broken heart; that's love's job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst feeling in the world is knowing you've been used and lied to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone is strong enough to bring you down, show them you're strong enough to get back up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These break up and heartbreak songs are beginning to make sense again and I really wish they didn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often it's the little things that changes people's impression of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If perfect's what you're searching for, then just stay the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey. I just met you. &amp; you look craaaazy, what's your makeup brand? Crayola maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Sea World have a seafood restaurant I'm halfway through my fish burger and I realize, Oh my God.... I could be eating a slow learn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing you is my hobby, caring for you is my job, make you happy is my duty, and loving you is my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every little thing I try to do always reminds me of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I never live to see tommorow, will he know I loved him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading old conversations with you makes me realize how much has changed. I miss you, or at least the person I knew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a relationship, you can't just focus on yourself. You need to understand each other and PROVE that you're meant to be together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not length of life, but depth of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being committed in a relationship means keeping your word and being trustworthy. Say NO to heartbreak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You not always end up where you thought you were going, But you will always end up where you were meant to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can be sick and feel like crap, but just talking to you makes me feel so much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes time to understand a girl. But if she's really worth it, you'd take time to try and figure her out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roses are red, Violets are blue, he s for me, not for you, and if by any chance, you take my place, I ll take my hand, and smash ur face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept your defeats with your head up and your eyes open, with the grace of an adult...not the grief of a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple things become complicated when you expect too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the cutest, sweetest, nicest, greatest, most romantic...... insensitive jerk I have ever met.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to forget you, but thinking about you just hurts me to much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In almost every case, nothing is stopping you, nothing is holding you back but your own thoughts about yourself and "how life is."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A liar will always be a liar. They will only get better at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love doesn't mean being inseparable; it means you can be separated and nothing changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't try to fix what's not broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hesitating if you should send out a text because you want to talk yet you are afraid of being annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents expect us to treat them like how we treat our friends, but yet they never bother to treat us the same way back. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If our relationship was a book, I'd rip out the last page so it could never end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like everytime I take a step away from you, something is pulling me back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're lonely always remember that theres someone out there loving you more than words can explain&amp;smile just knowing that person is me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The saddest thing that can happen is when one falls in love while the other wants nothing more than friendship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you say "I love you", you are making a promise with someone else s heart. Try to honor it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would wait forever to be with you, but I'd prefer to spend my forever WITH you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you feel like giving up, remember why you held on for so long in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A best friend is someone you can run to when it feels like the whole world is chasing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laying in bed remembering a conversation in your head and thinking of what you could've said differently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when your stomach rumbles in a quiet place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I could live in your arms and spend every moment I had with you....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Him: I want you. Her: For Him: Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you wear glasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want, we don't get. What we get, we don't want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing when you're bored and walking alone when there's no one around you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's worse then having an enemy, is having a friend that doesn't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person who never learned to appreciate you is exactly the same person who will never learn to love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The things we find most valuable to our soul are the ones that are so far out of reach, it only appears in our dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't play with my heart for entertainment. Play with yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is everything okay?" N?o?,? ?e?v?e?r?y?t?h?i?n?g? ?i?s? ?n?o?t? ?o?k?a?y?.? "Yeah I'm fine."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was playing hid-in-go-seek with my heart, and then he found it.... And has had it ever since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being  and pregnant is not cute.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>