<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/wARBeuQO6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/BFeeQO5gqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/yM0NqqohuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/oNp1a6rAhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/1pkJn7nQ6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/D020iXzMGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/RnS58nZOiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/hk79b0E4Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/N8bgCX4hr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/nBkmSktE7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/VQI7aJ4Hk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/Oy3pDeK6xS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/vJsNDbmsb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/1eJtiWw0yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/krdsf4QRBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/vKdZ4KqVgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/FCzgaz87fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/6e1Qe5AQ1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/SMgrZhsref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/OpkUwr4ycK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/dFEXP9UWAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/nUsALMqx6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/AggbCMxAPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/ZrNXaaWiN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/vzeqKQl59X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/2beG84J6dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/u9vlmEt0OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/ixY4DvpJql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/2blpzBvHWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/CCH1h0hQ06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/8H9SO9Xzc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/znknMpyQHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/DVsxH6MbkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/Dr57FF2Hbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/pVu711CtcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/EDhF7PU7Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/1oZpzEMDoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/oiMFgT2Od5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/hUITv8w6WD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/tCck2wKZbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/G2BeDIjbeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/5SSltRCSpz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>