<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatbtrumps immigration plans mean for HR executives https://t.co/MQRUHIcmfy #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenHatke Sept is better than Oct :) btw -- my daughter (5) loves your books. Awesome bed time reading. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When does the next "mighty jack" come out? My daughter and I can't wait @BenHatke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[other thing changing in earnings calls: more ceo's talking about talent.  3 out 5 talk about importance of people @steverattner https://t.co/fHRyVvo78p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe "big brother" now; will become commonplace within 5 years; more than 40% of millennials ok with it  https://t.co/IbCTZ7jGaQ via @BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart move by e&amp;y.  Will create a better quality and more diverse workforce https://t.co/CynPOsWVUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEOs must take view.  Anti-Trump employees putting bosses in the hot seat https://t.co/vHcoNHbKoh https://t.co/SQc3nRJguG via @business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 key things for HR to pay attention to in 2017

https://t.co/YuUXusI7bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good roundup of company statements on trump immigration ban @jenamcgregor @RexHuppke https://t.co/SJE13lT3a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for CEB https://t.co/QWjvjOb1xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring freezes are rare these days – they limit employers’ ability to access needed talent &amp; demoralize workers https://t.co/IEf6utjbqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring freezes limit your ability to trade up on talent https://t.co/OTnGSKd00i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the time for companies to figure out how to address the CEO/median worker pay ratio. https://t.co/2ou7ZZRhds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seventy-three percent of executives expect the frequency of change to increase this year. https://t.co/WTKziPJcqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major changes in areas like public policy and technology will shape both employer and employees challenges in 2017. https://t.co/uUFJ3xv2J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about a rubber match in Jan of 18? @JoeNBC https://t.co/TG06oRQpXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National champs! https://t.co/XQmJoBaZYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smart insights from @jenamcgregor @Josh_Bersin @mchui on what to expect re talent in 2017 https://t.co/B4HbruSFQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good thoughts on importance of building capabilities to make perf reviews work rather than getting rid of them https://t.co/jkJK5iCEPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all of the news about CEOs mishandling culture, they are open to criticism from employees.  Can they handle it? https://t.co/B7s0biGOZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter can't wait until this is in the bookstores! https://t.co/ghF5Pz5o7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with increased focus on transparency of pay outcomes, executives must remember fairness of process is more important https://t.co/ULOQuEs8Fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court ruling saying pay differences ok if based on previous salaries at odds with other efforts to close wage gap https://t.co/RRiBf6Ypka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a new bot for slack is helping employees figure out which co-workers employees can date @LeahFessler          

https://t.co/HcW5Ymo76t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty smart by @adobe for getting all employees to think about flexibility rather force a few to ask @DonnaCMorris https://t.co/iWIHGgJh9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good step by @united to empower employees to solve customer problems, but will be hard to accomplish https://t.co/wXDU32CaRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest talent analytics question not about technology, about who has relationship with line client, HRBPs or talent analytics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting with 70 vps of analytics. great quote: data visualization makes graphs pretty, but doesn't tell a story - need better relationships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great round up of Sheryl Sandberg's new book: Option B.  Worth the read @facebook
https://t.co/IIHSUWOtnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desire to standardize leave policies across the country could backfire for the HR executives pursuing it
https://t.co/6IwnmH2v2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be one of the highlights of the year!  Looking forward to it.  #reimaginehr https://t.co/xnA3rwZnvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive work by some cool 5th greets @flinthillnews https://t.co/ubUgxqq2A6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[milennials are experience hoppers, not job hoppers

https://t.co/MF8M8UjN9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way to understand your true culture --&gt; look at your budget and rewards systems https://t.co/N4NxLEuEKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kentbabb Great to meet you.  Kroppb@CEBglobal.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good read on gap between hype and reality in talent analytics.  Lots of potential, but road is long https://t.co/dnqnQBtFXR @TalentEcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HG04SbFSES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox hires 3rd party to determine next steps for Bill O'Reilly https://t.co/gvtaUlMPSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has the trump administration impacted career perceptions? @balancegal https://t.co/LWBs3IVNsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No PR for your HR? = not winning for critical talent https://t.co/zrnNCnCIqh #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to@TalentEcon @FaKalman for having me join the podcast.   Culture most common talent issue CEOs talk about on earnings calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation with 30+ heads of talent analytics, realization: relationships more valuable than tech to make talent analytics works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J&amp;J realizes wellness not just competencies drive executive performance, very smart @JNJNews https://t.co/FJp3YvzIWO #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best CEO pay strategies are less about the form or even the amount of compensation and more to do with transparency. https://t.co/dIwThuyFTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall Street is up — and so are CEO salaries, now averaging $11.5M https://t.co/8ReWw74HbQ via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are experiencing career impacts from trump administration https://t.co/GMKGUO75Hq #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate America Will Keep Moving Forward on Diversity, Sustainability | CEB Blogs https://t.co/HHCxlg8cUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really nice round up of international womens day activities @lnicholas928  https://t.co/jDGXRds1H8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporations will increase focus and investments on D&amp;I during the Trump Administration https://t.co/xWQK0KiSus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat insights on how the sales roll continues to evolve @nick_toman https://t.co/pckKAz3itf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic roundup of Trump’s new travel ban means for employers https://t.co/GaxnwtOaem #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blind may become the social media tool that your employees use to talk about your company https://t.co/T2aHBKPFQ6 @teamBlindapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Capelli is half right when it comes to not generalizing about employee performance https://t.co/lGEYfPvLXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TalentEcon: Even as a call for greater #transparency takes hold in #business, some information is best kept secret. | https://t.co/Nb5E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expand your inclusion campaign to make it real from @lnichols928, nicely done @accenture @hp @elainekturville https://t.co/UrED1sknOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[boomers experience and job hop as much as millennials, myth busted  https://t.co/fhT2OvFUWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do new tech-based recruiting strategies discriminate against some groups? https://t.co/qbhz0dtg5H #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecommuters are older and wealthier than other employees @flexjobs https://t.co/udhVIWOwdQ #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartest insight on GE CEO succession plan, lots for other executives to learn from https://t.co/0SspvpXmQe #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You shouldn't be reading this until Monday -- The Summer Friday Is The New 'It' Perk Among Employers via @forbes https://t.co/9zanWbBfDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Netflix corporate manifesto makes their culture as clear as can be https://t.co/ArZwYTlKta #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Summer Fridays are a win-win for employees and employers https://t.co/4wJYfSfka5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody should leave work a little bit early today (if they can) :)  After all, it is a friday during the summer. https://t.co/JZTuP7PkMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Uber’s investors and directors, the leadership change shows the company is serious about culture https://t.co/e4YoXbakcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR is asked to find + develop leaders to fill future roles when they don't know what those roles will look like. https://t.co/G87Q7nZCDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To change a culture you have to be willing to spend money @CEBTalentDaily https://t.co/95zksJRQPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people might make it to 4:15 :) https://t.co/ww9M1tWWVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Friday around lunch time.  Just go ahead and take the rest of the day off! https://t.co/tkMMhOqOWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[should employers focus on performance or happiness (some say that the best employees are a littl unhappy) @drtcp https://t.co/B2H8S7Waso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Fridays are an extension of the growing importance employees are placing on flexibility &amp; work-life balance https://t.co/l6uEx0fvFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Fridays are an extension of the growing importance employees are placing on flexibility &amp; work-life balance https://t.co/senXGu1hNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Fridays are an extension of the growing importance employees are placing on flexibility &amp; work-life balance https://t.co/QzqnuX4hf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just be sure to get it to them before Friday afternoon. https://t.co/oluqMTk9Cb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formalizing Summer Fridays sends message to employees that their employer cares about them and work-life balance https://t.co/x81VErfASH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss early ticket pricing for ReimagineHR.  Secure today and join 1.000+ Senior HR executives! Offer ends 6/15 https://t.co/7PV2xEmJos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUMMER FRIDAYS!  We should all be doing this.

https://t.co/2IoIkcjhGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take these actions now if you fear robots are coming for your job https://t.co/J6Nyv8gfvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR must make sure they have the basics right on talent analytics @HarvardHBS https://t.co/hX4hcwuJP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing office politics has reached a brand new level, and it is costly.  https://t.co/nOKINP92Ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does AI + Person = better investor outcomes, @MerrillLynch thinks so https://t.co/E3XGLtposm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see impact when Gartner Employees and HR executives come together #gartnergives https://t.co/whbQFbGqfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women in sales hit quota as much, if not more, than men. But, they’re paid less. See more via @CEB_Sales research: https://t.co/PxhXTSkAud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great lessons shared about hiring people with intellectual disabilities #ReimagineHR #gartnergives @SpecialOlympics https://t.co/YPd3fxKOzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great give back moment. Packing meals for 50,000 at #ReimagineHR #gartnergives https://t.co/4VnVOBMcBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great learning and excitement at #ReimagineHR how change and future of work is impacting all employees https://t.co/V6dVthcd7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating importance of spirituality and nutrition in employee potential #reimaginehr https://t.co/yd0okieFL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The word "digital" on your resume --&gt; better job opportunities https://t.co/BKI29TUyMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is your CEO being criticized?  here is how to respond. https://t.co/B7s0biGOZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best advice on what to do if somebody at your co writes a google manifesto by @lnichols928  @talentdaily https://t.co/pK57RM4Cj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dropping $500 at the vet for my dog I wish I had this @ElaineKTurville https://t.co/0QV8PWFWaN #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough question for HR: what does freedom of speech mean in the workplace? https://t.co/UP2Gpmnpif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the workplace, you're not just a representative of yourself, but also a representative of the organization. https://t.co/5qR3vikUtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google memo writer in gray area on whether or not he can sue https://t.co/dCn7xDB7aF #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good roundup of the Google memo story from a variety of viewpoints  https://t.co/hZ3O8qdewM #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vacation is not a vacation unless you disconnect, but how do you do it? https://t.co/Czu00R0OP8 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your CEO is not talking about the policies of the day, your employees may walk https://t.co/7dNGxSYg8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundaymornexp Both!  The team at the show did a great job of making it easy and fun.  Great experience all around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't explain all hiring challenges, but see how opiod epidemic impacts labor force participation  https://t.co/m15vIooEWh @stevelevine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI -- here is the replay of the #summerfridays piece from CBS Sunday Morning https://t.co/bje2hQHzZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just waking up and not sure what to do? Watch https://t.co/x7mMx60Gbz to learn how to help your employees over the summer @conorknighton]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>