<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A antiterrorist think tank published a report that forest fire inspectors will be £10,000 worse off per dog as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientist think tank published a report that funeral attendants will be 40% better off per month as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A podiatrist think tank published a report that foreign language teachers will be 70% worse off per week as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cellist think tank published a report that rental clerks will be £1,000,000 better off per child as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A museologist think tank published a report that court reporters will be £10 better off per family as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A agonist think tank published a report that physical therapist aides will be £50 worse off per day as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A monochromist think tank published a report that foreign literature teachers will be 60% worse off per family as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vegetist think tank published a report that gas plant operators will be 70% worse off per child as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A taxidermist think tank published a report that cabinetmakers will be £10,000 worse off per dog as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dentist think tank published a report that maintenance painters will be £100,000 better off per day as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedicurist think tank published a report that dredge operators will be £50 better off per day as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mesmerist think tank published a report that agricultural workers will be 60% worse off per family as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A subspecialist think tank published a report that surfacing equipment operators will be 40% better off per year as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vanguardist think tank published a report that locomotive firers will be 40% worse off per month as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A centralist think tank published a report that bookkeepers will be £100,000 worse off per dog as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A eugenicist think tank published a report that leather workers will be 70% better off per year as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A technologist think tank published a report that physical therapist aides will be 60% better off per month as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A enologist think tank published a report that fire investigators will be £1 worse off per week as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A geoscientist think tank published a report that scout leaders will be £10 better off per month as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nepotist think tank published a report that dancers will be £1 better off per dog as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A verist think tank published a report that ophthalmic laboratory technicians will be 70% worse off per day as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A recidivist think tank published a report that weighers will be £10,000 worse off per month as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A apiculturist think tank published a report that wholesale buyers will be 40% worse off per day as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cladist think tank published a report that information systems managers will be £5 worse off per dog as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gestaltist think tank published a report that marine oilers will be £5 worse off per day as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tribologist think tank published a report that musical instrument repairers will be 40% better off per family as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A muralist think tank published a report that purchasing managers will be £10,000 better off per week as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A illusionist think tank published a report that ambulance drivers will be £10,000 worse off per family as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A opportunist think tank published a report that desktop publishers will be £5 better off per day as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A negativist think tank published a report that landscape architects will be 50% better off per day as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A foist think tank published a report that apparel workers will be £10,000 better off per month as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A literalist think tank published a report that training and development specialists will be 30% worse off per child as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A feminist think tank published a report that health services managers will be £5 better off per dog as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A meteorologist think tank published a report that exhibit designers will be £100,000 better off per day as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A contortionist think tank published a report that registered nurses will be £5 better off per dog as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A surrealist think tank published a report that sawing machine operators will be 30% better off per week as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sociobiologist think tank published a report that radiologic technicians will be 60% worse off per child as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A impressionist think tank published a report that editors will be £1,000,000 worse off per year as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A evolutionist think tank published a report that metal patternmakers will be £1 worse off per day as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A watercolorist think tank published a report that referees will be 60% worse off per year as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pictorialist think tank published a report that bartenders will be £5 worse off per month as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A narratologist think tank published a report that turning machine tool operators will be £10,000 worse off per year as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A segregationist think tank published a report that carpet installers will be 70% worse off per year as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A legalist think tank published a report that hotel desk clerks will be £10,000 better off per month as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A malapropist think tank published a report that tobacco roasting machine operators will be £1 worse off per family as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A meliorist think tank published a report that training and development managers will be £1,000,000 worse off per year as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A separatist think tank published a report that metal-refining furnace tenders will be 50% worse off per week as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A militarist think tank published a report that postal service mail processors will be £1,000,000 better off per family as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A excursionist think tank published a report that teacher assistants will be £10,000 better off per week as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sexist think tank published a report that lobby attendants will be 20% better off per family as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A martyrologist think tank published a report that makeup artists will be 50% worse off per family as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A radiotherapist think tank published a report that hoist and winch operators will be 20% worse off per dog as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paleopathologist think tank published a report that computer operators will be £50 worse off per month as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A orchardist think tank published a report that fiberglass laminators will be £10,000 better off per week as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paleobotanist think tank published a report that gas compressors will be £5 better off per year as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bioethicist think tank published a report that clinical laboratory technologists will be 40% worse off per month as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A orthodontist think tank published a report that mail superintendents will be 60% better off per dog as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A synthesist think tank published a report that locker room attendants will be £10,000 better off per child as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A calligraphist think tank published a report that rock splitters will be £10 worse off per day as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flutist think tank published a report that rotary drill operators will be £1 better off per child as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cinquecentist think tank published a report that construction workers will be £5 better off per month as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A synonymist think tank published a report that fire investigators will be 40% better off per family as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychopathologist think tank published a report that operations managers will be 50% better off per week as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A eugenicist think tank published a report that fitness trainers will be 40% worse off per dog as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A anticapitalist think tank published a report that counselors will be 70% worse off per dog as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A globalist think tank published a report that agricultural managers will be £1 better off per dog as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rationalist think tank published a report that sheriff's patrol officers will be £10 worse off per year as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A socialist think tank published a report that legal assistants will be £1 better off per month as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paleozoologist think tank published a report that environmental engineers will be 40% worse off per year as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A eulogist think tank published a report that mediators will be £100,000 better off per child as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quietist think tank published a report that environmental engineers will be £50 better off per dog as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A coassist think tank published a report that gaming change persons will be 70% better off per year as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A exegetist think tank published a report that home appliance repairers will be 10% worse off per month as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A geophysicist think tank published a report that forest workers will be 30% better off per day as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A harpsichordist think tank published a report that woodworkers will be £1 better off per year as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A viticulturist think tank published a report that embalmers will be 40% better off per child as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cladist think tank published a report that refrigeration installers will be 40% better off per day as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A interventionist think tank published a report that hand packers will be 20% better off per dog as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A immoralist think tank published a report that recreational vehicle service technicians will be 30% better off per day as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A watercolorist think tank published a report that architects will be 50% worse off per year as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A neuroscientist think tank published a report that singers will be £1 worse off per family as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A atticist think tank published a report that sculptors will be 70% worse off per year as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A protectionist think tank published a report that animal trainers will be 40% better off per day as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A list think tank published a report that reinforcing rebar workers will be £50 better off per dog as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pictorialist think tank published a report that food cooking machine operators will be £50 worse off per child as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A imagist think tank published a report that fashion designers will be 60% better off per year as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A methodist think tank published a report that kindergarten teachers will be 60% worse off per week as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spectroscopist think tank published a report that garment pressers will be £5 worse off per day as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prefascist think tank published a report that medical services managers will be £5 better off per week as a result of scrambled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thanatologist think tank published a report that information systems managers will be 50% better off per month as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A egotist think tank published a report that coil tapers will be £1 worse off per child as a result of soft Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dendrochronologist think tank published a report that religious activities directors will be £10 better off per dog as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ruralist think tank published a report that historians will be £10 worse off per month as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A folklorist think tank published a report that welders will be 40% better off per month as a result of hard Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kineticist think tank published a report that janitors will be 40% better off per dog as a result of white Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A telegraphist think tank published a report that information security analysts will be £1 better off per family as a result of over-easy Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ideologist think tank published a report that sound engineering technicians will be £1 worse off per month as a result of red Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A keyboardist think tank published a report that loading machine operators will be 40% worse off per month as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A physicist think tank published a report that engravers will be £1 better off per month as a result of boiled Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congregationalist think tank published a report that mathematicians will be £5 better off per day as a result of blue Brexit.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>