<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @glennbeck: Candy loves to police Romney!   As soon as he begins to win she shuts him down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michellemalkin: SNORT: Obama (whose auto bailout money went to China, Germany, Russia, Mexico &amp; UK) attacks Romney on outsourcin ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GatewayConf: "God doesn't come to take sides. He comes to take over." @drtonyevans #GC12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RickSantorum: More women have lost jobs under Obamanomics than men. Mr. President, struggling families need jobs not promises #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hughhewitt: Another undecided voter...this one bringing up W...sheesh #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @glennbeck: Did he just say NO CAP GAINS TAX?   Go mitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LegendQuotes: ”Once our minds are ‘tattooed’ with negative thinking, our chances for long-term success diminish” ~ John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andrewwommack: Religion tells us what we must do to be right with God. True Christianity tells us that we are right with God through ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @S_Wigglesworth1: God is everything the Word says He is. We need to get acquainted with Him through the Word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @craiggroeschel: RT: @JoyceMeyer: Unforgiveness always keeps score, but love keeps no record of wrongs. 1 Cor 13:5)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobhamp: Law is anything that provokes self-effort. Today's revelation can become tomorrow's law. He is the Author AND the Perfecter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @toddisberner: "You have reached the pinnacle of success as soon as you become uninterested in money, compliments, or publicity." - a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billjohnsonBJM: Big government is mans answer to sin. Prov. 28:2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckNorrisDid: Chuck Norris can order, and receive promptly, a McDonald's breakfast after 10:30am. From Wendy's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TexasHumor: There are two types of people. Texans, and people who call their Coke "pop".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MomentumConfere: Psalm 67:1-2May God be gracious to us and bless us and make his face shine upon us, that your ways may be known...  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspired_Ones: Adversity causes some men to break, and others to break records. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@theRealKiyosaki: Don’t be most people; most #people don’t achieve their #dreams.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRobertD: Be willing to learn to think thoughts that are not coming from your own head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@RickWarren: Don't expect power in speaking to people about God without speaking to God about people first.” Excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheRobertD: No matter what U have to figure out today it is nothing like the attached. Now aren't U Happy? http://t.co/6Hgu2MVFzr”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "Let failure be your teacher... Not your undertaker."- Zig #Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheZigZiglar: "You were designed for accomplishment, engineered for success and endowed with the seeds of greatness."- Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were designed for accomplishment, engineered for success and endowed with the seeds of greatness."- Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@NikWallenda: #nevergiveup! and follow your dreams. #theotherside”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "The foundations for a balanced success are honesty, character, integrity, faith, love and loyalty." -Zig Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you just gotta http://t.co/FfBZjsSCbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mashable: Dash Cam Captures Bear Getting Hit by Car, Walking Away [VIDEO] http://t.co/llVZNcMg1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Massive submerged structure stumps #Israel archaeologists -- what is it? http://t.co/PHOnRnXPmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mashable: .@Marvel's 'Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.' TV Show Debuts First Promo [VIDEO] http://t.co/bmOhvyGxAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KeithCraft: The devil hates God-ordained relationships that's why he works so hard to bring offense and division. Forgive and apologize…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @usnews: Dead Boston Marathon bombing suspect left the U.S. for 6 months last year during which he was in Russia http://t.co/otU5qSkiWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobertsLiardon: "@ricklgodwin: Patience is not the ability to wait, but how you act while you're waiting! #livebold"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastorbrady: Romans 5:20 (NIV)
But where sin increased, grace increased all the more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: The fastest way to change society is to mobilize the women of the world. -Charles Malik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "I had to pick myself up and get on with it, do it all over again, only even better this time." - Sam Walton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxLucado: Don’t take pride in well-crafted prayers. Don’t apologize for incoherent prayers.  Just be honest; honest to God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRobertD: A conclusion is the place where you got tired of thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BethanyCOM: Something is wrong when our lives make sense to unbelievers. -Francis Chan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PastorJohnHagee: Being a Christian doesn't mean you won't fall...it means Jesus will catch you when you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrMikeSmalley: Remind yourself continually what God believes about you.

#Confidencebooster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastorbrady: Lets get better at telling compelling stories rather than being angry protestors. We have good news to tell not agitate ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dennismccaskill: “Many of us are hunting mice – while lions devour the land.” ~ Leonard Ravenhill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_Organic thanks for the follow! #livelifeloudly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "How you see your future is much more important than what happened in your past."- Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@davidjlyons: When you stop chasing the wrong things... the right things have a chance to catch up” Good advice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "It's easier to explain price once than to apologize for quality forever.– Zig Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@skitguys: Money. It's a touchy subject...watch the Skinny on Tithing: http://t.co/80OlZz5cW9 #pastors #church” #funnybuttrue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When darkness overtakes the godly, light will come bursting in. Psalm 112:4 NIV  #TestimonyTuesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When darkness overtakes the godly, light will come bursting in. Psalm 112:4 NIV Gotta love that "bursting" part!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@GatewayPeople: "If God asks you to do something extraordinary, it's because He wants to do something extraordinary." (@PsRobertMorris)”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DrMikeSmalley: When You Talk About The Failures Of Others You Become An Enemy To The Grace Of God.   Excellent advice Mike! #Ouch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not where you begin but where you end that counts. - Ben Carson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to remain silent and be thought a fool than to speak out and remove all doubt.  - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "The greatest source of happiness is the ability to be grateful at all times."- Zig Ziglar” Live it and love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@stevenfurtick: The level of your impact will be directly proportional to the price you are willing to pay.  For you @TimmyKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyAndrews: “Do battle with the challenges of your present, and you will unlock the prizes of your future.” #TravelersGift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Fit_Motivator: Wake up with DETERMINATION. Go to bed with SATISFACTION.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44 years ago today!! I still remember watching it on TV. Amazing !! #Apollo11 #ManOnTheMoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JoelOsteen: You have too much in you to stay where you are. Your destiny is too great to get stuck.” Amen to that! #letsrockit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome speaker at the Awaken Now Conference, @AndyAndrews. Great stuff! Get his book The Travelers Gift! Then get 20,000 days &amp; Counting b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome speaker at Awaken Now, Andy Andrews. Great stuff! Get his book The Travelers Gift! Then get 20,000 days &amp; Counting by @TheRobertD!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out with Ben Carson tonight. Good stuff! #AwakenNow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More attended his ticker-tape parade than had honored Lindbergh after his triumph. What are u doing with your mistakes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[, climbed into the cockpit of his plane, and made for the skies, bound for Los Angeles. He landed in ....Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this day in 1938, a 31-year-old aviator named Douglas Corrigan walked out onto the tarmac of an airfield in Brooklyn, New York and...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not enough time in your day? Watch this brief slide show : Got Time http://t.co/fbs5Pz0U7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@AndyAndrews: If you want a life that is wildly outside of average, you cannot act or think the way that other people act and think.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRobertD: RT @thinksimplenow: “Only those who will risk going to far can possibly find out how far one can go.” ~T.S. Eliot
#Quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't be a spectator, don't let life pass you by. -Lou Holtz"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of my own personal challenges...What are YOU waiting on? http://t.co/FuSyYUBy6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@RickWarren: Where the grass is greener, the water bill is bigger. #EnvyIsStupid”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your history determine your destiny. #livelifeloudly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@RickWarren: Talent that sits on the shelf rots. Use it or lose it.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is never a better measure of what a person is than what he does when he's absolutely free to choose. - William M. Bulger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@rileystephenson: You're not a victim. No matter what you've been through, You have a history of victory! #BestDayEver” #GoodStuff !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out with Mom #saycheese http://t.co/HfGWgQjMoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OMGFacts: Bill Clinton sent a total of 2 e-mails during his presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanineTurner ..sounds just like the KGB  before the 1991 wall came down... 1 in 4 in Russia was a KGB informant !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOST EGYPTIAN PYRAMIDS? http://t.co/Q8jCm3uqVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheRobertD: It’s not too late to make an impact today. What can YOU do to make today better?” Make a decision to be a positive influence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ABombshell: You know your kids are awesome when you think, "How much longer until they wake up from their naps? I'm ready to play!" #il…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TulsaDJones: Admiring a persons accomplishments yet fail to review how they treat the behind the scenes team may find us admiring a sho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favorite places in the world! #bbq http://t.co/02YSGVChKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@jerrysnider: A dream developed never leaves you where it found you.” Good !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the friendly skies again.... http://t.co/zGOADFPSNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When obstacles arise, you change your direction to reach your goal, you do not change your decision to get there." -Zig Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SuriTV - An Early Look http://t.co/blhoADSSoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have friends in overalls whose friendship I would not swap for the favor of the kings of the world.   - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1John534 absolutely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admit it. I like Windex. http://t.co/r48OAdIz7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Success is going from failure to failure without losing your enthusiasm.” ~ Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever have engine trouble and you're the problem? http://t.co/ZhApsTgidJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is the true definition of Living Beyond the Ordinary! http://t.co/drDG0leUDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got weeds?? Pull em! 
http://t.co/qUm1vNAOQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I in a field of weeds? On a HOT Texas day?
http://t.co/LULIw39bP5 http://t.co/PNjFSkqKZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weeds by Gene Bailey ...out standing in a field...http://t.co/qUm1vNAOQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost Arrested in Moscow! by Gene Bailey http://t.co/83Gz9jgNAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true! I was almost arrested in Moscow! Watch this and don't make the same mistake I did! http://t.co/wQhTYaTkgb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>