<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/pcPLcql05g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/UajLzArXt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/JGtedTTP2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/S45KH7q6mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/IfdJcHC0oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/SMiwblDHTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/DbjRycUCol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/kqqDCl4J3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/nNHjYRcuCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/BVVMMy40ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/JND0rZIhex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/Vftf7dY1ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/ldmkFWzD8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/KeYgAeJrOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/dfUlb1B9o8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/QEXj78Scmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last words to the 'Star Spangled Banner?' 'Play ball!' - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/DwoMT9lfkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/1xQAzVrkXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/dlg2otDrFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/XKUxtcfXbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/trAQbs3Ksc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/kQXSvUvnZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/CO7U1GCWkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/FCTRJnK4My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/uwMoy03lDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/sySWMYeAa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/mVayC3g5o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop earning when you do what you love. - Asha Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/lT7HLVzLeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/BccxRo2uEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/w3S67b3DnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/O02sMT9QLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/t9uYk96vhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/8EfRJT95ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/7HRGjWR4A6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/g7QpZfKvxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/tENxqpUPRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/41dUZoJcGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/y59OueTnx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/mw3CnPQGLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/xD8wLo5BDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/W0P4vVI3VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/5DTWrFPtrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to http://t.co/JOvm1EKUqq  http://t.co/aQ1zKLuqzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/tkpMBbdubo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/Oe5Kb2UbjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/H3m3QUC8Rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/31hfPr0KUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/c5qQS510hG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/xl0dGwbCYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/aHtDImWqfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/r5eu9CC7XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/PIy0l1JuX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/6HmNLfuOSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/jWetOcZEAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/TY83Rp5NQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>