<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ZAVyJfLwg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/yR9pq1tCRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/iMVdK3eUlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/Nshdu6ZvSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/1TP5gh2pR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/px6rPQMRwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/6iBSsKYOOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/UGTYvtn1Dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/GYnmtedIpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/qWCcNf2wAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/exPzrukWgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/DKGLFrdRMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/mWl53s889P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/6sSiJxwoJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/bpARDe0Zfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/RIvlH4KtES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/zqyXlhnqYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/9XxbJdluG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/fN3t4xnGtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/iGBUoCiKMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/VLcWUdSTbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not really interested in making money. Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/erwJrrm3IL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/yr2IzFAWt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/2wXGOZN4BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine is God's way of saying you're making too much money. - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/GFdHmiDMxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/VUptFlfJPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/dL1ylO50Nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to http://t.co/XNpXHUJ26N  http://t.co/HAVeH3F5Rz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/wAQWm3yNa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/x9i1d095rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/uYOooOn6z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/aqM9oHnnXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/j7yrz6NTGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/nfiIgFr6sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/1TnHLhwrPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/XQs6o9xVKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/GWpYiaYFMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/mo76JllUf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/mRsZGmjsBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/0dcIatq7jP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/DvH8AGZyYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/RAHVEyrgix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/lgoWYEBxRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/JwOTbNYTvx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>