<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't mean you can't have those jobs and just be a partisan hack, but it's a pretty good indicator of intellectual firepower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because those are serious jobs that involve grabbing with major consitutional and legal issues. Unlike, say, blogging. https://t.co/87yklXzWmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billbarnwell: The Browns are +5 in takeaways today. Since the Browns returned to the NFL, teams with a turnover margin of +5 or better…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan Eh. In 90% of cases these boards are for photo-ops and fundraising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AstorAaron: Remember when Bill Clinton said, "It's the economy, stupid!"? He was talking about Presidential elections, not midterms. Pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPA_94 I repressed that. Though I will defend the tan suit criticism until the day I die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video is badly made and pretty stupid, but wow do I relate to it. https://t.co/cW15qQFgzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gasp! The biggest scandal since John Kerry ordered a cheese steak with real cheese instead of gross Cheese Whiz. https://t.co/rjRJtcWrgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjane87: Perhaps one of the biggest challenges facing conservatism is that the ideological underpinnings of the movement as we know it…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad microtargeting from @GinaRaimondo. The "urban 4 year old" voter segment doesn't usually turnout in primaries. https://t.co/HDEFMdA9ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McKeeForRI: #TeamMcKee is hitting the streets getting everyone ready to vote on Wednesday. Our crew is out all across Rhode Island toda…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDon @SenWhitehouse Endorsements don't vote, but this late surge in support — especially from a staunch liberal — are a good indicator of momentum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there another referee strike? #GarbageCall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brajadurai This is almost as bad as your iced coffee opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonahNRO: There’s no way they were picked last because they were lazy kids too? https://t.co/nCdiCQ5ak0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One reason — at every stop, the driver refuses to move unless people are behind the white line. The train is so packed people can't get on and off, much less move. Either don't let people on or don't enforce that! @MBTA #OnlyGovernment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's taken the @MBTA 45 minutes to go from Grigg Street to BU East. That's less than two miles. And people wonder why @Uber does so well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CohenAtTPPF: The quintessence of 2018, laid bare...

https://t.co/9JicQrd5Mm https://t.co/VpEHmBS6sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForecasterEnten: The base of the Democratic Party is women. It's increasingly minority women. They're making their voices heard this pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottieRock28: Devil: “You can have your Eagles Super Bowl win, but it’ll come at a price.”

Philly Sports Fan: “Eh, it’ll be worth it…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterBeinart: The lesson of @AyannaPressley's extraordinary victory: Even in Tip O'Neil's old district, all politics is now national ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColinAYoung: The MA race for governor:
In this corner, a guy who grew up in Needham, served as state budget chief and then ran a health…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenDezenski Bad night to be a man in Democratic politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbernstein: In addition to anything else, recent #mapoli elections have shown that Dem primary voters in Mass. these days will pick a w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who could have seen this coming? https://t.co/fwDJ4m8RXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've said before, the transformation of the Senate from a deliberative body to a confirmation mill is one of the unexplored stories of contemporary politics. https://t.co/1aqwLfoeca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebelpioneer I think that's what semi-formal means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my most left-wing opinions is that it's sickening to watch a successful, intelligent person forced to defend the actions of the man who, for all his faults, she loves. https://t.co/1LUaO02Pmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: Sears' CEO is a real life Bond villain who only meets with his subordinates via video chat and forces departments to compete for funding quarterly. Shockingly, this hasn't been good for the long-term health of the company. https://t.co/ooNaExbXrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I choose to think Arielle is actually a Machiavellian operator who understood how to court elite support while dealing with an apathetic middle school electorate. https://t.co/QCyDFZwfHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BridgetPhetasy: Both the extreme left wing and right wing groups of privileged American adult children playing out their little culture…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ Your forbearance is nothing short of saintly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ So I'd be excluded? I see how it is Liana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nate_Cohn: I don't think there's a ton of evidence to support this yet, but I am starting to wonder whether we're going to be really st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen First, I don't think that has correlation to whether they want to be in class or not. 

Second, naturally, I take the much more cynical view that this, like most protests, is about feeling good and spending time with like-minded friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen What percentage of teenagers do you think would rather hang out with their friends than be in school? Over/under 80%?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen Actually, there's a model for that — anti-Vietnam college students scheduled "teach ins" to inform their more apathetic classmates about the flaws of American engagement in Indochina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen Avoiding something you don't want to do, like go to class, is the laziest form of protesting. If they somehow went to school more it would actually mean they care about the underlying concern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High school students protesting by leaving class is like me protesting by going to a bar. https://t.co/QhVQPxJFAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I like about this is how he blends wannabe-tough guy patois with his decidedly mild mannered love of golf. https://t.co/W03GLQkMRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @POLITICO_Steve: Why are they arguing about what I believe is a prerequisite to be governor of Illinois? https://t.co/XgdENIKpBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanTrende: (a) This is way past the point of diminishing returns, such that it probably wouldn't matter if he raised another $100M dow…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Russmoore713: The Rhode Island pension fund was lower than this 9 percent. The RI Pension fund is basically The Baltimore Orioles of in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bland, gauzy positives and tepid criticism of the incumbent aren't the way to go when you're a 100:1 long shot with a massive fundraising disadvantage. https://t.co/W3bXb6dMQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DBJmoney: Read my story to learn more about what these companies are concerned about and how tariffs might impact Colorado’s economy:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LianaPatricia_: If you are one of those people whose biggest worry this month is kids who aren't from YoUr NeIgHbOrHoOd trick-or-treati…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith And I don't think it's a wave election if the party loses seats in the stronger chamber. Whether fair or not, the constitutional architecture of our politics makes it hard to be competitive if your message alienates the voters who live in most states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith Elections are the only mark-to-market indicator in politics, so we'll find out soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I think that's limited to upscale, educated white women, aka House of Representative map voters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith At least anecdotally, Republicans I know (in liberal Massachusetts) are enraged by this as much as Democrats were enraged by Trump's election and BK's confirmation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I think you're really underestimating how much, regardless of the merits of the position, Republicans believe BK was a victim of character assassination by both cynical Democratic operatives and the insane Feminazis. I could be in a bubble of politically engaged people, but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I think in both states base mobilization is enough for the GOP candidate to win, even if they lose the lion's share of swing voters. That's why I think Kavanaugh will end up being a boon in the Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I'm skeptical the electorate HH is facing is that different from the one faced by Donnelly, CMC, and other Trump-state Dems. Do think Florida is a different story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaBogen You have a nickname, it's Jules. Because I use and have impeccable taste in all things, it's the only option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForecasterEnten: I see we've learned nothing from 2016. Dean Heller is down by like a point in my forecast. He's down by less than that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence that Kavanaugh will end up being a political fiasco for Democrats. Remember — that party has never won an election when cultural issues were preeminent. https://t.co/zk1SnKqFeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that Democrats have never won an election that's revolved around cultural issues. https://t.co/tRqRyo9PPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanTrende: Because long-term strategies in politics are useless.  No one has any clue what our politics will look like in 12 years, le…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the website that lets people name and shame adulterous (with no regard for accuracy,) this is the internet at its worst. https://t.co/NHh3V8WwKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cc: @raylehmann @DCameronSmith Apropos of our thread last week. https://t.co/v6tXjNwv7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TedNesi: “The last time more than half of eligible voters turned out for a midterm election was 1914” https://t.co/gq3iSrkvy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattGlassman312: Tons of partisan believes their side isn’t willing to sink to the ruthless level of the opposition, and that’s why the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I've always been skeptical of a "two track" outcome where Dems win the House but lose more than one Senate seat. That doesn't fit with my view of modern midterms as fundamentally nationalized referendums on the party in power. I'm now a lot more comfortable accepting that CW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadioFreeTom: This is a terrible response, because it cedes that courts are now our lawmaking bodies, and then argues for defying those…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith Maybe it's just static and there will be regression to the mean next week, but I'm much more confident in predicting a split-chamber result (which I've been leery of given the fundamentals of modern partisan politics) than I was before Kavanaugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I agree re: Manchin. I just also think there's been a demonstrable increase in Republican partisan engagement, which all but rules out a 2010-style wave, which requires winning swing voters plus a turnout differential to win in unfriendly territory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I don't think the red-state Senate movement and small dollar donation surge occurred independent of the Kavanaugh hearings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonallendc: Republican leaders during Tea Party efforts to disrupt town halls, scream at lawmakers at the Capitol: Yay, democracy!
Repu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann @DCameronSmith I'm skeptical that backlash will extend beyond upscale, educated suburban women who are concentrated in blue-State CDs. It'll take an election, the only mark-to-market indicator in politics, to find out, but right now this looks like a big short-term and long-term GOP win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonHaidt: if you're wondering why American democracy seems to have decayed so quickly, the graph below gives a big part of the story. W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Senate's transformation from a deliberative body of thoughtful, albeit self-important, legislators to a partisan confirmation mill is one of the underreported stories about 21st Century politics. https://t.co/Ho3IZuk4nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emzanotti: Wait why is she dressed like the villain from Raiders of the Lost Ark https://t.co/6D8IaxyTpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajjaffe: No one should treat a senator like this, regardless of the vote. It’s a position that should still receive some respect &amp; reve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ @SyedRAkhtar You really underrate the amount of work that goes into golfing and drinking with a client or pol. #JustSaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ @SyedRAkhtar He's enjoying his position as capital, exploiting the labor that you don't own the product of. Not his fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart political analysis, whatever your opinion about the merits. https://t.co/sEWmsK6RCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: 100% agree that is the equilibrium we are headed towards post-Garland. https://t.co/PhvSdnawR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aseitzwald: Per capita, no one can touch Rhode Island politics for weirdness:

A 3rd party gubernatorial candidate was just arrested wi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TedNesi: A true test of “no such thing as bad publicity” https://t.co/mB6pfzdx1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: If he's confirmed this weekend, not sure the high lasts four weeks. Dem voter anger over it is far more likely to. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbarro: 1) If the prior background checks contained the goods, we’d have heard about it last week or earlier.
2) If the prior backgroun…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unclear if the trend is sustainable for the next 30 days unless the hearings drag on, but it looks like Kavanaugh is a boon for Dems in the upscale Romney-Hillary CDs, but a toxin everywhere else. https://t.co/dZWCfuO4Ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanCassino: After I gave a talk last week, a woman told me that she'd like to participate in polls, but didn't know how to tell incomin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KennethBaer: In the postwar era, we have never won an election that centered on cultural-national issues. Economics/health care is how…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KennethBaer: Democrats wanting to make this election a referendum on Kavanaugh should recall 2016 when we successfully made the electio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Americans remembered the degree of venom directed towards a young Chelsea Clinton during her father's Presidency. She was called ugly not just on Rush Limbaugh's show, but in a New York Times editorial unfavorably comparing her to Al Gore's daughter. https://t.co/3vQob8JdZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: Some will view this as Trump showing lack of control. But to me it is consistent w/his strategy: rather than outreach to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This trend is garbage and the clearest sign yet of rampant cultural decay. There, story written. https://t.co/AlaNr0W8fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megLhowley Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NateSilver538: Yeah, people are getting this wrong.

Schumer restoring the 60-vote SCOTUS filibuster would likely be a cynical, tactica…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joel_Searby @nealjsimon @CSODear @walkerforakgov @GregOrman @HayesForMaine @OzForGovCT @EliasonCongress @mgrohman @StevePoizner Those are fair, especially the third since it's a results metric instead of a process metric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joel_Searby @nealjsimon @CSODear @walkerforakgov @GregOrman @HayesForMaine @OzForGovCT @EliasonCongress @mgrohman @StevePoizner When will you be? And if you won't be this cycle, what should we judge you on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joel_Searby @nealjsimon @CSODear @walkerforakgov @GregOrman @HayesForMaine @OzForGovCT @EliasonCongress @mgrohman @StevePoizner If you don't want to be judged on outcomes, what does victory look like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joel_Searby He's not seriously or credibly able to do anything but be a spoiler candidate. American politics isn't configured for third party candidates, it's configured for outsiders who commander an existing party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nate_Cohn: I could cobble together a lot of admittedly fragmentary evidence to argue that the GOP had a good weekend of polling post-Ka…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't a serious, credible candidate for US Senate. No statewide third party is unless they're a) famous like Ventura b) liquid wealthy like Bloomberg or c) a former office holder like Murkowski. https://t.co/68DouEWD4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LilyMasonPhD: This is a good example of ideology functioning as an identity rather than a set of policy positions. https://t.co/uODBWEa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianaPatricia_ She's running.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: Probably the biggest cloud still hovering over Democratic hopes for '18 are the continued signs of low engagement among…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: In 1984 Gingrich famously complained that Reagan wasn’t doing enough to polarize the electorate; more than any other sin…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>