<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. plans to rewrite rules that impede self-driving cars: The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) is moving ahead with plans to revise safety rules that bar fully self-driving cars from the roads without equipment like steering… https://t.co/L1fskosGVC https://t.co/qW2CCmq7Zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: BNYM Technology’ has a mission to provide our business partners with technology based solutions that enhance their ability to be successful through world-class software solutions maintained on a stable and secure… https://t.co/JwKY3tUNu6 https://t.co/nBrXfSKpoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square pushes into consumer lending with installment payments service: Square Inc , the payments company founded by Twitter Inc Chief Executive Jack Dorsey, has launched a new service that enables customers of its small-business clients to pay for… https://t.co/qP3gsFknnF https://t.co/khQEhEMUec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric airplane startup Zunum chooses Safran engine turbine: Aircraft manufacturer Zunum, backed by Boeing Co, will use an engine turbine from France's Safran SA to power an electric motor for the hybrid regional airplane it aims to bring into service… https://t.co/20gQ3f7zFs https://t.co/GoYXXYceTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple, Amazon deny Bloomberg report on Chinese hardware attack: Apple Inc and Amazon denied a Bloomberg report on Thursday that their systems contained malicious computer chips inserted by Chinese intelligence, statements from the tech companies released… https://t.co/TN2mMgBrgd https://t.co/OmI3JTcTSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota, SoftBank in first-ever alliance, target self-driving car services: Toyota Motor Corp and SoftBank Group Corp are teaming up to develop self-driving car services, signaling deepening alliances between top automaker and tech firms as the global… https://t.co/9Ag7sBNFqy https://t.co/u4j9bz6DvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Careers Center | Java Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/5yx2ESUWuI https://t.co/NiqfDwEGLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Information: Software Developer – ******* Job Email Opening Title Software Developer – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon University is an Equal Opportunity Employer/Disability/Veteran. Description What We Do: At the SEI… https://t.co/xn6tTZ9nGa https://t.co/TiSOpBz6zK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position Title Software Developer Entry Level: Location US-PA-Mechanicsburg Requisition ID 2018-11296 Business Area Software Category/Discipline Information Technology/Software Development Position Type Permanent employment Local Unit &amp; Position… https://t.co/BnxbJs1q40 https://t.co/m8ecSAeqYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer management software firm Glassbox raises $25 million: Glassbox, an Israeli provider of customer management technology, said on Thursday it raised $25 million in a round of financing led by Updata Partners, a software-focused growth equity firm… https://t.co/lKsnmQaotI https://t.co/CaY5DyTTL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/K2ATNqAdFJ https://t.co/iLafab6Tng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota, SoftBank to partner in future car technologies: Toyota Motor Corp and SoftBank Group Corp said they would team up to develop new transport services, adding to a slew of deals aimed at sharing costs and securing expertise in technologies which… https://t.co/kwlcaEDYW3 https://t.co/zkpPti68Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Testing Analyst (Unix/Linux/ Shell Scripting): Job Description – Develops testing plan scenarios for complex unit, process, function, integration and acceptance testing with a focus on automation – Responsible for definition, planning… https://t.co/mYACAl6d3p https://t.co/XP6Kb733cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SK Hynix boosts investment in new South Korean chip factory: SK Hynix Inc said it would invest 20 trillion won ($17.8 billion) in a new memory chip manufacturing plant opening on Thursday in South Korea, about 29 percent more than originally budgeted. https://t.co/YbeWzjWgzw https://t.co/lLj0OMnqzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer/ Process Engineer: Location: Wilkes-Barre Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers Jobs CNC PROGRAMMER/ PROCESS ENGINEER US – PA – Wilkes-Barre Job Description * Generate CNC programs with quality design standards and… https://t.co/AP8l9ixxFn https://t.co/uTBr5artJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota, SoftBank to team up in self-driving and other technology: sources: Toyota Motor Corp and SoftBank Group Corp will announce a partnership on automated driving and other technology on Thursday, sources with knowledge of the matter told Reuters. https://t.co/p6JhoFQwl9 https://t.co/YVYXrrnbPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota, SoftBank to partner in self-driving and other technology: source: Toyota Motor Corp and SoftBank Group Corp will announce a partnership on automated driving and other technology on Thursday, a source with knowledge of the matter told Reuters. https://t.co/aW6UiRPerz https://t.co/e3H9hlEksW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota, softbank to announce partnership in self-driving, other technologies: source: Toyota Motor Corp and SoftBank Group Corp will announce partnerships on automated driving and other technologies on Thursday, a source with knowledge of the issue told… https://t.co/akDDObgp4Y https://t.co/Ph2EDoDdok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook, responding to lawsuit, says sex trafficking banned on site: Facebook said on Wednesday in response to a lawsuit accusing it of not doing enough to protect users from human traffickers that it works internally and externally to thwart such… https://t.co/PaYrc9jDja https://t.co/jvOyPMHXEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JAVA Developer Lead: Senior JAVA Developer Lead Ref No.: 18-39820 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Position:https://t.co/uhLOGZuV7Z developer Lead location:Pittsburgh PA 12 Months contract Job Description Java, J2EE, Spring MVC, Spring… https://t.co/9vZGnZU2zR https://t.co/4nd72RA8el]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. judge says China's ZTE violated probation; extends monitor's term: A U.S. judge on Wednesday issued an order finding that China's ZTE Corp violated probation imposed in March 2017 when the company pleaded guilty for conspiring to evade U.S.… https://t.co/YT07DqSDQs https://t.co/qKcheOkn8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director Business Intelligence and Analytics: Job Description Harte Hanks is a global marketing firm that specializes in helping brands win attention, build trust and earn loyalty in an ever-changing world. Experts in defining, executing and optimizing… https://t.co/UEi2MYIpbE https://t.co/YLJ3hd4jkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. judge says China's ZTE violates probation; extends monitor's term: A U.S. federal judge in Texas on Wednesday issued an order finding that China's ZTE Corp violated probation imposed when the telecommunications company pleaded guilty in 2017 to… https://t.co/DRbOqWQ3Ju https://t.co/jg3YFiKvxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Cloud Systems Engineer III: Job ID : 73216BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description DevOps Cloud Systems Engineer III Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. is the world leader in serving science, with revenues of more than $20 billion… https://t.co/toRBYeMEL6 https://t.co/VIbFbRZ5Or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Developer (Java REST Web Services): Securities Data Service is a provider of reference and market data to many business lines within BNY Mellon. ‘ As part of our Technology Roadmap, we are focused on the modernization, re-engineering, and delivery… https://t.co/t8JlcHUHpR https://t.co/UnVf6vcdll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst II- Rev Cyc: Job Description Job Title: Operations Analyst II- Rev Cyc Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Revenue Cycle Department: Rev Cyc Systems Support Location: 2… https://t.co/kchJ0IPif8 https://t.co/2Xng2rfoIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Data Warehousing: Software Developer – Data Warehousing job description | Excell – blog – NewsRoom – Contact – Login – Investors – INVESTOR DASHBOARD – PRESS RELEASES – STOCK – ONLINE INVESTOR KIT – SEC FILINGS – CORPORATE GOVERNENCE… https://t.co/PQx80ac7pF https://t.co/Q7R6hZyYik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer Enterprise Content Management APS: BNY Mellon is the world’s largest investment company.’ We serve exceptional clients, many of the world’s leading investors. They rely on us to connect to opportunities in hundreds of markets across… https://t.co/urh2RDpBX5 https://t.co/YpM2p6VW0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet provider groups sue over California net neutrality rules: Four industry groups representing major internet providers and cable companies filed suit on Wednesday seeking to block California's new law to mandate net neutrality rules. https://t.co/VaMAYdrEAx https://t.co/v1RpVEIy5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart caption glasses refocus the action for deaf playgoers: For all his adult life keen theatergoer Tim Hardy, who is partially deaf, has watched plays with a torch in his hand and a script on his lap so he can follow what's being said on stage. https://t.co/Fc5qqILVIO https://t.co/1AoRKKJnfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groups representing internet providers sue California over net neutrality: Four industry groups representing major internet providers and cable companies on Wednesday filed suit seeking to block California's new law to mandate net neutrality rules. https://t.co/7ymPAY8qmw https://t.co/snnCRhVxUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebay alleges Amazon poached sellers from its platform: Ebay Inc on Wednesday accused https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc of trying to poach sellers for its own platform through Ebay's internal messaging system. https://t.co/3wwjvOnAod https://t.co/WHwmNlXgmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critical Customer Engagement Manager (SAP Ariba): Critical Customer Engagement Manager (SAP Ariba) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our… https://t.co/oZbQqPfdlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer — Mid-level: Full Stack Java Developer ‘ Mid-level ‘ Provides Java application software development services or technical support in situations of moderate complexity. Has thorough knowledge of the Software Development Life… https://t.co/Ftg2W5r5HQ https://t.co/XCkYJcBBq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Summit to stay in Lisbon for 10 years: Europe's largest tech event, the Web Summit, will remain in Lisbon for another 10 years, its founder Paddy Cosgrave said on Wednesday in a boost to Portugal's aspirations of becoming a technology hub. https://t.co/PvADtrpXlX https://t.co/ceDiQdPrSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test (C++): Software Engineer in Test (C++) in Bala Cynwyd, PA (Philadelphia Area) | Technology – Software Engineering at Susquehanna International Group – About – Trading – Quant Research – Technology – Campus Programs – gamer blog… https://t.co/ie4FhYPPTM https://t.co/P13r80e013]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mauritius bank SBM says unit's India operations hit by cyber fraud: Mauritius banking group SBM Holdings said on Wednesday that its Indian operations suffered a cyber fraud earlier in the week, and that the bank has potentially lost up to $14 million. https://t.co/HsvrMhPIUs https://t.co/MLM0i2S3s4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TD Ameritrade invests in cryptocurrency exchange ErisX: Retail brokerage TD Ameritrade Holding Corp said on Wednesday it has invested in a new cryptocurrency exchange called ErisX in a bid to offer clients digital asset investment options beyond the… https://t.co/vjHHjlgarD https://t.co/iUqHG1BJ8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer – Intermediate (Epic Applications): Job Description Job Title: Programmer – Intermediate (Epic Applications) Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Information Services Department:… https://t.co/YHBiouSxtq https://t.co/i2uOwtYqrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell exploring IPO option if tracking stock bid fails: Dell Technologies Inc confirmed on Wednesday it had met with some investment banks to explore an initial public offering if its plan to buy the tracking stock of VMware Inc falls through. https://t.co/y3QDGUXfXg https://t.co/FOv30aBgJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Business Process Analyst Workforce Planning: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/Sd1t94kqRn https://t.co/tj4ZYARHX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Summit to stay in Lisbon for 10 years: CEO: Europe's largest tech event, the Web Summit, will remain in Lisbon for another 10 years, its founder Paddy Cosgrave said on Wednesday in a boost to Portugal's aspirations of becoming a technology hub. https://t.co/oaI3aLHgjg https://t.co/UwMQiGPb7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent Music files for U.S. IPO, first-half revenue surges: Tencent Music Entertainment, which owns China's most popular music apps, has filed for a U.S. IPO seeking funds to develop content and new services, in what is expected to be one of the biggest… https://t.co/UZgb0eJjSD https://t.co/Rr4h3g6ad1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AV Coordinator, Electrical Computer Engineering: Job Description AV Coordinator, Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering (*******) The Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE) at Carnegie Mellon University (CMU) has an immediate opening for an… https://t.co/pRCUhtXzTQ https://t.co/k8wFbGJR6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renault-Nissan, Daimler mull extending alliance to autonomous, battery tech: Renault-Nissan and Daimler may expand their cooperation to battery and autonomous cars technology and mobility services, the companies said on Wednesday. https://t.co/h1NWMrKsH2 https://t.co/kwrk3ShVxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram back up after worldwide outage: Facebook Inc's photo-sharing social network Instagram is back up for some users on Wednesday, after suffering a worldwide outage days after it installed a new head of the app. https://t.co/Daf7fAWjSF https://t.co/ec8KNFxjDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram hit by outage in several cities: Facebook Inc's photo-sharing social network Instagram was not working on Wednesday for users across several cities, including London, San Francisco and Singapore. https://t.co/nx4drkUUVI https://t.co/rnEydmMTrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environment Support Analyst: Environment Support Analyst Ref No.: 18-42425 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Title-Environment Analyst Location-Malvern, PA Provide expertise to support and maintain non-production UNIX environments. Tasks include monitoring… https://t.co/vvPbmkCW3d https://t.co/DUSZTyBWDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Inc's Instagram hit by outage in several cities: Facebook Inc's photo-sharing social network Instagram was not working on Wednesday for users across several cities, including London, San Francisco and Singapore. https://t.co/HEhWiOvv9z https://t.co/UIoqCBo4LJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBOL/Mainframe developer: SR. COBOL DEVELOPER LOCATION: PITTSBURGH, PA * COBOL, CICS, DB2 ARE THE MAIN SKILLS. * WORK IS MOSTLY RUNNING BATCH JOBS AND WRITING FROM RSS TO DB2 WITH COBOL. * MOSTLY APPLICATION SUPPORT WORK FOR VENDOR ATM APPLICATIONS… https://t.co/oJuko96qwH https://t.co/0ztuWW5EBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full-Stack Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems. Looking for a highly motivated and engagednet-centric… https://t.co/PJKXGqqKnW https://t.co/jpogkgwoId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SR Number ERS-/ERS-/2018/****** Designation Project Manager Location Pennsylvania Job Family Engg (Engg – S/W &amp; S/W Product Engg) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for conceptualising and delivering the solution/product to the… https://t.co/pQBQqvUNAM https://t.co/vMab8RDPnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech giants allied against proposed Australia law seeking encrypted data: Four global tech giants - Facebook, Apple, Alphabet and Amazon - will oppose an Australian law that would require them to provide access to private encrypted data linked to… https://t.co/CeVTBMDhH7 https://t.co/FyJzyITbuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Tesla directors proposed James Murdoch to succeed Musk as chairman: New York Times: Some Tesla directors have proposed that James Murdoch, fellow board member at the electric carmaker and chief executive officer of Twenty-First Century Fox Inc,… https://t.co/wqePQquppP https://t.co/RywfK1QYcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent Music files for Nasdaq IPO, first-half revenue surges: Tencent Music Entertainment, which owns China's most popular music apps, has filed for a U.S. IPO seeking funds to develop content and new services, in what is expected to be one of the… https://t.co/NeolEY4pch https://t.co/jqIu0wpzgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman sues Facebook, claims site enabled sex trafficking: A Texas woman, claiming that she was raped, beaten and sex trafficked at the age of 15 by a pimp who posed as a Facebook "friend," has filed suit against the social network, alleging its… https://t.co/aCJtFHQEBE https://t.co/om9lG3ljPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager of Customer Experience (SAP Ariba): Manager of Customer Experience (SAP Ariba) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community… https://t.co/8dizQCCNtl https://t.co/19Xc5y9Vph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharp makes long-awaited OLED foray, wary of big spending: Japan's Sharp Corp unveiled its long-awaited move into the organic light-emitting diode (OLED) market on Wednesday as the Apple Inc supplier looks to catch rival Samsung Electronics Co Ltd. https://t.co/PnoZgw517q https://t.co/8sqJIigeJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharp marks long-awaited OLED foray with smartphone launch: Sharp Corp said on Wednesday its first OLED smartphone would go on sale later this year in Japan, marking its long-awaited entry into the market for the advanced panels as it seeks to catch up… https://t.co/4jaa2Ha4Qj https://t.co/ApqUvhsl6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autonomous Train Control Software Engineer – Dev Ops: Autonomous Train Control Software Engineer – Dev Ops Search by Keyword Search by Location Email similar jobs to me Please enable JavaScript to subscribe. this Job Autonomous Train Control Software… https://t.co/qCeaB43TAx https://t.co/DVClZ2lUvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla must defend lawsuit alleging abuse of foreign workers: A federal judge has ruled that Tesla must defend itself at a trial over allegations it knew foreign workers at one of its facilities were threatened with deportation if they reported an injury… https://t.co/SQmCgtqb7w https://t.co/bwg4zCpT97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook says hackers did not use stolen logins on third-party sites: Facebook Inc said on Tuesday that investigators have determined that hackers did not access other sites that use the social networking site's single sign-on in a massive cyberattack… https://t.co/vbTTlgkb7v https://t.co/CEUboDrMRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Java: Software Developer – Java job description | Excell – blog – NewsRoom – Contact – Login – Investors – INVESTOR DASHBOARD – PRESS RELEASES – STOCK – ONLINE INVESTOR KIT – SEC FILINGS – CORPORATE GOVERNENCE – WEBCAST AND… https://t.co/gwX3o08ts6 https://t.co/7JeypkKHxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Business Development Manager – Data Science: Job ID : 69556BR Location : US – California – Carlsbad|US – Massachusetts – Waltham|US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description The Senior Manager, Business Development will lead Data Science… https://t.co/6W3HLzNww8 https://t.co/MYbsvO7eEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD needs perfection to justify share price rally: analysts: Advanced Micro Devices Inc shares have been the S&amp;P 500’s rock star gainer this year, but a recent slide signals some investors are hedging their bets that it can make major inroads in the… https://t.co/2kRLx8sZcA https://t.co/zQmf4p2sVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook says hackers did not access other sites with its login: Facebook Inc said on Tuesday that investigators have determined that hackers did not access other sites that use the social networking site's single sign-on in a massive cyber attack that… https://t.co/UxKpbpGvWP https://t.co/tQ68TberOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce, QA Engineer III: Job ID : 75315BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/8n1MCafmUX https://t.co/W2yWNxcSAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook says hackers did not access other sites that use its login: Facebook Inc said on Tuesday that its investigators have determined that hackers did not access other sites that use the social networking site's single sign-on in a massive cyber… https://t.co/t61WhVwObC https://t.co/DpAe9vfNgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK regulator to investigate EE, Vodafone over data coverage: Britain's telecoms regulator said on Tuesday it was investigating whether mobile operators EE and Vodafone had provided accurate information about the coverage of their 3G and 4G mobile networks. https://t.co/qQbDQJiBAW https://t.co/2ZNTcSUNbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook says investigating if security flaw impacted Workplace app users: Facebook Inc said it was investigating if a security breach that it revealed last week had impacted users of its corporate chat app, Workplace. https://t.co/KO6ohqEeM2 https://t.co/U9aysqfoOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon raises minimum wage to $15, urges rivals to follow: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc said on Tuesday it would raise its minimum wage to $15 per hour for U.S. employees from next month, giving ground to critics of poor pay and working conditions at the… https://t.co/ewTJzV8Yq8 https://t.co/dePSRQNOwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon raises minimum wage rates in Britain: Amazon said on Tuesday it is raising its minimum wage in Britain to 10.50 pounds ($13.59) an hour for all employees in the London area and 9.50 pounds an hour for staff in all other parts of the country,… https://t.co/xE0XkvBCer https://t.co/tWe8AtExgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Bernie Sanders applauds Amazon for wage hike: U.S. Democratic Senator and prominent Amazon critic Bernie Sanders praised the company's move to increase minimum hourly wages to $15 on Tuesday and said other companies should follow its lead. https://t.co/kuFGFpdr2r https://t.co/nKA9cVrH40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Manager, Control — Financial and Emerging Technologies Control Team (IT Control Support): Control – M3 Responsible for identifying, analyzing, monitoring and minimizing business risks, and ensures proper control policies and procedures are in… https://t.co/AK0lXmxdam https://t.co/Zu9pP9nQR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMW says rivals are interested in joining forces on self-driving cars: BMW rivals and ride-hailing companies are considering joining its consortium for developing self-driving cars as auto industry profits come under increasing pressure, board member… https://t.co/ubwCf5D68K https://t.co/JWMudMdwkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla worried by China tariffs even as deliveries surge: Tesla Inc announced record quarterly car production numbers on Tuesday but warned of major problems with selling cars in China due to new tariffs that would force it to accelerate investment in its… https://t.co/LqLn2worKE https://t.co/dmLVkJiulx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TomTom shares lifted by BMW, Peugeot contract wins: TomTom shares jumped 4 percent on Tuesday after the Dutch navigation company said it had struck deals with carmakers BMW and Peugeot. https://t.co/HpLMfeyp6j https://t.co/fhy32nv07J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent's online music unit files for U.S. listing: Tencent Music Entertainment Group on Tuesday formally filed with regulators to list in the United States, under the symbol "TME", in what could be the biggest U.S. IPO by a Chinese company. https://t.co/hzrwpiwsb9 https://t.co/U1MRpvgfAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer/ Process Engineer: Location: Wilkes-Barre Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers CNC PROGRAMMER/ PROCESS ENGINEER US – PA – Wilkes-Barre Job Description * Generate CNC programs with quality design standards and… https://t.co/CiwfrWqvYw https://t.co/0qZ6KAbM2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK regulator to investigate EE, Vodafone over data coverage: Britain's telecoms regulator said on Tuesday it was investigating whether mobile operators EE and Vodafone had provided accurate information about the coverage of their 3G and 4G mobile networks. https://t.co/sR7rkcZfYU https://t.co/EMFoPLwj8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to meet with Google, other tech executives: Kudlow: U.S. President Donald Trump plans to host executives of internet and social media companies at the White House, likely later this month, White House adviser Larry Kudlow said on Tuesday. https://t.co/QMcSi7hT6s https://t.co/5f5bvjCYV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla worried by China even as deliveries surge: Tesla Inc announced record quarterly car production numbers on Tuesday but warned it was facing major problems with selling cars in China due to new tariffs that will force it to accelerate investment in… https://t.co/ix2kEyjkWo https://t.co/2XF2PiVBLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK regulator Ofcom to investigate Vodafone, BT on data coverage: Britain's telecoms regulator Ofcom said it would separately investigate if Vodafone Plc and the country's biggest mobile operator EE had provided accurate information in response to… https://t.co/fQQ3aDDul3 https://t.co/bX0EyNJyXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla misses weekly Model 3 production target, flags tariff costs: Tesla Inc missed its weekly Model 3 production target on Tuesday and said it was facing a 40 percent import tariff in China due to the ongoing U.S-China trade war. https://t.co/jGRvBNcxhI https://t.co/2EpoIv2XGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla produced 53,239 Model 3s in third quarter: Tesla Inc produced 53,239 of its Model 3 sedans in the third quarter and delivered 55,840 of the vehicles to customers, the company said on Tuesday. https://t.co/eXmux6trNY https://t.co/2nWHAKh1zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Manager in Projects Rail Automation: **Quality Manager in Projects – Rail Automation** Locations:Munhall, Pennsylvania Job Family: Quality Management New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Mobility **Business Unit:** Mobility… https://t.co/iSdNAo1RZ2 https://t.co/DvAR7IDJqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerson Electric to buy GE's intelligent platforms division: Factory automation equipment maker Emerson Electric Co on Tuesday agreed to buy General Electric Co's intelligent platforms business, a day after the conglomerate replaced its chief executive… https://t.co/e5bXlM6ad2 https://t.co/RA9UUhqvZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. tech sector getting by without Facebook and Alphabet: The technology sector appears to be doing just fine on Wall Street a week after it lost two of its highest-profile components to a newly christened communication services group. https://t.co/GZ5m3GY1T1 https://t.co/NBfUzPTKzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit uncertainty weighs on Jaguar's electric car investment decision: Britain's biggest carmaker Jaguar Land Rover has yet to make an imminent decision on whether to build electric cars in its home market partly due to uncertainty over the final Brexit… https://t.co/8LfzMmauAj https://t.co/JrURq6sw49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ubisoft shares climb on Google game streaming partnership deal: Ubisoft shares rose on Tuesday, outperforming weaker European markets, after Google said it had partnered with the French video games maker to test its video game streaming service. https://t.co/hwIAywMVxh https://t.co/fI64Inn615]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ubisoft shares rise on Google game streaming partnership deal: Ubisoft shares rose on Tuesday, outperforming weaker European markets, after Google said it had partnered with the French video games maker to test its video game streaming service. https://t.co/SvZHSXK7YH https://t.co/tBGll555od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: Department Mobile – ReachMobi Employment Type Full-Time Minimum Experience Experienced COMPANY OVERVIEW ReachMobi is more than just one of the world’s largest mobile content providers. Our audience of over 20 million plus… https://t.co/1ieljr5DNB https://t.co/BOpbFhuYM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics third-quarter profit seen at record, but peaking, as chips shine: Samsung Electronics Co Ltd is set to post a hefty jump in third-quarter profit to record levels after its chip unit put in a sterling performance on demand from data… https://t.co/nypUi5VIfe https://t.co/bCrndtZS2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Laser Turret Programmer: Responsibilities: Reviews special CNC programs based off Cad files provided by Engineering for set-up personnel at the computer controlled equipment (i.e., laser, turret) Creates sheet sizes and CNC programs for prototypes to… https://t.co/8i6dYDTMUR https://t.co/zVcyrW2BIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager, Scrum Master: About the position Prudential’s Annuities and Life Technology Group is on a journey to transform its Project Management Office (PMO) into a robust, outcome-driven delivery organization. We are seeking a Senior… https://t.co/mQmS3owdBF https://t.co/qvABDhhHvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – IBM iSeries: Software Developer – IBM iSeries job description | Excell – blog – NewsRoom – Contact – Login – Investors – INVESTOR DASHBOARD – PRESS RELEASES – STOCK – ONLINE INVESTOR KIT – SEC FILINGS – CORPORATE GOVERNENCE – WEBCAST… https://t.co/JJc1qD1WPh https://t.co/2iXH7bXoj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL and BI programmer, Global Strategic Pricing: Job ID : 59634BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description Position Summary: We are looking for a SQL and BI developer who will be responsible for designing databases and ensuring… https://t.co/wrqagCmN0I https://t.co/wroLou4fG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French carmaker to launch car-sharing service in Washington DC: French carmaker PSA, maker of Peugeot and Citroen cars, will launch a car-sharing service in Washington DC at the end of October, a senior PSA executive said on Tuesday. https://t.co/UJalCezZJD https://t.co/LXYFSTLOFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup Ripple signs up payments firms for crypto-based platform: Three companies that provide cross-border payment services plan to use technology developed by startup Ripple that employs cryptocurrency XRP to speed transactions, the firms said on Monday. https://t.co/LwoI17p7wj https://t.co/I9vT1nBgWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to test game-streaming service with latest Assassin's Creed: Alphabet Inc's Google said on Monday it has partnered with Ubisoft to test its video game streaming service by offering the latest installment of the Assassin's Creed series. https://t.co/xUORJLix8J https://t.co/7Pr42pvGPC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>