<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Leonardo DRS Leonardo DRS is a leading supplier of integrated products, services and support to military forces, intelligence agencies and prime contractors worldwide. Focused on defense… https://t.co/iYal2WAHY4 #python #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the… https://t.co/TFnwff9T7I #python #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script… https://t.co/bEBFvu9B7n #python #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: LawnStarter [*************************** is looking for a Senior Backend Engineer to join our growing product development team. LawnStarter is a fast growing startup with an engineering team… https://t.co/0cgjmqE4Y5 #python #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge rejects U.S. demand to exclude AT&amp;T argument in Time Warner merger trial: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - AT&amp;T Inc can cite a voluntary commitment not to withhold content in licensing talks as a key part of its defense when an… https://t.co/y6GHrGGlZO #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/vreg3LPRYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Leonardo DRS Leonardo DRS is a leading supplier of integrated products, services and support to military forces, intelligence agencies and prime contractors worldwide. Focused on defense… https://t.co/XhWoZjJlAh #python #hiring #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Hi , Greetings from Macropace Technologies. We have a job opening with suits for you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested for this position. Software Developer Bellevue, WA Fulltime position… https://t.co/sDMH935eOv https://t.co/xUoI26XDoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Bellevue, WA: Software Developer Bellevue, WA Fulltime position Job Description: Minimum Requirements: Must have a minimum of a Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. 1 year of experience with… https://t.co/Lk16HG1s1U https://t.co/XcW2m1n5MG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/tWyOFz5AyV https://t.co/vm707nTfhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: In this exciting role, CW will be part of a fast-paced storage I/O R&amp;D team creating and maintaining tools for running experiments and process data in support of… https://t.co/aDThg2q9Qk https://t.co/I2eNS4WjBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a… https://t.co/vmaCJ5BpwP https://t.co/K8uVEipZOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Should have Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream * Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python * Should Have… https://t.co/puBn1jl8XO https://t.co/eC7e0rW02A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/DkaoC6DqTi https://t.co/1XfHe2VwsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer  We are looking for engineers who: Are customer-focused, driven and passionate in creating premier experiences through well designed, tested and maintainable code-bases. Are always looking to learn and improve –… https://t.co/KIKWVb796w https://t.co/5M3IMZYyfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Job Description Principal Software Engineer (WD***********) What you will do: As a principle software engineer you will own and lead software design and development for an SOA-based, multi-tenant, cloud platform. We’re… https://t.co/8Q66dTANxt https://t.co/pw0zcfgjpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk Developer: W2 only GC,USC only Sr. Splunk Engineer with some Python Scripting Expertise in Splunk Searching and Reporting modules, Knowledge Objects, Administration, Dashboards, Clustering and Forwarder Management. Perform Splunk administration… https://t.co/jnMwTJhgjz https://t.co/C1ZKExcV3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Adminstrator/DevOps Engineer: Description: Leidos is seeking a DevOps engineer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for the CEGS system, a real-time operational SIGINT processor. The CEGS applications run under a virtualized… https://t.co/u068h7oFRI https://t.co/uiZpz7Y99I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/lFJyCWsp1G https://t.co/iIJYp9bZR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – TS/SCI with polygraph: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment extends beyond the… https://t.co/kTO8YtZpRs https://t.co/8rbpxSstie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $150k – $250k Posted Today Are you a Senior Data Engineer with Data Pipeline, Python &amp; Machine Learning experience? If so, read on… We harness the power of machine learning and predictive analytics to… https://t.co/NgLo22SVUz https://t.co/M7JER5La5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Python &amp; Machine Learning: San Mateo, CA Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Data Scientist with Python experience, please read on! Based in San Mateo, CA – We are a well-funded, VC-backed startup inventing predictive… https://t.co/BSZSnuEH3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job TitlePython Developer – ID:31445 Duration6 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job Skillspython, SQL, AWS LocationBloomington, MN Date Posted04/10/2018 Qualifications Python, Relational Databases, HTTP APIs, Data Formats (JSON, CSV, XML),… https://t.co/TKQWY9mWVz https://t.co/hy85gBOraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/UZtLrDfAak https://t.co/b89DE6m1yU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Location US-NJ-Somerset | DE | US-NJ-Somerset # Positions 1 Experience (Years) 3 Category Engineering Position Description/Company Info Legrand has a great opportunity for a Software Engineer to work in multiple… https://t.co/REu7umQVEU https://t.co/WzAtFv6L0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer – Agile JAVA/Angular/Python Developer and Integrator: This position is in the BNY Mellon Information Lifecycle Management group, responsible for building and buying solutions to support Cyber Security Data Masking, Records Management,… https://t.co/J5LuWXH2eE https://t.co/wtdRE3wn3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (TS/SCI) – Herndon, VA: Java Developer (TS/SCI) – Herndon, VA ===================================== Req #: ******Location: Herndon, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job… https://t.co/NxDKTnLjfs https://t.co/7xdHRlKZsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java / Full Stack Developer) – Open Source Office: Job Description Job ID: R43430 West Creek 4 (12074), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still… https://t.co/IgZPmvDBRk https://t.co/gNmlot9R1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/P9Ty7d91U3 https://t.co/HhWsK668YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Client Reference Code: 216836 Job Scope The Software Engineer participates in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service delivery,… https://t.co/GnR3CW0rgn https://t.co/087CNZhz8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Client Reference Code: 216836 Job Scope The Software Engineer participates in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service delivery,… https://t.co/v1nSiDLcsd https://t.co/BJ3tlLc6Ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France builds WhatsApp rival due to surveillance risk: PARIS (Reuters) - The French government is building its own encrypted messenger service to ease fears that foreign entities could spy on private conversations between top officials, the digital… https://t.co/YOmji75jMN https://t.co/zrrhoJjywm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Engineer TS/SCI Polygraph required: Description: The Cyber and SIGINT Solution Ops under Defense and Intelligence Sector of Leidos has a career opportunity for a Database Engineer with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in Annapolis… https://t.co/IAypUvL074 https://t.co/ZbdzAqBo6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scientific Computing Software Engineer: Description: Leidos is seeking Scientific Computing Software Engineers to support a variety of sophisticated state-of-the-art acoustic training and simulation systems. Position provides opportunity to travel to… https://t.co/JSoGbtbcvQ https://t.co/7Y8v8FfOcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer (Python): Sr Software Engineer (Python) Requisition No.: 159801 Category: Development Location: Burlington, MA, US Do you want to help eliminate barriers between ideas and business outcomes? We want you to bring your unique… https://t.co/yXMM6Zf825 https://t.co/rnuKlvcLjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Risk Analyst Lead: Purpose of Job We are currently seeking talented Quantitative Risk Analyst Lead for our San Antonio, TX facility. Conducts and develops quantitative and analytic models, assessments and/or applications in support of risk… https://t.co/JFtNUXv1Wi https://t.co/TdDjUs2mnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer – Python: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today Are you a Back-End Developer? Do you have experience with Python? Do you have awesome communication skills? If so, then please read on! Based in San Francisco, CA, we are… https://t.co/9qLwJjIY6m https://t.co/Ehztuj5HCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Video Engineer: Client Reference Code: 216833Job Scope The Video Operations group is responsible for operating the video ecosystem at Spectrum and is comprised of the following groups: Video Core, Video Systems, Planning &amp; Implementation and… https://t.co/V1vMY5Ez5L https://t.co/fhsMigGmhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer (Docker): Description: Innovate and create at Leidos! We have no shortage of challenging technical problems. Join Leidos team and apply your talents to solve them. If you are a DevOps Engineer wanting to work at either Reston, VA or… https://t.co/vy81zeiiOY https://t.co/QGAka0SERh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer – Full Stack: Client Reference Code: 215393Job ScopeLeads in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service delivery, datacenter and… https://t.co/hGmLNi6YRu https://t.co/DZo1dwHg7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Bellevue, WA: Software Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: In this position, the candidate will be integrating and validating different machine learning frameworks also developing POCs in the augmented/Virtual… https://t.co/4bi5Eo2RnB https://t.co/qdVXPRwNbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: We are expanding our web development team and looking for someone that has experience in full-life cycle development of web based applications using Node.js, React, Backbone, or Angular. The ideal candidate should be… https://t.co/ddCrENsIfW https://t.co/ENlGKdSiV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst/Scientist: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Alexandria, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/11/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/uFJxKRNxcx https://t.co/nckOUEMuno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting: Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting jobs in 08057 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/t3pqtv4QMw https://t.co/mRUBeUpUkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Developer Innovative Learning Technology Initiative: Programmer/Developer Innovative Learning Technology Initiative University of California Office of the President Requisition Number: 20170497 Appointment Type: Staff – Career Personnel… https://t.co/lf80uKUgjM https://t.co/MNikDV7buh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/ke7I50NXCw https://t.co/fhEtb06ciO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/Htv6Zz76FD https://t.co/8m9YlZA3MS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/dpl0PL4cjT https://t.co/wGzHp4GelB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Developer – Python: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-130K +bonus Design, develop and support systems within the financial modelling and research area. Design and develop new code and review existing code changes to ensure… https://t.co/LxUTBjHBy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/GbKS1OznRb https://t.co/QtH55eyFtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Scientist / Analyst – MATLAB / Python / C++: Job Description Research Scientist / Analyst – MATLAB / Python / C++ (12692) Introduction: The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and… https://t.co/HqWfK9L5i3 https://t.co/WGiuSlmUZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C. and Barranquilla, Colombia. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small startups to large enterprises,… https://t.co/X7IQ7Czb3A https://t.co/Bn1A9F6P3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/zqOJnSi3Wu https://t.co/JDccAOc0n3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/XbtLRvZzQA https://t.co/A3o0qwctTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer (Python Backend): Do have outstanding programming skills, business acumen, and the ability to come up with creative ideas and transform them into high-quality software solutions? If so, let’s talk! We are seeking an Engineer who is… https://t.co/Ix3yTlAhaq https://t.co/5ixhJ8G6xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer IV / Python Developer: Required Skills: * BS or MS computer science * 4 years experience in software development * Experience with Python &amp; Java Nice to Have Skills/Not Required: * JavaScript, Django, &amp; Raptical/MySQL database *… https://t.co/QM70ONR0QL https://t.co/ILOYtcZhB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Digital Tech Senior Assoc, Mulesoft Dev: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/jJYNhXYsAL https://t.co/Voc8mc49wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description: Leidos currently has an exciting career opportunity for Mid-Level Software Engineers to work in our Beavercreek, OH office. 　 POSITION SUMMARY: This is an exciting opportunity to use your experience to support AFRL’s… https://t.co/gIzXxFFGln https://t.co/2Bo4m21iPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator, Sr. (1st Shift) – Greenbelt, MD: Description:The Network Operation Center Lead/Sr Systems Administrator Shift Lead supports the Decennial Systems of Systems hybrid cloud infrastructure and its applications. The Network Operation… https://t.co/2gmRRQ1GJM https://t.co/yrB1uoSGCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/179cadOpQb https://t.co/BQTvxHxV3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/uegFakymZU https://t.co/Aod9DiT0JK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Big Data Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/bje1p9HXl4 https://t.co/7G8KTh25Ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Incident Response Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/A6LAnnVILy https://t.co/AOeF7gvHnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer for Healthcare Analytics App – Validate Health: Interested in being part of a small founding team, so you can see your direct impact on improving the healthcare industry? Want to be one of the rockstars building an innovative product… https://t.co/ANv2N2fXuE https://t.co/M7jBvYuka5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/ge6aG1u1Dt https://t.co/HbZ4IReTBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineer – C/Python, Herndon VA: Req ID : 423985BR Job Code/Title : E2553:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/mUlZXgfgVb https://t.co/SQnEGGFElN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with adaptable skills in Object Oriented Programming (Remote): Do you enjoy reading and applying new concepts to constantly improve the quality of your code? Do you value collaborative teams, honest communication, and a teaching culture?… https://t.co/AK0c1KIcZO https://t.co/cC7Zw34nKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinetic Weapons Effects Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Kinetic Weapons Effects Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission… https://t.co/g3jmDla5aK https://t.co/BQnnGoWj0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/Pe926aivvQ https://t.co/o7YiT43H06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted 01/11/2018 Located in a beautiful office in the Mission District in San Francisco, we are an early staged funded B2C Fin-Tech start up that is combining Artificial Intelligence, Machine… https://t.co/OP94m3j9aE https://t.co/51ZQeNYxdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: In this exciting role, CW will be part of a fast-paced storage I/O R&amp;D team creating and maintaining tools for running experiments and process data in support of… https://t.co/t0qwEg8LiQ https://t.co/70is7GOpYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/JtQbBxPMmI https://t.co/omMxw762py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: LOOKINGGLASS CYBER SOLUTIONS is hiring for an experienced, dynamic and technically versed Software Engineers. This chosen candidate will look to be apart of and support a small software engineering team responsible for assessing… https://t.co/HlhivlTKtr https://t.co/wliHEtwIHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Services Systems Administrator: Overview The Business Technology Enterprise, part of the Business Technology and Operations Group, cuts the keys that allow Vision Critical to unlock the vast potential of our people through aligned business… https://t.co/na6eWqogms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer: Our developers create industry-leading digital work for some of the most recognized brands on the planet. A successful candidate will bring a track record of constantly innovating and maintaining a broad knowledge of development… https://t.co/dQSd8Ou0TC https://t.co/ZKkVuv8hN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/k9dnxBVdfT https://t.co/d7frQcXksb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front End Engineer: New York, NY Full-time $130k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Lead Front End Engineer with a track record of success, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Autonomy – Great work environment – Ability to rise within a… https://t.co/tmviwBM47b https://t.co/53y33Y6tf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Automation Engineer: Looking for a Python Developer with 2+ years development and DevOps to automate the network. Must have experience working in an enterprise environment. You will automate select network operation tasks and work… https://t.co/R110nQt159 https://t.co/ex5MYVh4FD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/vvFsCoCh5F https://t.co/SybIE59XfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/kI3dSkpj6X https://t.co/oyekzRYK5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/wnKQYvimPS https://t.co/r15vR1DLYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/WjpFCdUqoW https://t.co/a9TqCgOpJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Startup/Python/HIPAA Compliant: San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! Based in San Francisco we are a digital healthcare startup that is looking… https://t.co/UY3vOw6ly8 https://t.co/I8XWZRlgBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python: A well-known prominent automobile manufacturing company is looking to add a Software QA Engineer to their R&amp;D team. In this role, youll be responsible for extending and customizing their existing Python automation framework. You… https://t.co/OQiVHcAIPR https://t.co/YicY4QuZth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 3: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/2VTpTOeIGe https://t.co/ll3roN5In1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: A. Johnson. Please reference job # below: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database… https://t.co/hoUqYdyv49 https://t.co/NqNVEdgcbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX: Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX – Parmesoft Inc. – Houston, TX – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/GSrkaKebPE https://t.co/wWhjjFHihB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/IIGulJjW34 https://t.co/GNJvmOG5hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/DMavMMiu6Y https://t.co/6CALvLLsIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Burlington, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsLinux,DevOpsTax TermsW-2Overview Position: DevOps Engineer Location: Burlington, MA Duration: 9+ month contract.… https://t.co/cFPMpeJyxG https://t.co/FUJDTXdo8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Generalist: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Software Engineer – Generalist Engineering | San Francisco, CA | Full Time Job Description Software Engineer – Generalist Work from… https://t.co/bIJ0t8Gc6y https://t.co/7L5A4CPfYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Network Security Engineer: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10271 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is one of the world’s largest behavioral and social science… https://t.co/jkMI9quFOk https://t.co/MRPtObLN7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/owmX5ICjeF https://t.co/P9OQZdhHlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Automation Test Developer : Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: must have at least 2 years of experience developing C++ test framework and test cases OR C++ application development experience Good to have 3… https://t.co/gjE4OuchMm https://t.co/UMJWV2PHqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused – employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team of… https://t.co/rp4IVymwW2 https://t.co/YSf1zm0cn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Engineer, Platform Engineering: Job ID: 142263  Location Name: CA-FSC SF Off (0174) Address: 525 Market St, 32nd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105, United States (US) Job Type: Full Time Position Type (Regular/Temporary): Regular Job Function:… https://t.co/m1qbPz0t9v https://t.co/qECHV4RBWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/8QSg4m834q https://t.co/3fpqy2Qukt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/npBIiq3UgR https://t.co/kLKPh8iojT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/PMeayxSDfH https://t.co/hw4KuBS3SM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/giBozbsWJy https://t.co/VNExdJ2CHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer: Our developers create industry-leading digital work for some of the most recognized brands on the planet. A successful candidate will bring a track record of constantly innovating and maintaining a broad knowledge of development… https://t.co/dPqKMRSPow https://t.co/IHgCEUSkzR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>