<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description: Leidos has an opening for a Sr. Systems Administrator (Microsoft Windows &amp;#38; Red Hat Linux platforms). Work will be performed at the National Maritime Intelligence Center, Suitland, MD. **This position requires an… https://t.co/PZrcEbiHXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/tDAyf7jlD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporting Analyst III: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/Xh0bT2t3Rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – SharePoint – Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/3cOG8gSeC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: NETE Point Developer Rockville, MD 20852 NET ESOLUTIONS CORPORATION (NETE) is a multi-award winning company founded in 1999. NETE is a full service Information Technology (IT) company dedicated to providing value focused consulting… https://t.co/wptTyP6Kqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[o365 / SharePoint Collaboration Tools Specialist: Fivesky is looking for a highly motivated and talented Collaboration Tools Specialist to join a fast-paced, dynamic, and challenging environment. The ideal candidate must have a background of working with… https://t.co/evWUYQ2aZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring Engineer (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The Monitoring Engineer will primarily be responsible for the overall monitoring, maintenance of the Network Operations Center. They are the first point of contact responsible for reactively monitoring… https://t.co/r3acb5e60V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/duSoRyAw28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administration T3: Description:JOB DESCRIPTION:&amp;#160; Leidos is looking for a System Administrator to join our Origin program team. The ideal candidate will serve as an engineer on the Service Operations Team on a classified government contract.… https://t.co/GP8Q2WWoyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Business Intelligence Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Antonio, TX Job Type: Strategy &amp;#8211; Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the… https://t.co/omvvB3V8bO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager 135: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: Senior Project Manager is responsible for leading teams to deliver project(s) that span across one or more business units. Manage resources, schedules,… https://t.co/TmdwKEsOBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Mobile Browsers: Microsoft Edge, Firefox Focus, Google Chrome, and More: Surfing the web on your phone is about to get a whole lot better. https://t.co/pjeA5ucfdR https://t.co/ClbNmncFZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Discover Technologies, LLC provides SharePoint professional services in both the commercial and public sectors to ensure effective delivery of contracted services to customers world-wide. In this role, Discover Technologies… https://t.co/KTounBAnFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/Mme2oxb8f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Officer (IA Security Specialist [Journeyman]) – 16588: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical… https://t.co/xtSB4XNOtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/3ooL6CAoJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16080: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/ES7TkwrtZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/p7et6WedRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern, Data Analytics/Software Engineer: SSL is a leading provider of commercial satellites and spacecraft systems, with broad expertise to support satellite operators and innovative space related missions. The company designs and manufactures… https://t.co/87E1amTvxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description:The Origin program is in need of an experienced SharePoint developer to design, build, configure, maintain and conceptualize complex and detailed SharePoint sites for our customer on various customer systems.&amp;#160; There… https://t.co/Aiu6lvSkUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer w/.NET *HOT CONTRACT*: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/3ivznJMzUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Integration Architect, Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/1JjTZblAOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager JOB SUMMARY The Associate Project Manager supports cross-functional program teams to ensure projects meet objectives and are delivered on-time. Under the general supervision of a Manager or Director,… https://t.co/8RPMZZYdJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions): IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions) Job Number: 1600620 Description This position is responsible for providing leadership and technical deliverables in the design, development, testing, documentation, and… https://t.co/VNsZ55Fxru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap PS4 and PS4 Pro Bundles and Deals (2018): If you're hunting for a PS4 or PS4 Pro, these are the cheapest bundles you're going to find. https://t.co/LeawduN8Iv https://t.co/cZfTdiOLLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/iRnQslj5Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst Subject Matter Expert 16496: #CyberJobs #CamberIT Technical Solutions Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides… https://t.co/3bn5DMI2gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect: Americas » United StatesProfessional Services and Customer SolutionsSharePoint Architect NextLabs®, Inc. is the leading provider of policy-driven information risk management (IRM) software for large enterprises. NextLabs’ flagship… https://t.co/3p8GTGqYU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CND Analyst (Network Senior) – 16399: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/4guuIb9xft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/eThJWOBsox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/h1M2Xta0R7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator: Description:Leidos has a career opportunity for a SharePoint Administrator at Nellis AFB in Las Vegas, NV. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; Applicants will support… https://t.co/spPhdNq0j7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Officer (IA Security Specialist [Journeyman]) – 16588: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical… https://t.co/j7P6QcY0Tj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:Leidos has a great opportunity for a Senior Software&amp;#160;Developer at Lackland AFB in San Antonio, TX. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; The selected… https://t.co/iAIBFGoou5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/RYx5uoPvD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused &amp;#8211; employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team… https://t.co/V9GUQfgy4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: The (Near) Future of PCs: Laptops are getting mobile processors and behaving more like phones. How will that change the way we use them? https://t.co/GU6gROaxts https://t.co/bshg66udd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Architect (AEM): Job Summary: Migrating an existing website onto AEM platform and building out a new experience for existing customers. The AEM Senior Architect provides technical leadership throughout the life-cycle of a project, with specific… https://t.co/fGeXLQqdSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/2xcflRqeMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/S9XXaMG5Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/X0GJCRVets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Manager (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The SE&amp;#38;I Change Manager will establish and manage a structured change management program on behalf of US Census Bureaus (USCB) System Engineering and Integration (SE&amp;#38;I) team. &amp;#160; Responsibilities:… https://t.co/ILWDFhjhnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/sKUDu8LMMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/O21dAungo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/lF2HHozjKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/0tEf3LwSQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/YzeeB5qYxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/R0rBpkkafn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/mD5KdPnCdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RSS Readers Are Due for a Comeback: Feedly, The Old Reader, Inoreader: After years of letting algorithms make up our minds for us, the time is right to go back to basics. https://t.co/mgutbysOrA https://t.co/tXmIwzkAdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/0D4scFRgZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:Leidos has a great opportunity for a Senior Software&amp;#160;Developer at Lackland AFB in San Antonio, TX. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; The selected… https://t.co/AbZECV7XxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/8eePiQMfjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Engineer: At Farm Credit Mid-America, we believe people are our strongest asset. We are consistently looking to hire individuals from a wide range of experience and capabilities who have a desire to serve. Currently, we have over 1,100… https://t.co/nfwTDkEc01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/azcItxaAyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/EVaOW84yrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp;#038; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers… https://t.co/DR2nE7oUPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/g5u2wDBflw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BrightStart IT Intern – System Administrator: BrightStart IT Intern &amp;#8211; System Administrator Lawrenceville, GA Our team: At Brightree, we believe in building innovative technology solutions and providing services that improve clinical and business… https://t.co/JyXR8WOnbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer: LCG is seeking a Senior SharePoint Developer to join a highly skilled Agile web development team. The team develops web applications predominantly using .Net, SharePoint, Angular JS, SQL Server and does Customization and… https://t.co/Qs1GRH2kFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Engineer: Description:Leidos has a career opportunity for a Senior Network Engineer in Honolulu, HI. Candidates must possess a current TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. The individual will be required to conduct… https://t.co/EqD6cO0DqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions): IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions) Job Number: 1600620 Description This position is responsible for providing leadership and technical deliverables in the design, development, testing, documentation, and… https://t.co/F0WZMLEhod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build a PC: Building your own computer yourself is a lost art—one due for a revival. https://t.co/RdrKInoTbL https://t.co/79c1IUOArv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring Engineer (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The Monitoring Engineer will primarily be responsible for the overall monitoring, maintenance of the Network Operations Center. They are the first point of contact responsible for reactively monitoring… https://t.co/VV9Jlqkm6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Integration Architect, Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/TK6oXOWMLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description: Leidos has an opening for a Sr. Systems Administrator (Microsoft Windows &amp;#38; Red Hat Linux platforms). Work will be performed at the National Maritime Intelligence Center, Suitland, MD. **This position requires an… https://t.co/a7h5zGpe0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer: Mission Headquartered in Seattle, Washington, Wireless Advocates is a third-party provider of wireless products and services both online and in approximately 600 retail locations nationwide. Together with Fortune 100 channel… https://t.co/xfHdbFcGpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on Ft. Meade, MD. Job… https://t.co/dWdloKsZma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Architect (AEM): Job Summary: Migrating an existing website onto AEM platform and building out a new experience for existing customers. The AEM Senior Architect provides technical leadership throughout the life-cycle of a project, with specific… https://t.co/8NBN4qOQSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description:The Treasury Solutions &amp;#38; Development (TSD) Organization supports the Total Information Processing Support Services (TIPSS) contract vehicle which is used by the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) for IT contractor… https://t.co/sWq7fAzFuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Analyst: Description: The job of the Configuration Management (CM) Analyst is to perform the necessary functions to maintain configuration control of aircraft system hardware and software configurations. PRIMARY… https://t.co/yYMHjrBuEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for a Network Operations Analyst at the DISA Headquarters Command Center on Ft. Meade,… https://t.co/RfVrNAP3Sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/NBdTQUN7Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administration and Operations Analyst: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for a Network Administration and Operations Analyst at the DISA… https://t.co/7zBSxP98hW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Easter Tech Sales (2018): Nintendo, Apple, Dyson, Lenovo: When you're done painting eggs and munching on candy, check out these Easter tech deals. https://t.co/ls2bbWltt8 https://t.co/PmlWETbtQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eDiscovery Analyst: Description:The Civil Health Solutions Operation is currently seeking an eDiscovery Analyst to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore. &amp;#160; Leidos is looking for an eDiscovery Analyst to join our eDiscovery team and work… https://t.co/OK1aT8JQvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/AzassLpgDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/mWwAqUNsil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring Engineer (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The Monitoring Engineer will primarily be responsible for the overall monitoring, maintenance of the Network Operations Center. They are the first point of contact responsible for reactively monitoring… https://t.co/NX2O4Ew6P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:Leidos has a great opportunity for a Senior Software&amp;#160;Developer at Lackland AFB in San Antonio, TX. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; The selected… https://t.co/RLB2DL6zfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Manager (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The SE&amp;#38;I Change Manager will establish and manage a structured change management program on behalf of US Census Bureaus (USCB) System Engineering and Integration (SE&amp;#38;I) team. &amp;#160; Responsibilities:… https://t.co/o6k8zRBqea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Architect (AEM): Job Summary: Migrating an existing website onto AEM platform and building out a new experience for existing customers. The AEM Senior Architect provides technical leadership throughout the life-cycle of a project, with specific… https://t.co/QCBH1J2tfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Systems Integration Specialist: Overview Love working with people? Passionate about technology? We’re looking for a tech enthusiast with a project manager mindset to join our team as an Integration Specialist II, where you’ll serve as the technical… https://t.co/1TdFEeEiAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description:Leidos has a current job opportunity for an experienced SharePoint Developer with expertise in JavaScript to support our DISA customer on the GSM-O program. This position is located in Chambersburg, PA. JOB DESCRIPTION… https://t.co/J8j4gwCSsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- TS/SCI Polygraph Required: Description: The Cyber and SIGINT Solution Ops under Defense and Intelligence Sector of Leidos has a career opportunity for a Software Engineer with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in Annapolis Junction,… https://t.co/nwtnoqUCdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/HoC18FRWKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on Ft. Meade, MD. Job… https://t.co/XFQN2E5lrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Speaker Deals: Sony, JBL, Ultimate Ears, Insignia: We've found awesome deals on some rockin' speakers. https://t.co/FdZnwflXy6 https://t.co/CyT3SpsBRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager with sharepoint exp: Project manager with sharepoint exp Ref No.: 18-11897 Location: Redmond, Washington Job Description:- Position : Project manager with sharepoint exp Location : Redmond, WA Type : Contract (12 Months) a) Taking… https://t.co/s59tOXpYQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/rvrKby05hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer -TS/SCI Polygraph required: Description: The Defense and Intelligence Division of Leidos has a career opportunity for a Sharepoint Developer with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in Annapolis Junction, Maryland. PROGRAM SUMMARY: Do… https://t.co/ClwxPAZrot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/pmQTqkaThW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer w/.NET *HOT CONTRACT*: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/wlOYN67wcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Systems Administrator: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a talented SharePoint Systems Administrator… https://t.co/wbsGCYw4uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description: Leidos has an opening for a Sr. Systems Administrator (Microsoft Windows &amp;#38; Red Hat Linux platforms). Work will be performed at the National Maritime Intelligence Center, Suitland, MD. **This position requires an… https://t.co/QhoWb7Emgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused &amp;#8211; employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team… https://t.co/VM2Rm6GkI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/KJw0e6ES2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description: Leidos has a career opening for a SharePoint Developer located in Alexandria, VA. &amp;#160; Position Summary The SharePoint developer will act as an administrator to design, implement and preserve numerous SharePoint… https://t.co/UhVbafCPbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:Leidos has a great opportunity for a sr. Software&amp;#160;Developer at Lackland AFB in San Antonio, TX. Candidates must currently possess a TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. &amp;#160; The selected… https://t.co/KXV0esj4Bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's New Data-Sharing Policies Are Crashing Tinder: Users can't log into the dating app after Facebook adjusted its app integration policies. https://t.co/vIEyBmAf7W https://t.co/ecd4DW3zVJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>