<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't play with my heart for entertainment. Play with yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day, I will find a person whom I will love forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.I.T.C.H - Beautiful Invidual That Creates Hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. I'm sorry that I have to sit here hiding my feelings for you, so I can keep what we have instead of losing you forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving someone and not expressing it is like wrapping a present and not giving it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love you because you re a reflection of me, you re everything I want. You treat me with respect, trust, and you love ME for ME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To trust means to make oneself vulnerable to antoher. It's placing complete faith in them trusting they won't use it against you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m going to smile like nothings wrong, talk like everything s perfect, act like its just a dream and pretend that he s not hurting me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday, you will find one who will watch every sunrise with you until the sunset of your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the worst feeling in the world to love and hate someone all at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first time I saw you was the last time I saw my heart...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When all my dreams come true, the one I want next to me. It's you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move on. Its just another chapter in the past. Don't close the book. Just turn the page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replaying a song repeatedly because I'm just too lazy to search up a new song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can t make the same mistake twice. The second time you make it, it s no longer a mistake, it s a choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up in the morning and looking for your cellphone first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be a lot easier to get over you if we weren't friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although the contents are significant, the cover is relevant as well. Because majority simply judge a book by its cover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet that you have no idea that all my quotes are created while thinking about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst feeling ever when you want to tell someone something but scared about what they will say...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It still makes me smile to know that, at one point in time, you used to be mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside I hope you know I'm dying, with my heart besides me in shattered pieces that never be replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone doesn't see you in their future, maybe it's time to put them in the past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It hurts when you're always there for people, but when it comes to you, no one is ever around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the little things, take up the most room in your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful...the ones that make you smile are the same ones that can shatter your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a relationship,  +  = , not , not , not . Get your facts right bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you're busy looking for the perfect person you'll probably miss the imperfect person who could make you perfectly happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think you re not happy with your life, always think that someone is happy simply because you exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people should come with subtitles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith is what you hold onto when you can't reach anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can suddenly stop and say you don't love someone anymore, you never loved them in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep blaming her for taking you away from me, when the truth is you could've fought for me, but instead you let me go as if I was nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The walls we build around us to keep out the sadness also keep out the joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy: Giant polar bear Girl: What! Boy: It broke the ice. s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falling in love is easy, staying in love is hard, and letting go of love is the hardest part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good listener is very nearly as attractive as a good talker. You cannot have a beautiful mind if you do not know how to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleeping is nice. You forget about everything for a little while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with love will have some thorns, but a life without love will have no roses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those mornings where you just want to lie on bed and not do anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm NOT single and I'm NOT taken. I'm simply on reserve for the one person who REALLY deserves my heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a kid I picked up food that were dropped and blowed on them to remove the dust... Jk I still do :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew how to impress you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Will Tell You To Get A Life. Simply Reply: Where Did You Get Yours I'll Avoid Going There.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going back to a conversation in your head and thinking what you should had said instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not trip, I said hello to the floor with my face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you say "no one loves me" I silently screem in my head "I do"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was stupid to think you would actually care...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes in order to hold on to something you must let go... &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to like me. I'm not a Facebook status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's impossible to forget someone who had gave you great memories throughout. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painter draws a painting "Door of Heart" without handle. Man:Where's the handle Painter:The Door of Heart opens from inside not the outside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people simply does not deserve better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, so you made a mistake. Beating urself up about it isn t going to make it any better. Rise above that and remember that u aren t perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, the whole world came crashing down on me...So I got some tape and stuck the map back onto the wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actions may speak louder than words, but there are still three words EVERY girl wants to hear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most exciting, challenging and significant relationship of all is the one you have with yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somethings in this life we just never get over, and you were one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny, the more you hate on me, the more OBVIOUS it is to everyone how jealous you are of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cry me a river, build me a bridge, and do us all a favor and jump off it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're my dream, when are you gonna become my reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane  Ehh, we prefer " mentally hilarious "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest part about moving forward is not looking back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need an instruction manual, I'm perfectly capable of screwing it up without printed help, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sing like no one is listening, dance like no one is watching, and run like heck when they all start laughing at you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love when you're ready, not when you're lonely...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the type to stay committed, as long as you can do the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbyes hurt, pictures never replace being there, memories bring tears, and words can never replace those feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying here with you so close to me. It's hard to fight these feelings when it feels so hard to breathe..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the little things that easily ruin my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont piss me off! I'm running out of places to hide the bodies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is so short. Just enjoy your life and keep smiling no matter what happen, try it &amp; you'll know life is so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It only takes a second to make a mistake. It can take a lifetime to make it right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don t ever under estimate a woman s ability to find things out. Eventually, they will know everything about you and your past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those surprise hugs from the back. &lt; .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having you is the best thing ever and loving you is what I plan to do forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You re the reason I live and the reason I die, you re the reason I smile yet break down and cry...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some girls claim they want a good guy, but when they meet one, he s "just a friend." Then they fall for the player &amp; get their heart broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the pain of a person, because in all honesty, everyone hurts. Some people just hide it better than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feeling of rejection when you call your pet over and it walks away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being single is a lot wiser than being in a wrong relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You asked me why I don t talk to you anymore. Well maybe it s because you slowly pushed me out of your life. I m glad ur finally noticing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby give me a chance to prove to you that I'll be the best decision you'll ever make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It crushes me so much to know that I tried my hardest to be perfect for you, and I still lost you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all honestly I don't want anyone but him and I think it's alway going to be like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about tomorrow when today is all we have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part of life is when your family becomes your friends and your friends become your family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I see a typo I look at the keyboard to see if the two keys were near each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear You, Making you happy is the best thing I've done. And it's the one thing I want to do for the rest of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are loved more than you will ever know, by someone who died to know you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who hate you are just your confused admirers. They can't figure out the reason why everyone loves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m not popular, but I have good friends. I m not rich, but I have what I need. I may not be liked, but I know I m loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I fell for you, would you catch me or just let me hit the pavement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love has a way of leaving us with a full head but an empty heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With this pain in my heart sometimes I wake up thinking "You still matter to me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like a puzzle...sometimes it takes awhile to find the right piece that will complete it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You lied to me for your happiness.. I lied to myself for your happiness ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the power vested in me, I now pronounce you deleted and blocked. You now kiss my ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musicians are so much sexier than normal guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You started as my dream. You became my reality. Now you're only a memory.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>