<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/R4vpPVpa9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/NE8RJdI3XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/Y8XqHrJsHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/p6XW50AlZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/PlEG5HhYD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/gLyTTdi9tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/znygFGLIqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/d6EoBTtbC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/eCQJlxS2yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/wkjQW17F4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/CSQ2mImfCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/MUT4pgFpRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/B2i6CZWo2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/tWgJ3jlH2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/wj950GUyl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/ci50JZYdSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/i8FGx9vNWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird of paradise alights only upon the hand that does not grasp. - John Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/ZehtmSnZ3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/lpLP9ifXFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/ykkniAoTxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/GSpwBoWkok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/Fu0bHnAKxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/qRBLftJbRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/2S8NfBkSx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/ax6vGFGHfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make a rock'n'roll record, technology is the least important thing.  -  Keith Richards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/LopHdWy8Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/Aw6igzHimz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/TEpBadwpxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/UEVM3e8ED9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/i1a0JciQPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/76x2NZy4En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/rq52yzAoDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/nhqkpmThUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/JhjbF1kOf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/Oepw8nCGXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>