<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the end of the world as we know it, and I feel fine... ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh is this nonsense supposed to start at a certain time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: gary bettman eat dog shit if the nhl player dont play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck it's almost Christmas and I haven't watched Home Alone yet... ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 you better be careful with that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever has Simpsons tapped out for iPhone at me up jonj1606]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws @elliottbaron your on the game hard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show of hands, who wants to get up at 6am and work for me tomorrow? ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte as long as it wasn't stupid Lisa garbage face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte I was so pissed skupin didn't win ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She looks like a goblin lmfaaooo @UnkleKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets go Skupin! #Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivor Finale!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amanda_malik19: Going to Walmart to get snacks for the 3hr finale of survivor!!! #survivorfinale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bensanity_15: Going commando to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iMax2021: "I'm a real nigga, giving feelings just ain't me, the more attention you give them, the more options they seek."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh @brieetaang lmao Cummin got ya ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alannamitch me too! â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh @brieetaang ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shots shots shots #Champs #Yagerbombs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh oh yea I'm talkin about Shoeless btw Brie said she mentioned it to ya, hope to see you there ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh fuck that I wanna be apart of the orgasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh no worries just make sure your fine asses are there Sat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte added!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 tell that to @the_ironsheik he was talking shit about him earlier lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik hell ya! Your the man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte what's your username]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeeBudge @melaniec55 you my friend have not been living...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh you guys suck not reaching Nash! Don't fade Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 jobber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge oh and the yellow one Trini died in a car crash in 01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 mmmmmm Quinn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge the red one is bigger now and the green one is in mma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 @chellatamby91 it's legit too cuz a lot of the crap on it is stuff that they haven't put on the other DVDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge you'll think I'm fucked but I bored one day and watched comic con panels online of fans asking da green and red ?s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: Obama urges NHL and union to 'do right by your fans' http://t.co/CgIaqEer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeeBudge @melaniec55 yup that's what intrigued me to watch, I used to love her off till the green ranger spoiled my fantasies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 @chellatamby91 I got the attitude era bluray no more blurring they settled the lawsuit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge oh damn really? How many seasons was it? I know it's a Canadian show but I don't know much about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: metta world peace of shit or peace of real?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: melo impress me and i give his wife old country if i want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 yuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 tbh why don't you take your ball and shove it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge yeaaa when I heard she was on I watched and actually enjoyed the episode I saw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 shut up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 tbh why don't you take your ball and shove it up your candy ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniec55 @ameebudge not trying to intrude but flashpoint is legit Amy Jo Johnson is in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do they employ people at Walmart to work in electronics if they don't know shit about anything? ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your gonna have negative opinions all the time and shoot down positivity then stfu cause nobody cares what you have to say anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT SURVIVOR TONIGHT! ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, Christmas is right around the corner ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 Kev, Kev get a plate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work done. Team bring it strong letssss gooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your gonna dress like a slut on da bus at least be good looking, common woman ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Na Na Na Nash tomorrow! ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: Today is the Happy Hump Day but for the @chrisbrown mother it is the the Happy your son eat dog shit and fuck yoursel ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenWalker7 congrats dude that's crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ausduh: sexpress yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasinaysmith that's what I was gonna say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik your the man Sheikie but so is Romo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow me up on Instagram JonJ1606]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justina_barton laa laa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amanda_malik19: Somebody just egged my car....like what the fuck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: Have A Nice Day and go fuck yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work -__-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bottoms up, hoes down let's get this shit started!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It smells like someone took a shit on this bus like seriously, learn how to shower people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: The #HappyFriday to everyone accept that no good motherfucker Gary Bettman. He big time jabroni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 don't hate hockey's the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ssnyder1835 between you and @GregCapullo who's Batman and who's Nightwing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Survivor_Tweet I think Lisa's a scumbag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ @wwedustyrhodes funny guy Jr!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte :( well I won't spoil it for you, happy studying! Hope you do we'll and we'll see you soon :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte I already had a couple sips though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte I have a double double for you and I'm assuming your not watching survivor in the learning commons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanessa_orz no worries :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanessa_orz don't let the losers get ya down, you know your better than dem anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanessa_orz fool you thrice you must just be too damn nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justina_barton fuck snapbacks.... Fitttttttttteds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 definitely not important enough to discuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K your definitely a stupid dumb bitch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRock: Success - chase it. 

Respect - earn it. 

Love - embrace it. 

#TeamBringIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospital interview, session, survivor, sleep.  #TeamBringIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh I'm surprised dis fweeeezin girl didn't enjoy her soup from timmies then :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh mmhmm ps stop bein so angry with your tweets try and have a good day :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh it did the trick for moi this morning :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck, got my hopes up about the lockout being over ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 @handley_9 lol yessss Hudley!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's just thirsty for it. Lmao! @Chellatamby91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me how I just won an iPad at my Christmas party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRock: 5:38am. Los Angeles.

Do today what they won't, so tomorrow you accomplish what they can't. 

#TeamBringIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iMax2021 ðŸ’¤ðŸ‘ŽðŸƒâœˆðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iMax2021 your mom is wrong, and she also sent you to the attic to sleep with fuller on the hide a bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iMax2021 shut the hell up Home Alone could exist at any time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: RGIII go to hall of fame for most sex with white girls]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>