<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Pollution from Freeway Extends Further Than Previously Thought: Environmental health researchers from UCLA, .. http://tinyurl.com/mvx7qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Crude Reality of Peak Production: If crude oil can double in value with the world in recession, just imagine.. http://tinyurl.com/lakjuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Proof of Global Warming: “The multiple frosts that have blanketed Western Canada in the last week are th.. http://tinyurl.com/l3t8fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rave Polar Cities To Save Us: Global Warming: The James E. Lovelock Virutal Museum of Climate Retreat Living Pod.. http://tinyurl.com/nolcyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: Global Warming: Question: Is it getting hot or what?
We hear about global warming all the time, but do .. http://tinyurl.com/kl9wnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming Myths And Those Who Cannot Count: If, as I suspect, global warming is real but not catastrophic i.. http://tinyurl.com/m7xu6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Warming, Man-Made? Not So Much&#8230;: Some researchers believe that the solar cycle influences global cl.. http://tinyurl.com/njy8pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have it Your Way - Global Warming is Baloney: Thank goodness for the Brits! Not only is British Politics swingin.. http://tinyurl.com/kthanv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking water from air humidity http://ping.fm/FQukw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bacteria From The Deep Can Clean Up Heavy Metals http://ping.fm/nSd8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Rural Land Use Too Important To Be Left To Farmers?  http://ping.fm/POEsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Trees and Soil, Not Just Cleaner Coal-UN http://ping.fm/p7aos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Satellite Detects Red Glow to Map Global Ocean Plant Health http://ping.fm/5paHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bacteria From The Deep Can Clean Up Heavy Metals: A species of bacteria, isolated from sediments deep under the .. http://tinyurl.com/ms3azh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Rural Land Use Too Important To Be Left To Farmers?: As demands on rural land increase and we are all having .. http://tinyurl.com/lodeyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking Water From Air Humidity: Not a plant to be seen, the desert ground is too dry. But the air contains wat.. http://tinyurl.com/nvq729]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[test2: test2 http://tinyurl.com/nt763o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[test: test http://tinyurl.com/nhnsmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yahoo: yahoo http://tinyurl.com/ntefrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chu Calls for Global Warming Action: U.S. Energy Secretary Steven Chu expressed optimism that the world will avo.. http://tinyurl.com/q9cbyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cap & Trade And Global Cooling: There is a well-publicized campaign around the world to reverse the alleged impa.. http://tinyurl.com/qgtbgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunspots and Global Cooling?: During the past year the sun has become VERY quiet.  What that means is that the n.. http://tinyurl.com/r5wqgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cap & Trade And Global Cooling  http://ping.fm/IC8em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chu Calls for Global Warming Action  http://ping.fm/2TN47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Environment Days Study: Sindh Facing Major Environmental Disaster: Expressing grave concerns over the ramp.. http://tinyurl.com/pgq9gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backgrounder: World Environment Day: The world will witness and celebrate the 38th World Environment Day (WED) o.. http://tinyurl.com/rarm24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backgrounder: World Environment Day http://ping.fm/hosvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM calls for greener Laos on World Environment Day http://ping.fm/Ww4sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biofuels discounted on World Environment Day http://ping.fm/OcoKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Environment Day to be celebrated in UAE  http://ping.fm/R9TAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Activities To Do On World Environment Day  http://ping.fm/LtHw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biofuels discounted on World Environment Day: Good news for eco-friendly drivers filling up on fuel as celebrati.. http://tinyurl.com/pcp4tt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Environment Day to be celebrated in UAE: Movies, tree planting and corporate initiatives are taking place .. http://tinyurl.com/pmg3j7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Activities To Do On World Environment Day: On Friday evening, Oxford Bookstore, in collaboration with Pear.. http://tinyurl.com/ouo3vc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time To Catch Up On Recycling  for more http://ping.fm/rWtMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bing test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://lifeofearth.org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time To Catch Up On Recycling: A Blenheim woman has called on the Marlborough District Council to take its own z.. http://tinyurl.com/n69fcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Global Face of Recycling: Many of us are aware of how the U.S. approaches recycling, but have we ever taken .. http://tinyurl.com/mqxq5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Event to Aid WREN: Wondering what to do with that old television, computer monitor or appliance that i.. http://tinyurl.com/ncfnhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Resolutions Are on City Agenda: Several resolutions changing the recycling process in the city will be.. http://tinyurl.com/mfs82y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time To Catch Up On Recycling  http://bit.ly/M14HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Global Face of Recycling  http://bit.ly/WP4K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Plant Fire Smoke Not Toxic: Faragher  http://bit.ly/181lQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Resolutions Are on City Agenda http://bit.ly/2ExbTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Event to Aid WREN http://bit.ly/U4OzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really Interesting http://bit.ly/vArqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling Plant Fire Smoke Not Toxic: Faragher: The Minister for the Environment, Donna Faragher, says a thoroug.. http://tinyurl.com/lzv8yt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pilot Recycling Scheme Under Way: An environmentally friendly project rewarding households with points based on .. http://tinyurl.com/ly8mf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No kidding: State’s Serious About Recycling: So what’s with this Ronald T.W. King guy?
He turned his recycling b.. http://tinyurl.com/lnc4fy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few Rules for Recycling Electronics: Jeffrey L. Nixon, the owner of an electronics-recycling company called Eart.. http://tinyurl.com/ktrq24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change Making Everest Harder to Scale: A sherpa who holds the world record for climbing Everest has warn.. http://tinyurl.com/nejc9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker Outlines 4 Key Changes In Climate Change Bill: Federal climate change legislation recently approved in .. http://tinyurl.com/knd6zs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten Reasons Why Population Control Can’t Stop Climate Change: Without doubt, climate change is the greatest chal.. http://tinyurl.com/mubd4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Slams Democrat&#8217;s Climate Change Bill: A climate bill championed by Democrats in Congress and endorsed .. http://tinyurl.com/kuu7yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change Not Black And White Issue: It is a topic with political, social, and economic implications far be.. http://tinyurl.com/nooudq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to select your Summer Vacation Destination?: Have you and your family made the decision to plan a summer vac.. http://tinyurl.com/la3wsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recyclables Are Still Being Dumped in Landfill: Our house is resembling Steptoe&#8217;s Yard these days with &#8.. http://tinyurl.com/l4qujg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Moves to Improve Car Efficiency: President Barack Obama has announced groundbreaking plans to make cars mo.. http://tinyurl.com/kvkme9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environment Muddle Oil Outlook: A global economic downturn, lower but lately rising oil prices and an aggressive.. http://tinyurl.com/ntt96k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Global Warming Laws Protect Poor People?: Heat waves, droughts and floods affect poor people disproportionat.. http://tinyurl.com/nj94l8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab Free Latest Database  of Handicraft Suppliers http://www.hellotrade.com/business/handicrafts/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Huge List of Fashion Jewelry Suppliers http://bit.ly/vup1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The National Stationery Show http://bit.ly/dy0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming Soon Chinaplas http://events.hellotrade.com/tradeshows/chinaplas/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming Soon FEIMAFE http://events.hellotrade.com/tradeshows/feimafe/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming Soon Intersolar Expo http://bit.ly/73aQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advise About California Craft Shows http://bit.ly/g2cWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding California Craft Shows http://bit.ly/dnj2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Enterprise in California Craft Fairs http://bit.ly/6mjA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eco-Friendly Decorating Ideas at Craft Fairs http://bit.ly/A9Kyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia Construction Frenzy Needs Green Injection: Powered by solar energy generated on its roof, Taipei 101, the w.. http://tinyurl.com/ckukhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Poll: Global Warming Can be Stopped: A new national poll indicates that a majority of Americans think that g.. http://tinyurl.com/d6gcxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Select Chandeliers? http://bit.ly/jx9Nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crafts Selling Made Easy- Home Party Craft Shows http://bit.ly/19sJo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane Warning: In Hot Water http://bit.ly/14m7bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Katrina Hurricane Will be Increase in 2015 http://lifeofearth.org/2009/07/hurricanes.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Katrina Hurricane Will be Increase in 2015 http://ping.fm/WI2Lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane Warning: In Hot Water http://ping.fm/TOwdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane Warning: In Hot Water: Last year was no fluke. The mighty Atlantic conveyor belt is in high gear, and .. http://tinyurl.com/ljmz2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricanes: Hurricanes are giant, spiraling tropical storms that can pack wind speeds of over 160 miles (257 kil.. http://tinyurl.com/nfg9cu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife Fishing Provides You Free Summer Fun  http://ping.fm/1Ghgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife Fishing Provides You Free Summer Fun http://bit.ly/PEuhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Climate Change Deniers Guilty of Treason?: It seems as though the so-called skeptics have really gotten unde.. http://tinyurl.com/n56hge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife Fishing Provides You Free Summer Fun: With his Texas-rigged plastic lure deployed in this small portion.. http://tinyurl.com/l8l5py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directory of Human Infectious Diseases http://ping.fm/CLwDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directory of Human Infectious Diseases http://www.iamunwell.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Download Upcoming Maruti Suzuki SX4 Model Wallpapers http://bit.ly/1uq6Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Download Upcoming Maruti Suzuki SX4 Model Wallpapers http://ping.fm/SNDbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Save Earth From Human Activities http://lifeofearth.org/earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Save Earth From Human Activities? http://ping.fm/dnnfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-Mexico Border Wall Could Threaten Wildlife Species: A 700-mile security wall under construction along the Uni.. http://tinyurl.com/mpn9ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive Growth Of Life On Earth Fueled By Early Greening Of Planet: Earth&#8217;s 4.5-billion-year history is .. http://tinyurl.com/kv87no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&#8216;Hotspots&#8217; Of Human Impact On Coastal Areas Ranked: Coastal marine ecosystems are at risk worldwide .. http://tinyurl.com/nt28yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Summit Focused on Economy, Climate Change http://ping.fm/2NUTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Summit: Feed the Hungry or Fuel Hunger? http://ping.fm/2Z7yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Agrees To New Climate Change Targets http://ping.fm/j1Mk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Summit: Feed the Hungry or Fuel Hunger?: As the rich Group of 8 (G8) nations convene in L&#8217;Aquila, Italy.. http://tinyurl.com/lwxpf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Agrees To New Climate Change Targets: The leaders of the world&#8217;s biggest economies ended their first da.. http://tinyurl.com/mw5vep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G8 Summit Focused on Economy, Climate Change: Leaders of the world&#8217;s eight major industrial countries, mee.. http://tinyurl.com/nkkh98]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>