<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/F6OZBClQq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/Tf9b6Rsp57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/fQgWraCaCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/VfGb5PMmIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/syDhROc7V7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/2ukMIiuNmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/IRLAHz0TIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/m3EuGunVCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/8vr4jIrSMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/6W9ScNbu6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/S4MRFkmsDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/D4slshSHHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/EKgxyLnXhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/QM8Mz6Ks45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/GFdHmiDMxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/XgUJkMXIx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/1aGZewFPa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/c37l8hFyzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/hxaFFfhwlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/QNSDgH9AVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/399xv1f5pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/4kQpvVmTll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/wHnUlBirE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/rzPn7cq4XY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/b2DUbUrRi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/9dgourL5tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/rIL2Zwv53B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/dUXELRwZsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/8ywUmcA6co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/ivMSCyPtge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/xgiJcw9Pj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/6G4iR3Uh2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/oGaKYvBqoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/BNMqHFrr3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/FCXantMGiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/WmTEFaptwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/KFOtXkKihd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/Ysxt8OO53u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/H6nrBa3OID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/XSAoAZpYIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/ox26GkgdS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/GnEOxi8x5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/6shrOXniov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/UtpjLRHMlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/0FHMr29IW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chiffons   http://t.co/x1LDC06axL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>