<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/ncILXBmxAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/w4k1Wc2mDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/9n4TcwGz3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/uf4Ivyu42Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/aQDuNd19Bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/W38cHLPnNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/bSwGM3clGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/eLARNlxgWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/iRxe0SHoS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/zs7TvOvc6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of The Hollywood Sign  http://t.co/cz0smWzn5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/RB8oWX57Ik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last words to the 'Star Spangled Banner?' 'Play ball!' - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/aT5jsZp9qT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/CvuLkfUAdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/mGX1eeHBBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/1RkJi5baKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/PP3fFQ4KOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/A7dMn3Bx9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/wxuaEbpuxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/loq3fKy1bL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/N7QB0YM2CK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/qKXCh7cVC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/nukRaIGgdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/bo3fsdS6EL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/aIZBZ1Xj5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/bYFgrV15P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/slFM5f8qmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/azuV8ezY6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/K5XpJrAN4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/V95uEAzrUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/99yKZJcXI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/cYY2JP9Pjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/udwq39ZIx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/Gu7kSLV3XM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/qWgCIB7HXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/JUsVcT9aM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/qKXCh7cVC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/fcQDgwujxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/5IIstxwgwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/kTcECo1eyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/YLDnjNyVba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/oshzftVLCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/5WagjHDy0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/yXmNd9urcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/0FRUoEwBpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/G5znaqVcGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/FITI6n9ulc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>