<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[JEG: Africa is on time http://t.co/KQLTfvzSYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Nudging to use: Achieving safe water behaviors in Kenya and Bangladesh http://t.co/pzU1cuOZjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Entrepreneurship policy and globalization http://t.co/7AyV6ir6i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Economic inequality in the Arab region http://t.co/kHqyXx5kFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: The African Financial Development and Financial Inclusion Gaps http://t.co/QHX304KOic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Why don’t households invest in latrines: health, prestige, or safety? http://t.co/V0Zuvwgpd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Inequality of Opportunity in Health in Indonesia http://t.co/u3a8FeWuyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Saving More to Borrow Less: Experimental Evidence from Access to Formal Savings Accounts in Chile http://t.co/gEZQCxWMCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Why Don't Remittances Appear to Affect Growth? - Working Paper 366 http://t.co/rnLa2sd38d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of cash and food transfers: Evidence from a randomized intervention in Niger: http://t.co/i92uxaQbXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Women’s individual and joint property ownership: Effects on household decisionmaking: http://t.co/uJy277U05n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Inequality of opportunity and economic growth : a cross-country analysis http://t.co/jaP1uMjJlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Development as Diffusion: Manufacturing Productivity and Sub-Saharan Africa’s Missing Middle - Working ... http://t.co/2XNtY9KDE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Development Reduce Migration? - Working Paper 359 http://t.co/OtnLnGX0rJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Quality healthcare and health insurance retention: Evidence from a randomized experiment in the Kolkata slums: http://t.co/NDzGyouP60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Encouraging health insurance for the informal sector : a cluster randomized trial http://t.co/A8zOZlVpG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Acute morbidity and labor outcomes in Mexico: Testing the role of labor contracts as an income smoothing ... http://t.co/yXqMvSgvwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Migration and Development Research Is Moving Far beyond Remittances - Working Paper 365 http://t.co/bYOCz7FD18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Seasonal Credit Constraints and Agricultural Labor Supply: Evidence from Zambia http://t.co/bPk0kIUtSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Non-contributory pensions http://t.co/2g3NqMzWSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Bases, Bullets and Ballots: the Effect of U.S. Military Aid on Political Conflict in Colombia -- by Oein... http://t.co/FPtMHtNNF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Assessing the Price-Raising Effect of Non-Tariff Measures in Africa http://t.co/AbrS1p4hZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Household cooking fuel choice and adoption of improved cookstoves in developing countries : a review http://t.co/1oPk2d3WB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Tackling Social Exclusion: Evidence from Chile http://t.co/Hd6l1TeJSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The price of empowerment : experimental evidence on land titling in Tanzania http://t.co/dF8dWTCgts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Child labor and learning http://t.co/VijQOmr0le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Directing remittances to education with soft and hard commitments : evidence from a lab-in-the-field ex... http://t.co/lsXuCRBAXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Progress toward the health MDGs : are the poor being left behind ? http://t.co/dupu9ZjUNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Political Reservation for Minorities Affect Child Labor? Evidence from India http://t.co/lYCPFSNTGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Child Mortality in sub-Saharan Africa: Why Public Health Spending Matters http://t.co/OPManSCWWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Effects of interventions to raise voluntary enrollment in a social health insurance scheme : a cluster ... http://t.co/eWNovwLgAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The harmony of programs package: Quasi-experimental evidence on deworming and canteen interventions in ... http://t.co/rKh27uHCJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: CROP DIVERSIFICATION AND CHILD HEALTH: EMPIRICAL EVIDENCE FROM TANZANIA http://t.co/uln60Em1xQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An African Growth Miracle? http://t.co/cWuaNwEjCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Informality and Development http://t.co/KvmWV1x431]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Estimating the Impact of Microcredit on Those Who Take It Up: Evidence from a Randomized Experiment in Morocco http://t.co/AxUTdI8m1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: The Need for Enemies; http://t.co/RK67HuN33T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Impact of South–South FDI and Trade on the Export Upgrading of African Economies http://t.co/TqAi76y8Lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Aid effectiveness in Ghana: How’s the L’Aquila food security initiative doing?: http://t.co/t9Qbf0S0DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Changing Norms about Gender Inequality in Education: Evidence from Bangladesh http://t.co/XHDAmghqG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can market-based approaches to technology development and dissemination benefit women smallholder farme... http://t.co/67ZaKvALOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of shocks on gender-differentiated asset dynamics in Bangladesh: http://t.co/iSwBR9rknN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can Elected Minority Representatives Affect Health Worker Visits? Evidence from India http://t.co/hCxniS4oLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Food prices, road infrastructure, and market integration in Central and Eastern Africa http://t.co/5FJmwwESUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Seeing is believing ? evidence from an extension network experiment http://t.co/kS0VHkvC1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: It's All in the Timing:Household Expenditure and Labor Supply Responses to Unconditional Cash Transfers. http://t.co/pN4FE9FSMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Aid is good for the poor http://t.co/V8vyhsjLsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Mobile phone coverage and producer markets : evidence from West Africa http://t.co/qSIlz8fURB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittances after natural disasters: Evidence from the 2004 Indian tsunami http://t.co/aHaM0tFv1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Methods of Identification in Social Networks -- by Bryan S. Graham http://t.co/8JmHQiwwgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Determinants of Empowerment in a Capability-Based Poverty Approach: Evidence from The Gambia http://t.co/NbgmDEBPwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: International remittances and financial inclusion in Sub-Saharan Africa http://t.co/SJ1UvsZu9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: International trade, the gender wage gap and female labor force participation http://t.co/d2gZ6icEsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Brothers, household financial markets and savings rate in China http://t.co/xQEMXphAJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Land Market Restrictions, Women's Labor Force Participation and Wages http://t.co/iopzLcIzcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Kinship and Consumption: The Effect of Spouses' Outside Options on Household Productivity http://t.co/iLxPxXlEBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: District Governance and Student Learning in Indonesia http://t.co/FePH58Y7vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Bargaining power and biofortification: The role of gender in adoption of orange sweet potato in Uganda: http://t.co/Et75Y8U2cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How Has the Developing World Changed since the Late 1990s? A Dynamic and Multidimensional Taxonomy of D... http://t.co/1PysIMBJPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Politics Before Pupils? Electoral Cycles and School Resources in India http://t.co/gDzHboFS7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Manufacturing Growth and the Lives of Bangladeshi Women http://t.co/Tosbp33rUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Are Cash Transfers a Silver Bullet? Evidence from the Zambian Child Grant http://t.co/DzcB4aZmK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Intensive Margin of Technology Adoption - Experimental Evidence on Improved Cooking Stoves in Rural... http://t.co/SnzkVuZZNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Air Pollution and Respiratory Ailments among Children in Urban India: Exploring Causality http://t.co/09thxJaRuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Private Sector Participation and Performance of Urban Water Utilities in China http://t.co/cmeuKFq4tN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: The Informal Sector Wage Gap: New Evidence Using Quantile Estimations on Panel Data http://t.co/dYJb737UN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Education and Household Welfare http://t.co/MNd8Qg5CDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Poverty-growth-Inequality Triangle: The Case of Indonesia http://t.co/tZeUZH5VM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Social Factors Affecting Women's Susceptibility to HIV in India http://t.co/o3ikcuiPCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Minimum wage and informality in Ecuador http://t.co/yeQH5zZETb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Is Democracy Eluding Sub-Saharan Africa? http://t.co/De9yTfUGMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Using evidence and operational responses to accelerate gender equality in Kenya http://t.co/JXHiDj8xOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Education Transfers, expenditures and child labour supply in Indonesia: An evaluationof impacts and fly... http://t.co/pwKuRABumJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Determinants of School Choice:Evidence from Rural Punjab, Pakistan http://t.co/dIDdDgZxjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Girls for Sale? Child Sex Ratio and Girls Trafficking in India http://t.co/iUJ22Pn0lO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender inequality, female leadership, and aid allocation: A panel analysis of aid for education http://t.co/ye1OyBfifL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Delinking Land Rights from Land Use: Certification and Migration in Mexico http://t.co/iNIvDx0FMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of Village Savings and Loans Associations: Evidence from a Cluster Randomized Trial http://t.co/Zf5eh2c2DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Worker Mobility in a Global Labor Market: Evidence from the United Arab Emirates -- by Suresh Naidu, Yaw... http://t.co/9Wya4E8Vy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Damming the Commons: An Empirical Analysis of International Cooperation and Conflict in Dam Location -- ... http://t.co/4A7yn3suHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Evidence for Relational Contracts in Sovereign Bank Lending -- by Peter Benczur, Cosmin L. Ilut http://t.co/fQcE0M0DQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: The effects of exporting on wages: An evaluation using the 1999 Brazilian exchange rate devaluation http://t.co/jt3QCUTz2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An Empirical Investigation of the Calorie Consumption Puzzle in India http://t.co/IXxBjYAAGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: What is Behind Latin America’s Declining Income Inequality? http://t.co/F0Jd1vxqDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Health shocks and coping strategies: State health insurance scheme of Andhra Pradesh, India http://t.co/sY31a81pV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Beyond the field: Impact of Farmer Field Schools on food security and poverty alleviation http://t.co/MiNloJfAHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Propaganda and Conflict: Evidence from the Rwandan Genocide http://t.co/t0wihyLlms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An Empirical Investigation into Measurement and Determinants of Food Security in Slums of Kolkata http://t.co/nd3vKNgy9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittances and sustainability of family livelihoods in Zimbabwe: Case Study of Chegutu Town http://t.co/jqG96cgWhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An Enquiry into the Sluggish Growth of Workers’ Remittance Determinants in Bangladesh http://t.co/pxfGTL66Sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How Migrant Heterogeneity Influences the Effect of Remittances on Educational Expenditure:Empirical Evi... http://t.co/NwuyNxDF26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Foreign aid effectiveness in African economies: Evidence from a panel threshold framework http://t.co/Po4gcKKs5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Access to Piped Water and Human Capital Formation - Evidence from Brazilian Primary Schools http://t.co/qjiH25VmrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can Microfinance Reach the Poorest: Evidence from a Community-Managed Microfinance Intervention http://t.co/PTh3f6lyDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Should Parents Work Away from or Close to Home? The Effect of Temporary Parental Absence on Child Pover... http://t.co/0iMlGziAh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Transfers for extreme poverty reduction: Implications for patron-client relationships in the context of... http://t.co/eLLUQWZHDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Transitions in a West African Labour Market: The Role of Family Networks http://t.co/XN5qQwEo1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Poor, the Prosperous and the ?Inbetweeners?: A Fresh Perspective on Global Society, Inequality and Growth http://t.co/a7SyNx9XAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Impact of Shocks on Gender-differentiated Asset Dynamics in Bangladesh http://t.co/zOxO9I3uFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Shelter from the Storm: Upgrading Housing Infrastructure in Latin American Slums http://t.co/cExZmwev9M]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>