<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know your audience. Display strength to Klingons, logic to Vulcans, and opportunity to Ferengi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Used sparingly, some light swearing can help emphasize your damn point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let upper management dismantle your team, nor your team members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Admitting one's failures is a sign of confidence and strength. It reassures others that failing is okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Even if computers can talk now, remember how deeply stupid they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep up with new technologies. Today you get a holodeck, but tomorrow could bring a holographic doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The least you can do is to make everyone onboard feel acknowledged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're on red alert every day, then red alert means nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Try to understand more than half of the technobabble. Ask for metaphors to explain the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: If your organization won't install fuses, don't touch any consoles while your ship is under attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your superiors are just as fallible as you are. It's okay to talk back to them. Just do it respectfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Create an atmosphere of trust, not fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a realistic understanding of what your ship can and cannot do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: Antimatter is not a toy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In a strange new environment, be wary of making changes until you understand more about what's going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It takes hard work to become a master at single-tasking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: "That's the way it's always been" is never an adequate reason to continue doing something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tell your employees when they do well, even if you believe they are empathic and can read your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard multiversal tip: Be careful; not even a Jedi or a Time Lord can withstand Vogon poetry. So say we all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: The enemy of my enemy is sometimes a dangerous sociopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard emergency tip: When all else fails, route main power through the main deflector dish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Forgive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Good crew members love what they do. Get off their backs and let them enjoy their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Obedience never lasts long when it's based solely on punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't underestimate the college intern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Fight for what you know is right. Only arrogant bullies think resistance is futile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't scoff at anything. You don't know as much as you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Give your experts time for unstructured play. It makes them more creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Study history. The answers are there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Hone your inner bullshit detector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard sanity tip: If there are four lights, say there are four lights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Get your own damn work done. Others will follow suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: Don't fall in love with holograms, even if your friends do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your first impulse will often be wrong, but you have to start somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Improve your vocabulary by reading books. Words can be your most powerful tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Have an opinion on one side of an issue. Stay out of the neutral zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let a crew member's age blind you to their skill level, in either direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Calm the hell down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Not all Klingons are violent. Don't be racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Yes, the uniforms are tight, but please, eyes up here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Expecting people to work long hours is short-sighted, counter-productive, and potentially dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard rationality tip: There is no such thing as a ghost or a devil. It's just an alien. It's always an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Adopt the latest technologies right away, even if they're in beta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Add to the group energy of the room, or leave. Don't be bored. Don't be boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Malfunctioning systems must be fixed right away. There is no excuse for delaying repairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Break a complex, urgent problem into subcomponents, one for each of your lieutenants to solve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Once all their basic human needs are taken care of, crew members are motivated by the meaningfulness of their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard responsibility tip: Don't leave known, wide-scale problems behind for the next generation to solve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If a crew member needs to become more responsible, give them more responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take some alone time. The crew will be fine without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard education tip: The important things will never be on your exams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When crew members are unsuccessful, urge them to try again. Encouragement and persistence may be all they need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Maintain a slight air of mystery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Everyone's a critic, but some criticisms are more correct than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Some of your decisions are going to be mistakes. You have to make them anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Use the metric system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you build up enough reputation, people will listen to any drivel you say. They'll even repeat it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The best creative solutions should come from your crew, not from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep group meetings short. Take your time with one-on-ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Standard procedures are just suggestions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The universe is a ridiculous place, but do try to be dignified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard theology tip: Unproven gods are hypotheses waiting to be tested. Proven gods are aliens with better technology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Most conflict arises out of confusion. Clarify quickly before weapons power up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Empower others to command when you are unfit. You never know when your mind will be taken over by an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Succeeding at the very last second is still succeeding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Engage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In an emergency, don't be afraid to let the crew see you in your pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard devops tip: When in doubt, launch a probe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Withhold advice on matters you do not understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Results are more important than protocol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you've recently turned into a monster, go take a vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard exploration tip: Yes, there are 400 billion galaxies, but it will take 1,000 lifetimes to map this one, so let's focus for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Remember what you liked to play with as a child. Identify the larger, grown-up versions of those toys at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard programming tip: A computer is like a mischievous genie. It will give you exactly what you ask for, but not always what you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When a crew member's behavior changes significantly, inquire and investigate. It could be important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be on the same side as the crew, not against them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a reputation for completing missions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If specific implementation details are important, then include them when giving the order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Intuition is valuable, but it's not a substitute for facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: You are a dignitary representing your organization, always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Once in a long while, pilot the shuttlecraft yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Time is the rarest commodity. Manage yours wisely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard recursive tip: http://t.co/z8rmqhZVrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The most successful discussions happen in person, not over phone, email, or view screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Starfleet doesn't want officers who will blindly follow orders without analyzing the situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: One mission at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard coping tip: When your government shuts down, you… should… um… http://t.co/cSEjsp2HaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's okay to be gentle and kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard safety tip: Don't leave Earth without a replicator.

"@NASA preparing to launch 3D printer into space" http://t.co/UISRy45uwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it so the crew feel welcome and appreciated. Remember there are other starships they could transfer to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard technology tip: Advanced systems aren't necessarily easy to use. Improve the interfaces, or try pushing buttons at random.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Humility without confidence is sheepishness. Confidence without humility is arrogance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Debate honestly. The goal is to arrive at the truth, not at your preconception.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Get excited about your work. Your excitement is contagious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Having too many leaders is indistinguishable from having too few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If your team is outstanding, have a camera crew chronicle your work and stream it on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you're threatened with catastrophe, it's rational to try a risky maneuver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Sometimes you just have to bow to the absurd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Videoconference with your mortal enemies. The results may surprise you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>