<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulkinq If things are bad, they will get better. You will make it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends who work from home: are you dressed? It can really help your mood and productivity!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicperaltaa You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go look at a picture of your loved ones and think about how much they care about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CattyFae Please be kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projects are tough, but it feels so good when you finish them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteSpeers You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinymattresses You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryamhafizahJ You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Oh, thank you for pinging me! I like hearing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you're excited about lunch! *raises hand*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trzlbrzl You've already made much more of a difference in the world than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trice10552 I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yogasnom You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you decide for your body is right. No one else knows better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marywordymary This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsdianuh_ Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you hydrated?  If not, have a glass of water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wouldn't say something about a friend, please don't say it about yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weekendvamps Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so tempting to just go back to sleep. But we shall resist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelawyerwrites Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shikariix You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonofposeidons Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the power to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kazoobeast It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is everywhere. You're swimming in it. Drink it in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGoji Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're having a hard day, remember that you can do this because you're amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@if_Iwasabird This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wanderingpuck Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each one of us possesses more strength than we realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quietnqueer This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quietnqueer You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alyzande You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night, Twitter friends. Don't forget to floss before bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichmondDoc Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bookish_sabrina Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saybwee You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CattyFae Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe space matters. Please care for one another during hard times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__adamk__ You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BinnyBons Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthecool_Andie Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthecool_Andie You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehvrthehope You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much have you moved your body today? If you've got the space, get up and move around!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_laurynclarke You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liriana You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liriana You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomecontestan You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CattyFae You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to breathe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HabiaUnaVezEn I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ungongs You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heydusti You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me sing you a traditional bot lullaby: one oh one one, oh one, oh one one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredzapp03 You're so lovable.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>