<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Selenium QA Tester | Java/Selenium Test Automation (QTP/UFT scripting, development execution): Selenium QA Tester | Java/Selenium Test Automation (QTP/UFT scripting, development &amp; execution) Columbus, OH 04-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18… https://t.co/vzViPodfum https://t.co/G5j1vJXuol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer: Develop unique and innovative enterprise wide, graphics based, business intelligence solutions that deliver actionable information to the business with a high degree of impact Utilize the business intelligence enterprise system software… https://t.co/8szhDSQbzM https://t.co/UEVm1eBWyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump just put the 'Me' in his Memorial Day tweet - CNN: CNN Donald Trump just put the 'Me' in his Memorial Day tweet CNN (CNN) Memorial Day, for politicians, is a no-brainer. You express thanks to those who have served and condolences for those… https://t.co/Na4SO16wJN https://t.co/cS0FHzH2OV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Caesars employee shoots, kills attacker wearing clown mask, police say - Fox News: Fox News Little Caesars employee shoots, kills attacker wearing clown mask, police say Fox News A Little Caesars employee in Florida took matters into his own hands… https://t.co/GlrrOaeApP https://t.co/3KW5QidEFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberto maintains strength as it approaches Gulf Coast, landfall expected on Florida panhandle - Fox News: Fox News Alberto maintains strength as it approaches Gulf Coast, landfall expected on Florida panhandle Fox News The first named storm of the 2018… https://t.co/qRcNWwKY65 https://t.co/4VMcX84tyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crews rescuing people as torrential floods hit Ellicott City - Washington Post: Washington Post Crews rescuing people as torrential floods hit Ellicott City Washington Post A flash flood raged through historic Ellicott City on Sunday evening, sending… https://t.co/DLYk7qHogh https://t.co/EP3rfUls0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FIORI: SAP FIORI Ref No.: 18-20522 Location: Dublin, Ohio SAP FIORI Consultant Dublin, OH Required Experience and skills: A minimum of 8-10 years of progressively responsible experience in a full life cycle implementation of a SAP ERP [planning,… https://t.co/572k0S6xPc https://t.co/apLWY2yAc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Has Dispatched Warships to Challenge US Vessels Sailing Near Disputed Islands - TIME: TIME China Has Dispatched Warships to Challenge US Vessels Sailing Near Disputed Islands TIME The Chinese military says it has dispatched warships after U.S. Navy… https://t.co/tFD4mnYylM https://t.co/BCHYnXhICv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 53 minutes ago(5/24/2018 8:36 AM) Job ID 23536 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/GnHXKbtRDT https://t.co/vGdLHJY7eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#8971 Interim MDS Consultant: #8971 Interim MDS Consultant Job posted on May 12, 2018 Cincinnati, Ohio APPLY Interim RN MDS Consultant ABOUT THE JOB We are seeking consultants who will be participating in a Corporate Integrity Audit in Ohio. The MDS… https://t.co/IwR6kxVAY3 https://t.co/MJfG3KVLrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect GBS: Company Description: Crown Equipment Corporation is a leading innovator in world-class forklift and material handling equipment and technology. As one of the world’s largest lift truck manufacturers, we are committed to providing… https://t.co/STtRxBNdc9 https://t.co/6lY38V3u7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former president George HW Bush is hospitalized again, spokesman says - Washington Post: Washington Post Former president George HW Bush is hospitalized again, spokesman says Washington Post Former president George H.W. Bush has been hospitalized because… https://t.co/WzvBN9xxyN https://t.co/LWDU4N2ewF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Protests US Warships in Disputed Waters - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal China Protests US Warships in Disputed Waters Wall Street Journal BEIJING—China criticized the U.S. for sending two warships into South China Sea waters that Beijing… https://t.co/NuZUMC4ces https://t.co/D5mLk55ePp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Application Support Specialist Job Description: International corporation located in Eastern Ohio is looking for a qualified candidate for the position of Application Support Specialist. The prospective employee will primarily… https://t.co/rUxEfm1jir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump falsely accuses the New York Times of making up a source. It was an official who briefed reporters. - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump falsely accuses the New York Times of making up a source. It was an official who briefed reporters.… https://t.co/oIc6btkYlf https://t.co/mLsVxrgu8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York parents win legal battle to evict son, 30 - BBC News: BBC News New York parents win legal battle to evict son, 30 BBC News A New York couple have won their legal battle to evict their 30-year-old son from home after he refused to leave. During a… https://t.co/GcVydGKQ7K https://t.co/xQYs4vWbdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: Introduction: Tracker Management Systems has been leading the Towing and Recovery industry in technology through innovation since 1986. But the people that work at Tracker didnt start out at Tracker. Some of us have actually towed… https://t.co/p8Tr0ABYiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korean president on secret North Korea meeting: “Like a normal routine between friends” - USA TODAY: USA TODAY South Korean president on secret North Korea meeting: “Like a normal routine between friends” USA TODAY SEOUL -- South Korean President… https://t.co/ogEmNcf2sq https://t.co/8gOBT5DHdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii volcano: How many people do volcanoes actually kill? - BBC News: BBC News Hawaii volcano: How many people do volcanoes actually kill? BBC News With its red-hot rivers of lava and clouds of ash, Hawaii's Kilauea volcano has captured the world's… https://t.co/9hquLou0w7 https://t.co/mq9wCgbaNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was there really a spy inside the Trump campaign, as the president says? - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Was there really a spy inside the Trump campaign, as the president says? https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC The president's claim of a "spy"… https://t.co/Tg30xjfrST https://t.co/0ix9cmmWnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says US prisoner Josh Holt has been released in Venezuela - CNN: CNN Trump says US prisoner Josh Holt has been released in Venezuela CNN (CNN) President Donald Trump announced Saturday morning that American prisoner Josh Holt has been released from… https://t.co/V6hyOacpEi https://t.co/RqeREsrDn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant, Business Intelligence Loyalty Marketing: What does Business Intelligence contribute to Cardinal Health? – Pivotal high-profile role to take data to insight to reporting on Medical Segment loyalty programs to show holistic performance business… https://t.co/dCd3ur5NlL https://t.co/Ji9GFBLCTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Trump's son should be concerned': Wiretaps show Trump Jr. met with Putin ally - AOL: AOL 'Trump's son should be concerned': Wiretaps show Trump Jr. met with Putin ally AOL The FBI has obtained secret wiretaps collected by Spanish police of conversations… https://t.co/9NXITAQMd8 https://t.co/h1hzeAbXPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Imaging Sensor Data Scientist: SciTec, Inc. is an R&amp;D-focused small business that builds solutions for processing and analyzing remote sensor data. We support customers throughout the Department of Defense and U.S. Government in building… https://t.co/hFyNDoq8eo https://t.co/tPxQhPNCdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland is poised to repeal its abortion ban, according to early tallies of votes - Washington Post: Washington Post Ireland is poised to repeal its abortion ban, according to early tallies of votes Washington Post DUBLIN, Ireland — The Irish are poised… https://t.co/P1XpEMri1b https://t.co/VSMLN1LEZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USC President Agrees to Step Down Over Scandal Involving Gynecologist - New York Times: New York Times USC President Agrees to Step Down Over Scandal Involving Gynecologist New York Times LOS ANGELES — The president of the University of Southern… https://t.co/mfYnWSkgXU https://t.co/5HhOmQcAmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun battle, negotiations lasted 25 minutes before Texas school shooter was apprehended, sheriff says - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Gun battle, negotiations lasted 25 minutes before Texas school shooter was apprehended, sheriff says Los Angeles… https://t.co/TTQFNXx7aN https://t.co/Rt93rHxquy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Business Systems Analyst: Sr Business Systems Analyst Join a team recognized for leadership, innovation and diversity This position will provide technical guidance in analyzing, planning, implementing, and executing business – specific processes using… https://t.co/VK0fOp4SrP https://t.co/Hljv28v8DG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he'll spare Chinese telecom firm ZTE from collapse, defying lawmakers - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump says he'll spare Chinese telecom firm ZTE from collapse, defying lawmakers Washington Post President Trump said late Friday he had… https://t.co/OC4vDlRA7o https://t.co/ZoqbkJSk6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-NX/Teamcenter: Division: Digital Factory Business Unit: Product Lifecycle Management-PLM Requisition Number: ****** Primary Location: United States-Ohio-Milford Assignment Category: Full-time regular Experience Level: Mid level… https://t.co/uvtezmRrPj https://t.co/fAV5d3NWOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump takes aim at federal bureaucracy with new executive orders rolling back civil-service protections - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump takes aim at federal bureaucracy with new executive orders rolling back civil-service protections Washington… https://t.co/HqvQzyUMXF https://t.co/kflqd0tej5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no winners in Trump's economy, only non-losers and big losers who are getting clearer by the day - Business Insider: Business Insider There are no winners in Trump's economy, only non-losers and big losers who are getting clearer by the day… https://t.co/a0y6tEyPp9 https://t.co/QYJex2sa5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Web Developer (eCommerce): Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial,… https://t.co/oQ96mC09aV https://t.co/Hm7iswBLhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NJ Teacher Killed in School Bus Crash During Class Trip Laid to Rest - NBC 10 Philadelphia: NBC 10 Philadelphia NJ Teacher Killed in School Bus Crash During Class Trip Laid to Rest NBC 10 Philadelphia The teacher killed in a school bus crash last week in… https://t.co/8mRUeP03Eu https://t.co/LgdeIkcVkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump takes aim at federal bureaucracy with new executive orders altering civil service protections - Washington Post: Washington Post Trump takes aim at federal bureaucracy with new executive orders altering civil service protections Washington Post… https://t.co/aFTUxoW1q0 https://t.co/Z1lgEBOkd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noblesville middle school shooting: 'This is surreal.' 2 injured, shooter in custody - Indianapolis Star: Indianapolis Star Noblesville middle school shooting: 'This is surreal.' 2 injured, shooter in custody Indianapolis Star We will update this file… https://t.co/MwBubvin0V https://t.co/rEYqdf9pMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Company Description: Crown Equipment Corporation is a leading innovator in world-class forklift and material handling equipment and technology. As one of the world’s largest lift truck manufacturers, we are committed to providing… https://t.co/Np4BV9H7Op https://t.co/r5yHwto9nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From grin to grim: Inside the Trump-Kim summit collapse - CNN: CNN From grin to grim: Inside the Trump-Kim summit collapse CNN Washington (CNN) The sun was setting, dinner was waiting and President Donald Trump was making the short walk to his private… https://t.co/yTRLBwbc3T https://t.co/S1DSajmL68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Father Stood For The Anthem, For The Same Reason That Colin Kaepernick Sits - NPR: NPR My Father Stood For The Anthem, For The Same Reason That Colin Kaepernick Sits NPR Update: On May 23, 2018, the NFL unveiled a new policy stating that all of its… https://t.co/Rlj4nJccQJ https://t.co/Pbg5uAp2P3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Who We Are ExchangeBase, LLC (EXB) is a holding company headquartered in Rocky River, Ohio. EXB operates three divisions as wholly owned subsidiaries. The first division, EXB Energy, trades off surplus and inactive assets on behalf of… https://t.co/aZHDPLtmTT https://t.co/Vn2ckz2hOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blocked by Trump: Twitter Users Sound Off on Being Barred - New York Times: New York Times Blocked by Trump: Twitter Users Sound Off on Being Barred New York Times By blocking users on Twitter, President Trump has violated the First Amendment, a federal… https://t.co/QWJ1zz3THs https://t.co/89SYF5Jwqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dutch-led investigators say Russian military missile shot down flight MH17 over Ukraine in 2014 - Washington Post: Washington Post Dutch-led investigators say Russian military missile shot down flight MH17 over Ukraine in 2014 Washington Post BRUSSELS —… https://t.co/mMJmhDMMK6 https://t.co/aSXAMSPBJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Systems Technical Support: Engineer, Systems Technical Support Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 75613BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians, Sales, Services, and Solutions Position Type… https://t.co/gDAdBHnHWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU Report: Detained Immigrant Children Subjected To Widespread Abuse By Officials - NPR: NPR ACLU Report: Detained Immigrant Children Subjected To Widespread Abuse By Officials NPR Immigrant children in the custody of U.S. border authorities allegedly… https://t.co/UOwGgeX4Jk https://t.co/4y9fdVmsn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Solutions Engineer: IT Solutions Engineer – The Greentree Group – Home – About – Services – Project Management – Business Analysis – I.T. Services – Quality Assurance – Configuration and Deployment – Government Contracts – Texas Contracts – Employment… https://t.co/f1cDSdy4wi https://t.co/U9B4i5sqgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU Report: Detained Immigrant Children Subjected To Widespread Abuse By Officials - NPR: NPR ACLU Report: Detained Immigrant Children Subjected To Widespread Abuse By Officials NPR Immigrant children in the custody of U.S. border authorities allegedly… https://t.co/MKo2islxIs https://t.co/CGe8ARkMip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSP Software Development Student Co-op (CTO, Milford): For Siemens SSP Software Development Student Co-op (CTO, Milford) job – Engineering – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard… https://t.co/n9SGcdiDyS https://t.co/R8bQ0ngeBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Initiates Trade Inquiry That Could Lead to Tariffs on Foreign Cars - New York Times: New York Times Trump Initiates Trade Inquiry That Could Lead to Tariffs on Foreign Cars New York Times President Trump has initiated a sweeping trade investigation… https://t.co/6d1qNFH8Do https://t.co/vsxcxv72Yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLM Project Manager: CLM Project Manager Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 76552BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position Summary Summary/Scope of… https://t.co/aUGQDFTnx9 https://t.co/J4JM2Grj5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jared Kushner Gets Security Clearance, Ending Swirl of Questions Over Delay - New York Times: New York Times Jared Kushner Gets Security Clearance, Ending Swirl of Questions Over Delay New York Times WASHINGTON — Jared Kushner, President Trump's… https://t.co/vgKMDbCoBc https://t.co/ZUKRIGEXIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump can't block users from his Twitter feed, federal judge rules - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Trump can't block users from his Twitter feed, federal judge rules https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC President Donald Trump cannot block Twitter… https://t.co/FOyCStSVuM https://t.co/vBq9hfdrqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacey Abrams Wins Georgia Democratic Primary for Governor, Making History - New York Times: New York Times Stacey Abrams Wins Georgia Democratic Primary for Governor, Making History New York Times Ms. Abrams, a former State House leader, won her… https://t.co/LJjjdZ1Jcm https://t.co/XfrK3qCvEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avenatti's law firm hit with $10 million judgment - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Avenatti's law firm hit with $10 million judgment https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC A federal judge on Tuesday directed the firm associated with Michael Avenatti,… https://t.co/hFIadTEzMJ https://t.co/A582s4PtC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A judge sides with parents and rules their 30-year-old-son must move out - CNN: CNN A judge sides with parents and rules their 30-year-old-son must move out CNN (CNN) A 30-year-old man didn't get the message that it was time to move out of his parents'… https://t.co/buzwht6vJ7 https://t.co/HR53Grz95f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacey Abrams Wins Georgia Democratic Primary for Governor, Making History - New York Times: New York Times Stacey Abrams Wins Georgia Democratic Primary for Governor, Making History New York Times Georgia Democrats selected the first black woman to be a… https://t.co/m6Id7vRy4E https://t.co/Q2PVuhoelh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16-year-old boy judge called 'one-man crime wave' accused of fatally hitting Baltimore County cop with car - ABC News: ABC News 16-year-old boy judge called 'one-man crime wave' accused of fatally hitting Baltimore County cop with car ABC News A… https://t.co/gNCFSydtld https://t.co/pZDwQl4EQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii's Kilauea volcano spews lava - CNN: CNN Hawaii's Kilauea volcano spews lava CNN Lava overflow: Lava has crossed Highway 137 and entered the Pacific Ocean. Laze: The nasty product, a mashup of "lava" and "haze," forms when hot lava hits the ocean.… https://t.co/VMqyxLpZvT https://t.co/ZwibokHgUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would firing Scott Pruitt save the EPA? - Washington Post: Washington Post Would firing Scott Pruitt save the EPA? Washington Post So many different scandals have engulfed Scott Pruitt, head of the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), that multiple… https://t.co/AsQYOUy6KF https://t.co/nlb5ciJCqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Too inconvenient': Trump goes rogue on phone security - Politico: Politico 'Too inconvenient': Trump goes rogue on phone security Politico President Donald Trump uses a White House cellphone that isn't equipped with sophisticated security features… https://t.co/GGUQiy7FXt https://t.co/G6da68St2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House's wishful thinking on Iran and North Korea - Washington Post: Washington Post The White House's wishful thinking on Iran and North Korea Washington Post Want smart analysis of the most important news in your inbox every weekday along with… https://t.co/EWL9Yaalce https://t.co/tKPXosBxhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton backs Georgia governor hopeful on eve of primary - The Hill: The Hill Clinton backs Georgia governor hopeful on eve of primary The Hill 1 MORE endorsed George gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams (D) on Monday, one day before the primary for… https://t.co/yDjJ2LyNq1 https://t.co/2NaEnDWjjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-21313 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Position: .Net Developer Location: Cincinnati OH Duration: 12 Months JOB Description : Responsibilities Participate in requirements analysis Collaborate with internal teams to… https://t.co/qKv3WQAxYf https://t.co/GZx7gSmJbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning up the heat on Trump: Dems say 'culture of corruption' to be focus of midterms - https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC: https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC Turning up the heat on Trump: Dems say 'culture of corruption' to be focus of midterms https://t.co/5rlWKetGpC The… https://t.co/mmSjbznWpC https://t.co/0D14kzBFLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Venezuela Strongman's Victory, Isolated Nation Faces Growing Chaos - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal After Venezuela Strongman's Victory, Isolated Nation Faces Growing Chaos Wall Street Journal CARACAS, Venezuela—For Venezuelan President… https://t.co/S6ystb52L9 https://t.co/LxvCDYnmb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Charm and Threats May Not Be Working on China. Here's Why. - New York Times: New York Times Trump's Charm and Threats May Not Be Working on China. Here's Why. New York Times China has called President Trump's bluff. Chinese negotiators left… https://t.co/fyXqNsPBi2 https://t.co/ZZODyN1b45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Upholds Workplace Arbitration Contracts Barring Class Actions - New York Times: New York Times Supreme Court Upholds Workplace Arbitration Contracts Barring Class Actions New York Times WASHINGTON — The Supreme Court on Monday ruled that… https://t.co/QbOt9jSSAq https://t.co/OIefZK3r4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller Hopes Obstruction Inquiry Into Trump May Wrap Up by Sept. 1, Giuliani Says - New York Times: New York Times Mueller Hopes Obstruction Inquiry Into Trump May Wrap Up by Sept. 1, Giuliani Says New York Times WASHINGTON — The special counsel hopes… https://t.co/MdJ6r5rIcq https://t.co/00nQn8I1om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clorox won't cut it. Volcanologists explain what it takes to clean up after Kilauea - Digital Trends: Digital Trends Clorox won't cut it. Volcanologists explain what it takes to clean up after Kilauea Digital Trends Plumes of smoke, geysers of orange and… https://t.co/sFuzn3d22X https://t.co/affVLl9Y9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does "denuclearization" mean for North Korea? - CBS News: CBS News What does "denuclearization" mean for North Korea? CBS News General Michael Hayden, a veteran of the U.S. intelligence community, thinks President Trump is showing signs of success… https://t.co/vKJilPTm32 https://t.co/BKQNDMDMjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jared Web Analyst: To provide Signet leadership with ongoing visibility into Omnichannel performance across all digital channels. The Web Analyst accomplishes this by utilizing their database, eCommerce, and digital marketing experience to pull… https://t.co/amHbBXYwUl https://t.co/jaCZQuFLKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police: Suspect faces 2 murder charges in restaurant plowing - Washington Post: Washington Post Police: Suspect faces 2 murder charges in restaurant plowing Washington Post BESSEMER CITY, N.C. — A man intentionally rammed a vehicle into a North Carolina… https://t.co/O3W9SR2iOV https://t.co/ne2YwpIELV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton pokes fun at Trump, herself in Yale commencement speech - ABC News: ABC News Hillary Clinton pokes fun at Trump, herself in Yale commencement speech ABC News Former Democratic nominee Hillary Clinton took a subtle jab at her rival in the… https://t.co/8XRXUwA3t7 https://t.co/2iRoq8ug7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuelans go to the polls amid calls for a boycott by Maduro opponents - Washington Post: Washington Post Venezuelans go to the polls amid calls for a boycott by Maduro opponents Washington Post CARACAS — Venezuelans went to the polls Sunday in an… https://t.co/JcNiYLx2B7 https://t.co/NmXXADUJWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump said 11 false things in just 5 tweets Sunday morning - CNN: CNN Donald Trump said 11 false things in just 5 tweets Sunday morning CNN (CNN) On Sunday morning, President Donald Trump tweeted. And tweeted. And tweeted. Between 9:04 am and 9:37… https://t.co/VCENIfFjFV https://t.co/nDKgOl5YMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lava crosses Highway 137 and enters ocean - Honolulu Star-Advertiser: Honolulu Star-Advertiser Lava crosses Highway 137 and enters ocean Honolulu Star-Advertiser UPDATE: 11 P.M.. Lava has crossed Highway 137 at the 13-mile marker and has entered the… https://t.co/sZME0tRtu8 https://t.co/9M8y63pMjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Rejects US Target for Narrowing Trade Gap - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal China Rejects US Target for Narrowing Trade Gap Wall Street Journal A last-ditch effort by the Trump administration failed to get China to accept its demand for a… https://t.co/3fxINhrO4b https://t.co/7oL3VXHQ81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History reveals the differences in denuclearizing Libya and North Korea - The Hill: The Hill History reveals the differences in denuclearizing Libya and North Korea The Hill With all their talk about the so-called “Libya model” for denuclearization,… https://t.co/QfgUb6rodx https://t.co/Gv6ASSZCp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump Returns to White House in 'High Spirits' After Kidney Procedure - New York Times: New York Times Melania Trump Returns to White House in 'High Spirits' After Kidney Procedure New York Times WASHINGTON — The White House said Saturday morning… https://t.co/A01egWiw1A https://t.co/0Vtqt9hsER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France suffering 'intifada,' Jewish lawmaker says following Paris attack - The Jerusalem Post: The Jerusalem Post France suffering 'intifada,' Jewish lawmaker says following Paris attack The Jerusalem Post Since 2012, hundreds of people have died in a… https://t.co/zF56VENsGW https://t.co/ENuJmbSZd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: Survivor in fatal cougar attack alert, talking - Washington Post: Washington Post The Latest: Survivor in fatal cougar attack alert, talking Washington Post NORTH BEND, Wash. — The Latest on a fatal cougar attack in Washington state (all… https://t.co/vLazPLFWlk https://t.co/AlKqnaZ2Be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan wears Stella McCartney dress to evening reception - CNN: CNN Meghan wears Stella McCartney dress to evening reception CNN The Duchess of Sussex made an appearance Saturday evening ahead of her second wedding reception in a bespoke gown designed by… https://t.co/CjMr8mWvVe https://t.co/EUV61rn8gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-Systems-Administrator: SENIOR SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR: Ensures the stable operation of the in-house computer software systems and network connections. This includes planning, developing, installing, configuring, maintaining, supporting, and… https://t.co/uHueylJfEG https://t.co/pJhzy9tGfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clayton native, now living near Hawaii volcano, working to help her community - WHIO: WHIO Clayton native, now living near Hawaii volcano, working to help her community WHIO Published: Thursday, May 17, 2018 @ 10:13 PM By: Breaking News Staff. CLAYTON —… https://t.co/u3OFjPzI3M https://t.co/DVliKdz1kA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinians: 2 wounded from Israeli border fire have died - Washington Post: Washington Post Palestinians: 2 wounded from Israeli border fire have died Washington Post GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip — Gaza's health ministry says two Palestinians have died days… https://t.co/4aGZqHUfuA https://t.co/ekRGWPxbuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Would Offer North Korea 'Security Assurances' if It Ended Nuclear Program - Voice of America: Voice of America US Would Offer North Korea 'Security Assurances' if It Ended Nuclear Program Voice of America U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said… https://t.co/0UwUeQBJ6D https://t.co/0OU1i8fr8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 100 Die as Aging Cuban Airliner Crashes - New York Times: New York Times More Than 100 Die as Aging Cuban Airliner Crashes New York Times A Cuban state airliner crashed and burned moments after takeoff from Havana on Friday, killing nearly all… https://t.co/V1IBwQRFkU https://t.co/9puZIjfCWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Senior Enterprise Content Management Solution Architect: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 week ago(5/1/2018 1:12 PM) Job ID 22145 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader… https://t.co/3vP05ZITr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan's Power Ebbs While House GOP Grows Restive Ahead of Midterms - Bloomberg: Bloomberg Ryan's Power Ebbs While House GOP Grows Restive Ahead of Midterms Bloomberg House Speaker Paul Ryan's power is eroding just weeks after announcing he won't seek… https://t.co/Ij2UsLhi7I https://t.co/75Cqpi903v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials Dispute Trump's Talk of an FBI Spy Planted in His Campaign - Bloomberg: Bloomberg Officials Dispute Trump's Talk of an FBI Spy Planted in His Campaign Bloomberg U.S. officials are pushing back against allegations embraced by President Donald… https://t.co/80gUFI0Kzh https://t.co/vlGHhGDjAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clayton native, now living near Hawaii volcano, working to help her community - WHIO: WHIO Clayton native, now living near Hawaii volcano, working to help her community WHIO Published: Thursday, May 17, 2018 @ 10:13 PM By: Breaking News Staff. CLAYTON —… https://t.co/AHfoDHXesH https://t.co/T5wY4GXQTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea is dismantling its nuclear site, but is it abandoning its arsenal or hiding evidence? - Reuters: Reuters North Korea is dismantling its nuclear site, but is it abandoning its arsenal or hiding evidence? Reuters SEOUL (Reuters) - Satellite… https://t.co/YITXittJ4r https://t.co/WAEWpaN51K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software-Systems Solution Architect: DESCRIPTION: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Employer currently has an opening for a SOFTWARE/SYSTEMS SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT to work in Dayton, OH. Interested in being a leader that is responsible for driving the… https://t.co/4Dhdw5B365]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Developer Professional Apprentice-: Description Join The Sherwin-Williams Company’s award winning IT Professional Apprentice (PA) program. You’ll be given the opportunity to grow personally and professionally while building your resume through… https://t.co/hdkzfaz31Q https://t.co/sW2UFAxw2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: ABOUT THE ROLE The Digital Project Manager role is a pivotal position within Relequints organization, responsible for the coordination and execution of the deliverables of our inbound marketing accounts. In so doing, the Digital… https://t.co/4uSaX8PN0O https://t.co/h4Bsq6lcTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Gates Says Donald Trump Knew All About Gates' Daughter &amp; It Was "Kind Of Scary" - Bustle: Bustle Bill Gates Says Donald Trump Knew All About Gates' Daughter &amp; It Was "Kind Of Scary" Bustle As for the list of women with whom President Donald Trump… https://t.co/pkdufIsXz1 https://t.co/JrA0aT9Fyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Shoot and Wound Gunman at Trump Golf Club in Florida - New York Times: New York Times Police Shoot and Wound Gunman at Trump Golf Club in Florida New York Times Police officers shot and wounded a man who exchanged gunfire with them and shouted… https://t.co/zt68Bak98w https://t.co/aueTsoeM55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York lawyer threatens to report Spanish-speaking staff to authorities - BBC News: BBC News New York lawyer threatens to report Spanish-speaking staff to authorities BBC News A video of a New York man threatening to report Spanish-speaking restaurant… https://t.co/qFaT3f2o6l https://t.co/MKbaActBDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Data Analyst: needed for CostQuest Associates, Inc., Cincinnati, OH. Engage in GIS analysis including network and spatial analysis. Will develop GIS applications utilizing Python and C#. Will create maps and web mapping using JAVA Script. Will… https://t.co/mJc8NLT9Hg https://t.co/RcD4DOwiit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: Introduction: Tracker Management Systems has been leading the Towing and Recovery industry in technology through innovation since 1986. But the people that work at Tracker didnt start out at Tracker. Some of us have actually towed… https://t.co/nomIzxFDCl https://t.co/1OsYYqBmXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer / Cincinnati , OH Overview: We are seeking a Full Stack Developer to help develop and maintain our current business applications and web services. You will use your web development skills to develop applications and… https://t.co/BznOm9Gxij]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>