<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@benfowlkesMMA I dislike when other writers tweet their work at me in response to something I've posted but I've been there, man.

https://t.co/HqQ8WMkIiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It got terrible reviews but if you like quirky rom-coms you might enjoy The Clapper on Netflix. Ed Helms is terrific in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow clap. Well done! https://t.co/RRwtKm6RJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karinacomms @GlobalBC @SoniaSunger @NeetuGarcha @monikacoen Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPOkenny Shooting and processing is like the only creative thing I do where a team of people doesn't weigh-in on what needs to be changed. LOL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo @vcinbc Solid release.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO YOU HAVE ROYAL WEDDING FEVER?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau government ‘sought to suppress the evidence’ of pipeline ‘gamesmanship,' say court documents https://t.co/igMRBbjKIi via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPOkenny Alien Skin is fun but it doesn't handle RAW files (unless that's changed). I moved to RAW about five years ago -- so much better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPOkenny Thanks. I’m quite pleased with it. I do a Lightroom/Photoshop combo. Mostly Lightroom and then finish in Photoshop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickwellsy Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love it when a print comes together. https://t.co/YnOvDIrhGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incorrect. https://t.co/flB4n03dWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great trailer. This looks really good. https://t.co/hMR0r4iFcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I was just going bald but my beard on one side of my face has a big bald patch, too. Is this the first stage of death?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dressed as Marcus Aurelius for #NationalCaesarDay. Now I just feel stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My young cousin is modelling in London. He’s got a great look, as they say in the biz... https://t.co/L9o0lIkXkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very nice. https://t.co/VLW5PRUnJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo Horton hears a poo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice shot. https://t.co/JVqcNKBzUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fuel bill has doubled since I moved to White Rock. Hoping generous federal government will also cover MY losses. Let's keep Graeme moving/working! #KinderMorgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KGordonGlobalBC Lol - it was before dinner and everything is on the table which is out of frame. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Dude — I just totally saved your life!”

“I was fine — let’s just go inside.”

“Dude — you were drowning!”

“I might even go back in...”

“DUDE.” https://t.co/8mE2Ob4khF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn’t all of it First Nations land? https://t.co/GuCdyssPAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got these rad new stools at Structube — three metal stools for $130! Can’t beat that! https://t.co/JdC19aEqHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexbkane: Doctors Without Borders reacts to the "bloodbath" in Gaza: "What happened today is unacceptable and inhuman...It is unbearab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL https://t.co/a6bUvGbDm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Heaven, to me, is being able to swim in a pool full of Skittles. 

"Or Sprite."

-- London McRanor, age 9.75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little more than halfway done with the first draft. https://t.co/inRKIdt9XC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I pity your wife if you think six minutes is forever..." 

Bohemian Rhapsody (Freddie Mercury Biopic) - Official Trailer https://t.co/R0MgxRR11d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How thin does your hair have to get before you give up and buzz it real short/shave your head? I feel like I'm suddenly wearing a poorly woven hair hat -- one that,  in unfavorable winds or direct sunlight -- makes my scalp look like a rock covered with scanty moss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karinacomms It’s been a grave week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuck at the Messy tunnel. Late for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Typos. You get the drift...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta “I told you I was I’ll.” (Sorry)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Spike Milligan. “I told them I was I’ll.” East Sussex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Didn’t an Irish comedian use that one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I use this on my tombstone, @Planta? https://t.co/JoHeOGBeqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophielui @steeletalk @DavidSedaris @CKNW Reading his diaries right now. I love his casual/hilarious observations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admire how casually he drops cocaine into the conversation on a national talk show. https://t.co/1bNeqdGQD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter. https://t.co/hsHZBm8QNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first movie crush. :( https://t.co/DkyB2qdzdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy fix for Escobar: Lesgobar, opening soon. #YouAreWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPOkenny Excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Are you saying it might have been my reflection?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man just walked by my window wearing a bikini made of coconuts how is your night going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pulmyears But you have Flam! — which is great btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[H/t to whomever is running Deadpool 2’ s marketing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asuuming every kids’ soccer team from Brussels is called the Sprouts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomsonjennifer Have you considered having brunch? #solutions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our baby doesn't ask for our consent when she poops on us. @SuzyPatrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very good promo.

https://t.co/nNzFFFhiWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really loving Barry. And Henry Winkler is hilarious in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six months sober today. Not yet in a place to write an introspective on a lifetime of boozing, but here's something that's more my style: a short story about one night that paints a vivid picture of why I shouldn't drink. 

https://t.co/UU8QswzbAM   

#MentalHealthWeek #getloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Self-preservation: I'm a wildly unpredictable drunk. 

I wrote this story a while back -- but never published it. I've got dozens of stories like it, good times and bad. Since today marks six months sober, maybe it's a good day to finally share it. 

https://t.co/UU8QswzbAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well shot. I don’t believe him, though. https://t.co/6N5tiMpnJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta I like the idea of it — kind of living it now — but some of the quoted passages seems terribly pretentious. I’ll probably get it anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Sobriety Be as Interesting as Addiction? A Writer Wonders https://t.co/uVcflO3rws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is terrific. https://t.co/qppEfZVML9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to get gas in Blaine this morning. Spent an hour in secondary. Good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regarding the Emergency Alert: I regret yelling "Suck it, journos!" and pushing the elementary school student tour to the ground as I sprinted over them out the front door of @GlobalBC. #JustaTest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why we need to face our mortality https://t.co/XJM1uEvkx4 via @bbcideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 16-month-old daughter keeps calling this @Dodgers stuffy “daddy”, if you’re wondering how my night is going. https://t.co/r6ouKy6vnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Rock's Baja Cantina gets 8 thumbs up from the McPatricks. @SuzyPatrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie Cash and smash, GSP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t get this one at all. What does tossing around a smaller guy do for Georges’ legacy? Cash and smash, GSP. https://t.co/Ar5G8RFf1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus Could be worse. https://t.co/y4YuVRsHVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. https://t.co/fCvZVeBIHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghosting. White Rock, BC. #photo #photography #longexposure #sunset #explorebc #Explore #travel https://t.co/J0u48hE3Ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pier. White Rock, BC. #photo #photography #longexposure #sunset https://t.co/GXhCMiHBmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for my first White Rock promenade run, so for next hour it will be known -- at least in my head -- as the GRAEMENADE™.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan gonna Dylan... https://t.co/CYNEkJMg8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night a woman told me and @SuzyPatrick that our baby is adorable. I thanked her and said it was all me. Everybody in earshot laughed. 

I wasn’t joking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta @theArtsClub @SuzyPatrick Hell, I’ve seen the show twice, too. Once in Toronto and the BAC tour. It’s a fun show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta @theArtsClub No, because I want to go with @SuzyPatrick. It’s all or noting, @Planta!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickwellsy I'M NOT ANGRY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're wondering how popular/sales are going for Mama Mia @theartsclub, I got a media invite 30 minutes ago and there are only single tickets left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VICE: Intimate photos of my parents as they both face terminal cancer: https://t.co/8Im4W1RlMt https://t.co/kfi64fwQB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The majority of British Columbians have never participated in a poll because they have call display.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My greatest achievement in photography is to hang five of my shots nearly straight. https://t.co/b97cuEpYKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Kodachrome was sweet but why couldn’t they take a plane? (Note: rhetorical question.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to work forearms more, bro. https://t.co/ROWzb2EuBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cottoncandaddy: today at my bar one guy made fun of his buddy for drinking a blue hawaiian and he goes "I don't give a shit if it's bab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope VISA comes up with a similar scheme. https://t.co/cqbUjGq9ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emrazz: Fixed it. https://t.co/65h9dQcfEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta You don'need to state something is your opinion when it's clearly your opinion, IMHO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY COMMUTE IS GOING WELL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats Vancouver on hitting the highest North American gas prices in the history of fuel.  It's a great time to live in White Rock, drop your kid at his school in Kitsilano, and work in Burnaby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is an international security threat. https://t.co/mLC3Xtnkhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver It’s 988 West Broadway. Today only one lane closed but they’ve done it often, which means three lanes (including bus lane) bottlenecking into one right after the intersection at Oak and Broadway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real love is listening to 94.5 because your son likes the DJs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I think mosquitoes are alien drones sent to collect blood samples...” — London McRanor, age 9.75.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @CityofVancouver, I’ve complained about this before. Why is Blue Sky Properties (or any developer) allowed to block two lanes of traffic at 9:15am on Broadway? One lane eastbound this morning. Ridiculous. https://t.co/mcUSR6hmQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol. https://t.co/mNhCST6OwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five minutes ago I was stoked to have peanut butter sandwiches for lunch today. https://t.co/4nA1lkzC2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in publishing. | Romance writer's bid to stop authors from using word 'cocky' fails in court https://t.co/kurJx9RoMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never thought watching Pitch Perfect 2 would lead to a frank discussion with my 9-yr-old about what a lady boy is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status. https://t.co/I7kssvWS49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet moves though. https://t.co/zMV6OJRm2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just used a drive-thru Starbucks, if you’re wondering about my current level of lazy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>