<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Spain Put the Siesta to Bed? https://t.co/EtfUILopXM

Spanish Prime Minister Mariano Rajoy announced at a par… https://t.co/vSZU3rzIlE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the DHS Can’t Find Cybersecurity Talent https://t.co/vTABpsc7So

We’ve previously looked at how many organiza… https://t.co/pTC8UwgJMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Women Can Avoid Paying the ‘Assertiveness Penalty’ https://t.co/1ILWWO2jYq

In the business world, numerous st… https://t.co/rXoXKz2trd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overall, Most Employees Are Feeling Pretty Good https://t.co/wHQSyihZQ7

The Edenred-Ipsos Barometer, an annual su… https://t.co/mCd2KXyY4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Hard to Hate the Bad Guy When He’s Good at His Job https://t.co/AX9YzMRlih

As those of us who remember readi… https://t.co/LPSMWfM2Dl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Minimum Wage Hikes Spur Automation? Maybe Not at McDonald’s https://t.co/dnGYXO3s8u

Opponents of a higher mi… https://t.co/MvFSDiMO29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ExxonMobil Shareholders Vote for Proxy Access https://t.co/fzOVbznG8Q

At a time when investors are taking on an i… https://t.co/tHazhtR4gE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court Rules Against Arbitration Clauses, Teeing Up Issue for Supreme Court https://t.co/DfhRfyIqI8

The United Sta… https://t.co/ReXKdYoMsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Revamps Performance Reviews https://t.co/EMYSQmWpY5

The investment bank is getting rid of its nine-… https://t.co/Ftr0wTS4r9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does It Pay to Pay Candidates for Pre-Hire Samples? https://t.co/Upr6o6Rzb3

In a recent Medium post discussing th… https://t.co/m3QuafaE7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why College Grads Are Eschewing ‘Big Business’ and Seeking Smaller Employers https://t.co/z5OBZQrKLd

Anne Fisher … https://t.co/5uCwJRRWm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France’s Controversial Labor Bill Establishes a ‘Right to Disconnect’ https://t.co/t0UCYo7DzZ

Under pressure from… https://t.co/LEFYhxeDg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Robots Eat 60,000 Jobs at Foxconn? https://t.co/xDVb8BYGCm

Earlier this month, we looked at a troubling trend… https://t.co/9NRHoUUUzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automakers and Tech Giants Compete for Self-Driving Talent https://t.co/ICvBbsTqDx

General Motors is seeing a mar… https://t.co/YqJb7Pktb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is More Money the Solution to the Skills Gap? https://t.co/F0JcfTtjaW

That’s what economist Thijs van Rens’s rese… https://t.co/JOP4MEph2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Ready for Price Hikes on the Health Care Exchanges https://t.co/BTCjAlxhDw

Insurers have proposed preliminary… https://t.co/rFOESCYBz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Case for Radical Pay Transparency https://t.co/KxMDtviSUF

Salary transparency is increasingly seen as a cruci… https://t.co/egBcA6k79M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Domino’s Responsible for Wage Theft by its Franchisees? https://t.co/rhcQcnuxQx

New York Attorney General Eric… https://t.co/JV6k74wpPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portrait of the Millennials as a Young Global Workforce https://t.co/dX5uo800H2

A massive global survey of millen… https://t.co/kTf78lQocF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Corporate America Ready for Democracy? https://t.co/GSTBN86sDK

Kelly Max, the CEO of Haufe USA, was elected to… https://t.co/mYonLBCLHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Rise of ‘Smart Drugs’ Means for Employers https://t.co/ZEDZoepTIQ

Controversies over performance-enhanci… https://t.co/27CQBTaig2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does a Dropoff in Temp Hiring Portend a Bigger Slowdown? https://t.co/SyihbjaXdT

The US economy has been sending … https://t.co/rayg1J3EVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maryland’s New Equal Pay Law Taps the Power of Transparency https://t.co/gh62V2RxPn

Last Thursday, Maryland Gover… https://t.co/opDZVVnwMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Small Businesses Afford Parental Leave? https://t.co/PoDYcPshcn

The mainstreaming of paid parental leave in c… https://t.co/QrR0K9xFuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Serve on a Board? For the Money, of Course https://t.co/GYaszWnFdn

Getting a seat on a board of directors (or… https://t.co/XbUkbwv8nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Wonder Young People Want Help With Their College Debt https://t.co/xeenjnnoTr

Boston Globe Magazine writer Nei… https://t.co/qN3keezeQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring by the Herd, Instead of by the Head https://t.co/avdw8YPaCE

Stripe, an online payment startup in San Franc… https://t.co/nDg4ercZe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Juniorization Driving Top Wall Street Talent In-House? https://t.co/neie42c8wL

Everyone knows that investment … https://t.co/BGEs7j8eYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Complaint About Compliance Training https://t.co/pH1gFxXL6d

Earlier this month, we looked at some research show… https://t.co/cSARL9ciGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culture Problems Come to Light in Mitsubishi Scandal https://t.co/5MOOGVkhco

Wednesday was a bad day for Japanese… https://t.co/hjsQ6tljux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Labor Department’s New Overtime Rule: More Reactions https://t.co/jKNVc1Si50

The new overtime rule announced … https://t.co/MTyGwuRPgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Health Care Price Transparency Tools Aren’t Delivering Savings Yet https://t.co/YcRBhunfCi

Responding to risi… https://t.co/wPKWdMeJ1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Future of Code, the End of Coding https://t.co/K9deIyrWCj

That coding skills are the only steady meal ticket … https://t.co/NJ4zSHOZzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Department Unveils New Overtime Rule https://t.co/pc8PTWo2Of

The final version of the US Department of Labo… https://t.co/wZNTd8dc0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge Sharing is Power Sharing https://t.co/ae1HwkFTv6

Power in the workplace depends to a significant extent… https://t.co/exEx53c7eE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allstate Embraces a $15 Minimum Wage https://t.co/Bei5k1dVmA

In its annual shareholder report, the insurer announ… https://t.co/spCk3ir4KC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BET CEO Joins Twitter’s Board https://t.co/Mcp6FzVu5h

Twitter has come under appreciable pressure in recent month… https://t.co/PNVhb848R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New EEOC Rules Allow Incentives for Wellness Screenings https://t.co/4AK9CBf8Ie

The US Equal Employment Opportuni… https://t.co/0wqCcUvua0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Recruiting Platforms Take Aim at Hiring Bias https://t.co/hKr6wWxwFU

We’ve previously touched on whether it i… https://t.co/jIcNCTBJFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nike: A Majority-Minority Company https://t.co/YHDEBGMScO

In a recently issued report on staffing and sustainabil… https://t.co/GVlGBYjDRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Some Facebook Time With Your Candidates https://t.co/FBZFp1tliu

Checking job applicants’ social media pro… https://t.co/iBxeuWYwUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falling Out of Love With Open Offices https://t.co/OZlTnj3k1U

The vaunted cauldrons of collaboration haven’t live… https://t.co/ZFCyJfVhLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Plans to Work Late (in Life) https://t.co/EHBJVOKjWa

New data from Gallup shows that the age at which Ame… https://t.co/2SKdCEklbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Law Expands Trade Secret, Whistleblower Protections https://t.co/69vzXaJIzR

The Defend Trade Secrets Act, whi… https://t.co/RtW6kKK7ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fed’s Diversity Deficit https://t.co/yiqTNUmKbH

A group of legislators is calling for more diverse leadership… https://t.co/ECYkeaPJSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick Takes: ‘Corporate Inequality’ and the Battle for Talent https://t.co/sTyJZMsQgl

Income inequality is a big … https://t.co/vPIB0mZ4Kb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Gig Economy Hold up in the Supreme Court? https://t.co/rM00Tymai3

The question of how to classify “gig e… https://t.co/Rm9xZvZAoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Silicon Valley Cuts Costs, Trendy Perks Are First to Go https://t.co/cX14R73Hn0

As venture capitalists exhaust… https://t.co/kcJ2rsGOHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Plays Capture the Talent with Online Hacking Game https://t.co/Vm3AcCSera

The drought of cybersecurity t… https://t.co/DRiWDKHTrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Department Moves to Collect Employee Injury Data from ‘High Hazard’ Businesses https://t.co/no2xE1Rphf

A ne… https://t.co/QkmDZCAw2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Write Off Telemedicine https://t.co/SyxyBJqLzC

At TLNT, Tom Valenti contends that offering telemedicine ser… https://t.co/6xn09hA8Of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEOs Come and Go, but Their Scandals Live on https://t.co/SRm75pDoMV

Companies affected by a scandal at the top o… https://t.co/HR6jIwyOOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nuances of Parental Leave https://t.co/c1J8YikMbW

As the push for paid parental leave in the US gathers steam… https://t.co/2BcrRsrsu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airline Accused of Discriminating Against Pregnant and Nursing Pilots https://t.co/9Ni1UeGb9Z

Four Frontier Airli… https://t.co/ScjtHTuhP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber to Allow ‘Guild’ for New York City Drivers https://t.co/cjzI8iLueF

Uber has agreed to help its drivers in Ne… https://t.co/1L7vOQzNAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Developing Economies, Robots May Beat Humans to the Good Manufacturing Jobs https://t.co/Y6Gj03BkPT

In a recen… https://t.co/y5chymBaj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does a Six-Hour Workday Translate into American? https://t.co/7zzFclRMIJ

Experiments in Sweden and other European… https://t.co/a6hZVywq3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Women Out-Earn Men https://t.co/h4SUsYFDXK

Generally speaking, women tend to be paid less than men for the s… https://t.co/acjFqQQSv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Credit Check Bans Backfire https://t.co/2BPJGtjlJP

Roy Maurer at SHRM highlights a new study finding that ba… https://t.co/0Xj7IqZDDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autonomous Employees Are Happy Employees? https://t.co/poTkb7dHZY

That’s the question Belle Beth Cooper digs into… https://t.co/7sITfqbACb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Best New Employee Might Be an Ex-Con? https://t.co/jz24G8wTmD

The hiring of employees with criminal records … https://t.co/EqJAqiz3Td]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mother’s Day Spotlight on Single Working Moms https://t.co/H3icWhMSRo

In a personal Mother’s Day message posted… https://t.co/Rin0N3TbRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[April Jobs Report Sends Mixed Signals, Points to Delayed Fed Rate Hike https://t.co/sECJCmwfaB

US employment rose… https://t.co/9mBnv88KhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boardroom Gender Quotas Work, But Do They Really Work? https://t.co/qaLwkKTOYC

To close the gender gap in corpora… https://t.co/z0tcrsqO2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber Hit With More Class-Action Suits https://t.co/NNQB4g09rO

Within two weeks of agreeing to settle class action… https://t.co/DSgG6KBqVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting a ‘New Benchmark’ for India’s Working Women https://t.co/UQklLcFTae

India, like other fast-growing econom… https://t.co/gQk65Njxkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Boards Need Technical Know-How https://t.co/vVzblsUw3g

Digital strategy, data security, and other IT concerns… https://t.co/fhiHFCzyAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Sexual Harassment Training Backfires https://t.co/2nPLS8AoLD

Training courses to prevent sexual harassment a… https://t.co/0NVNunyKs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s Behind The Rise of the Outsider CEO? https://t.co/1pM18vVsq4

Last month, we highlighted Strategy&amp;’s 2015 C… https://t.co/dhqWcudtL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the Gig Economy Only for the Privileged? https://t.co/UWwkG9fjIA

The much-vaunted gig economy is disrupting in… https://t.co/Ag1tICtThe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit Could Make for a Messy Divorce, Employment Lawyers Warn https://t.co/QGYS7bTDjr

On Friday, our own Adam Br… https://t.co/yS6kIyjefL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Pay Transparency Alone Close the Gender Gap? https://t.co/ukka9yse9a

University of Baltimore law professor Na… https://t.co/uzngMbhv2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discrimination by Data https://t.co/RYg2fPRJgN

Using algorithms to screen candidates is usually talked up as a wa… https://t.co/xV1S5hx7cS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parsing the Tech Sector’s Pay Gap https://t.co/jbLdLkZsio

A new analysis from the pay-transparency platform Compa… https://t.co/9it7Y2Apvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Employees Don’t Trust Workplace Fitness Trackers https://t.co/31KwjECqVV

As the consumer market grows for wear… https://t.co/EYptHAwOsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Home Workers Perform Better, Quit Less https://t.co/IBbHmTZi3x

The increasing number of jobs that can be d… https://t.co/K3xxtlmKwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effective Leaders Walk the Talk https://t.co/JbSRF9scdi

In the perennial debate over the qualities that go hand-i… https://t.co/Blc9IoJzBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directors, Deviate! https://t.co/wVJvLIlL6c

At the Harvard Business Review, CEB’s CEO Tom Monahan argues that man… https://t.co/E8m4yyQuj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Professionals Aren’t Taking Home the Big Rupees https://t.co/LcGVADVnxw

Suneera Tandon at Quartz highlight… https://t.co/nVFqCC9SS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evolution and Expansion of Benefits Over the Past 20 Years https://t.co/CCLHKTsmfs

SHRM conducted its 20th an… https://t.co/Obo7enHZuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Talent Ramifications of Brexit https://t.co/KwVBMvfOc1 

Should Britain vote to leave the European Union, ther… https://t.co/q7UnmnPkMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Under-Vacationed Nation https://t.co/pIhvBJZnar

Andrew Soergel at US News and World Report outlines the troub… https://t.co/ewKATK9DI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Room for the New American Dad https://t.co/zbst3UPDzm

The State of America’s Fathers 2016, the first repor… https://t.co/jT25Qq8L5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @reachpearljohn: CEB's @briankropp offers insights on why companies should keep performance review ratings. https://t.co/FgelMbee25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TEDTalks: "We need to think about how to design social media experiences that promote civility and reward thoughtfulness." https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Women Could Be the Future of Manufacturing https://t.co/x2Y7kAtDQu

Manufacturing is likely to experience more… https://t.co/Vq9lpTfuHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughing and Learning With Second City Works https://t.co/8nsinXIkrv

Just as news-comedy shows like the Daily Sho… https://t.co/olGe8TjPem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just How Bright is Our LinkedIn Future? https://t.co/y9dsxFRcih

Microsoft’s $26 billion acquisition of LinkedIn c… https://t.co/bm2ys8L7UQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Work Costs Employees Roughly $3,300 a Year https://t.co/DOP7kSvoO9

That’s according to a new Careerbuild… https://t.co/f06tYya3gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smart insights on how digital is changing the non-profit world https://t.co/Ho6ZSWmEax  @ElaineKTurville #Accenture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Air Conditioning Wars https://t.co/mDRC6jqgpq

Anyone who shares an office is familiar with the perennial cont… https://t.co/tSS7iqAkT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barclays Expands Leave, Adds Flexibility for New Parents in US https://t.co/rTkdAUojBR

The American division of B… https://t.co/cy09ULrFht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Just Respect Your Elders; Recruit and Retain Them https://t.co/Y5hWOUY7fD

As the US workforce ages—a lastin… https://t.co/RIV87fR5CI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McDonald’s Is Moving to Where the Talent Wants to Be https://t.co/2zAZdCYpM3

McDonald’s recently announced plans … https://t.co/vkWDRmLjif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Market Chaos Is One of Many Brexit Risks https://t.co/pcaom1kK3v

With a week to go before the UK votes on w… https://t.co/yZmEB277yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Microsoft’s LinkedIn Acquisition Could Transform HR https://t.co/3NQrkcVuUy

The $26 billion acquisition deal,… https://t.co/E8NL4NSGJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Staying Power of the Stay Interview https://t.co/vlIdL3Fqiy

Mark McGraw at HRE discusses a new tool organizat… https://t.co/vt2uJuJ4Vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Want to Inspire Your Employees, Get Some More Sleep https://t.co/fbfmDodeBx

You’ve already heard about the… https://t.co/gWUhCwvrUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28 Employers Sign White House Equal Pay Pledge https://t.co/WdOAglK9ou

In advance of the United State of Women su… https://t.co/UZa7loQBNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MsJessicaCash: Proud that CEB is one of the first 30 co's in the nation to sign the @WhiteHouse equal pay pledge: https://t.co/tidfLG72…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>