<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Software Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software, hardware, and portfolio of… https://t.co/4WEptK6EXj https://t.co/RjlYo8JWaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager /SCRUM Manager: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global… https://t.co/v9DEns4Aex https://t.co/FoWMZPJAag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer – US Citizenship/ability to obtain security clearance: Evolver is a technology company serving the Federal, Commercial, and Legal markets that addresses client challenges in the present and transitions clients into the future by… https://t.co/uIuKJ2BGOK https://t.co/hGh3UtJ2EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/1EQUcBmDp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Armour says 150 million MyFitnessPal accounts breached: (Reuters) - Under Armour Inc said on Thursday that data from some 150 million MyFitnessPal diet and fitness app accounts was compromised in February, in one of the biggest hacks in history,… https://t.co/uuncKvyKe6 https://t.co/IDkQKJeYQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: SCRUM Master Ref No.: 18-10465 Location: Pittsburg, Pennsylvania Hi, I hope you’re doing well today!!! I, Ghazala(Enterprise Solution Inc.)would like to check your availability for an Urgent job opportunity asScrum Masters basedinPittsburg,… https://t.co/ehfH4ybyBy https://t.co/cGxm6NY2Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: Join our Big Data Team and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! KEY ACCOUNTABILITIES: * Provides thought leadership… https://t.co/pWEsSnP4GJ https://t.co/176Y84Pv1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Test Automation Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software, hardware, and portfolio of… https://t.co/xRz3qinVYB https://t.co/uoBvqxGHtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: ABOUT THE ROLE The Digital Project Manager role is a pivotal position within Relequints organization, responsible for the coordination and execution of the deliverables of our inbound marketing accounts. In so doing, the Digital… https://t.co/yZ5KxbCPBz https://t.co/CEUIw8iPVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Software Engineering: SUMMARY This role will be responsible for Leading and developing a global software engineering product team responsible for the development of Jamfs flagship Apple device management solution, Jamf Pro, and the Jamf… https://t.co/8wUFnD3Zd9 https://t.co/fRUnONT6n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Huawei 2017 profit jump helped by cost controls, smartphone sales: HONG KONG (Reuters) - China's Huawei Technologies [HWT.UL], the world's third-largest smartphone maker, posted a 28 percent rise in 2017 net profit on Friday, driven by cost… https://t.co/joybvmByE9 https://t.co/xd7ILkEN1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Specialty II: Developer Specialty II (067) – Y &amp; L Consulting Inc. – Austin, TX – 02-27-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths –… https://t.co/MsVCiwPTYD https://t.co/8PgT9c6fIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Engineer- SDET: Automation Test Engineer- SDET Ref No.: 18-00411 Location: Illinois Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/07/2018 Automation Test Engineer- SDET 6 -12 Months Contract Chicago, IL Required… https://t.co/Vxn8rxkOpg https://t.co/MXShFPwFlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing development of the team within… https://t.co/Q4oKRVgIKc https://t.co/4MfOYBr9bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:29933 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsA minimum of four years of related project management. A minimum of two years of scrum master experience. Kanban methodology knowledge and experience is a plus.… https://t.co/0eUmhqMQKM https://t.co/WlZ9edjDkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software QA Engineer: TransCore (TRN), a subsidiary of Roper Technologies, Inc. (NYSE:ROP), is seeking a full-time Lead Software QA Engineer to join our team in San Diego, California. Job Summary: This individual will participate directly with the… https://t.co/J1x24Yji49 https://t.co/fvbxkk6gtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Data Analyst: Permanent position open in the Rockville area for Health Data Analyst. Primary Responsibilities: * Converting business requirements into technical specification for data integration and reports * Configuring the front-end and… https://t.co/w4RK2rdqWB https://t.co/MQsehZebm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber avoids legal battle with family of autonomous vehicle victim: TEMPE, Ariz. (Reuters) - The family of a woman killed by an Uber Technologies Inc self-driving vehicle in Arizona has reached a settlement with the ride services company, ending a… https://t.co/47LauPjVwh https://t.co/HvDzFmkwCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Full Stack Developer: RedShelf was built to improve education. Working with the higher education community, we design products to make course materials more affordable, accessible and engaging for students everywhere. Our partnerships with leading… https://t.co/r2MUIGzRZQ https://t.co/Ybm7lOUwqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV: Software Engineer IV- Embedded As an IV Solutions team member, you will work with a creative, experienced and dedicated team of engineers on delivering innovative solutions for the pharmacies throughout the world. Our solutions help… https://t.co/4RxavrsOyV https://t.co/EMSfnzkD86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Analyst: The IT Team at Wayside Publishing is expanding and seeking new talent! Through our custom learning management system, the Learning Site, Wayside delivers interactive digital content developed using the most modern pedagogical… https://t.co/Y7IGxvGYb4 https://t.co/PZcGd5UdcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Integration Test Lead: Sr. Integration Test Lead – (1800004E) Description JOB SUMMARY: The Senior Integration/Test Lead will be responsible for systems integration, test plan, design and support technical activities related to CRM/ERP integration for… https://t.co/Qiq27NwW6L https://t.co/CxCg4GR0Qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer with 8 plus years’ experience: W2 DIRECT HIRE ONLY! NO C2C OR SPONSORSHIP ALIS Software, is currently seeking an experienced for a C# .NETSENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WITH 8 PLUS YEARS EXPERIENCE for a DIRECT HIRE opportunity with… https://t.co/6e8TP0u84g https://t.co/VCuBMaqaso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York offers free cyber security tools to public to deter hackers: (Reuters) - New York City will offer free cyber security tools to the public as part of a new effort to improve online safety, officials said on Thursday, a week after Atlanta was hit… https://t.co/eA3PA61ICO https://t.co/89jPx7jiXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Architect/Developer (CONTRACT): Our enterprise technology strategy and solutions engineering team is in need of both part time and potentially full time seasoned .NET architecture / development talent. Our two technical leaders on this… https://t.co/jn5UAv9A9l https://t.co/JrAWZ0Ak2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Project Manager: Scrum Master/Project Manager (data) Dunwoody, GA 12 month contract Education/Experience Bachelor degree in IT, finance or related discipline 5-7 years of progressive work-related experience, particularly Project Management… https://t.co/DxnSoL2W85 https://t.co/Zv2ckLkguo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/pgz2W0Cjrq https://t.co/5aGnwPHAuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 5: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do.… https://t.co/7QKboZ2QOX https://t.co/UxdIEO0VSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Are Americans taking steps to protect their data after Facebook scandal?: (Reuters) - In the wake of the scandal sparked by Facebook's handling of 50 million users' data, Reuters polled Americans about how they are protecting their privacy online. https://t.co/ighEs7cwEd https://t.co/Zn4v14Tcmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Job Title: Senior Scrum Master Location: Chicago, IL Duration- 6 Months Roles &amp; Responsibility Guiding the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values to delight customers – Guiding the team on how to get the… https://t.co/eRMXfPBWWA https://t.co/6K2RrVWd7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master Certified (CSM), Professional Scrum Master… https://t.co/oBzym4DOPN https://t.co/2MK5qTKohT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We currently have an opening for an IT Project Manager in our PRS IT team. The IT Project Manager will have responsibility for the management and coordination of multiple concurrent projects within the PRS Product portfolio. IT projects… https://t.co/V4TflxQGCQ https://t.co/ZnE5mpxEv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Softheon is looking for several Software Engineers who can help in developing solid products to meet clients needs and improve end-user experience using new technologies such as microservices, single-page web applications, RESTful web… https://t.co/CGPGvuQBPg https://t.co/DAWBjye2RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/aG21NmGbkh https://t.co/xU9zHYYSAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: Scrum master philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 02/28/18, Posted Date – 02/28/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2COverview Required Skills Set: Years of Experience: 5+ years Scrum Master experience in software… https://t.co/7gJqKOjziW https://t.co/rfqbCPLDtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook cuts ties to data brokers in blow to targeted ads: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Wednesday it would end its partnerships with several large data brokers who help advertisers target people on the social network, a step that follows a scandal… https://t.co/twdOWpWfQD https://t.co/aXla0yPIMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: OVERVIEW Responsible for design, development and maintenance of software and firmware for electronic control systems deployed in the rail industry. This includes developing software requirements specifications, functional… https://t.co/U6u7USfvY7 https://t.co/N2i7ppJ3cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? We at MAHLE are a leading international supplier to the automotive industry. With our products for combustion engines… https://t.co/dLbKfBoAmL https://t.co/LHEWzXbUOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Software Developer: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place people… https://t.co/4e9NBXF6oY https://t.co/M8oIgdwCFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst: Job Family Business Systems Job Description Summary Facilitate the business analysis process to identify business requirements for system solutions or improved processes that will increase efficiency and overall… https://t.co/bs7bftOm3x https://t.co/8aQXjBssYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/aD0UD24q4t https://t.co/ntFycGfqPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3(Java Developer): Position: Software Engineer 3 (VISAJP********) Location: Foster City, CA Duration: 9+ Months contract Must have skills: 7+ years of Java programming. Strong OO and SOA skills, multi-threading. Oracle Database… https://t.co/auTLeJEQgY https://t.co/aX8LBode9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boeing said detected limited intrusion of malware: (Reuters) - U.S. planemaker Boeing Co "detected a limited intrusion of malware" that affected "a small number of systems," and said certain media reports on the disruptions were "overstated and… https://t.co/m50otyyxJB https://t.co/1x99R0NNSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10371 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Hi, Please find the below job description and if you are interested kindly share me you updated resume along with good time to connect Role: Scrum Master Location: Atlanta GA… https://t.co/lfGjdWaSnc https://t.co/kXh5VnqZpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/z4qYVaiJ7O https://t.co/fIk7hXRASK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineering – Job #: 180028050: Job #: 180028050 Associate, Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Provide high quality tech. solutions that address business needs by developing applications within mature technology environments. Duties:… https://t.co/vDr11kzuqs https://t.co/2DljnFPoum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Agile Coach: Position Purpose: Lead software development teams in project initiation, organization, goal and change management aspects of AgileDiscover opportunities to champion agile values and adoption across ITDevelop agile training materials and… https://t.co/6xo9pHEzZI https://t.co/OVqI5zxTPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Analyst – Software: Equus Software is a growing global mobility software provider in downtown Denver! We are looking for a Senior Tax Analyst to help ensure we stay at the top of our game with respect to our clients, software and tax modules.… https://t.co/dog9TEmJTd https://t.co/O1iPrU4Ih2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares dive again, stung by fatal crash, credit downgrade: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Tesla Inc shares fell sharply again on Wednesday, reeling from a credit downgrade of the electric car maker by Moody's Investors Service, federal probes of a fatal… https://t.co/sPWRStImnb https://t.co/iC5V1K9C6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Full Stack: ABOUT OUR CLIENT Our client believes the fundamental nature of work is changing from fixed to fluid, as AI and collaborative technology transform how people and companies work in the next economy. Theyre leading this shift… https://t.co/CV502G03IC https://t.co/MV2ucfGbX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/ab0sOL6uCw https://t.co/frfKSsvZmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: WORK WITH ALLIANZ TRANSFORMATION LEAD TO STREAMS AND TEAMS RESPONSIBLE FOR BUILDING OUT AN AGILE ENTERPRISE FRAMEWORK. * Experience with Enterprise Agile Transformations or Building Agile Teams. * 8+ years in the use of Agile methodologies… https://t.co/1oLZdpHWx4 https://t.co/vfMS0EHAoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Introduction: Supply chain system processes over 1B transactions per year for a face value of over $6B. If you want to be part of a team building highly scalable distributed systems using SaaS and Azure technologies then you… https://t.co/rTPubhf8Cn https://t.co/R0F76fIrYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: This Senior Project Manager Position in terms of business will be HR centered and systems exposure will be Workday. This Senior Project Manager is… https://t.co/A04HMZ3iQX https://t.co/TisVd6ctk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV- Embedded: Software Engineer IV- Embedded As an IV Solutions team member, you will work with a creative, experienced and dedicated team of engineers on delivering innovative solutions for the pharmacies throughout the world. Our… https://t.co/6XltXlPNb3 https://t.co/TjSh2TLUkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon sheds $52 billion in market value after report on Trump threat: (Reuters) - https://t.co/uhPpyoOsfT Inc's shares fell as much as 7 percent on Wednesday, wiping out about $52 billion from the company's market value, after a report that U.S.… https://t.co/9sQsSqmDl9 https://t.co/e7PWEap5zF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: As part of the TPGSI business team, Business Analyst (BA) will elicit and document business and technical requirements in support of TP strategic objective to design a new eligibility and enrollment system. This new system,… https://t.co/Th0mTbVXdA https://t.co/SWaONvA7En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV- Algorithm: Software Engineer IV- Algorithm As an IV Solutions team member, you will work hard with a team of engineers on delivering new innovation to the pharmacies for health systems throughout the world. Our solutions help to… https://t.co/OPX2hR0UdA https://t.co/xkyW0QtAet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer Software Engineer: VeriCheck, Inc. (*************) is in the online payment processing industry. We are currently seeking a Full-Time Mid-Level Software Engineer to join our development team. You have the ability to gather requirements,… https://t.co/iHDV2wPdR3 https://t.co/aLCWSvBNK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing development of the team within… https://t.co/U87ZsuIZCe https://t.co/kTwOPNYgH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey applications and custom… https://t.co/Gf5pMFMbgg https://t.co/G5ORaWJbXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies clamp down on crypto ads as regulators play catch-up: LONDON (Reuters) - A growing number of internet companies are banning cryptocurrency advertising, fearing reputational damage if their users are duped or left penniless, even as regulators… https://t.co/Ouq1mRbOgq https://t.co/vxb4nCvFLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Application Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Arlington, Virginia, United States Position ID: J1117-2327 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI is seeking a… https://t.co/exxxdQXnmo https://t.co/tjcJnztVfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Software Business Analysis at Redflex are part of a community that design and create leading edge solutions that make our cities and our lives more green, safer and smarter. We take a whole team approach to software quality, following… https://t.co/IvGSJwUhmr https://t.co/5zsnIMw9sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Localization Project Manager: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the… https://t.co/fb3HWcTlC9 https://t.co/JxfglY3Vbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer: Sr. Web Developer at eBay Skip Navigation Press tab to begin typing your search or press escape to close. Search Site close MenuHeader Logo – Our Company – Overview – Who We Are – Connected Commerce – Our History – Our Leaders – Our… https://t.co/Yg7p8rtapN https://t.co/egioQ8yCFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/uD3eeVOjmd https://t.co/2Li4CJAB1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – EA: Scrum Master – EA Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates. Daily… https://t.co/tComqSkegF https://t.co/Hd1SCBxZsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Facebook users sue over collection of call, text history: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Three users of the Facebook Messenger app sued Facebook on Tuesday, saying the social network violated their privacy by collecting logs of their phone calls and… https://t.co/5ON83g0fVf https://t.co/IOA5Mu0zLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Bentonville, AR Full Time/Contract Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level… https://t.co/dVkHr4mtUz https://t.co/nYRceEgsSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Introduction: Supply chain system processes over 1B transactions per year for a face value of over $6B. If you want to be part of a team building highly scalable distributed systems using SaaS and Azure technologies then you… https://t.co/tYCOsHIeAE https://t.co/yCMDXJx211]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: There are 7 billion people on this planet. And by 2050, there will be 2 billion more… many moving into urban centers at an unprecedented rate. Making sure there is enough food, fiber and infrastructure for our rapidly growing… https://t.co/9ggzIS2dpn https://t.co/rwOeql6vf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV- Algorithm: Software Engineer IV- Algorithm As an IV Solutions team member, you will work hard with a team of engineers on delivering new innovation to the pharmacies for health systems throughout the world. Our solutions help to… https://t.co/SQS1j8jv3M https://t.co/Ani6dwtx3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer with 8 plus years’ experience: W2 DIRECT HIRE ONLY! NO C2C OR SPONSORSHIP ALIS Software, is currently seeking an experienced for a C# .NETSENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WITH 8 PLUS YEARS EXPERIENCE for a DIRECT HIRE opportunity with… https://t.co/UkOwGAJsDy https://t.co/oFgwKp07j5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR775) Job: Date: Mar 15, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR775) (Job Number:434149) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/GT6fGRxlHP https://t.co/OupTU9Tcim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo steps toward a more diverse robo-taxi fleet with Jaguar deal: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Waymo will include up to 20,000 Jaguar I-PACE electric vehicles in its upcoming autonomous fleet as part of a long-term partnership between Alphabet Inc's… https://t.co/HJhEVO0GbH https://t.co/4pDi4rTDxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: InfosysIVS-Financial Services- Technical Test Lead Automation Testing Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/dwEgrha7If https://t.co/5Gd8Xmjx5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Analyst – Software: Equus Software is a growing global mobility software provider in downtown Denver! We are looking for a Senior Tax Analyst to help ensure we stay at the top of our game with respect to our clients, software and tax modules.… https://t.co/6l5WLqgQv6 https://t.co/jBCohOhXIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III, OTC Technology:: CME Group: Where Futures Are Made CME Group (****************) is the worlds leading and most diverse derivatives marketplace. But who we are goes deeper than that. Here, you can impact markets worldwide. Transform… https://t.co/bHHOF6yM3I https://t.co/wb89ScmWSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer: The Senior Backend Developer’s primary responsibilities are to code robust solutions and assist in managing a flexible pool of vendor and freelance developer talent to expand BlueprintNYC’s core products.He or she will uphold… https://t.co/f0D5cqdXte https://t.co/LIhTe2PNaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job Description Deliver value to Assurant by working as the Scrum master to help Agile based teams successfully and effectively deliver Sprints: * Facilitates activities including sprint planning, daily team activities, story… https://t.co/5xz2qsq0sz https://t.co/D9v0335NSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's Zuckerberg will not answer UK lawmakers' questions over data scandal: LONDON (Reuters) - Facebook boss Mark Zuckerberg will not answer questions from British lawmakers over how millions of users' data got into the hands of political… https://t.co/PtRpQ4yzOw https://t.co/cU5PwrEzPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:25428 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsExposure to various business intelligence applications and architecture such as Cognos, Tableau and data warehousing LocationVernon Hills, IL Date Posted03/06/2018… https://t.co/XKuDder5Fx https://t.co/8uLzzgYBMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission SME – TS/SCI Required: US Citizenship Required and (TS/SCI) Required Job Description: Direct a team of engineers to build mission capabilities. As a Phoenix Mission SME, you’ll be responsible for conducting traditional systems engineering… https://t.co/Md0fkFUApg https://t.co/8ZpqD4A2Os]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media Group Search all Cox… https://t.co/4I1pd69o5X https://t.co/3nNsCfPA2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Do you have the right stuff? Gullview Technologies is an exciting new and rapidly growing technology company focused on taking on the most vital and challenging business and technical challenges our clients face in competing in our… https://t.co/v6zuysvjil https://t.co/PvdIuws3r5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey applications and custom… https://t.co/bFv2Eyidtc https://t.co/h2uAo3GKkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/31zsahOjAJ https://t.co/7bXko6NH4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angry Birds maker Rovio cuts boardroom pay after profit warning: HELSINKI (Reuters) - "Angry Birds" maker Rovio proposed cutting the pay of its chairman and vice chairman following a drop in the Finnish mobile game studio's market value amid tough… https://t.co/h7puVbuYUD https://t.co/1LsQSC7XA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: UI/ UX Design Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design, Optimize, and add features to an existing HTML/JavaScript user interface Debug and fix all issues related to new features added Demonstrate progress to the… https://t.co/j3ZHZ8jPSy https://t.co/0JFhW5QPKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Software Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software, hardware, and portfolio of… https://t.co/zKqhNoTJfu https://t.co/YvDAseMRoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Android Developer: Prestigious Technologies Firm is currently seeking a Lead Android Developer. Candidate will be responsible for leading development and implementation of innovative mobile applications for Android devices. RESPONSIBILITIES: Develop… https://t.co/WZhTBaJSdO https://t.co/hczZyNZKSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS/DevOps Developer: AWS/DevOps Developer Raleigh, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsAWSTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12+ months contract with Mobilesmith. CTH. Try for GC. PHONE HIRE. Top… https://t.co/fRlQOU3V6u https://t.co/tkP64smkcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest people you will ever meet in any particular… https://t.co/9lIlta47JZ https://t.co/pT7GjxrTud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer: The Senior Backend Developer’s primary responsibilities are to code robust solutions and assist in managing a flexible pool of vendor and freelance developer talent to expand BlueprintNYC’s core products.He or she will uphold… https://t.co/aBmSbrMtrk https://t.co/hvgNfuPkCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator, state attorneys look for answers from Facebook: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The leading U.S. consumer protection regulator and attorneys representing 37 states stepped up pressure on Facebook Inc on Monday to explain how the social network… https://t.co/S6LMlz3gZY https://t.co/kMnWPvAKEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/1ttupeDgwo https://t.co/q1p1GyfrCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Specialist: We are seeking an experienced Senior Quality Assurance Specialist to add to our Software team. The individual will perform manual and automated testing of new software releases to ensure all business requirements are met… https://t.co/BNvLXVLw9N https://t.co/ls4XZJvV0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Architect/Developer (CONTRACT): Our enterprise technology strategy and solutions engineering team is in need of both part time and potentially full time seasoned .NET architecture / development talent. Our two technical leaders on this… https://t.co/WzkPcIo4gy https://t.co/ivFBWuQOUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Integration Test Lead: Sr. Integration Test Lead – (1800004E) Description JOB SUMMARY: The Senior Integration/Test Lead will be responsible for systems integration, test plan, design and support technical activities related to CRM/ERP integration for… https://t.co/0CZmrN6IKf https://t.co/UURQzuBcii]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>