<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[People need your prayers more than your criticism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You aren't ready to lead until you care more about the success of others than your own success. #leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you operate from stillness or striving? [Today's Blog] http://t.co/Z6avB8hRtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be able to learn from everyone. If you can't, it's not a sign of your intelligence. It's a sign of your arrogance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We long to be fully known and fully loved.  The gospel is the announcement that it's possible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is God calling you to stay where you are or step into something new? This could help you decide. https://t.co/IOkgfiaeEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you preach like Donald Trump, you'll end up like Donald Trump. [Today's Blog] http://t.co/cD5XDIE60g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace doesn't exempt us from doing hard things.  It enables us to do them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickBrandt: You plead my cause.
You right my wrongs.
You break my chains.
You overcome.
You gave your life, to give me mine.
You say th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus' power &gt; Our sin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no podcast in the world that can give you the love, care and joy you find in a local church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be back in the Gospel of Mark at Restoration City tomorrow. Like being reunited with an old friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We want quick and comfortable. God wants lasting and transforming.  Shallow roots don't bear much fruit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Examine me, O Lord, and try me; test my mind and my heart." (Ps. 26:2) We need grace to understand even ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prioritize the lasting over the immediate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Today's Blog] Can you name the 3 things your pastor most wants you to bring to church this Sunday? http://t.co/kXnS4HcND2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God only uses people who know their own desperation for His power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace doesn’t keep score. Maybe we shouldn’t either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madisonyli3 @Karen_Kong so glad it helped!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more we believe God loves us as we are, the more we grow into someone better than we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confront today’s reality to maximize tomorrow’s potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God changed my life in college. Praying He will use Restoration City to do the same for so many more.… https://t.co/ED1WtQHDcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most powerful person in any room is the one who is most authentically loving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Courage To Be Loved http://t.co/WnQ5uc3ZrZ http://t.co/GhkY1OOTM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tolerating unconfessed sin is like deliberately stepping on the air supply of joy in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God’s call on our lives can never be achieved in our own strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God wants to use you. Not a phony made up version of you but the you He created.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love people who ask how you're doing and actually wait for an answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're trusting Jesus with your salvation, you can trust Him with your provision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's great freedom in not needing to be impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass Transit &amp; Sermon Prep http://t.co/wc1WKVJxRv http://t.co/rgghyQdlic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more love you show, the more impact you’ll have. #leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God always has the final word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's plan for our lives flourishes in the context of community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the thought of the gospel freeing, confronting, challenging and lifting people all over DC this morning. #church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So honored to have a great friend and mentor, Rich Hurst (@richontoday), preaching at Restoration City tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no better time to keep your mouth shut than when you're exhausted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contributors always grow more than consumers .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love meeting Restoration City people for lunch. A cool office is a nice bonus! https://t.co/wtAL0mAMzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders, figure out how to weave the new podcast from @toddadkins and his team into your personal… https://t.co/8ltFLiO4pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want increased joy and effectiveness? Learn how to be present in the moment. http://t.co/n3McnnogKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard work, not laziness, is the evidence of a deep trust in grace. Grace supplies the power to aim higher!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Thursday night texts about our College Community Group! Jesus continues to grow that group &amp; deepen love for the gospel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baltimore! Praying and believing your best days are yet to come. https://t.co/v4X2u2oN0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Influence is about freeing people not controlling them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A community shaped by the gospel will be attractive to and welcoming of the most broken sinners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeMartinezDC @byaaroncdavis @drshow so good!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many breakthroughs and insights trace their roots back to unhurried moments. https://t.co/5zMqlJPwdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are places in this city that make you think you're in Europe. #DC https://t.co/w55FxIemJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envy is one of the most efficient joy killers imaginable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A United Church In A Polarized America" Catch the podcast here: http://t.co/RV71oobv72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A church that models unity in diversity would capture the attention of a polarized America. http://t.co/UjINxK24pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christians cannot settle for a diverse city.  We must work for diverse neighborhoods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting The Most Out Of This Sunday [Today's Post] http://t.co/HSsKo6NS72 http://t.co/WxvJD0Vp3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We will delight in obeying a God who we're convinced loves us even when we don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you live in 1 of 7 cities @SummitNetwork is planting in this year? Find out &amp; get involved http://t.co/wvPeWRRTGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Restoration City Is NOT Gathering This Sunday [Today's Post] http://t.co/sOMyPqMpB0 http://t.co/qbPQl1UeM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a great day at Restoration City.  So many stories of God working and turning hearts to Himself.  Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ of Nazareth, turn our hearts to you and quicken the Spirit within us as your church gathers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you making the choices that lead to a life of faithfulness? Find out tomorrow at Restoration City. http://t.co/2JqyyXcMhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rough week?  Remember, God's grace overwhelms our failures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If God is for us, who can be against us"?!? (Romans 8:31)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world of fakes, the future belongs to those with the courage to be authentic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing good grows in the soil of bitterness. [New Blog] http://t.co/Qi9yszFwTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faithfulness to God requires a battle against distractions. [New Blog] http://t.co/LlhFzqAxG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growth requires the humility to acknowledge you're still learning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The mouth of the righteous is a fountain of life" (Prov. 10:11). What are you speaking into people's… https://t.co/MHqBtgtDNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on stewarding what God has given you instead of why He hasn't given you more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don’t grow your own leadership by criticizing others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday - Friday is as sacred as Sunday. [New Blog] http://t.co/pDAzf2PG2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how easily we demand God punish others for the very things for which we expect His mercy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JrodSayers @passion268 go to whichever venue is easiest for you and your friends. bring a whole crew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to be great days! https://t.co/YXJPavFJq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authority doesn't create influence. Authenticity does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is alive. Hope is real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to @tonyalany for leading us so well this morning.  Amazing heart.  Pretty good voice, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making God a means to an end is idolatry. Using all of our means in the pursuit of God is worship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love summer in DC! @ Georgetown Waterfront https://t.co/F1ejdxNULa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't really know yourself without first knowing God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baptism Sundays are the best Sundays.  Can't wait for tomorrow at Restoration City.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You exist to know God. Leverage all of life in that pursuit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel is the ultimate display of God's glory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envying others never increases your success. It only increases your misery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Restoration City - don't forget to bring some diapers and toddler clothes with you on Sunday. http://t.co/dbMzVLB11D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We take opposition as a sign to quit.  God designs it as a prompt to pray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is more interested in deepening our faith and displaying His glory than He is in changing our circumstances. #TrustHim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a statue becomes a prayer. [Today's Blog]: http://t.co/0qqmNY6dTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're trying to hide it, you already know it's a bad idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So grateful @jdgreear started living his newest book long before he wrote it. #GainingByLosing http://t.co/iYbUyeIxyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal for today: Exchange my burdens for God's power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budgets are vision on a page. Love where God is taking us at Restoration City. http://t.co/4fAy47hQjn http://t.co/0Dr9ot8GET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll be doing baptisms this Sunday at Restoration City.  Want in? http://t.co/zg7JA6VO48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss a chance to gather with the people of God to hear from &amp; worship God. #church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing up way too fast! https://t.co/rX7aFdFTQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our friends form our character - for better or worse. Chose well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know the connection between learning and praying? [New Post: Learners Pray] http://t.co/DbEEWrxZwk http://t.co/Q9OjFNhw26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel saves, transforms and sends. Anything less isn't the gospel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't have one single person at church on Sunday who was on the Ashley Madison list.… http://t.co/22M5KiX15x http://t.co/Az0EYWiOSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special day with the boys while Laura was with family in Richmond.  Lots of time at playgrounds and… https://t.co/pQ4n9X1VWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have never been more excited about Restoration City Church than I am right now. Believing the best is yet to come!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>