<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/6OmyTKM2PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/Rd5eYiWm3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/jQC8OP8kwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/D2s381a5Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/BOm5HVLcg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/vRc7QdXrc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/TwrfZK5Wzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/01cC0azShw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/sPbh6JlfGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/mIzIJwhMvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/lYUtLg316E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/z63lGkhqf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/98pDcM2WaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/O8VNiBfNim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/W6XzMeKMbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/BnVjPST2V1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/RO92s1qwqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/CHyg32HCo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/Ww3uMBTdB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/tSj73jO12K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/up1BDlm5FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/gw3pSJmKAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/CdRQGarI4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/C9IpoXxvOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/J22eXs32RE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/dZm5bWLARt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/BgHXMFra9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Facebook-Top Tips for Business Success  http://t.co/0QSV7EBw8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/k803dNGCrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/wLm71CDqs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/MqMfQKYyaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/nKaw7z8C6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/rmoWXINXMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/gw3pSJmKAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/5yXOFd9faC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/K7o9kIralV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/RXR1trST7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/igGg5Ufb70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/dPCmqxkG25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/nAdUGqkZL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/nxuoH4aBHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/LUKG2elrHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/70nTgSu6LR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/AVw1v0Ah7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/1SBhfwJub7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/7FU6h4anMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/u3r3MeLL8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/wUasPOnWwi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>