<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeejayOV2 @RT_com April 1st?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan It's not in the RDS where my curse finds itself. Hmmm.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc True. This is why I @ you. Not to argue or have a go, but to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan Haven't you forgotten? If I back Saracens, I guarantee a Leinster win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc Fair. Enjoy tomorrow. Always good to have views questioned. It's the only way  I learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc This case is sad all round. Not a time to shout jokes in public for cheap laughs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc I think it's unfair for you to feel uncomfortable attending a match.
As for your second point, my nonsense was the suggestion that there is a specific relation to rugby. I don't see it like that.
 @'ing is my attempt to read intelligent answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan True.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc You're struggling to reconcile it because it's such utter nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan I would be shocked if any Saracens side were bate out the gate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan Aye. I thinking Leinster by no more than 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc The latter. 
There are bad people in the world. It shouldn't deter good people from enjoying good things. We all need our escapes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted @molloyjh @AnnLeinsterFan https://t.co/iafNytXDjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saracens @ 5/2 to win @AnnLeinsterFan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KeejayOV2: This just has to be enjoyed. Sensational from Andrew Conway. #MUNvRCT https://t.co/kRavabMZjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan @leinsterrugby Proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rugbyPhilBB Get a new hobby and good luck tonight. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @leinsterrugby @LaighinPit Like, tots Moike!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @leinsterrugby @LaighinPit Dark Soide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter Ooooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter I think Leinster will win but I like those odds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racing at 9/2....hmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell From Dub? Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's fake news ads in your neighbourhood, who ya gonna call? Gav Sheridan! https://t.co/hoTgSrj1sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevZCastle @DonTonyD @iamjondraper @solomonster https://t.co/AB3ySQgatr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciaran_Parker01 @Munsterrugby Savage TP debut Ciaran!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rugbyPhilBB Bank holiday weekend, Kinsale 7s festival, Ed Sheeran last night in Cork. Busy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Koci71 Agreed. As long as you're not being a dick, do whatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rugbyPhilBB Plenty reasons for it but still disappointing enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Koci71 I'm very confident that the majority of Munster fans will be all in for Leinster next weekend. A strong Leinster pushes Munster to be better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeeeeeeeeeeet https://t.co/R2liMUBkPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell No Indo? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyMick Sure. He'll be accepted or punished at next GE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 @BigDunc123 Hopefully a career in politics after the rugby!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyMick Nothing wrong with a bit of personal ambition if he becomes an effective administrator. Hard to know what electorate think until the next GE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbucsfan @molloyjh @Outhalf @IrishRugby @leinsterrugby Hey, that's me!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @LeinsterRoyalty If he does I'll eat my shoe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie Ah here. If it was a real thing I'd be all in. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think when he says 180 people, he added an eight and a zero to the number by mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odran, the gift that keeps on giving. @phog6189 @threeredkings https://t.co/hN6HnVj83x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 @JurassicArse Former alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings I was hoping he would be benching tomorrow to offer cover for the centres.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Fair point. It looks like he won't play again this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazziola @threeredkings Cool. It's just the site looks a bit amateur so I was concerned for a minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Mr Kings, could Taute have played in this development game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. https://t.co/p6L0YzXmOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know why this is a good thing, see the final question of this interview: https://t.co/QwyNlrM2jM https://t.co/jL56VFflXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazziola @threeredkings Are we sure that site is legit? It looks very amateur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDunc123 @0899mc Posters shouldn't be allowed in the first place but that's another debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulldoze the hospital leaving even more people without care. Makes sense eh. https://t.co/41CvGtZY0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family that took a wrong turn at some point. Deranged. https://t.co/XJdgCeNiXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage He says roll instead of role in the next tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLiberal_x  One for you. https://t.co/8E7vWpwzj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phenomenal! https://t.co/hhR3iQwAaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vOIU7ugcBM https://t.co/dIVtq5Zx2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dublinbarista: Regardless of what side of the vote you’re on, I think we can all agree that campaigning outside maternity hospitals is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detached emotionally indeed https://t.co/xYXdG1K52S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilreynoldsnfl Ticketmaster also throw tickets immediately on their sister touting website. They are scum. Please use another company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilreynoldsnfl It's the done thing in the US though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please ditch Ticketm*ster. https://t.co/OZN3iJLdtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio silence from other Pro-Life campaigners (from what I've seen) on the horrendous behaviour by ICBR yesterday. Speaks volumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @andymcgeady Exactly. It is both obscene and idiotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonrug: We all criticised the PRO14 for not bringing in enough TV revenue. Now they have increased it from about £11.6m to more than…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to the Taute try Vs Glasgow intensity GIFs from @threeredkings this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AMAZlNGNATURE: This will forever be the best video on the internet 😂😂 https://t.co/2rgsZgwvk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell @phog6189 I'm sick of a sterile Aviva. RDS will be rocking. I will be a lone Munster head in the Anglesea Terrace full of STHs. Fun will be had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @CorkSeashell RDS all the way. If stuck for tickets let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intensity GIF is not enough. https://t.co/qjqOEEwHrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then again I'd rather have seen Boylan debate one of his peers who are on the No side. https://t.co/ExqgdyEWNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home run for Yes side. Boylan played a blinder. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 The fact she was the best they could offer is a bit troubling. Though she didn't reach Sh*rl*ck level of fairyness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 Decided to watch. Have to agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinDeeganEsq Poor bloke took a wrong turn somewhere in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage Linky?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Muted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Aye

"Is this a joke etc..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Owen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Maybe you have certain accounts blocked then. You're better off. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug The overreaction! It's just an error.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reaction to this. Sheesh. https://t.co/ci8mt0qFlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G'wan sure. #menforyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 It's very Brazil Vs Germany at the last World Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage As for the "buddy" advertising stuff, I don't really have an opinion on this either way. I use PP as I find its website/app to be user friendly.

Educating yourself on the dangers is vital of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage I see gambling in the same way as other potentially harmful activities that are socially acceptable: Moderation. I set an annual limit and stick to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwainJTJones Juan Martin Fernandez Lobbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage Yo Tom. Where do you stand on buying and selling shares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:) https://t.co/fZn7Bu2O52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scullyaIiens: me taking note of all the irish people tweeting about the royal baby today https://t.co/hER23pKGVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EimzT Sunny af! Great pics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup What happening to soupies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage You on psn good sir?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Bill Johnston situation. Why still not re-signed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donnacha Ryan wanted to leave. He confirmed this. Why is the "feckin' IRFU are riggin it for Leinster" shite being brought up again.

Ryan wanted to leave. Good for him. Deal with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyMick Wootton up to today deserved a shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath You...you tricked me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_McGrath Never bet again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-match is not complete without the happy/sad times of @threeredkings on Patreon. I'm about to tune in.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>