<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought that if we lasted for two to three years that would be fantastic. - Ringo Starr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/tgNPjUQCxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/dYjgnGV0i1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/QEBTACm7zB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/y6A53wG02z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/nwkq4SMgNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/9G9c7uzoBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/dqjq4iq5Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/MaRMLEQDRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/SpuzDOHSFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not really interested in making money. Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/Aa38cPJ1kF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/Up1ji9XjhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/FyceaX9U8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/MLyo8RyQnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/f8od0NaRpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/Y8Vo23XBD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Peter Frampton  http://t.co/xNM03eDFnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/gTddTPnQZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/2dq9P9P4TX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/PEiJMruMJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/Ag4gEMOnpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/9AtMKY2yd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/ByFcidHHb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/VNDw73cU6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/Po1IvR0Orf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/qXk82yzFif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/GeZq8eKBXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/JmOrNd89lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/3fMjsW0RMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/kuzdeWe8Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/xnQMe55QQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/McZ2oLCs98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/StkRveBXjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/MQREjUdQ3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/e9PlaZwqSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/mk6Ah8lDTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/CHfcVSIkLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/taffjwkg8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/EOTW3Y4Z0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>