<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: First Student is a leader in transportation of children K-12. As the largest provider of student transportation in North America, First Student is more than twice the size of the next largest competitor. Industry-leading safety programs,… https://t.co/ByqBcOJBgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Associate: Software Engineering Associate Requisition ID: 180053684 Location: Columbus, OH, US Job Category: Technology Duties: Analyze the features and perform impact analysis, develops application to the requirements and testing of… https://t.co/JGu7882mnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yann Sommer: Goalkeeper, singer, guitarist and chef extraordinaire: There are few lonelier places than being the team's goalkeeper, especially when you're culpable for a mistake. https://t.co/R6AeQRTK72 https://t.co/SQbKC7Mgx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total Recall: The CNN news quiz: The immigration debate took some disheartening turns, and corporate giants are feeling the heat. On the plus side, everyone's catching World Cup fever. What do you remember from the week that was? https://t.co/mPm1YsjHPB https://t.co/WvUnk6ufYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BPM Developer: BPM Developer Ref No.: 18-23692 Location: Cleveland, Ohio Title:- IBM BPM Consultant Location:- Cleveland OH/Pittsburgh PA Contract Role – Experience in Architecting, Analysis and Development on IBM’s Business Process Management (BPM) tool… https://t.co/cmjOZYa79z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handcuffs, assaults, and drugs called 'vitamins': Children allege grave abuse at migrant detention facilities: In court documents, children allege grave abuse at migrant detention facilities, ranging from handcuffs to assaults to drugs disguised as… https://t.co/npY5Uy8wBO https://t.co/gbFhTm1DmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge rules that CFPB's structure is unconstitutional: A federal judge says the structure of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is unconstitutional. https://t.co/wlcwEXAxMX https://t.co/L8qTWjkoc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help move womankind forward: Reports of abuse against women and girls around the world are discouraging. But organizations are fighting back. From ending child marriage to stopping violence -- from education rights to gender equality, here are some of… https://t.co/lOjeKX5Rv1 https://t.co/ouCTWK8t5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Material Application Specialist: Arconic has an immediate opening for a Material Applicator. Fast paced, team-based environment. Duties include determining the most appropriate type and quantity of metal, based upon customer specifications and available… https://t.co/eV3EanBUgn https://t.co/brugX59LWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaf prisoners are trapped in frightening isolation: Sara Novic writes that deaf and hard-of-hearing inmates, in addition to not being given reasonable accommodations under the law, are also routinely neglected and mistreated. https://t.co/5RVIc1Lt5N https://t.co/0OFEKO1U8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not your typical summer beach reads list: It's time for our annual summer book reads. This is not going to be your typical list. For 2018, books that deal hard truths from history and culture are on tap. https://t.co/ToXUI3aTtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Req ID: 40602 Lubrizol, a Berkshire Hathaway company, is a market-driven global company that combines complex, specialty chemicals to optimize the quality, performance and value of customers’ products while reducing their… https://t.co/dKrbA4HRe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certified Business Analyst Professional (CBAP): Certified Business Analyst Professional (CBAP) Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your… https://t.co/gu1Hfocyl8 https://t.co/acE8FWsed1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Mickelson 'embarrassed' and 'sorry' for US Open putting controversy: He was bullish over the "putt-gate" controversy that threatened to overshadow the US Open, but now Phil Mickelson has had time to reflect and says he is "sorry." https://t.co/cWPrwh3bwq https://t.co/h5b9BnL6QX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage and Backup Lead Engineer (Remote/Virtual) Job: Storage and Backup Lead Engineer (Remote/Virtual) (Job Number:437328) Description: Job Description – Looking for a Lead Enterprise Storage and Data Protection Senior Engineer with design and O&amp;M… https://t.co/7WXpwq6xxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Exodus Integrity Services, Inc., (gotoeisinc), is a rapidly expanding technology company headquartered in Northeast Ohio. EIS provides quality services to our clients by instilling honesty, commitment, and hard work to find the most… https://t.co/dveYoPoNRA https://t.co/ryp3TCmYFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noura in her own words: Teen who killed rapist husband shares her story: Sudanese teenager Noura Hussein is on death row for killing her 35-year-old husband. CNN obtained a first-hand account from the 19-year-old, who has appealed her sentence. https://t.co/qXVVusI98M https://t.co/0fUKoemWZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This elite police force guards the Himalayas -- and also practices yoga: Members of the Indo-Tibetan Border Police join yogis the world over on June 21, to celebrate International Yoga Day. https://t.co/cX4ubbqmlg https://t.co/rS8GUTHM0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI: Sexual assaults on flights increasing 'at an alarming rate': The number of sexual assaults reported during commercial airline flights is increasing "at an alarming rate," the FBI said Wednesday, and the number of actual cases could be much higher. https://t.co/Pujbqjazuy https://t.co/KsiuaSnZAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrants undeterred by Trump's zero tolerance policy, fear of separation: At the Senda de Vida shelter, a few miles south of the border with McAllen, Texas, many of the 50 or so migrants contemplating their next moves seemed undeterred by a Trump… https://t.co/zRAAOFNwY6 https://t.co/EoLkMeiyUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Johnston, Iowa – United States Job Start Date – 06/01/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Desired Role &amp; Level: Standard Role / Level: Developer / Sr Project Scope and Brief Description:… https://t.co/onabscxMNF https://t.co/atikl9k0xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart 'disturbed' its former building is migrant shelter for kids: Walmart says it is disturbed that one of its former stores in Texas has been turned into a shelter for migrant children separated from their parents at the border. https://t.co/kCL6Rp9szT https://t.co/7WUyEvzM4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Will sign 'something' to keep families together: President Donald Trump indicated he would take action shortly to both improve security on the border and help keep families together, speaking briefly with reporters Wednesday. https://t.co/tMBIP3ZDpE https://t.co/pOQWnws8zY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood rallying around immigrant children separated from their families: Two series centered around Latino characters are challenging other shows to take a stand against the immigration policy that has resulted in children being separated from their… https://t.co/xXSHO6nJ2N https://t.co/Vo31jMyrXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instrumentation Engineer Certified LabVIEW Developer: Dynetics Careers – Instrumentation Engineer – Certified LabVIEW Developer Go to homepage Menu – Jobs – About Us Log in Login Log in Register now Forgot Your Password? Instrumentation Engineer –… https://t.co/gwHQlWjFn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ramps up midterm travel as Republicans grow worried about immigration debate: President Donald Trump is ramping up his political travel ahead of the midterm elections, eying November as the most potent referendum on his presidency even as he faces… https://t.co/OY6S1wuAMf https://t.co/RyD4ufjwit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Warehouse ETL Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/yB184EBObu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: SR Number APPS/APPS/2018/****** Designation Technical Lead Location Ohio Job Family Domain (Domain) Job Description (Posting). To act as a liaison between the business and technical teams| analyze and document business requirements|… https://t.co/8dAqYhmlNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid the World Cup, Vladimir Putin scores some diplomatic goals: The Kremlin may be locked in confrontation with the West, but the rest of the world is coming to Russian President Vladimir Putin. https://t.co/foN0gUYxmE https://t.co/CJ4VYyYkLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Program Project Management: At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers… https://t.co/HJOxbPldVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees held by Australia languish in a world beyond suffering and suicide: We are forgotten people, discarded on forgotten islands. https://t.co/8m9dmdBaeW https://t.co/ZZWz1mhWLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump supporters think of family separations at the border: Some say undocumented immigrants are to blame for bringing their kids to the border in the first place. https://t.co/UXJCtQbSfK https://t.co/m8jrJUjI40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's 50 best restaurants for 2018 announced: The world's 50 best restaurants for 2018 have been named in Bilbao, Spain. So where's the No. 1 place to dine? Hint: It's a restaurant in Southern Europe. https://t.co/A6vCP9xepg https://t.co/RFPXvicNF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Manufacturing Techno- Functional: Oracle 11i – Manufacturing Techno- Functional Ref No.: 18-23683 Location: Cleveland, Ohio Role: Oracle EBS R12 Order Management and Advanced Pricing Location: Cleveland, OH Duration: 6-12months W2 Oracle EBS R12… https://t.co/VSikmAzMKA https://t.co/wkHyN6biPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact-checking Trump on immigration, family separations: President Donald Trump on Tuesday delivered a stream-of-consciousness-style speech on immigration as furor over his administration's separation of families at the border reaches a fever pitch. https://t.co/uO6xVqIEX6 https://t.co/61ZjLpG2Rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL/SSIS Data Integration Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 weeks ago(5/1/2018 1:12 PM) Job ID 22084 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/pM9GZxPKYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz and Jimmy Kimmel are better at raising money for charity than they are at playing basketball: Sen. Ted Cruz can now add basketball scrimmage champion to his resume. https://t.co/HOICgfLkGF https://t.co/W5qowWMM8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe IDMS DBA: Mainframe IDMS DBA Ref No.: 18-01305 Location: Westlake, Ohio Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 06/04/2018 Required Skills IDMS Database Administration IDMS Database Maintenance and upgrades Starting up and Shutting down the… https://t.co/Gbebjxzv7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former top federal prosecutors call on Sessions to end 'zero tolerance' at border: A bipartisan group of more than 70 former US attorneys are calling on Attorney General Jeff Sessions to reverse the Trump administration's policy of prosecuting all people… https://t.co/JRo8SJJRN3 https://t.co/SyDmeHcz2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Developer: Roles and Responsibilities: 1. Gathers requirements from stakeholders, designs the solution aligned to requirements, platform(s) architecture and infrastructure. 2. Develops, tests, maintains, and enhances data stores (tables, views,… https://t.co/T6ubS53Ddk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans are satisfied with Trump's North Korea summit: One week after the high-profile meeting between President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, Americans are generally satisfied with what was accomplished in the summit between the… https://t.co/hKEgU3pBXX https://t.co/lFMqblV5Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zookeepers say goodbye to world's oldest known Sumatran orangutan: Perth Zoo has bid a tearful goodbye to Puan, dubbed the "grand old lady" of Sumatran orangutans, who died Monday. https://t.co/Zdqq3Yo0le https://t.co/MMGMRZUHQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer C# Programmer: **Software Engineer – C# Programmer** Locations:Johnson City, Tennessee Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Country Division… https://t.co/H8NwjDsfEl https://t.co/dJEL25YPsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and… https://t.co/LX1ofGegsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-CIA employee charged with leaking classified information: Joshua Schulte, a former CIA employee, has been charged with leaking classified information, the Justice Department announced on Monday. https://t.co/dldgeEmuKw https://t.co/wbW7VqUwKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: What Software Engineering contributes to Cardinal Health Software Engineering is responsible for designing, developing, implementing and supporting applications, systems and IT products required to achieve the company’s business… https://t.co/5SxHYNOOM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration officials say there was no call between US and North Korea this weekend: There was no call between US and North Korean officials over the weekend, two administration officials tell CNN, despite President Donald Trump telling Fox News on… https://t.co/oGgkLuDSnN https://t.co/qO9fKO7QsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Systems Analyst Senior: The Financial Systems Analyst Sr. position is a fast paced, deadline driven position that will focus on Customer Relationship Pricing &amp; Profitability activities to include management and validation of content for weekly… https://t.co/tOKDwDqiS4 https://t.co/z8QT3LbEOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sound of children crying for their parents at the border: Audio published by ProPublica of children howling for their parents after being separated from them at the US-Mexico border adds a visceral element to a controversial immigration policy. https://t.co/mze1mRYizh https://t.co/PZVQi2J23f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka's deafening silence: Anushay Hossain writes that Ivanka Trump must use her platform to advocate for children being forcibly separated from their parents thanks to the Trump administration's policy of zero tolerance. https://t.co/slwk24Kbcw https://t.co/mbHTD3Ivya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Job TitleSolution Architect – ID:31506 Duration24 Months Start DateASAP Job Skills Java, NoSQL technology (CouchBase or MongoDB) and integrations (Jboss/IBM Data Power) LocationMarysville, OH Date Posted04/17/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE… https://t.co/CVJXef6v1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the high school teacher bidding to make American rowing history: In between teaching biology and psychology classes, grading his student's papers and revamping lesson plans, high school teacher Bryce Carlson is an extreme sport athlete, weaving in a… https://t.co/gatXhElHxn https://t.co/ykScOY3tzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Acquisition Manager (Information Assurance Engineer): USfalcon – Careers USfalcon, Inc – Benefits – Employees &amp; Returning Candidates – New Candidate Senior Acquisition Manager (Information Assurance Engineer) LocationOhio Job Description and… https://t.co/ER2YLtwwyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reddit co-founder highlights importance of paternity leave: Paternity leave was the first time that Alexis Ohanian's fast-paced lifestyle as a hard-charging businessman and husband to tennis superstar Serena Williams really slowed down and he could take… https://t.co/4TnErxVJW9 https://t.co/0D5Kd6wgzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrities, Fox News and luck: How to get pardoned by Trump: "The media is the only way to send the message" to Trump, Simona Mangiante, wife of George Papadopoulos, told CNN. "I don't know how to reach him otherwise." https://t.co/RPo0giGsRv https://t.co/uxm5gHjlGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin could 'bring the internet to a halt,' banking group warns: Don't bet on bitcoin ever replacing the dollar or other traditional currencies, says a new report by the Bank for International Settlements. https://t.co/lqRIcEhkDI https://t.co/JH0WAhA4sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mother Meral': The woman trying to drive Turkey's Erdogan from office: Some call her Turkey's Iron Lady, and others call her she-wolf. But presidential candidate Meral Aksener prefers "Mom," and she wants to be the nation's next leader. https://t.co/BjB5aK1Cgt https://t.co/eUYuMnrBqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Threat Management and Incident Response Engineer: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for… https://t.co/L7p7HxOEZN https://t.co/RKmxqyISMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Seeking a highly experienced Project/Program Manager to plan and manage confidential business projects in our Nuclear Pharmacy Service business. Projects consist of a combination of some or all of: contracts negotiation and… https://t.co/3adk5S5HM8 https://t.co/QAATZW15cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Email Marketing Consultant: Web Developer – Email Marketing Consultant – Columbus, OH We are currently seeking a Web Developer to work as an email marketing consultant for a National Fortune 100 company in downtown Columbus, OH. An ideal… https://t.co/coEUgH40Mk https://t.co/7knw0dFFq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart shopper accused of making more than 1,000 fake returns: A 23-year-old Walmart shopper is accused of making fraudulent returns at more than 1,000 of the chain's stores across the country. https://t.co/dGBQTATDkE https://t.co/m6X1vIr9iz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack developer: For Siemens Full-stack developer job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers Job Full-stack developer… https://t.co/BI9G5Ww6Hd https://t.co/7gjYVWWIcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's dying of cancer. Now, he's the first patient to go to trial to argue Roundup made him sick: The first of hundreds of cancer patients will see his case against agrochemical giant Monsanto go to trial starting Monday. https://t.co/o3n4aRdJfc https://t.co/SHnbAiwmim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – CAT Modeling: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 20 hours ago(5/30/2018 3:29 PM) Job ID 23661 # Positions 1 Category Product Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/1Dy3YhMwKf https://t.co/Z6cILewOav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin can't wait for his next photo-op with Trump: In her presidential weekly briefing, Samantha Vinograd writes how Trump's performance at Singapore summit makes Putin even more eager to meet with him soon. https://t.co/8rRRLw7xsn https://t.co/MFbkDlAef9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior ETL/Java Developer: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn May 29, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #4918: Information Technology Job Code: #4918 Title: Junior ETL/Java Developer Job Type: Contract Job Location: Columbus OH Job Description: Manifest… https://t.co/R5FT4YsrL7 https://t.co/9Yv9KHvofS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGCT Cascais: Nicola Philippaerts races to victory: Belgium's Nicola Philippaerts won the Cascais, Estoril leg of the Longines Global Champions Tour for the world's top show jumpers. https://t.co/XoA1pqRtUg https://t.co/8TtR2rVa5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Long term-contract ETL Developer * Experience with designing, developing, testing and mapping server and… https://t.co/GsOYDc4Uto https://t.co/hpinUst3wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: First Student is a leader in transportation of children K-12. As the largest provider of student transportation in North America, First Student is more than twice the size of the next largest competitor. Industry-leading safety programs,… https://t.co/omIwKle0nF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India moves ahead with tariffs on US goods: India has proposed hiking tariffs on 30 US products in order to recoup trade penalties worth $241 million. https://t.co/zfX4QtIZc1 https://t.co/aKgZzCyzLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIGINT Technical Analyst, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/3/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/E9fa1X2E5h https://t.co/AbuJ6whTMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/06/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Description: This role is responsible for the overall direction, coordination, implementation,… https://t.co/52rit1qvfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who stands to benefit from the UAE's visa and investment rules?: The UAE opens up to foreigners in a move to attract top talent and investors. https://t.co/rB3BaMtLHe https://t.co/VAeL7BRtmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant, Business Analyst (Lean and Business Process Optimization): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to… https://t.co/A6oRijnO0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrants disembark in Spain after Mediterranean standoff: A group of migrants stranded in the Mediterranean for more than a week after Italy refused to let their ship into port have begun disembarking in the Spanish city of Valencia. https://t.co/5AQln96jmR https://t.co/DZfIZUFH4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kilauea volcano destroys 467 Hawaiian homes, officials say: Lava now covers 5,914 acres or an area of 9.24 square miles, according to Hawaii County Civil Defense Agency. https://t.co/oz67llc3Zf https://t.co/vhsWFUvWH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Performance Testing Lead: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 week ago(5/1/2018 3:14 PM) Job ID 23558 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/PZntyw4RIS https://t.co/5yMPJULQOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Business Analysis (SAP Order To Cash (OTC)): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/KnTen1Emrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead: The BioPharma Reporting &amp; Analytics – Tech Lead is a software engineering craftsman that is a full-stack engineering lead and coach that is an expert at working in all layers of an application and guiding and building a team of engineers. They… https://t.co/LJ5uSP61sK https://t.co/vqqzbx90NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer of extreme temperatures continues, to the beat of climate change: The summer of temperature extremes just keeps going, with record heat waves this month on all four continents that occupy the non-tropical Northern Hemisphere where it is now summer. https://t.co/OWBcGSHj4w https://t.co/udeegiKzpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's first ski descent of K2: High-altitude adventurer Andrzej Bargiel has become the first person to ski down from the summit of K2, descending from the world's second-highest mountain on Sunday. https://t.co/jeRzC1RmuV https://t.co/L7k4rIxxeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women bear Alzheimer's burden; researchers are trying to discover why: At the Alzheimer's Association International Conference, researchers are exploring biological and social differences that might explain why more women than men develop dementia. https://t.co/IJpwIu4tph https://t.co/ywwmTmEhcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle developer: Oracle developer cleveland, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/27/18, Posted Date – 06/27/18 Primary SkillsOracle EBS,Oracle DeveloperTax TermsC2COverviewclient skype Oracle Developer with one of our best clients with Oracle EBS… https://t.co/17qAN9DG2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police reportedly called on black man opening his own business: A San Francisco lemonade business owner is blaming racism for a call to police that saw him questioned outside his own store on suspicion of burgling it. https://t.co/89czjvOBh9 https://t.co/Rgc5qHaL1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician Mid/Sr TS/SCI Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio: Requisition ID 2017-34055 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Come join General Dynamics… https://t.co/qk0kEigHf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer | must have a thorough understanding of systems and data integration policies, practices procedures: ETL Developer | must have a thorough understanding of systems and data integration policies, practices &amp; procedures Columbus, OH 07-15-2018… https://t.co/TpDkZDD2VV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan vulnerable to Chinese invasion without US, foreign minister says: Without continuing United States military support, Taiwan would be vulnerable to an armed takeover from Beijing, the island's foreign minister told CNN in an exclusive interview. https://t.co/KziHrOB3KN https://t.co/QQ43fTeVCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Installed Support: Under moderate supervision, provides project management oversight and direction to ensure overall success of a limited number of initiatives by developing appropriate project implementation plans to include but not… https://t.co/y6Ww3ucB2J https://t.co/XlPZ8Q8XPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Iran will 'suffer consequences the like of which few throughout history have ever suffered before' if Tehran threatens US again: US President Donald Trump has launched a furious all-caps Twitter rebuke of Iran declaring "you will suffer… https://t.co/uHokP7C6wO https://t.co/zSytNVR9ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Business Analysis (SAP Global Supply Chain Business Analyst): At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to… https://t.co/BSdqHBkLsJ https://t.co/24ElGRBvGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan's most beautiful places: Taiwan impresses visitors with its sheer diversity of beautiful places. From man-made delights in cities such as Taipei to its gorgeous beaches and mountains, here's where to go. https://t.co/E4UtJDCRNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families of anti-Ortega protesters forced to take refuge in Managua cathedral, human rights group says: Mothers and other family members of detained anti-government protesters fled to the Managua Metropolitan Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception after… https://t.co/34dFBRvAkA https://t.co/UaSD3KTHII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic lawmaker calls for 'new generation' of leadership in party: A Democratic congressman from Massachusetts is calling for "a new generation of leadership" to emerge in the party come November. https://t.co/Pm5GZTRdFD https://t.co/BxF1Xi4pWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: FISA documents on Carter Page 'confirm with little doubt' DOJ and FBI 'misled the courts': President Donald Trump on Sunday accused the Justice Department and the FBI of misleading the courts, following the release of a previously classified… https://t.co/XzDFJNyKQ9 https://t.co/v6JrV4Oa6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Angular Developer: UI Angular Developer Ref No.:18-11860 Location: Columbus, Ohio Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 07/05/2018 Must Have Skills: Angular.JS experience HTML/ CSS Angular.JS software engineering experience Familiarity with… https://t.co/57QcCTfYFp https://t.co/wZ5Dx5vvpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storms, landslides and heat hit Asia: Extreme weather is striking parts of Asia with deadly flash-flooding in Vietnam, a tropical storm prompting evacuations and disrupting travel in China and an ongoing heat wave in Japan. https://t.co/8bJmvq6D9q https://t.co/zUQQkiI75B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer II – Multiple Positions: Discover your Promise by helping our students discover theirs Ohio University is seeking qualified applicants for the following positions in the Information Technology Department Web Developer II (2 Year Term)… https://t.co/j8Td3e79yO https://t.co/WYuTjYem2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed standoff at Los Angeles Trader Joe's ends with one store employee dead, wounded suspect in custody: A Trader Joe's employee is dead and a wounded suspect is in custody after a standoff in Los Angeles stretched through several tense hours Saturday… https://t.co/P6rcvp2hmD https://t.co/f3C8h5ivWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer / Project Manager (Design Group): Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, systems integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other… https://t.co/XV3j862TnX https://t.co/UTF0k5levd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Transformation: Signet Jewelers is seeking Project Management resources to support the Transformational Leadership Team (TLT). As a Transformation Project Manager for the TLT, the selected incumbents will be responsible for managing… https://t.co/zEP3GfLQPx https://t.co/LabpcXznaE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>