<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAngDarling argh , three hours in the 36 deg heat in forest and didn't manage. Only a day left before he dies we think..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@schnauzerpowser @suellenmorris thanks! If only I had the time!! Jo to the schnauzers! #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilyjaynemaher #cutestaffy !! you should enter her in comp to find britain's cutest staffy. enter here: http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@junglist_joe great photo!! you should enter it in photo comp to find britain's cutest staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaronKelly91 you should enter this pic here http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3 in search for britain's cutest staffy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francescarust so sweet! they just get a bad rep! we are looking for britain's cutest staffy. please help spread word http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirbear_x #Cutestaffy!! We are looking for britain's cutest staffy. Please check it out and help spread the word http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pawsandpurrs do you know a #cutestaffy? If so please tell them to enter comp to find Britain's Cutest Staffy http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3. Pls RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget about the #cutestaffy comp and please help spread the word!! ENTER HERE: http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to try and catch a wounded stray dog in Indian forest - using only a piece of rope and biscuits called'DROOL']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived back in Spain to photograph dogs in the hot sun for new project. 5 days of rain and cloud forecast. Sunny in UK tho! Joy..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some photos I did for @thegentleauthor of the wonderful raven keeper at the tower of London. http://t.co/gAGTQpEsAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HRP_PressOffice: Read about Raven Master &amp; his ravens at Tower in Spitalfields Life, beautiful photos @MartinUsborne @thegentlea ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stray podenco that I saw with wire round its waist has just been rescued! more here http://t.co/3hENyNwDu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Wellcome exhibition about Death: in 20thC more people killed by diarrhoea than by all wars combined: SHIT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hunting dog saved...http://t.co/uzGtMvzYyH Thank you everyone who chipped in...amazing. Touches my heart #galgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you catch a lost spanish hunting dog? http://t.co/xVk3tQNLrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone speak Italian?...http://t.co/HLlxjs3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New pics of Spanish hunt dogs #Gaglos on http://t.co/gpky8Jwq @fourandsons. Prints for sale to save these dogs here http://t.co/DP0fb3Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amsterdambside: Dog Drama by @MartinUsborne: http://t.co/3d1FVFbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darlingdog: @MartinUsborne look at that bendy neck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cl_hurst good. Thanks for being in contact!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelenWilsonArt: @MartinUsborne well done you! Im doing a smaller bit of 100 animal sketches in 100 days for the SSPCA so hats off to ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenWilsonArt that's great!!! Good for you. My full support. Stay in contact. Read the blog if you can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarkingBlondes please RT. Fine art Dog Prints for sale - all money to Galgos in need.  http://t.co/DP0fb3Gt #galgos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet please RT. thx. Fine art Dog Prints for sale - all money to Galgos in need.  http://t.co/DP0fb3Gt #galgos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterEgan6 please RT!  Fine art Dog Prints for sale - all money to Galgos in need.  http://t.co/DP0fb3Gt #galgos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish hunting dogs Prints for sale - money goes to rescued dogs. Pass on the word! http://t.co/DP0fb3Gt #galgos http://t.co/nAbGoHp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article about my dogs book in daily mail http://t.co/DA2xvSBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: @MailOnline on our @MartinUsborne exhibition in March. Read up before it opens on the 19/3! http://t.co/WOn09ojj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cl_hurst I'm in Spain with dogs I'm afraid. Just saw this. Did you try calling RSPCA? Any luck with it? Let me know if you need more help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarkingBlondes Pls RT the sad story of the Spanish hunting dog on my blog. People need to know, thnx http://t.co/Gk7WYnqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet Pls RT the sad story of the Spanish hunting dog on my blog. People need to know, thnx http://t.co/Gk7WYnqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterEgan6 Pls forward the sad story of the Spanish hunting dog. People need to know... http://t.co/Gk7WYnqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: Moon Bears Journey to Freedom Part 2: http://t.co/N2DJADcG via @youtube  Rugby on soon but please watch this breathtakin ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met nice lady at BBQ in Spain who said Bill Gates is making fake clouds to float around world to poison kids and control population]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise and fall of the Spanish hunting dog - a brief account. http://t.co/dwbHFhqo  Do people know about this??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kim_CocoonPhoto: @MartinUsborne Can you please RT this.
http://t.co/H26PJnDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain is in recession. I'm the only one in huge hotel complex. Receptionist made my breakfast - cold - whilst on phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi from the Galgos hunting dogs in Spain. Getting ready to pose in my crap outdoor studio.. http://t.co/dwbHFhqo http://t.co/muQ7Yxh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is helping others a huge act of the ego? Does my bum look big in this bird-saving outfit? Check this blog: http://t.co/sXdJbtIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SHADOWWABBITS8 will do!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonymarsh yes, apologies!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Visorvision yes, sorry, was hacked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayneford yes! Sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rebecca_Leisk thank you, will try and do what I can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: Dogging Around @VelourMagazine! @MartinUsborne #photography #thesilenceofdogsincars http://t.co/obQ38WDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My accounts been hacked. Please don't open DMs from me saying lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Spain to help Galgos hunting dogs - ritually discarded when the season ends http://t.co/EXtqSRRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: A taste of things to come @Independent profiles our @MartinUsborne exhibition opening on 19th March! http://t.co/RznYdG8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayneford  thanks for tweet Wayne. Hope to see you at opening. Will send invite soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@azizaazul Love it!!! Should ahve been the logo for the book!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @azizaazul: @MartinUsborne I was browsing your amazing photo book, when I just realised I have a one of my own. http://t.co/J3xrlUQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LYoungBorthwick thanks so much for your donation!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: @MartinUsborne @marcthevet Follow and support Martin, he's doing fantastic work and needs our help. (-:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOldClucker we have a fb page http://t.co/kBXpWq4TRp but not a page just for mango.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JensWall hi jennifer. if going to the same address £10 will cover postage for both prints. many thanks for your support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKWLB saw you just made a donation. MANY thanks from me and mango]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKWLB thanks louise. please help spread the word about the blog and Mango!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOldClucker @marcthevet @PeterEgan6 thanks for sharing!! we've raised about £300 so far.. getting there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kim_CocoonPhoto thanks!! will have a look now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet @PeterEgan6 This puppy saved from being sold for meat - trying to bring her to UK http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who knows how i can help save #pangolins ? recommendations of charities I could work with please? http://t.co/0RpVKUKd8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been researching illegal wildlife trade &amp; totally fallen for Pangolins. Interesting article here: http://t.co/rLC72sSOAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived in Delhi. No sleep. Bag gone missing. Got in taxi. Driver stooped for speeding. Then he hit motorbike. Then he demanded tip. INDIAAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissKimReed it's not a bad home. In south west London. Thanks for caring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for all the amazing support you have shown for Mango. Raised £250 so far! http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mango Wants Fish &amp; Chips! http://t.co/FOubt38UqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonkristinsson: @MartinUsborne Bears in cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonkristinsson now there's an idea!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to India to help wildlife. Have NOOO idea what's going to happen, but I suspect bears and more...keep reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tamara_Beckwith: It's my latest @hellomag #blog! 
@MartinUsborne @skstanding @GPnutrition 
@Thebritishladyv @doricooperman #JudasKis ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jumping dog to lift the spirits....http://t.co/o8Ze7i0RdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets bring Mango back to the UK and give her a new home. Look at that face! http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ http://t.co/FYowmd2qIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mango (puppy) was saved from the dog-meat trade. Buy her portrait to help bring her back to UK http://t.co/39PGpal3EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline AMAAAAZZZZING!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline thanks for the video. that does lift the spirits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 191: A PUPPY SAVED FROM THE DINNER TABLE! http://t.co/aTxIvdxJrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Usborne Photography - Spring 2013 news - http://t.co/Ml2dnx90rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason to stop the dog meat trafficking ... If cruelty isn't enough then rabies is: http://t.co/A6dYl3DJ6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline thank you for this. Hope you're doing good. Off to India on Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pupaid: Thanks to all ur fab support we're almost at 10,000 followers pls keep helping us raise awareness to stop this &gt;&gt;&gt;& ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissKimReed he does have a sister but not many friends. He's been so ill, so sad..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Jo, after 9 visits to hospital he's finally had to move to a care home- out of E London http://t.co/P0XWaza5MN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: Peter, Exciting Progress Towards Ending The Dog Meat Trade... http://t.co/EXWQ2WZdSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: I believe there are more people opposed to cruelty than those who are for it. One big idea will stop it. What is it? Sim ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a new photo book out by Nazraeli press  - pre order your limited edition copy here http://t.co/bXSNTNFUbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @julienewton_: Just seen @MartinUsborne The Silence Of Dogs In Cars @TLBGallery Beautiful evocative work!!! Welcoming gallery!!! #Pho ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessWhite99 oh god, you and the rest of hte world! Get better soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaletsdumoulin Ha!! You can order from my site http://t.co/RD6kvTTw74 Nice to tweet you!! how things???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @designboom: the silence of #dogs in cars by @martinusborne - http://t.co/K7PR2Zfcte - http://t.co/SVNt11uzMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessWhite99  there is, I'm in bed with mild cold. How you???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nice review in Evening Standard tonight  of my show @TLBGallery 4/5 stars..http://t.co/Urp3FG3Afj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tamara_Beckwith: Wonderful review for The Little Black Gallery's latest show. Brilliant! @TLBGallery @Martinusborne  http://t.co/XAa ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotteshbaugh: The Silence of Dogs in Cars by @MartinUsborne http://t.co/IV2ptKs5GV … #dogs #photography #amazing #dogs #amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog meat anyone? I photograph man eating illegal dog and he storms off. Then he asks for his food to go in doggy bag. http://t.co/xdvG5vH21f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline @tlbgallery you are very welcome!! Thanks for coming down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TLBGallery: 7th anniversary of photographer Bob Carlos Clarke's untimely death. Honour his memory http://t.co/2gcQdNiWXz @kickstarte ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come out to play in the snow. Book signing @TLBGallery in chelsea at 11:30 this morning, snowball fight after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @portmagazine: 'Silence of Dogs in Cars' @MartinUsborne will be signing copies of his book at @TLBGallery tomorrow morning @ 11.30 ht ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>