<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/4QZAOBHalV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/8Hc1LbiYib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/BOMwsHoVOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/OSDF3XRK9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/uoH8JDlzxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/nOfMKsVdNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/kOlKWSAaJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/WqJVhC2UQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/fhVxKzkJKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/YW60379ePg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/fG13scqWUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/U9tt0g8Uzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/USf4jJyhGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/akTgbF2xw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/XuCC3igici]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/Cm6ImJBxcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/dCDF7crwJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/031k4x3cmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/NuetbaQPq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/D9kX9h2ON8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/DzafCPVBTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/IkZb17dotl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/KUFWnKYjhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/K0ms8HSbOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/ZdnKi3uHNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/csh2qhpKKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/XRZ5WEDZ4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/zCOeNKOICa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/SlMTmb5GIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/HrOYwjjjQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/vPJZdDtyrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/wZQ57Onwcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/sjrQE1CsJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/Pg4EuulXyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/BQlkYlcLZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/DbveODKIze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/Ou44saruNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/45pjstdBru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/68mJC5jmad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/9ynN6XMd0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/n6MGy59TAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/IO3Iklw1h1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/orUf3bdCno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/Zo7dR4zulA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/RZVfZgIv2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/QJ9eV8c2H5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Ox0DBVzHoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/wD6yICE9pW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/OTBWYVnsD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/xNZ7LelpTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/wfHdle1qhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/7WqiNLKhDZ]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/pI4xhLESpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/vt4hrwT5LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/v2Q38r4VXS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>