<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/Re773QWy8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/p5PCxVNJ52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/pbah1azAKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me where your priorities are. Show me where you spend your money and I'll tell you what they are.  James W. Frick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/wwPiFJypiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/GtOGIiqGbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/2BQnKkvwwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/pEyzkQAEMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/dXmKvNKbFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/wbXSZ9B8YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/JPmq06wy7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/zjaMicXym1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/SVCXZAYGj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/mAMLIph734]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/MeDvVTBymW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/VO5REGkXhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/UyXRaGHRUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/FqShsC3Hsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/DUQCIY4cPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/McZ2oLCs98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/QmCVQVVvPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/zhHfnSN1Uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/nZNsDHqnqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/lToA9pqq3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/SoGLNfobSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/D1n6QR8HuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spencer Davis Group  http://t.co/RPUxpKzUBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/7cpE6wbp3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/bSEPRG4tU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/PyUVsZ8DV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/zmr5WSDafC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/qM6axNnrT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/bHrSmpPXPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/9T9odDDEjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/8R364HYqWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has great marketing, among the best PR and marketing in the world. - Ron Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/qbAVX4kco9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/Ag4gEMOnpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/FyceaX9U8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/zqFMCuPA1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/xE2fQUqyaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/pRgValDy2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/WJ0d5nai22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/yWXh6NYsvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>