<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A real decision is measured by the fact that you've taken a new action. If there's no action, you haven't truly decided.-Tony R. #FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leafs_NHL Please send a DM if you would like to reach out to me like this.... Thank You.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filipemasetti Happy Friday! Make it a great one! #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Agenda=success]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBQ is on, the patio is clean and the rum and coke is poured! Happy Thursday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SDImktg: SDI Marketing is hiring Promotional Representatives in Toronto http://t.co/mnc5d3DH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyKreativ yes I know. I have to admit, I am quickly becoming an "apple" fan.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emails come instantly to my new iPod. An hour later my blackberry notifies me. #pullupyoursocksBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filipemasetti huge glare!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Power30under30 great question! Answer---&gt; @tonyrobbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Power30under30: If you could have dinner with anyone who is dead or alive, who would it be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SellingChange: FYI, If U don't have a profile pic &amp; career/personal description in UR Twitter bio, ppl R unlikely 2 follow U, no ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoodandWineGirl any perks of going this weekend ?! :) I hear there is a lot to sample and a lot of giveaways....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanTomblin No more! Should be an interesting season 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Smart Case" is coming up on #cbcdragonsden All painting/screening done by Versatile Spray Painting--------&gt; Heslin Family owned! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBCdragonsden on Now! Tune in....might have a shout-out to Versatile Spray Painting. Heslin family owned for three generations....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoodandWineGirl we are heading here this weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wealthy_barber Great to hear Dave! Congratulations on the new venture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wealthy_barber on Dragons den next season! That's exciting!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Wealthy Barber' joins Dragons' Den http://t.co/2lJkjTks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It starts with why! Work on controlling your thoughts and focus on your end game #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuccessHow Thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinTheJackal great to connect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New iPod touch plus docking station and attachment for the car! My girlfriend knows me so well :) #awesomebirthdaygift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So grateful for the incredible people I work with here at Platinum Edge! Thanks for a great birthday morning :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qudimat Thanks for the mentions! :) Have an incredible week #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GolfDigestMag: BREAKING: @TaylorMadeGolf acquires @AdamsGolfInc for $10.80/share in cash. That's about $70 million. (via @EMichaelGW)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiscesAreUs Another year older today! Happy Birthday to all the other pisces joining me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyKreativ Scared me with that honk! Have an awesome weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andrewsheehy228: Astral Media has been purchased by Bell. Does this mean that Corus will be purchased by Rogers next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@streeterstevens Thank for the shout-out! And a big #FF to you for capturing the greatest moments in life with a single photograph!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @streeterstevens: #FF @mike_heslin Passionately hooking people up with careers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what makes my day? Getting retweeted by @G1000inspection. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a way to start a Friday! Met with @MarkGCoaching :) Couple projects in the works.... #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_robin_sharma @kirstistubbs That's the "what". I believe she is asking "how" you get yourself into that state of mind....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artisanobakery Looking forward to launch a powerful and productive Friday morning with @MarkGCoaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wealthy_barber "Pay yourself First" @strombo! Do it people :) #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wealthy_barber on @strombo tonight! Excited to see Dave on the show....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djdavehall: Join me Saturday, St Patty's Day. Spinnin' tunes at the Fox &amp; Firkin. #YongeandEglinton locate. 4pm till 2am. #shamrocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OakvilleChamber: Welcome our new members including @marsanhomes and @oakvillemusic #oakvillechamberofcommerce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much energy in Platinum Edge right now, I think the walls moving :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MissKahlaB: Watching Dragon's Den...#entrepeneurship meets entertainment ☺ #cbcdragonsden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#dragonsden #cbc @CBCLive. Tonight! Let me know what deal you would invest in....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escape from dark/negative people. They will kill your creativity, excitement, and productivity. #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Power30under30: "Nothing is impossible, the word itself says 'I'm possible'!" -Audrey Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're seeking individuals with a strong sales background and a true hunter mentality. In this role you will be part of a high-energy team w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorontoThrives and there are sales jobs available! On the search for sales professionals in the city! #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArleneDickinson on @strombo tonight! Looking forward to it....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkGCoaching: Energy is contagious if you want to be infected. What's the worst thing that could happen. #conceivebelieveachieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UndertheNeonSky: Nothing great was ever achieved without enthusiasm #quotes Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DealBind: Check out DealBind for every daily #deal and #coupon in your city! http://t.co/RakLv2Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Par on the 1st! It's going to be a good year :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CornOnTheJob: Fill in the blank:  Dream jobs are _____________.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dusting off the clubs tonight..... First round of the year tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G1000inspection Thanks Gemil! I will email you.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People don't buy WHAT you do; they buy WHY you do it. ----Thought of the week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shepherd_group: Is It Ok To Walk Away From Business? http://t.co/nxCTatJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you looking for a new and exciting opportunity in the Staffing & Recruiting industry? We are currently looking to add Account Managers …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're seeking individuals with a strong sales background and a true hunter mentality. 
In this role you will be part of a high-energy team …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know of golf courses opening the Halton/Hamilton area this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrockUniversity: Job opportunity at #BrockU as Mathematics Development Programs Coordinator. Application deadline March 12 http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shepherd_group @entripy Yes it does! The reality is throw on your nicest suit, get out there and make things happen! More fun ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kimgarst: The only thing we can control is us...our attitudes, our outlooks, our choices. Don't stress over the rest. FOCUS on what  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KONY 2012: http://t.co/8DSyA28t via @youtube Spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenEagleGolf For sure! I'll be throwing darts at some point up there this year :) When are you opening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenEagleGolf  Amazing golf and incredible people here! Happy 50th :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No voice! Have to rely on emails, texts, and social media to get my message across over the next few days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the search for motivated young professionals in #toronto There is a vision that you can be part of! Something truly great....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Briana_Ewart: @filipemasetti I thought of you when I watched this, #Kony2012 http://t.co/Hgn2VmsV watch it, spread it! #stopatnothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a 1 am drive into Buffalo for a 6 am flight! :) Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuffaloNiagara what's the weather like down there around the airport? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bahamas here I come! See you in a week :) #livewithpassion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tonyrobbins is a major driving force behind our operations. Looking forward to handing out books to all we meet!#livewithpassion Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkGCoaching: If you are not excited about your life, it will be pretty difficult for anyone else to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FocusGolfGroup Looks great Doug!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shepherd Group: http://t.co/37iBoEbt via @AddThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @inlifeawareness: “Its not about the goal. Its about growing to become the person that can accomplish that goal.” ― Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scenery in the city today  http://t.co/5xAcsWKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyrobbins live on @oprah right now! Amazing down here in toronto!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#lifeclass with Tony Robbins in #toronto this energy is contagious ! Time to take action :) #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Robbins in Toronto -9000 people strong http://t.co/V0XzJUos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The walls are shaking in here with energy! @tonyrobbins @Oprah #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WonderMoms_ca @oakvillebiznet Thanks everyone especially Tamara! Thanks for the exposure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So powerful down here at Oprah's life class in Toronto! 9000 people strong #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderMoms_ca: RT @oakvillebiznet: Platinum Edge Recruitment  http://t.co/in8MN9h0 @mike_heslin #OakBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Toronto for the rest of the day to listen and learn from some of the worlds most successful business and life mastery coaches!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see @Oprah and @tonyrobbins tomorrow, look up the definition of excited: you will see a picture if me! #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlphaStarr @wondermoms_ca Do it! And thanks, glad you enjoyed #livewithpassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OakvilleBizNet Thanks for sharing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WonderMoms_ca Thanks Tamara for posting this up :) greatly appreciated . Hope your having an incredible weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eric_forsyth Already out riding in Oakville! Haha #yourglassesareinthelobby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eric_forsyth haha. Nice! So excited to cruise all of Ontario!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bentley on the phone bringing in business!  http://t.co/k1DJbjtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my dog could climb trees I would have a nice collections of squirrels by now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrantfordDiva t Thanks for the RT! Hope you had a great Easter :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@WonderMoms_ca: Jealous:) Have a blast RT @mike_heslin: Off to see @tonyrobbins on Monday! #livewithpassion @Oprah” THANKS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love It!  http://t.co/7yrO3bha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of 6 shelves stocked up!  http://t.co/VgveCeeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see @tonyrobbins on Monday! #livewithpassion @Oprah]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>