<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity may knock only once, but temptation leans on the doorbell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream it.
Believe it.
Achieve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have difficult days, have faith. https://t.co/4RqDIRdHfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would life be if we had no courage to attempt anything. -Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being positive in a negative situation is not naive. It's leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we did all the things we are capable of, we would literally astound ourselves. -Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true. https://t.co/eX6kUez5XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let yourself be silently drawn by the strange pull of what you really love. It will not lead you astray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are not what has happened to you. You are what you choose to become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord, lead me so I can lead others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all fall, pick yourself up and start a new. https://t.co/egpCgSLz2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you say yes to others, make sure you are not saying no to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to have it all figured out to move forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is always a demonstration - not just a set of words or a feeling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: What's your favourite comfort food? :)

Get this awesome tee here --&gt; https://t.co/KitzpJwFOI https://t.co/E8V0XGa1Sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I choose to be happy today. https://t.co/UgmSpQRUBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless. -Mother Theresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time you enjoy wasting, was not wasted. -John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdoch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength does not come from winning. Your struggles develop your strengths. -Arnold Schwarzenegger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never too late - never too late to start over, never too late to be happy. -Jane Fonda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great point. https://t.co/0gM2efqIhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person you should strive to be better than, is the person you were yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 great pieces of advice. https://t.co/Eb8EB39LDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best &amp; most beautiful things in life cannot be seen, not touched, but are felt in the heart. -Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose positivity today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you lose something, don't think of it as a loss; accept it as the gift that gets you on the path you were meant to travel on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence without ambition is a bird without wings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worry does nothing but steal your joy and keep you very busy doing nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day may not be good but there is something good in every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What lies behind us &amp; what lies before us are tiny matters compared to what lies within us. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest glory in living lies not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall. -Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True!! https://t.co/RF61pIBnnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you desire to make a difference in the world, you must be different from the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of your thinking determines the quality of your life. - A.R. Bernard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do just once what others say you can't do, and you will never pay attention to their limitations again. - James R. Cook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive try ignorance. - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful things happen when you distance yourself from negativity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiness of your life depends on the quality of your thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count your rainbows, not your thunderstorms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for the good in every moment. https://t.co/idrnqn5ACn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without dreams, we reach nothing. Without love, we feel nothing. And without God, we are nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because we are all one when we forgive others we forgive ourselves, which is the first step in the healing process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is better to look ahead &amp; prepare than to look back &amp; regret. -Jackie Joyner-Kersee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By being yourself, you put something wonderful in the world that was not there before. - Edwin Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can see the positive sides of everything, you'll be able to live a much richer life than others. - Celestine Chua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You deserve a vacation :) https://t.co/19Z3IRtRRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to trust the journey, even when you do not understand it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you can win, you have to believe you are worthy. -Mike Ditka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you do something out of love, you don't count the cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice. https://t.co/0pFIIan7up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With every rising of the sun, think of your life as just begun. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give more, expect less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday. https://t.co/SRtxXCW2KZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life isn't measured by the breathes we take but the moments that take our breath away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughter is the sound of the soul dancing. https://t.co/aSPy6AYH7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promote what you love instead of bashing what you hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to fly, you have to give up the stuff that weighs you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your passion is priceless. Never stop the pursuit. https://t.co/F4XQrzgroO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself only with people who are going to lift you higher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this very moment, life is perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things turn out best for the people who make the best of the way things turn out. -John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is hard at first, messy in the middle and gorgeous at the end. https://t.co/OHjOeeqtai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmazingiGrace: YOU'RE INVITED! We've been given special permission to invite our followers to an ADVANCED Screening.  Click this link -…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being defeated is often a temporary condition; giving up is what makes it permanent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Treat EACH &amp; EVERY day like a new beginning. -&gt; Visit https://t.co/1qRf0GTTd3 &amp; signup for our inspirational emails https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends are angels who lift our feet when our own wings have trouble remembering how to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is found when you stop comparing yourself to other people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more powerful then someone who has faith and a mission. https://t.co/m8wIFrz5gI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/TUV6Taouau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you handle it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Love takes action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL https://t.co/kBqbIITFXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's "no" is not a rejection, it's a redirection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/ir7ID3wtnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being rejected from something good just means you were being pointed toward something better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter. - Martin Luther King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes there is!! https://t.co/4CE0sdavpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about having the skill to do something. It's about having the will, desire &amp; commitment to be your best. -Robert Hernandez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't love too soon.
Don't trust too fast.
Don't quit too early.
Don't expect too high.
Don't talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: Look for the good in every moment. https://t.co/6YOPX8a3em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you've imagined!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a storm always comes the calm. https://t.co/T1Gkap4wsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What defines us is how well we rise after falling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has ever made himself great by showing how small someone else is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your beliefs don't make you a better person, your behavior does. #walkthetalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: To think is easy. To act is hard. But the hardest thing in the world is to act in accordance with your thinking. - Johann…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith… https://t.co/b5Ds9gbXwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell the truth or someone will tell it for you. - Stephanie Klein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without Dreams
We reach nothing.
Without Love
We feel nothing.
Without God
We are nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it with passion or not at all. https://t.co/0Qw2S0imyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never a loser until you quit trying. -Mike Ditka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait. The time will never be just right. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray, forgive yourself, appreciate others, listen to your gut, do things you enjoy, &amp; remind yourself that we are all loved &amp; connected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your head up high. https://t.co/GCbqKRjVft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Have FAITH! God has  a message for YOU. Visit -&gt; https://t.co/1qRf0GTTd3 &amp; sign up for our daily emails. https://t.co/vUsH…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>