<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to californiatortilla and everyone who came out to support the team headed to… https://t.co/YvxcAdIawc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. So grateful for today. Thank You, Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus may not do what you expect. But He'll never let you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imitating others is cheap. Finding your own voice takes incredible courage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the language you use build the culture you want? http://t.co/HLmjjhMBaj http://t.co/xdAOyMLiTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for the days spent here earlier this month and parents who are so welcoming.  No place on… https://t.co/tLEnSYbBsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude predicts performance. If somebody is negative, their performance is going to be negative. http://t.co/smkTa59jqN via @michaelhyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let self sufficiency rob you of the joy of surrender. [New Blog] http://t.co/MWvMfrOc4k http://t.co/MbGyypUdl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is enough. Always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel frees us from the chains of religion's hypocrisy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in or moving to Brooklyn?  Check this out. https://t.co/nWlIjgbwlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends who go to Kigali are great. Friends who bring you coffee from Kigali are even better!!… https://t.co/nHjKSnhFJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I remember that Jesus is the head of the church, the more I enjoy being a pastor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's great joy in bringing God a blank page instead of a script. [New Blog] http://t.co/Ml785a5ynk http://t.co/BXfKkIrsyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love people who love the church! So grateful for the incredible people who serve on Sunday… https://t.co/MmVPOsnnQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for Restoration City to be back together tomorrow morning.  10am. Synetic Theater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing God has big plans for His church in DC this fall.  Love being on this journey with my… https://t.co/IJeYoftNfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our lives lack prayer because our hearts lack faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Apart from me you can do nothing."(Jn.15:5) It's exhausting to spin your wheels in the mud of nothingness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New to Restoration City? Free for dinner on Sunday? Laura &amp; I would love to have you over to the house: http://t.co/dTIhfIZHRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! https://t.co/5KC9pjPLqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus breaks us free from the paralysis of perfectionism. [Today's Post] http://t.co/qL8a3B2AkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, DC!  Great to be back home after some incredible days with family.  Thankful for the gifts of rest &amp; work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much joy! Love this little guy. https://t.co/ZugNIZ6vJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much love and gratitude for this incredible woman.  Laura, you give so much and love so… https://t.co/nVQUAhqNVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's the people most comfortable in church who are the least comfortable around Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't just read books you already know you'll agree with.  Look for authors who challenge your thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you in need of a little digital detox? [Today's Post]  http://t.co/U79fcnHPO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest: The Person, The Mission and The Provision Of God http://t.co/8JQswocceV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember - no Restoration City gathering tomorrow morning.  See you on the 23rd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn is 1 of 7 cities @SummitNetwork is planting in this year, see the list &amp; meet the planters http://t.co/wvPeWRRTGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders - are you actively shaping your organization's culture or passively discovering it? http://t.co/BkWC2pElLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack's reaction pretty much nailed it, "Wow!! God made all of this?!?!" The beauty of creation shouts… https://t.co/8WdYRKmqhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following Jesus rarely takes us down the expected path. It's the unexpected that builds our faith! https://t.co/0dHgyxO7VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss the chance to register for #Passion2016 before the price goes up.  These will be life changing days: http://t.co/1KwqDDjOdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura got some rest and I got 51 hours alone with the boys.  We survived and learned a lot. [New Post]: http://t.co/ZNLS0geWW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of life's biggest moments come in obedience to God's quietest whispers. Obey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!  So grateful for Jon, Jeremiah &amp; Natalie.  Love the way they led us in worship this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing revives the soul like praying through God's Word.  So many promises to make our hearts soar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel enables and compels us to transform souls and societies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget it. You two are not getting breakfast in bed!! https://t.co/DElxTwhHlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership longevity is significantly enhanced by a willingness to listen and learn. Leaders are learners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace doesn't exempt us from effort.  It empowers effort with supernatural effectiveness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanielquick Here's a great resource: http://t.co/3SLYSYQlLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Bible doesn't bother you, you're not reading it right.  [New Post] http://t.co/NUVhQ0dcb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get in trouble every time #ILoveMyChurch trends higher in my heart than #ILoveTheChurch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are made in the image of a relational God and the path to being fully alive is the path of community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love thinking about how much God is going to accomplish through His church all over the world today. #ILoveTHEchurch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cousins. https://t.co/ipotxPhIhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our dependance on God grows in the gap between our vision and our ability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evil is real but hope, love and freedom win in the end. #911Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy. Love watching his little personality emerge. https://t.co/L5Jkg5GaqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let adulthood rob you of the blessings of friendship. [New Post]: http://t.co/PvSNq1TELq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our small stories take on incredible beauty in the context of God's eternal story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is your most valuable commodity.  Spend it more carefully than money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't settle for what you can do in your power today. Rely on the strength of the God who raises the dead! (2 Cor. 1:9)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlotte friends: Do not miss the launch of @mercycharlotte. A brand new @summitnetwork church plant in Charlotte, NC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw @warroommovie this weekend and loved it - so strong on the power and beauty of prayer! So good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might not be there yet but I love the transition to fall.  It feels like a season designed for… https://t.co/Zyd07wQ5Fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The love of Jesus breaks our addiction to the applause of man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed today at Restoration City? Catch the podcast here: http://t.co/ZeJyq4Pd7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow at Restoration City: Mark 7:1-23 - Religion and Jesus aren't synonyms. They're polar opposites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @passion268: Anyone who registers for #Passion2016 TODAY will receive a FREE collection of the talks from Passion 2015! http://t.co/XtIm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is the revolution our souls are longing to experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible team leading us in worship tomorrow morning @RCChurchDC.  Going to be so powerful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's mobile!  It may not be pretty, but it's effective. https://t.co/pheaHp7ebO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“But always seek after that which is good for one another and for all people.” (1 Thessalonians 5:15)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's calling is always accompanied by God's enabling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! https://t.co/otBQ7deXYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to celebrate Restoration City's first anniversary this Sunday! http://t.co/bUIQK8Lox8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is often doing His most powerful work when He's least explicable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every desire of our soul can be fulfilled in Christ and none will be satisfied apart from Him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw so many serving so selflessly for the good of others today. Humbling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the best day of Jack's life.  Thanks, Alexandria Fire &amp; Rescue! https://t.co/Z2hSwTCUpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kids have no idea that fall is about cooler temperatures &amp; changing leaves. They think it's about everything tasting like pumpkin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in our darkest moments, Jesus is with us and at work.  Don't give up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CatalystLeader: “We ask God for signs, wonders, and miracles, but refuse to go into circumstances where we need them.” - @ChristineCain…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it isn't a little scary, you aren't being authentic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A church that isn’t living on mission is a church that isn’t seeing Jesus clearly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing more fun than leading is speaking into, encouraging and believing in the next generation of leaders!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CatalystLeader: LEADERSHIP MANDATE: To awaken the wonder within to stir and disturb the imaginations of the people + organizations you …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time we indulge fear we diminish faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't trade digital impressiveness for personal effectiveness. [New Post] http://t.co/hu817CuUi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest gift you can give others is to become the person God created you to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous day in #DC. Love the simple reminders of how majestic this city is. https://t.co/eiO51h6t1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC friends, @jdgreear is coming to town for a @catalystleader event on 11.17. I'm going. See you there? http://t.co/inEQVxecSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack's favorite part of Community Group? Couch time with Gizmo! #LiveInCommunity https://t.co/667yg2DyvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying we  never get over the beauty, hope and power of the local church!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdeckard @AstroDoughnuts True...but not available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious…what's the best food truck in DC/NoVa?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trust in the Lord forever, for in God the Lord, we have an everlasting Rock.” (Isa. 26:4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legalism is always an affront to the grace of the cross.  "For freedom Christ has set us free." (Gal. 5:1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indecision is exhausting.  Get counsel, pray, search the Scriptures and then DECIDE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will replicate what leaders celebrate. [New Post] http://t.co/JNKDgTa7cC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make mental space for what matters most. https://t.co/fL3DsSEx5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one wins when a leader disengages. "The one who leads, with zeal." (Rm. 12:8) Keep your head and your heart in the game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leverage whatever voice and influence God has given you to accomplish as much good as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't care enough about your culture to defend it, you shouldn't be the one shaping it. [New Post] http://t.co/lfEro4mQDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership is about modeling culture. http://t.co/tXdhrGzERv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus supplies all the time, resources and power to fulfill His vision for our lives.  Don't hold back!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>