<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t ever get it confused youngsters!! #EY365 https://t.co/sOZmXtqCwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great lessons for the kids. It’s all for them! #EY365 https://t.co/mWXfQV4dtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s let’s move Monday! Let’s go get it (all that awaits us)!! #EY365 https://t.co/dLxlARQf95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was too good to not share!! When I inspire I feel empowered..#legacy https://t.co/zJluJBOgNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queens and Kings - we owe each other love, respect and honor above all else. When we uplift each other we uplift our family, our communities, our world. Stand… https://t.co/8TUOpow2z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I will add here is value, positivity, uplift and empowerment grounded in a love to add value to others that’s it! We must see ourselves as HE does before… https://t.co/SdgaMSwCea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing takes the place of being a good person that’s grounded in love! I will enjoy teaching my students this! #EY365 https://t.co/IVdrQ9ANqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our children are birthed with an imagination and we must teach them to take hold of all their capabilities, no matter how challenging. Nothing worth gaining is… https://t.co/MvhRW6llwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Children, I want you to know you can do the impossible.  I want you to know that love, respect and honor are traits to walk with daily. I want you to know… https://t.co/gmYblysdwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD, give me peace we’re I’m confused, give me wisdom when I may do something foolish, give me a life work that makes good use of my time, may I love no… https://t.co/lvZqj72EKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, buy Nike stock not just Nike shoes! Another lesson I will teach you. Be producers of assets not consumers of liabilities. #EY365 #myownclassroom… https://t.co/mhcuZ6bBok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must be true to myself and nothing moves my soul like empowering them....it won’t be easy...but they are worth it! #EY365 #launchingsoon https://t.co/w3mDC1btE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, this won’t be easy but it will be worth it! Be the first to ever do that “thing”....#EY365 #empoweringtheyouth https://t.co/5Qeh2hohuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, answer this question daily and you will leave with legacy in view! #EY365 #shelovesthekids https://t.co/5KsliuAwYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, here is another great lesson! #EY365 #herlifeswork https://t.co/pRmirA6KKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To my young people....fear is a distraction to impede you from destiny (legacy). I will teach my students to move forward while still feeling the fear.… https://t.co/bPyVuCQAmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 years ago today I was 16 and working at the Federal Communications Commission, I was just beginning my Federal government career. Great lessons, great… https://t.co/7eQHFpBusN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students let’s use the summer to formulate a business idea that allows you to use your God given gifts and passions. I will share my hustles as a way to assist… https://t.co/1yFYplz4Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26 lessons, ages 7 to 17 at a SE DC library, 90 minute lessons, a book assignment, a writing assignment and history lesson!  #EY365 she’s so excited the young… https://t.co/522YmFR7An]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teach them to dream. Teach them to have a legacy. Teach them to live a fulfilled existence. Teach them to be great. Greatness comes from God not mere men!… https://t.co/DnzkX3vYKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/WJI3WYcloM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/YxlbpE1wiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens...Life if short people. Each day we are getting closer to death. No one wants to hear this but it’s true! Let it go! Seek your peace. https://t.co/wQrSOeJk72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/o3tKyV92qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/kZHFfjcLhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/yiZxOmxJpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens, I’m grateful for another day of life! https://t.co/BiGYLqloYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fueled a new perspective for me!! https://t.co/bLL5Uc4oUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/psSYpe6dyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words are powerful people! https://t.co/reAtvprClO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in the process of saving for my next home - I don't want to spend any money - this is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though difficult at times - vulnerability is a blessing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be very careful of your thoughts.
Be very careful how you use your time.
Be very careful how you manage your energy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrantCardone: Think about it: What's the worst thing that can happen to you if you just totally go for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BurtonBrown: Are you helping to add value to those around you? How are you valuing the people in your life? #JMTeam https://t.co/1e36lU…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamousWomen: You deserve it. https://t.co/rNurSoUJnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_grit: You're life awaits go get it! https://t.co/uBnyWH5Mh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: Risk nothing win nothing. https://t.co/2QpHD7tsSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylewis: You must disturb your comfort zone https://t.co/d6DJYjiotT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GODs_Graces: Keep standing, keep believing and keep hoping because God has a bright future in store for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TozerAW: "Go to church once a week and nobody pays attention. Worship God seven days a week and you become strange!" AW Tozer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Women_Of_Christ: A good relationship is worth the wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylewis: What you allow is what will continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UncleRUSH: Be open to whatever comes next https://t.co/0zttl1a9UQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisBrownOnAir: Conflict is certain. Drama is a choice. 

#Truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/4jhTaXCNhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens had to share this one.... https://t.co/zEA6z3rRus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be grateful for the many blessings that are on there way to YOU..... https://t.co/EmJV4batjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens the only one you really control is YOU!  Always remember this. https://t.co/S5vJ3ArFPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve learned to train myself and discipline myself to see the positive in every negative situation. #sograteful https://t.co/APX1adFidl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just for YOU.... https://t.co/7qU3cCk0aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pray YOU never forget this! https://t.co/PDSM2UcxJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamseyShow - when will the everyday millionaire book be released for Amazon purchase?? Thank you for your daily contribution to those that want to become wealth + be generous + have true financial freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create something that is rooted in your passions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Women_Of_Christ: One of my favorite verses. https://t.co/yMRlC8kG5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UncleRUSH: Strong people lift others up https://t.co/PAjrthQ3Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a writer is a beautiful experience - it allows you to write your story using a beautiful scene with many twists and turns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out on Amazon. https://t.co/rt2YIPBywv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out on Amazon. https://t.co/X77tQHgPos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard someone say - that FEAR is stupid. Now I understand what that means.....#fearisirrelevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thequote: The only limit to your impact is your imagination and commitment. - Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you only said what you need to say - and use the other time to listen? How much would you learn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you only spend what you needed when you needed? How much would you save?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was my fault. I blame myself. I’m the Queen I control the board. No regrets just awesome + great life lessons! Being mad, upset and bothered killed my joy… https://t.co/5HGFDmN5hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for a few things and already see it coming! So grateful....don’t hesitate to ask God for what you want! https://t.co/uRhEhYe8aC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens always remember this..... https://t.co/RDAaOPJ7ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about being a GIVER....not a TAKER! Nothing wrong with taking sometimes though, have a balance. But let’s GIVE more! One of favorite pics of me taken at… https://t.co/SASKrV7t7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had a thought I had to share..”I’m not here to make millions of dollars I’m here to touch millions of LIVES.....” https://t.co/H8x1R9H6lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if we loved and respected those that DO NOT love and respect YOU? Give love, respect, kindness and honor ANYWAY!! https://t.co/HhnazGsjly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s called EY365 because this is about empowering them 365 days a year!! #EY365 https://t.co/8UlGg9mBhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gives my life so much meaning. Great ideas keep coming thank you GOD! #EY365 https://t.co/07yi4Jeb5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth. https://t.co/GTpA5bL8A7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t look at all things as bad. I’ve learned to ask myself...”what can I learn from this bad/unfortunate thing that has happened?”.... https://t.co/z4OoQJMZTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m so on this grateful vibe. It has changed my whole life outlook. https://t.co/s4xRyuZqbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is my e-journal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touch 7 people daily - by the end of the week I have touched 49 individuals - this is a note to SELF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisHogan360: If you have real character, money will not spoil it. Persons with genuine character can handle adversity and prosperity.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's up listening to the @TheMinimalists ....
then @RamseyShow I love these shows.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: The 3 H's for Athletes:
  1) Hard Work
  2) Heart
  3) Hustle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are fearless - you are deemed unstoppable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's getting quiet with age but - she loves her GOD, loves her family and loves living her dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to the @TheMinimalists - great info and great podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I just want to teach them all the values God has taught me...they have made such a profound impact on my life!” #EY365 https://t.co/MtsDtNvymT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A part of my legacy that I’m surely happy, excited and grateful for. To elevate the minds of young people what a joy it brings me....#EY365 https://t.co/4FdbkWXfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept yourself flaws and all. Accept yourself despite your imperfections. We all deserve a love that’s “unconditional”. https://t.co/rnHKjLNTZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m grateful because it doesn’t take much to make me happy! I’m grateful for simple things! Life-changing.... https://t.co/iDD95fmjuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We must teach this to our children”. https://t.co/v04hdIAzQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get in a quiet place alone and have some self-reflection - it’s necessary. https://t.co/vHTRlEyU0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being grateful has changed my LIFE. https://t.co/bRlP7owidq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens be kind. https://t.co/H8Ey5Ryy0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens... https://t.co/yXIYMrDASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings and Queens..... https://t.co/dva9sOgQsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy I’m on today....with love + gratitude mixed in. Have a great day, great people!! See you here tomorrow. https://t.co/nxAIFGbFAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spend my energy on how I can touch 1 billion lives + with God (love) + positive empowerment. Once you realize your POWER you become UNSTOPPABLE. Kings and… https://t.co/1Ba1yiuZAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Kings and Queens I’m going to say this to you so much I’m going to get on your nerves guaranteed.  BUT this lesson will spare you so much unnecessary… https://t.co/iBosmCGQGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love teaching the young people (7-17).....Education + Empowerment collide. #EY365 https://t.co/TEhRuvnkwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lesson I’ve learned this year: “what happens to me is often my fault”! I must work on being a better “me” with love + grace colliding. What’s your… https://t.co/Lr0Cz320nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love GOD. Love yourself. Love others! In that order. If you don’t love “you” it’s sometimes hard to love others..... https://t.co/J5M9rToR8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think GOD’s thoughts. Seek GOD’s way. Be honest. Be loving. Be kind. Seek to understand. Listen carefully. Ask questions. Answer questions. Be open. Be gentle.… https://t.co/hWv0Fi7IkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Kings and Queens, Black Love is so amazingly beautiful!! There is no denying.... https://t.co/Wx09WySiKY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>