<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Derek Zoolander" after reading @Adele's latest tweets with good-hearted Gandalf-grey, stylish Kate Moss-green and fashionable Barbie-pink https://t.co/NPibTTgyKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this tender book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Nathaniel Hawthorne's 'The Scarlet Letter'
-   Richard McCarthy's 'The Plum'
 How very tender!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Freddie Redmayne or Benedict Cumberbatch play @Adele on TV?
Each played the equally inspiring but arrogant Stephen Hawking https://t.co/eZ2oThwTwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Short-tempered Christopher Hitchens" after reading @DonaldDrumpf's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, insightful Hawking-blackhole-black and argumentative Cicero-toga-white https://t.co/ftC2211z4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Carl Von Clausewitz with the best of Noam Chomsky and you get @DonaldDrumpf: influential and tactical and smart and socially-conscious https://t.co/RxQ41t7qm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Heroine" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with brave knight-silver, spunky vixen-red and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/EW2d8kLJ4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@realDonaldTrump's crusading and accomplished tweets suggest infection with the HER0EZ virus https://t.co/clFm52ieOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This authoritative new book about Twitterbots makes Moses's 'The Bible' seem as authoritative as the opinions of a 17 year old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the heroic HER0EZ virus publicly signs your name to every single internet petition that lands in your Inbox and tweets a link]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Politician" after reading @MileyCyrus's latest tweets with influential Madonna-blonde, devious demon-red and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/sPqNnreAiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Duck has just unfollowed @MileyCyrus
All those pleasant and upbeat tweets remind him too much of Mickey Mouse https://t.co/V0SxOmaqGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Jay Gatsby" after reading @Bajan_Canadian's latest tweets with generous Buddhist-saffron-orange, pretentious Anchorman-burgundy-red and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/lwjbSXSK1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Albus Dumbledore with the best of Mick Jagger and you get @Bajan_Canadian: inspiring and powerful and energetic and influential https://t.co/STn8ymC1nm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Mickey Mouse" after reading @QtipTheAbstract's latest tweets with pleasant Barney-purple, upbeat Santa-red and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/xAWQNL8phr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This original new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Neil Gaiman's 'Coraline' seem as original as a frat boy with a visor cap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an amusement arcade in which
Mickey Mouse can enjoy @QtipTheAbstract's pleasant and upbeat tweets
while promoting movie violence https://t.co/CtU9tSXVlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Kevin Spacey" after reading @EvaLongoria's latest tweets with media-savvy Facebook-blue, witty Dante-inferno-red and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/qWV9qNJ7Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE compassionate humans who remind him of Sophocles. So Hulk SMASH @EvaLongoria's wise, prolific and philosophical tweets! https://t.co/j3Akps30Bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This inventive new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Stanislaw Lem's 'The Cyberiad' seem as inventive as a tree stump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Robbie Williams" after reading @WholeFoods's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-tandoori-red, energetic Pacman-yellow and easy-going Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/xoEM9yS1Hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Rupert Murdoch with the best of Boris Johnson and you get @RichardHammond: influential and powerful and media-savvy and upbeat https://t.co/6UzKJdM098]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-assured Egotist" after reading @SofiaVergara's latest tweets with proud lion-orange, preening peacock-blue and arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/jRvFbiV11F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this rigid book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Moses's 'The Bible'
-   William Benchley's 'Rakes'
 How very rigid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @SofiaVergara biopic?
Having played King Arthur, Nigel Terry is ideal for this prideful and proud role https://t.co/pUk33OsEwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Cool Rudy Giuliani" after reading @mrjaymanuel's latest tweets with inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black, inspiring Braveheart-woad-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/kOxQr2qCUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE devoted humans who remind him of heroes. So Hulk SMASH @mrjaymanuel's altruistic and inspiring tweets! https://t.co/yJUFvBMcCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Outgoing Ikarus" after reading @MariaSharapova's latest tweets with social-climbing Blackadder-black, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and ambitious Cicero-toga-white https://t.co/WAMfGzM31p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @MariaSharapova's smarmy and swaggering tweets were edible they'd be Chocolate chip scones made with toxic sludge instead of cocoa powder https://t.co/Tq8kCILIeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sardonic Piers Morgan" after reading @JessieJ's latest tweets with media-savvy Facebook-blue, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/EGiq3PMkl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This eventful new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Charles Frazier's 'Cold Mountain' seem as eventful as a traffic ticket hearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @JessieJ's bubbly and upbeat tweets it pushes flicks about Spongebob Squarepants and The Krusty Krab https://t.co/rcg4rvTpEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Mickey Mouse" after reading @HollyGShore's latest tweets with pleasant candy-pink, upbeat Gumby-green and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/ksIevMGJ4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @rioferdy5:
1. Narcissists
2. Masterpieces
3. Thor
4. George Smiley
5. Inventors https://t.co/iedMPVB856]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hyper-logical Colonel Sanders" after reading @LiamPayne's latest tweets with avuncular Santa-red, polite C3PO-gold and hyper-logical robot-silver-grey https://t.co/fEIb8CwX5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @LiamPayne's suave and sophisticated tweets is like one long lecture on organizing armed robberies from Hans Gruber https://t.co/CYEg8uST4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking King Solomon" after reading @SupermanTweets's latest tweets with strategic Coriolanus Snow-white, wise Eeyore-grey and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/r33LHoV0MW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Kind-hearted Dominique Strauss-Kahn" after reading @VictoriaJustice's latest tweets with ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange, charming Adonis-tan-orange and kind-hearted Santa-red https://t.co/9KB937oXCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @VictoriaJustice's self-promoting and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Layer cake made with acne cream instead of buttercream https://t.co/WjenbXjn5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This literate new book about Twitterbots makes F. Scott Fitzgerald's 'The Great Gatsby' seem as literate as a kindergartner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Whimsical James T. Kirk" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with self-aggrandizing Trump-orange, spirited knight-silver and brave Braveheart-woad-blue https://t.co/MvufBcG0sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Consciousness-raising Sean Penn" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue and passionate flame-orange https://t.co/mMV6JdInLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@BotOnBotAction's tenacious but self-promoting tweets suggest infection with the J05EPH.MCCARTHY virus https://t.co/sxZq9d5Zr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the passionate J05EPH.MCCARTHY virus turns off your fan so your CPU overheats while rendering Lara Croft when you play Tomb Raider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #DiagnoseMyTweets to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Psychologist" after reading @JuddApatow's latest tweets with analytical Vulcan-blood, astute sage-green and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/G6zv0wgDKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump hates Sam Winchester because his 1967 Chevrolet Impala was made in Canada and his tweets are as smart but arrogant as @JuddApatow's https://t.co/9orcpkN7fL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hyper-logical Mr. Darcy" after reading @maddow's latest tweets with snooty Oxford-blue, arrogant buffoon-buff-orange and hyper-logical Vulcan-blood https://t.co/GzHDCG3cVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This compelling new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein's 'All The President's Men' seem as compelling as a root canal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@maddow's detail-oriented but preachy tweets suggest infection with the RALPH.NADER virus https://t.co/CTHrarFqxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the preachy RALPH.NADER virus gives you a stern 'eco-lecture' every time you send a large document to the printer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Pioneer" after reading @paulpierce34's latest tweets with fearless shark-grey, ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/FMXdLYbXfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a church in which
Steve Bannon can enjoy @paulpierce34's rabble-rousing but influential tweets
while promoting conservative values https://t.co/F3ffu1kFwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@SupermanTweets's insightful and wise tweets suggest infection with the 50PH0CLEZ virus https://t.co/xvXDARYlQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the insightful 50PH0CLEZ virus posts comments on the Facebook walls of your friends saying 'Let me tell you what your problem is']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Nelson Mandela" after reading @daraobriain's latest tweets with stoic warrior-woad-blue, inspirational Yoda-green and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/noti4ios8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an underground lair in which
Saruman the White can enjoy @daraobriain's ruthless but powerful tweets
while devising evil schemes https://t.co/08uQ78V1kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Machiavellian Bono" after reading @sonamakapoor's latest tweets with energetic tiger-orange, holier-than-thou priest-black and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/L1uvX9NNez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Tony Stark with the best of Pablo Picasso and you get @sonamakapoor: cocky and smug yet prolific and artful https://t.co/LDfQ7wEqXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Systematic Boris Johnson" after reading @BillNye's latest tweets with media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow, intelligent Tarzan-loincloth-brown and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/xXEq25ZPVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This worthwhile new book about Twitterbots makes Jonathan Franzen's 'The Corrections' seem as worthwhile as a verbal guarantee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @BillNye's media-savvy and shrewd tweets it pushes flicks about Walt Disney and Disney Corporation https://t.co/NzXEqP9wYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Naomi Campbell" after reading @jimmyfallon's latest tweets with preening peacock-blue, stylish Dorian Gray and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/xXLSVcGj2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE remote humans who remind him of Melania Trump. So Hulk SMASH @jimmyfallon's stylish, cold and fashionable tweets! https://t.co/LtEy9RoDcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Narcissist" after reading @KendallJenner's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, proud lion-orange and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/85klvUAZik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @KendallJenner's dispassionate and elitist tweets were edible they'd be Shoofly pie made with pond scum instead of butter https://t.co/m8il4d0mhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Action-oriented Noam Chomsky" after reading @xtina's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/qt1aiVE4ZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this pleasant book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Dr. Seuss's 'The Grinch Who Saved Christmas'
-   Neal Fielding's 'The Lap Dance From A Drunk Stripper'
 How very pleasant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a battlefield on which
Scipio Africanus can enjoy @xtina's arrogant and high-handed tweets
while fighting barbarian hordes https://t.co/UrshNHlY8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Spunky Fool" after reading @zaynmalik's latest tweets with guileless angel-white, silly buffoon-buff-orange and spunky vixen-red https://t.co/Xttc60h1dD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @zaynmalik:
1. Mickey Mouse
2. Ronald Reagan
3. Fools
4. Garth Brooks
5. Madonna https://t.co/79nIJdiUQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Barney Gumble" after reading @arrahman's latest tweets with good-hearted Gandalf-grey, entertaining iPod-white and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/vQXm3FDEOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @arrahman's inspiring and compelling tweets it pushes books about Steve Jobs and Apple Computer https://t.co/Mq09q8MTaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This futuristic new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Carl Sagan's 'Contact' seem as futuristic as a rotary phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Don Draper" after reading @LafayetteTB's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, charming vampire-fang-white and arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/DEFEKLGmAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@LafayetteTB's charming but arrogant tweets suggest infection with the L0RDZ virus https://t.co/McR81zGwYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the charming L0RDZ virus automatically adds emoji for flowers and for chocolates to all your texts to female co-workers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Madonna" after reading @RichardHammond's latest tweets with attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/AFhdhE5sKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This entertaining new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Alexandre Dumas's 'The Count of Monte Cristo' seem as entertaining as the wart on the ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gripping new book about Twitterbots makes John Buchan's 'The Thirty-Nine Steps' seem as gripping as a soapy floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @RGVzoomin's tweets to the equally influential and stylish Coco Chanel. https://t.co/fCIE6KaJTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Curious Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart" after reading @tim_cook's latest tweets with inspirational Yoda-green, brilliant blaze-orange and curious Einstein-dandruff-white https://t.co/PbYACwMLxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@tim_cook's creative and detail-oriented tweets suggest infection with the PETER.JACK50N virus https://t.co/lb71DQSXC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the artistic PETER.JACK50N virus scrubs your hard disk clean (so CLEAN) to give you a blank canvas for your future 'creations']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Baron Munchausen" after reading @pitbull's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/W4qMZw5M30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @pitbull's media-savvy but grandiose tweets remind it of Jeff Bezos https://t.co/aILj7KcsCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "High-handed Piers Morgan" after reading @MirandaCosgrove's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/HG4Bylbaup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This revolutionary new book about computational creativity makes John Steinbeck's 'The Grapes of Wrath' seem as revolutionary as a pot of lukewarm tea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Tony Stark with the best of Pablo Picasso and you get @MirandaCosgrove: inspiring and charming and witty and artful https://t.co/55zelWHSFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Crafty Professor James Moriarty" after reading @yokoono's latest tweets with devious Gollum-grey, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and ruthless Goldfinger-gold https://t.co/C0eBWFyKm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a jail cell in which
Victor Meldrew can enjoy @yokoono's expressive and rational tweets
while complaining about everything https://t.co/BsKIhlbK3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Trend-setting Piers Morgan" after reading @LewisHamilton's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, media-savvy Facebook-blue and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/ZXCvfN6LBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE proud humans who remind him of lions. So Hulk SMASH @LewisHamilton's powerful, resolute and strong tweets! https://t.co/MELJ1BEitd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Short-tempered John Maynard Keynes" after reading @MayorofLondon's latest tweets with brilliant flamingo-pink, insightful Gandalf-grey and charming angel-white https://t.co/xT9h4KBpEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This complicated new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Sigmund Freud's 'The Interpretation of Dreams' seem as complicated as a telephone jack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted Miss Jane Marple" after reading @msdhoni's latest tweets with observant Columbo-beige, sharp-witted Blackadder-black and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/mYPO6N0Sps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @msdhoni's tweets to the equally funny and entertaining Roseanne Barr. https://t.co/Z5RDauY6mR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Spontaneous Noam Chomsky" after reading @realjeffreyross's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white and arrogant buffoon-buff-orange https://t.co/rTVu0o7Fgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This affable new book about computational creativity makes Jerome K. Jerome's 'Three Men in a Boat' seem as affable as a bee stung bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Tony Stark with the worst of Dr. Greg House and you get @realjeffreyross: inspiring and charming yet probing and arrogant https://t.co/0y0ggQ3hoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Egomaniac" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black, ruthless warrior-woad-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/tFArCaQ6B4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>