<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[java: java developer-****** Ref No.: 18-27514 Location: o fallon, Missouri 1. strong java, webservices, micro services who can understand business quickly and provide solutions 2.Excellent communication skill. https://t.co/qitApe0O2j https://t.co/yjdwSEOO9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/C++ Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Westborough, MA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/26/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/DztTgIJmMP https://t.co/oxHkeme5pP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. We are looking for a Java Developer to join the Verizon mybusiness team. The work you’ll be doing will support a B2B portal that our customers use to service their wireless accounts, generate reports,… https://t.co/uyZGIsCjRA https://t.co/S264C4hO0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java production support role: Java production support role Ref No.: 18-29739 Location: Sunnyvale, California Java Production Support Executive Job Purpose: Maintains Java based applications in Production. Involved in Debugging, Maintenance and code fixes… https://t.co/4pOEXV3vtW https://t.co/FylUi3kgmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Sr Java Web Developer: – Sr Java Web Developer Job Locations US-MA-Cambridge Category IT/Technology Management Overview Fuel your intellectual curiosity and professional growth. Forrester is an idea company, where smart, motivated, curious… https://t.co/F5sVU0I9SG https://t.co/y352Kh1WWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer Profit Sharing): Java Software Engineer (~25% Profit Sharing) ============================================ Req #: ******Location: Aurora, CO USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must be Obtainable… https://t.co/SI0GGlk2cc https://t.co/losJGFgMGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr./Principal Java Software Engineer Data/ETL: Summary: CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our new data services product offerings. We are in need of a senior level Java/ETL developer to work on data processing interfaces. Positions involve… https://t.co/yn4ubgecCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Developer: HomeAdvisor is looking for a senior-level JavaScript Developer to join our Software Development team. In general, we are looking for someone who has experience working on public-facing web properties, and being part of a… https://t.co/ijd1WCq25f https://t.co/bWjE0EDtjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium beats England for 3rd at World Cup https://t.co/dHTYYO0gwN https://t.co/omAIB3zSak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Java: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5359 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=*******… https://t.co/VWvhQiDI1W https://t.co/cFhHtSOvcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer in Jersey City, New Jersey, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core… https://t.co/J4NljUH1uh https://t.co/uBJWZ00qr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (JAVA, Python) – Expert w/Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-42748 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides development… https://t.co/MnvSMdQehh https://t.co/wwKAiRkpd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with AWS: Java Developer with AWS Ref No.: 18-26800 Location: Los Angeles, California Hi, Hope you are doing great!! I would like to check your availability and interest for this position. Job Overview: POSITION: Java Developer with AWS… https://t.co/tuMWGUoMuM https://t.co/FGGJM3zGjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacBook Pro 2018 hands-on: Quieter keyboard, 'Hey Siri' and True Tone: Apple unveiled some refreshed MacBook Pros this week, and I promised we'd be getting a unit to review ASAP. Sure enough, look what arrived in the mail today: a shiny, new 13-inch Mac.… https://t.co/lZZWo4Pn7d https://t.co/uX3myVdSPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-10711 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/15/2018 Role:Java Developer Location: Malvern, PA Job Type: Contract Job Description Technologies: Micro services, Git, Bitbucket,… https://t.co/lnfovWXaRV https://t.co/0YUTyWPz5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java EE full-stack Developer (Loyalty Digital Marketing): Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food… https://t.co/M1OHGlbKY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer 3 – Software Engineer 3:   Job Description – Java Software Developer 3 – Software Engineer 3 (18000999) Java Software Developer 3 – Software Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18000999 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/gTEjPrGSg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with WordPress Experience: Insurance Careers and Jobs | Plymouth Rock Assurance Login QuickPay Contact Us – – – Insurance – Auto – Home – Commercial Auto – Renters – Condo – Umbrella – Teachers Plan of NJ – AARP Member Program of MA –… https://t.co/4klE8bGxEF https://t.co/hVZ6F79bIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services: ******/JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services Ref No.: 18-29616 Location: Richmond – Virginia, Virginia ARCHITECT-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: JAX-RS – Java… https://t.co/wLR9DbhX5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Microservices Developer: Java Microservices Developer in Irving, Texas, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers… https://t.co/jmPBQ7xrt3 https://t.co/1FHl8bicHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan says a family of woodchucks ate his car: Don't underestimate the damage a few hungry rodents can inflict, even on something as inedible as an SUV. https://t.co/mP4FRirbrI https://t.co/eYxtVcaqvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer – Agile JAVA/Angular/Python Developer and Integrator: This position is in the BNY Mellon Information Lifecycle Management group, responsible for building and buying solutions to support Cyber Security Data Masking, Records Management,… https://t.co/O2WKMRRkPQ https://t.co/zfWH6oUhXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US indicts 12 Russian intel officers for hacking Democrats in 2016: Special counsel Robert Mueller and his team have received an indictment for 12 Russian intelligence for hacking Democrats leading up to the 2016 presidential election. The spies are… https://t.co/Ef9QnKYbTu https://t.co/NBa5g66iKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Java Developer – ( TS/SCI clearance with a Polygraph Required.): Requisition ID 2018-38340 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description… https://t.co/iOrotFQFRL https://t.co/tBfJwtYDec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Principal Architect, Application Development (Java): Designs technical infrastructure for applications and assists in defining application tools. Develops the applications architecture and blueprints which reflect business logic of the section or… https://t.co/qnqBU44dAN https://t.co/kMKsPwb7zG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer: Java developer (with UI) in Richmond, Virginia, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/yZsn92jaVL https://t.co/TT6EILPUTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner 'self-made'?: You know it's something when a dictionary feels the need to weigh in. https://t.co/LzU3f3lvjZ https://t.co/k4ZNC5leJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5368 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* ****************************************************************************** &amp;… https://t.co/C0mrSxKV1f https://t.co/CmdF3ZjxiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer: Java Fullstack Developer Ref No.: 18-26394 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Java Fullstack Developer Location – Philadelphia , Pennsylvania / Arden , Delaware Duration – 12 months Required Skills – Full Stack Developer –… https://t.co/tNOLhHyKTp https://t.co/Jb3uDbTHM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Position: Full Stack Java Developer Job Description: Arrow Electronics, Inc. a Fortune 150 company with global headquarters in Denver – helps the worlds best technology companies think Five Years Out, working together to… https://t.co/BmcXNQF3mE https://t.co/tiPDa70F5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-26426 Location: Sunrise, Florida Job Role: Java Developer Location: Sunrise, FL Contract Role Job Description: Core Skills: Core Java, J2EE, SQL, Spring, Springboot, JAVA API/webserivces Additional skills: Big… https://t.co/KLQ6IHUBvE https://t.co/QuyzZXMVT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA lead: JAVA lead Ref No.: 18-26572 Location: Mount laurel, New Jersey Job title: Java Lead Location: Mount laurel, NJ Duration: 12 months 10+ experience – Strong knowledge of Core Java, HTML, CSS, Object Oriented Programming Concepts, Design Patterns… https://t.co/SQnz3OXUSv https://t.co/rMNNZRDOFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr./Principal Java Software Engineer Data/ETL: Summary: CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our new data services product offerings. We are in need of a senior level Java/ETL developer to work on data processing interfaces. Positions involve… https://t.co/YJGEba5r7S https://t.co/X77aMFqRae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER: FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-27566 Location: CINCINNATI, Ohio Minimum 5 years in Java Executed a minimum 2 projects using Spring Boot ecosystem Executed a minimum 2 projects with a Frontend JavaScript Framework… https://t.co/47f4pV7cK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/z6ryViMsrx https://t.co/16ih5umoFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 5-year-old died from cancer, but not before preparing his own obituary: "My name is: Garrett Michael Boofias https://t.co/iP6axkKqQy https://t.co/xJVGdaYgeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers collected personal info from closed Facebook groups: It looks like Facebook has another privacy issue on its hands, this time over its closed groups. CNBC reports that Andrea Downing, a moderator of a closed Facebook group, discovered that a… https://t.co/mEjiNbOh0s https://t.co/aaTqnczj4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Applications Developer – Lead: For Siemens Java Applications Developer – Lead job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – –… https://t.co/efJ0eGBSV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Vice President: Suchergebnisse – Deutsche Bank Karriere – Unternehmen – Nachrichten – Karriere – Investoren – Verantwortung – Research – #PositiverBeitrag Deutsche Bank Search Search Query – ENEnglish – Suche – Kontakt – ?FAQ – News –… https://t.co/6So9owI008]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft’s collaborative Whiteboard app is now available: Microsoft's Whiteboard app, which lets users collaborate on an intelligent canvas through their Windows 10 devices, is now out of preview and available for download. As with a physical… https://t.co/58cmxsiFhp https://t.co/nAlS1mRjxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer- JAVA: Backend Software Engineer- JAVA/J2EE Ref No.: 18-26083 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey Backend Software Engineer- JAVA/J2EE, Spring framework including Spring Boot and STS, SOA and microservices, GIT, REST APIs https://t.co/vaw5BWljP2 https://t.co/3FaJDQxR3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Careers Center | Java Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/SLVd2G0OzY https://t.co/5MaJArebzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Fox analyst: Trump is a malevolent fool: Ret. Lt. Colonel Ralph Peters tells CNN's Anderson Cooper that watching NATO diplomats deal with President Trump at the NATO summit was like watching "psychiatrists deal with a disturbed child." https://t.co/HXy8BGIBTY https://t.co/TS8OP5oLaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Software Engineer Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML: Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML Tracking Code ******* Job Description Do you have great ideas about how to create user interfaces (UIs) that are intuitive… https://t.co/FTYZeDgOi9 https://t.co/fFXH4Y3Y2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… We are looking for a Lead Java Developer to join the Wireless Ecommerce Team. Join our Information Technology team where you will work on old and new technologies and find ways to meet our… https://t.co/3q3ibxHS9q https://t.co/2kCIXY84RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Architect, Application Development – Orchestra Networks / Java: The Reference Data Hub (RDH) is a multi-domain MDM solution based on the Orchestra Networks EBX5 solution.’ We are looking for a data/technical architect who is very familiar with… https://t.co/PAHgKJNA7P https://t.co/7Di7VrDZa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: ***ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply*** General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT), a leading provider of systems engineering, integration, IT service operations and support solutions, is… https://t.co/oYUmo1pBwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Software Engineer Full Stack: Sr. Java Software Engineer – Full Stack – FirstPRO 360 Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Life Sciences – Medical Device Sales – Project Services – Supply… https://t.co/H3i8NTBJB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Team Lead – will relocate!: job detailsJob Number:1219201Job Title:JavaScript Team Lead – will relocate!Job Type:Full-timeLocation:Jersey City, NJHours:Post Date:Apr 19 2018Salary:$180K-$190KDetailed Job Description: Great financial firm is… https://t.co/BCVMKke16G https://t.co/6YqBveSOSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java DevOps Manager: Java DevOps Project Manager Salary: $150-160k, +$30k bonus This is more of a program/project manager to oversee Dev interface to track desk stakeholders vendors, this is an individual contractor, no direct reports, they want someone… https://t.co/agyQx3GEVp https://t.co/qCILX3p3o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer: Java developer Ref No.: 18-29092 Location: Irving, Texas Job Description: Position: Job Title: Java Developer Job Location: Irving, TX Duration: Fulltime Permanent Hire Compensation: Competitive Salary + Benefits. Job Description:… https://t.co/riF9NRZyQz https://t.co/G4Ergx6iya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Financing Services Weehawken MIS Java Database Warehouse Deve: Are you passionate about delivering robust and scalable IT solutions to an enthusiastic and driven business? Do you enjoy working in a global group of likeminded IT individuals? We re… https://t.co/d4Bvl552Vp https://t.co/z1qERVceiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Java: Senior Software Engineer – Java at EXPERIAN Skip Navigation – Consumer – Small Business – Business – More…X Experian Site Sections – About Experian – Consumer Support – Credit Advice – Global Sites – Company Profile –… https://t.co/gbU4fgg4hq https://t.co/6DOKR2nmZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's head of human resources quits after discrimination probe https://t.co/mha2JN1ZwC https://t.co/X5E11qz92b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java, GUI Rich Clients: Core Java, GUI &amp; Rich Clients Ref No.: 18-25856 Location: Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey Role: Core Java, GUI &amp; Rich Clients Position: Contract// C2C // W2 Duration: 12 months Location: Englewood Cliffs, NJ Technical Skills:… https://t.co/dfzRfkIeJx https://t.co/o6RUwjRRay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java IVR Developer: What you’ll be doing. If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and find ways… https://t.co/PlD0hKCBnH https://t.co/5v38fslPKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java/GoLang): Software Engineer (Java/GoLang) : 18-01877 Ref No.: 18-01877 Location: San Jose, California Akraya is looking for a Software Engineer (Java/GoLang) for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please… https://t.co/20KabeWJXt https://t.co/Y7JzGl3xk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investors around the world aren't happy about the trade war https://t.co/zZ6exEzicv https://t.co/ZXIbBTTx0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ JEE Developer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Java Developer to join our team in Kingstowne, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Responsibilities: – Design and implement… https://t.co/U7pkULAc0n https://t.co/tsHze0bb3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Razer's Blade is almost the perfect gaming laptop: Razer's revamped Blade stands out in a sea of great gaming laptops. It's not the lightest, and it doesn't have the most powerful graphics hardware, but it's one of the most polished notebooks we've seen… https://t.co/xiPdNUUOKw https://t.co/ObT8jEWFio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer SSO: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be responsible for providing software design and development, and second line production support for our external customers’ single sign-on suite of applications supporting Verizon’s… https://t.co/FB8mIGcTBl https://t.co/v96m0kGgvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Risk and Compliance: Java Developer with Risk and Compliance Ref No.: 18-26328 Location: Winston Salem, North Carolina POSITION: Java Developer with Risk and Compliance LOCATION: Winston Salem NC JOB TYPE: Contract / Permanent JOB… https://t.co/iajc8PjlnG https://t.co/4ogKDHQED2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API: Java API Ref No.: 18-24345 Location: Monterey Park, California Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 10 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Java API Programmer… https://t.co/S5uUmoaFjE https://t.co/YoeIAqgkqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Scheduled Maintenance The SAP SuccessFactors HCM Suite is currently undergoing scheduled maintenance. We apologise for any inconvenience this may cause. Please visit the Support Portal or contact Customer Support if you need further… https://t.co/wqJp7CyoLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine learning, Hadoop, Java/Scala/Python: Machine learning, Hadoop, Java/Scala/Python Ref No.: 18-27450 Location: Pennington, New Jersey Must Have: 1. Machine learning techniques 2. Hadoop 3. Java/Scala/Python 4. Statistical programming languages like… https://t.co/8KlLLQFG7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, C#, C++, Java: Req ID : 434279BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Looking for a career with purpose? One that challenges your mind, grows your skills and contributes to our Nation’s most critical missions?… https://t.co/WQXm0rxa79 https://t.co/4ApiTo37ON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump critics aim to make 'American Idiot' UK's top song: Oh, the things President Trump will be greeted with this week when he visits London: demonstrators, a giant "Trump Baby" balloon -- and a uniquely British musical protest. https://t.co/aXGBKLdhLd https://t.co/nXzt5GOsYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ETL Developer w/Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-39050 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Researches, designs, develops and/or modifies… https://t.co/6Kf1Y9lSX6 https://t.co/lHfbD5VDTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (JAVA/DevOps tools and methodologies) – Expert: Requisition ID 2018-40633 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Looking for… https://t.co/2bjbHo40ZT https://t.co/NSX8k2t8YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer/Software Craftsman: SENIOR JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER/SOFTWARE CRAFTSMAN DETAILS LOCATION: North Dallas, TX INDUSTRY: Custom Application Development OFFICIAL TITLE: Senior Software Engineer WHY JOIN OUR TEAM * Great company… https://t.co/rG4jfodAT0 https://t.co/6RP46mF9t7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple’s iOS App Store changed the way we think about software: Ten years ago today, Apple officially launched the iOS App Store and -- for better or worse -- it helped rewrite the rules of society. The iPhone, which debuted about a year prior, came with… https://t.co/8C5aNVyCel https://t.co/Pzs2OLNyOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-09805 Location: Raritan, New Jersey Position Type:Contract Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 04/25/2018 Hands on experience in designing and developing applications using Java EE platforms Object Oriented… https://t.co/nZ2UW0LxLg https://t.co/TpUeXOyZpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers Overview… https://t.co/Z5LE1MtGxk https://t.co/53KvQFPOSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5-year-old North West featured in first fashion campaign: North West has just set a new bar for 5-year-olds. https://t.co/2QuMNl72Jf https://t.co/rOsWSkwNnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java: Java Ref No.: 18-26323 Location: Irving, Texas Java Job Description: Key Skills Required: 1. Strong Coding Experience. 2. Good Knowledge of Core Java/ Advance Java 3. CRM knowledge is an added advantage. 4. Good communication skills. https://t.co/4smyMjNedK https://t.co/FhrUbadHBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reese Witherspoon is one step closer to Oprah-dom with new DirecTV deal: Hello Sunshine is saying hello to a new deal that will give the Reese Witherspoon-led media company a new platform for its female-driven content. https://t.co/iK2nSgAYwx https://t.co/0765lHuBHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java with Spring boot Maven: Java, J2EE with Spring boot Maven in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home –… https://t.co/1WlJwguVJD https://t.co/FxztVHRSON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer with Hadoop Experience: Job TitleJAVA Developer with Hadoop Experience – ID:23206 Duration24 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsJava, Big Data, Hadoop LocationPrinceton, NJ Date Posted01/22/2018 JAVA Developer with Hadoop Experience Location:… https://t.co/PjYvLY0RRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump touts confidence in Kim Jong Un: CNN's Brian Todd reports on the diplomatic disconnect, following US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo's meeting with North Koreans in Pyongyang. https://t.co/XCzi55pb9P https://t.co/FVouAQTPw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Company Description American Well, a national leader in the rapidly growing field of telehealth, seeks a highly motivated and professional Full Stack Java Developer. We partner with the top health systems, health plans,… https://t.co/V9zYXrcEIW https://t.co/51NHBRFd8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan is spending years making one train line a minute faster: The efficiency of Japan's bullet trains are a modern marvel, and now JR East, the East Japan Railway Company, wants to increase it even further. The company began a two-year construction… https://t.co/28JZs8OIvw https://t.co/1RdlO57kP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Financing Services Weehawken MIS Java Database Warehouse Deve: Are you passionate about delivering robust and scalable IT solutions to an enthusiastic and driven business? Do you enjoy working in a global group of likeminded IT individuals? We re… https://t.co/bbQ4GOmBhC https://t.co/ty9CJ5XZNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Java/Middleware: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions in the financial… https://t.co/wwFNkiWXzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robin Wright breaks silence on Kevin Spacey: According to Robin Wright, she and Kevin Spacey were more co-workers than friends. https://t.co/Ke4PWhunGM https://t.co/QgxppXOYvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Enterprise Solutions Delivery: Java Developer – Enterprise Solutions Delivery As part of Eagle’s Enterprise Solutions Delivery team this role will design, develop and test features and functionality which provides the critical shared… https://t.co/LCCgaTDF7P https://t.co/eAkMEe4Km7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Java Developer: For BNY Mellon Specialist Java Developer job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers – Investor Relations –… https://t.co/ZAgAgxIofH https://t.co/GFjl19RkLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ JEE Developer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Java Developer to join our team in Kingstowne, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Responsibilities: – Design and implement… https://t.co/pyGZPBjY3Q https://t.co/BVt7EFyiYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer (App Dynamics Consulant): Java developer (App Dynamics Consulant) Ref No.: 18-26163 Location: San Jose, California Role: App Dynamics Consultant Location: San Jose,CA Duration: 9-12 months Digital : Mongo DB, Assurance : ERP/CRM Testing –… https://t.co/lWh3MR9Lzq https://t.co/fgnXxtfrxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How model Hailey Baldwin made a name for herself: Hailey Baldwin grew up surrounded by stardom, but she can rightly make her own claims to fame. https://t.co/txvMbNAkcz https://t.co/AJJhryWUwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Lead for Performance Optimization: Java Lead for Performance Optimization – What We Do Featured Tips for Building AI into Mobile Apps In the News – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work – Financial Services –… https://t.co/XwJlKKEgVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Java / C++: 113963BR Job Description: U.S. Citizenship status is required as this position will need a U.S. Security Clearance within 1 year of start date. Raytheon BBN Technologies is seeking a Software Engineer to join our… https://t.co/pHG5g79FFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Java Developer: Jr. Java Developer Ref No.:18-11065 Location: Milford, Ohio Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 06/21/2018 Jr. Java Developer/Entry Level Software Engineer Must have a Bachelors Degree Diverse Lynx LLC is an Equal Employment… https://t.co/SBGEfn77Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Halawa, HI Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/26/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/hp4JYXWgbO https://t.co/Sbjw544Fhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Java Developer: Engineer JAVA DEVELOPER / American Express Canada is a company with a long history and a bright future. A Canadian employer since 1853, Amex has created a culture that nurtures extraordinary talent and turns careers into… https://t.co/KDHpbYaQsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: ******/Java Architect Ref No.: 18-29554 Location: Mountain View – CA, California Microservices-L3 (Mandatory) . Overall IT experience should be more than 8+ years . Experience in Java Architecture for more than 5 years . Strong in Java .… https://t.co/4D1wK2ZWY2 https://t.co/Pw7afPpcRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-03101 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position Type:FullTime This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional… https://t.co/JYnXmMe6ZI https://t.co/mDolFZovKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-26065 Location: Mountain View, Virginia Experience in Java Experience in Java Spring MVC Good Communication skills Must have domain Knowledge Must worked on Agile Model. Experience in RDMS Experience in… https://t.co/BnxcQBpflm https://t.co/f8GGt3fBav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon identifies soldier killed in apparent insider attack in Afghanistan: The Pentagon has identified the soldier killed in an apparent insider attack Saturday in Afghanistan as Army Cpl. Joseph Maciel of South Gate, California. https://t.co/ia5WJ5hVm6 https://t.co/1ds9U40QXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Java Software Engineer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – Job cart – Location: United States – Global (English) English Available in 145 locations… https://t.co/wEP8o7qOF2 https://t.co/NsDdmdVmrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Join our Information Technology team where you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our customers’ needs and make it easy for them to do business with us. You will work fairly… https://t.co/ef0hs0LZ1U https://t.co/MOcJQLbnU8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>