<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Develop a disciplined financial mindset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stay positive that's why I always win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love. Live. Give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn all that you can, while you can, when you can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be kind. Execute. Be diligent. Treat people right. You win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are grateful you are incapable of complaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let fear stop you - fear is torment. 
Feel afraid, feel fearful - but continue to take the steps to live your legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbcwashington Louie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/kjZBybF7Hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/WRldwEZ9CD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/DnqNPIIjYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/LcUmtyRawh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/GZYOKpASOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is power when we align with GODS word".....
#thedailybibleverse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask and you receive, knock and the door will be opened, seek and you shall find - Matthew 7:7 
Another favorite.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything is possible for the one that believes - Mark 9:23
One of my favorite scriptures....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Music is healing" thank you Dr. Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it more important to be significant or successful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Let the doubters doubt and do it anyway. https://t.co/Fx6i0SrLrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat people well - always and everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grateful girl is a beautiful girl.
A grateful boy is a handsome boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live to give more than you live to receive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add value to yourself and you can always add value to others......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see, touch, feel, hear and think sensibly so I"m grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you simply grateful today? 
Its guaranteed to change your mood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/mI7wUIX8vL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once age appropriate teach your children all your life lessons - show them by example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Passion trumps all. https://t.co/gQMLAqvmNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: God sometimes takes us into troubled waters not to drown us, but to cleanse us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thequote: Never make someone a priority when all you are to them is an option. - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotivatedLiving: Instead of putting people down all of your life, inspire someone, change someone's life for the better, make someone s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to live (spend) the rest of my life giving it away to the children of this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Each of us has a fire in our hearts for something. It's our goal in life to find it &amp; keep it lit. -Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no room for complaints when I am grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for: God, my family, my friends, self-love, freedom and a legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to the blessings: OBEDIENCE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one fear we should have - 
We should FEAR GOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The word will change your life...your thought life, heart life, physical life, emotional life, spiritual life.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do these things you will be blessed....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if - in every action we merely looked to love each other and bless each other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She sees it unfolding and she cannot believe it - but she is so excited for all the possibilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm here to educate, empower and inspire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I"m grateful - I'm happy.
Happy girls are pretty girls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many doors are opening for me - today, tomorrow and the next day! 
Many doors are opening for you - today, tomorrow and the next day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend time with those you love + never stop dreaming (acting upon) your dreams......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to self: let go of whatever is no longer working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natalie, be nice to people even when they are not always nice to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: You don't need a reason to help people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: If you're single, stop worrying. God is saving you for someone special. Someone worth the wait. Someone who will never…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't buy your children a video game, buy them a stock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SCOREMentors: Thank you to our 10,000 #volunteers for inspiring SCORE's clients and equipping them with tools for #smallbiz success! #N…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FitspirationaI: ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/8KboVdfgmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My passion for education will land me on radio - as an owner or ???...how cool would that be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: The pain of discipline is far less than the pain of regret. -Sarah Bombell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Every day may not be good but there is something good in every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for life and I appreciate love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear is torment - do you believe this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you want to be remembered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Epic_Women: Remember this. https://t.co/MaaTJOrw25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak greatness over yourself, your children and all those you love and care about....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visualize your visions often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am working on book # 3 - its for woman and young girls - it will be my favorite work so far.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are responsible for your own happiness!
BUT - be around people that add to your happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Have faith, something great is waiting for you on the other side of FEAR. https://t.co/MQmZYUYBV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create things you are proud of.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give attention to what you love....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let it go - so you can move on with your life.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the positive in every negative situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up grateful, go to bed appreciative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your priorities first and you won't compromise outside of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness grows as you pursue your passions.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have the ability to be a powerful force in the world.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm learning to let things bother me - less and less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe we all can live a magical life....#lifefilledwithGOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be patient and work...then leave the results to GOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you know better...you do better - thank you Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am happy and grateful for another day to live this thing called: LIFE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Humility is not thinking less of yourself, but thinking of yourself less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: There is nothing better :) https://t.co/t2C0k7kact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: Don't compare yourself to others. Compare yourself to the person from yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Be thankful for where you are. https://t.co/7gjwuNGYeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Women_Of_Christ: Let go of yourself and ask God to fill you up. https://t.co/qV58JX5aOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is good - I see what the ends going to be (at least far enough to keep moving).....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/vHoCHdgM8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/0rp0xlCWq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for 1,000 things...too many to count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love people. Bless people. Serve people.
Just don't let PEOPLE control you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I imagine it...I do the work...I get the results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your children turn 1, buy them a stock instead of toys......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less I have in bills, the more I have to invest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm researching building a home instead of purchasing a home - supposedly its cheaper........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisHogan360: Having a house is great, but let's be honest: when you have that home paid in full and no longer have to send payments t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I listen to my Father, I win.
When I don't listen to my Father, I lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always seek to understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be patient and Be diligent you will get the desired results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doubt kills fear - never forget this. Just get to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have cell phones made us lose our sense of humanity, do we talk to each other any more?? Do we really talk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: Keep moving. https://t.co/aUkuM1DwUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natalie, let self-love and self-respect always reign in YOU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOD,
Thank you for love, forgiveness, wisdom, revelation and understanding.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>