<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great night @PoetryGlasgow with @ekreeder Oli Hazzard and Shara McCallum https://t.co/mEcSOfGmvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thoroughtful should be a word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My polling station this morning was so quiet. I was the only person (apart from the volunteers).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share McCallum and Oli Hazard tomorrow evening @PoetryGlasgow https://t.co/Lw3Q1atFon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MAP_magazine: @giles_bailey @warholmooc @dvyng_ @DIRTsplendour @gilda_williams @M0REM00REM0RE @jameselkins @LUXScotland @colinjherd @ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TJXMc3SloU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Very excited the talented JL Williams @jlwpoetry (who happens to be one of our alumni) is launching her new collection tom…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Signed books by some of our recent visiting writers ready for the #CreativeConversations archive @uofglibrary @UofGlasgowA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jameswesleym: A Strangely Funny Russian Genius https://t.co/IGFdLjQl3U via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZOMAG_: In ISSUE 01 we're featuring poetry by Maria Harper. We're absolutely in love with this one. #poetry #poetryscotland #creativewr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucille Clifton https://t.co/jf2W5V5Xkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful morning @EssayCatalyst - subtle, challenging survey/provocation on form @ekreeder and amazing song-essay-story-talk from @IAMKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to @ekreeder's Essay Catalyst day @ByLeavesWeLive ! Some amazing things to read in a Dropbox folder! Essay = Dropbox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surrey Poetry Festival is happening @GLiveGuildford on 6th May!  https://t.co/blZWktAsw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michel Leiris to Georges Bataille - "I am somewhat embarrassed; anyone would be, I think, in my place, and you know me well enough to be..." https://t.co/5UjE2J3WjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gesture of Writing - Vilem Flusser https://t.co/LSvifp4rHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait! https://t.co/nKUvof6g3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of the time I have my phone and my phone case in separate pockets jfyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO AMAZING that @TyehimbaJess has won the Pulitzer Prize for @wavepoetry OLIO - The book is extraordinary!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bland as a bat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met the oracle of Gatwick Airport and it said... https://t.co/e1kEwMYvVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great new book by the wonderful Joy Williams!! https://t.co/A6dkhFw8sR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruth Stone https://t.co/vofBTJd0JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PotterClaire you have returned the favour as I didn't know about this new one!  @TwoLinesPress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening? https://t.co/S6CQdJXpOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9iINqCfS6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently got the chance to see amazing work by Lonnie Holley. Song his and footage features some of his artwork: https://t.co/dGLUtLDaba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariaxrose @InfoPrice it was so wonderful! I loved hearing the poems and the essay was particularly tender disarming bristling witty great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mariaxrose: hearing @InfoPrice read poems&amp; talk on the experimental essay was such a joy,i have lots to learn from his delicate restrai…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manierre Dawson, Ascension, 1913 https://t.co/vs2DcXuUbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForwardPrizes: It's finally time to reveal the 2017 Forward Prizes for Poetry shortlists. #ForwardPrizes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bar in Glasgow opened last year and it has all these pictures on the wall - on multiple walls - all of white men. It's 2017. https://t.co/mKjdVb43RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eleanore Mikus 'Cardboard Relief Fold' 1961 https://t.co/kKLNkUv39P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obsessed with "well there we are..." @EmilyThornberry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Else Bostelmann 1934 https://t.co/PE2sFx15Z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine Equi on Frank O'Hara https://t.co/bc7lISfys4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really excited about this fantastic event this weekend @CCA_Glasgow run by @ekreeder and the @EssayCatalyst project: https://t.co/UbVlbuWVIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EssayCatalyst: Others readers include @SamuelTongue @jemma_tweets @Archieislander @ekreeder @colinjherd https://t.co/dXPTWzJw6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tVUiju6h9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sanders exorcises the White House: https://t.co/e41X1llCHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QI9Kk2rmBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stanton_Moore amazing wonderful tonight at Snug Harbor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstracts due 31st May for this Peter Manson Symposium run by @tttombbb @altkrelb @impcommands https://t.co/rqQmIrUJts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob Halpern, @undigest and @fullnommunism reading in Edinburgh tomorrow evening 7pm @ScotStoryCentre: https://t.co/39eRIOsbxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this Elaine Equi poem: https://t.co/hAPn8TCvjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roughly what percent of stuff said about poetry on Facebook / Twitter is worth saying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From another AWSingerman poem https://t.co/YnCfqLygdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking, re-reading and remembering AW Singerman through the poise, grace and wit of his language thought feeling experiments aka poems https://t.co/pztYRYAlfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a digger pulling down trees outside my window! #towardsvegetalbeing Luce Irigaray https://t.co/jVvkMRqDv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody knows what a book is anymore https://t.co/r4lxBrOd4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLondonMag: We're looking forward to seeing your very best poems for our Poetry Prize 2017. Startle us, intrigue us, excite us: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolecadwalla is doing fantastic investigative reporting. This election makes my skin crawl. https://t.co/MUK3eolpQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @poettrios: Translation as Collaboration | Call for submissions https://t.co/4QZLj8MvDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGlasgow: Have you seen former UofG student Alexander Singerman? If you have any info please contact @AyrshirePolice via 101. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[away and boil your he id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LitroMagazine: #Tuesdaytales is Chilly by @Colinjherd https://t.co/5uq9ualW36 via @LitroMagazine https://t.co/g1fJH9BIWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatOnEdinburgh: Head into The @SuttonGallery for their festival exhibition Thomas Cameron: Dream Sequence on from 27th July.
https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @glasgow2saturn: You're in luck! The deadline for submissions has been extended to July 30th. Keep writing &amp; sending us your stories, es…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRONT HORSE is an exciting new poetry art magazine: https://t.co/TzcaYXsrtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TaylorWDriggers: For me the hardest part of writing is that initial act of getting the words down and letting them be bad at first. #am…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EssayCatalyst: We are want to see your amazing experimental work. Get cracking. Sept deadline. https://t.co/DzZAGPeWYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SuttonGallery: Our @ThomasCameron exhibition opens a week today for a preview 6-8pm! See you there! https://t.co/TG71mAGqAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edbookfest: Want to take part in an interactive poem at #edbookfest?
Tweet your memories of festivals past &amp; add #LivePoetryLab
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AestheticaMag: Hanna Tuulikki’s sound installation Away with the Birds is grounded in the ecological @balticmill until 24 September htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw three brilliant students today, all working on amazing projects.  I have a headache but it's from the thinking their work makes you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Preparations for next term's #CreativeConversations going well Some excellent authors confirmed including Leila Aboulela &amp;…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Christopher Priest, author of ThePrestige, is our #CreativeConversations guest, 1pm Monday November 13th! A date for the d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the poems about coming out of a meeting and realising you have had yoghurt on your face the whole time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hixeros: Out today: FRIT, the first poetry collection from Eley Williams (@GiantRatSumatra): https://t.co/fOM3Vb24JV £6 incl. P&amp;P https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Listen again to Prof @louisewelsh00 essay on artists Colquhoun &amp; MacBryde via https://t.co/Mzja1Ynyyo @BBCRadio3 #GayBrita…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Hettie Jones poem:  https://t.co/zd16dzc8g0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to this event on 21st August with @edbookfest! Come and make my life as difficult as you can! https://t.co/9ijcXa2EsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or eat it? Up to you! https://t.co/VeT0LEKuDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the films of Jenny Gilbertson https://t.co/Pi7qMxyB4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PN_Review: The PN Review Prize opens today! Get your submissions ready, you have until the 1st September https://t.co/a1dOkV1ntH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatrionaWL thanks so much it was so much fun to do it and I was in awe of the brilliance of Jane and Calum - the book is so brill too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AimeeArmande wish I could have been at yours as well! There were so many fascinating panels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#woolf2017 Queer Bloomsbury panel! https://t.co/qAjCouCh0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Saturday @ScotStoryCentre 7pm @ruth___ie @chrissywilliams Wayne Miller and @AntonioAutumn https://t.co/OkrnnY36UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made up a New Form. The LILO: 4 long lines and a little cushion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UofGWriting: Great to see #uofgwriting PhD student @impcommands in the most recent @UofGArts Newsletter https://t.co/pQZVBYweEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZarfPoetry: new at the journal of brit&amp;irish innovpo! lisa jeschke on the latest prynneology &amp; me on veronica forrest-thomson 🦇🌼💜https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders Ken Van'Egercs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders what's an anagram of "Engrave Necks"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PerdutaGente I would be delighted to help for free! I'm not terribly strong though but I have a car and am enthusiastic!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders @intercapillary like stuffed olives!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders @intercapillary it's a snack ffs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJessCooke yes it is lovely and the theatre space is gorgeous - you can open the curtains behind stage to windows on to a beautiful garden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders like poetry, revenge is a dish best served as a snack! In a wrap! With mayo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a week to go until this.....https://t.co/OkrnnY36UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coeurdelilas I am going to have to credit you for your input on SNACK REVENGE btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders @atarbuck @IainFruitmarket Like Your Poetry Crispy and Full of Flavour? SNACK REVENGE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders @atarbuck I'm quacking in my boots (my boots are duck themed)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegsaunders @atarbuck I have my strap line: SNACK REVENGE: free snacks, complimentary poetry, revenge gratis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atarbuck @mikegsaunders yessss! That's the right answer! Although in this there technically isn't a right answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay classy @mikegsaunders!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNACK REVENGE vs ADJACENT PINEAPPLE which is better for a name for something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jlwpoetry in #LivePoetryLab frenzy: "start tart cart mart restart heart heart heart"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edbookfest: Today's #LivePoetryLab poet in residence @jlwpoetry is turning your #edfests memories into #poetry.

Follow along: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to have something in this volume on New Narrative from On Contemporary Practice which can be pre-ordered: https://t.co/zosh364nd9 https://t.co/wWkSZMXg1M]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>