<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["He was the kind of boy any young girl should date while she's still able to recover." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Inspiration needs disease, injury, madness." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All human beings search for either reasons to be good, or excuses to be bad." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With a plan, you only get the best you can imagine. I'd always hoped for something better than that." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Help me give up my addiction to hope." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tyler and me at the edge of the roof, the gun in my mouth, I'm wondering how clean this gun is." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's so typical, men want all the perks of being female, but none of the bullshit." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything is funnier in retrospect, funnier and prettier and cooler. You can laugh at anything from far enough away." S.T.F.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first step to eternal life is you have to die." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't bought Chuck's new 32 page short story "Phoenix" yet, make sure to check it out...  http://t.co/JvRdIWKbuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They're Vicodins dear. It's the Marilyn Monroe school of medicine, where enough of any drug will cure any disease." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you keep waiting for someone perfect, then you'll never find love, because it's how much you love them that makes them perfect." Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To hell with housework, our top priority has always been between our legs." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is like a ticking bomb." - Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you never been rabid, you ain't never lived." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be a big social experiment in getting what you don't want. Find value in what we've been taught is worthless." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not running away, I'm moving on." - Irvine Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Chuck Palahniuk's infamous short story 'Guts' ...  http://t.co/ngZWjSYhBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody's trying to make every minute of the present last forever. Preserve every second." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What makes earth feel like Hell is our expectation that it should feel like Heaven." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Game shows are designed to make us feel better about the random, useless facts that are all we have left of our education." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marla Singer. The big tourist... #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/BO0aGUL7nY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Of my 3 favorite authors, I'd like to have dinner w/ @chuckpalahniuk , have a drink w/ @WelshIrvine , and punch @Br ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did perpetual happiness in the Garden of Eden maybe get so boring that eating the apple was justified?" - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all want to leave our signature. Our lasting effect. Your life after death. Nobody wants to be forgotten." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I disconnect the telephone to keep the outside world in it's correct place." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is short, death is forever." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is your life and it's ending one minute at a time." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I can't be beautiful, I want to be invisible." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You realize that our mistrust of the future makes it hard to give up the past." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness. We have no scar to show for happiness." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters Quote. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/kSeXZ4MiOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What people forget is a journey to nowhere starts with a single step, too." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're a different human being to everybody you meet." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first time I jacked off, I thought I'd invented it. I looked down at my sloppy handful of junk and thought this is going to make me rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know how they say you only hurt the ones you love? Well, it works both ways." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The damaged loves the damaged." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any real truth, any precious fact will always be lost in a mountain of shattered make-believe." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Right now, getting killed would be a breath of spring." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doesn't reincarnation strike you as just another form of procrastination?" - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fertility Hollis #Survivor #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/iwAj3A1oED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're all of us haunted and haunting." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I need is a new story about who I am. What I need to do is fuck up so bad I can't save myself." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "You're that tree falling in the forrest that nobody gives a rat's ass about." - Chuck Palahniuk http://t.co/gpJMot7Gxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are not special. You are not a beautiful or unique snowflake. You're the same decaying organic matter as everything else." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you bury a goth child. Yes, it's still heartbreaking, only it doesn't look as bad." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DhammaPunk: #FollowFriday @ChuckPalahniuk &amp; @PalahniukQuote because it's wonderfully dreary &amp; bleak &amp; realistic stuff mi ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is calm. Calm and resigned and defeated." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Such a life, as your puppet, is not worth living." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need to rebel against myself. I need to do what I most fear." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we call chaos is just patterns we haven't recognized yet." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing happened, and nothing kept happening." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you think about it, Johnny Appleseed was a fucking ecological terrorist." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The difference between how you look and how you see yourself is enough to kill most people." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We live and die and anything else is just delusion." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I suppose it's comfort, perhaps a sense of self-control, doing worse things to yourself than the world will ever dare inflict." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those worst parts of your life, those moments you can't talk about, they rot you from the inside out." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just like dumping a dog, the worst thing a man can do is turn himself loose." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Slouching, lurching and salivating towards Bethlehem" Chuck Palahniuk's take on ZomBcon ...  https://t.co/m9v2fBTMPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sticking feathers up your butt does not make you a chicken! - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Terrified of abandonment, I began to wonder if sex was really just an excuse to look deeply into another human being's eyes." Doug Coupland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The craving inside of me is to be clutched at by some dead girl. To put my ear to her chest and hear nothing." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one really gives a damn about books. No one has bothered to ban a book in decades." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reality means you live until you die... the real truth is nobody wants reality." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone looks a little crazy if you're looking close enough. And if you can't look that close, then you don't really love them." -Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wish just once, I could say, 'This. This is good enough'. Just because I choose it." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damned alternate book cover. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/4vXBVHNug8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world will always punish the few people with special talents the rest of us don't recognize as real." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Night-timers &amp; Party Crashers #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/usEYJ60RcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RAsherPick: To watch the film adaptation of ROMANCE you should click here: http://t.co/d2a1VvAwpm less than 2 bucks and under 30 mins A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you prefer the better audio version of 'Romance', the story starts at the 19 min mark. Watch and retweet... https://t.co/gkcNUlFnNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't read/ watched Chuck's short story 'Romance', then do yourself a favor and do it now... https://t.co/wPFAZEMqo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find what you're afraid of most and go live there." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What if reality is nothing but some disease?" - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's worse that people can steal from you than money." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rip yourself open. Sew yourself shut." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The moment you make yourself available to any man, he starts to take you for granted." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As far as regret, I think that's the sign of a well lived life. If I grew old without having regrets, I'd regret my caution."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: The link is live - http://t.co/o37lx1Ty8H #AMA cc: @reddit ‘Ask Me Anything!’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: You know that feeling, when you go to a concert and you’re waiting for the band to come on stage?  I’m feeling like  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anything you can acquire is only another thing you'll lose." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/Vfkn0mcyP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're only supporting characters in the lives of each other." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["History is filled with brilliant people who wanted to fix things and just made them worse." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We spend our lives letting the world tell us who we are. Sane or insane. Saints or sex addicts. Heroes or victims." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hope is something really tough and tenacious you have to give up. It's an addiction to break." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The things you own end up owning you." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life's greatest comfort is being able to look over your shoulder and see people worse off, waiting in line behind you." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your heart is my pinata." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't want their lives fixed. Nobody wants their problems solved. Because what would they have left? Just the big scary unknown."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am an invisible monster, and I am incapable of loving anybody. You don't know which is worse." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I could wake up in a different place, at a different time, could I wake up as a different person?" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are these things really better than the things I already have? Or am I just trained to be dissatisfied with what I have now?" - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All the effort in the world won't matter if you're not inspired." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The idea that I can't share my problems with other people makes me not give a shit about their problems." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/738730gf4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More and more, the hardest part of crying is when I can't stop." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Luck is where preparation meets opportunity." - Amy Hempel]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>