<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel simultaneously diagnoses and transforms the true condition of our hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God lovingly leads us into circumstances that expose the sinfulness of our hearts. He reveals to heal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gospel seed may take years before blooming into conversion. Don’t get discouraged!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add this to the list of things I never thought I would do: Snapchat! johngmcgowan Now I just need to figure out how it works!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A disengaged leader is just as deadly as a micromanager!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy! Love my little Aidy! https://t.co/dW90S7vqm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hope of Easter isn't isolated to Sunday.  It shines joy, peace and mission into all of our days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup, #DC you're still pretty spectacular! https://t.co/MMbKQxeaJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City Easter 2016 Recap https://t.co/7RmHkGd1UM https://t.co/YJiyDHDHhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that our Community Group is celebrating Easter together! #happyeaster https://t.co/FK0HoaH53C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, it’s actually colder on #Easter than it was on #Christmas.  Hmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Celebrating new life, baptisms and an empty tomb. Loved every minute of today with… https://t.co/ub5dNeJ77J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May the empty tomb always mean more than a full auditorium! #HappyEaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He has risen; He is not here." (Mk.16:6) And nothing would ever be the same again! #HappyEaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in #DC and don't have a church home, come celebrate with us tomorrow! 10am. Synetic… https://t.co/sBmFHBbVEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else feeling huge anticipation for tomorrow at Restoration City? Can’t get here fast enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like the whole city is preparing to celebrate the defeat of death! https://t.co/yzsUKEpy4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His death gives meaning to my life! #GoodFriday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only God could use the savage evil of the cross as an eternal source of hope! #GoodFriday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eleven Arlington County churches coming together tonight to remember Jesus' sacrifice for us.… https://t.co/pdoSCW98vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isaiah 58 shapes our post-fasting game plan as a church: [New Blog -https://t.co/V2DhPmAXQE]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace has unleashed more generosity than guilt ever will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are few things as scary or sad as a person convinced they have nothing to learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our young adult retreat kicks off tonight!  Join me in praying it's a life changing weekend for all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our souls cling to whatever satisfies them the most.  Discipleship is the lifelong process of convincing your soul that Jesus satisfies more than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petescazzero @nlfnyc Love it! These courses have been a game changer for our church - so grateful for you and the way God is using you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your vision of community destroy your ability to enjoy the people already in your life.  New Blog: https://t.co/8qWMnCTmkK https://t.co/SxMaZCe91I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're fanatical about avoiding our own souls.  We numb, we distract, we change churches, we overwork, we gossip.  But avoiding what's there is a short term strategy that always fails and never transforms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don’t just grow our faith by saying a difficult yes, often times we grow it by saying a difficult no.

Read more: https://t.co/IyE7N0kJuj https://t.co/5G5rKKvnAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what greatness in the Kingdom of God looks like - serving so that others can hear about Jesus! @ Gunston Middle https://t.co/JyIZCSavYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're doing the "right" thing so that you can feel superior to others, it probably isn't the "right" thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God always breaks down before He builds up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byaaroncdavis So, it looks like this journalism thing might work out after all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a few of the people that made #RestoreDC so special today. Love seeing our church serve our… https://t.co/YiYBsrCmVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pastors, rejoice in what God did through your church yesterday.  Don't waste time comparing it to what He did in another church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of today is knowing that God used it to bring people from death to life!  Being a part of that is the most thrilling thing in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Restoration City.  Love how many of you served, invited, prayed and sacrificed to make today happen.  So great that we get to do this together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whom have I in heaven but you?  And there is nothing on earth that I desires besides you." (Ps. 73:25).  The more we can say this, the freer we are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Goal: Live at a pace that sets me up to be serving Jesus faithfully into my 90's but with an intensity that comes from knowing tomorrow isn't promised to any of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel compels us to draw near to people, situations and conversations we would naturally shy away from.  We draw near because God has drawn us near to Himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this little guy turned three a few days ago.  Aidan, you’re a natural encourager… https://t.co/38rwcg9gV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little lapses in integrity can do big damage to your reputation.  The small stuff really does matter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow on the grass (but none on the roads!!) is the perfect backdrop for heading to Restoration City for Part 2 of Christmas in the City! See you soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed this past Sunday's sermon?  That's why we have a podcast: https://t.co/oPVQVQYAJ5 https://t.co/VSLjisUCPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Grant, Lord, that I may know myself that I may know thee.” - Augustine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack: "Dad, I think you might even be smarter than a dolphin."

Me: "I'm growing less and less certain with each passing year!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating our 3rd anniversary as a church tomorrow.  Overwhelmed by the grace God has shown over the past 3 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[little stud &amp; little photobomber https://t.co/Ed0BGdGKpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People know what we value by what we make time for because investing our time is always costly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up for RestoreDC.  You should too: https://t.co/y78HsAZtPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Christianity is a statement which, if false, is of no importance, and if true, of infinite importance." -CS Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gotta figure out where to ship 'em! https://t.co/UgnuuSPgar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't love God until you believe He has your best interests at heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until we understand what Jesus has done for us, we'll never be able to do what He asks of us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without love, we're nothing. (1Cor.13:2)  Our hearts matter more than our achievements ever will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sin is a failure to remember the abundance of God's steadfast love. (See Ps.106:7)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bcloritts: Children have never been good at listening to their elders, but they have never failed to imitate them- James Baldwin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone needs grace.  Daily.  Stop being shocked by people's short comings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cold heart can’t carry the weight of a passionate life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tedashi leading strong in DC for the National Day of Prayer! @ Echostage https://t.co/owFyaO9CIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding our weakness is the precursor to celebrating God's grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caving to everyone's expectations is easy. It takes courage to set and maintain boundaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistent exhaustion prevents consistent excellence. #GetSomeRest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family trip to the zoo was a hit - thanks to this guy! https://t.co/m6Mt6rxcrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to being at Echo Stage this Thursday night for the National Day Of Prayer.  Join me! https://t.co/Vn6RXHr8oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain’s not lowering my expectations for this morning - going to be an incredible day with Restoration City Church!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love what our offices say about us at Restoration City Church! https://t.co/05Hi3Y3pEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying, dreaming and planning with our team all day today.  Pray the Lord gives us wisdom and joy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weekly meeting with your spouse might just be as important as a regular date night: https://t.co/Fp7BMnfcqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's been a bit of a baby boom at Restoration City and RCCKids needs your help! https://t.co/SjdMtkWu1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can do so much damage to the church of God as the man who is within its walls but not within its life. - Spurgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This little one will be joining our family this fall. Can't wait to meet her! https://t.co/3dUvAFPMnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS!!  Love it! https://t.co/XLyAirZxxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticism might produce compliance, but not transformation.  That takes grace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filling out preschool paperwork for Jack. This whole growing up thing is moving too quickly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be more afraid of not trying than of failing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Be strong, and let your heart take courage, all you who wait for the Lord.” (Ps.31:24)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest freedom is found within the boundaries God places on our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t dishonor your journey by trying to live someone else’s!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What A Weekend!! https://t.co/J0nqri9b4N https://t.co/UNw0uYVwZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isabelle2london just prayed for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna be a special morning at Restoration City - so much to celebrate after #SpringServeDC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond grateful to serve with such a fantastic group of people!  #SpringServeDC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going strong in Alexandria! #ServeDC https://t.co/L29EmEQJTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying 1 Peter 4:11 for everyone headed out to a #ServeDC site this morning. 

"Whoever speaks,… https://t.co/tbXUB8MkGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on God’s power, not the obstacle’s size!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a big decision when exhausted is the leadership equivalent of driving drunk. Give someone else the keys and get some rest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of the office! https://t.co/6SFrOxbJ5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitterness is a fast spreading cancer. (Heb.12:15) Avoid toxic people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be with our college community group tonight at GW! 8pm in the Marvin Center!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipleship.  We all talk about it. But can we define it? New Blog: https://t.co/A2GYipMXWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your schedule hasn’t changed, your priorities probably haven’t either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me, college ministry isn't just strategic.  It's personal. [New blog -https://t.co/veUY4LJSCp]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're following God when you find yourself on an unexpected road to an unexpected destination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God isn't hiding His will for your life.  He's unfolding it every single day. [New Blog: https://t.co/KH8ik16q37]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it takes more strength to receive help than to offer it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your greatest contributions to our world almost always come at the expense of your own comfort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! So grateful for @jamesmarshallg and his message this morning at Restoration City. Small church, deep bench!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: PARKING UPDATE: Due to Memorial Day wkd, the best parking today will be in the Synetic Theater lot. Look for signs &amp; connec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is for you. Even on the days you aren’t sure you are. He fights. We trust.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>