<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/T7YcVgTioI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/bBKCgaO3E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/L05SvOFbKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/qmdDqHGFBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/8BYTudRwa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/ohQbzX18ge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/k44zELp8Eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/OJSRfULjd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/tceUUxSPEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Help for the Autism Disorder  http://t.co/qxYQSEJsKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/IGE1YJ4wsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/tuHAg8jfnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/0RT1X3SHzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/bVFRECnj84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/bj97Duckw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/SIdxGCzFkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/ukBkrZ2TMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/v5d3R4N8cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/2pp7qUPg7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/JV24VSjdDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/y80QswxhFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/RoKODsLghu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/xwMG64xOM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/f1ZdivnGHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/8ByMclzIyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/JBsVUtOJZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/EVW6yAAmSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/SW86J5up8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of The Hollywood Sign  http://t.co/MNx30GFunb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/Nnm35U7dde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/WLKqi8dl6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/L5HtFAr9eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/G2liX7cMKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/OnSCMIa8wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/outENwEA2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/EuTWrBxtOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/fnf9AJEpRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/yFZDS70DwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/nORLWnpy9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/9MebNocnjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/LtltzILYUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/LwRAgCef4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/2NT41HiX5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/2fAI9EOMtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/R5NGH70zHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/mvy84zPQef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/sNOvahQahm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/yXeTOjAjeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/2fAI9EOMtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/fAPfZbckz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/Ru9bgXs9rq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/uTJD7BLs6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/IwcZzcB9XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>