<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/7wEUUySL3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/avZBTognoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/gf5ZlAoMhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/2i3IhX39VV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/rW1hT0LXWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/y7UD9QhT82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/OdGu0R5IJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/vwZJjdVM70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/VuuNJxOP2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/L4ZVjZY3ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/4dhbm7kojP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/NcugqMksZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/wZl7SMcCnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/N88WSwwMEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/szNcZvFq3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/gWuKZnFlbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/y7UD9QhT82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/9m8DRq7yzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/RMIVmgp1xC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these spooky skull candles!  http://t.co/MaMYQFbaEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/BksSqui0wA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/0dpkAz0usk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/f19qioUGhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/zXDKuQ0Xa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/dYvvNEf7fT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/oNfc9bnnxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/dWbdHTl0u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/Y5fN2ZQ0ip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl 1:  I spent my vacation fishing  Girl 2: Then why did you buy a new bathing suit?   Girl 1:  That was my bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/LAl9Gxmkhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/lemi2uWDup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/tT9NM6Z6VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol and gas do mix but they taste terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/Ioj3xcvYLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/ZDv9abwJKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/C8EOTHqHkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/RMIVmgp1xC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/bwRFczDb76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/uaqWxqNRUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/aff9hu8rtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/6zxMhU7CVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/49yjXyHcRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/Zibv7XK79l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/wiDciOIkNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/URxoJhXuAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/VlSCJXLJJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/lxCZrgA7eK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/SywvidnBDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/KeMIy3ozvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/VWqe2POhw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/E2RfUPE6n7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>