<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[During a brief chat, Hope Hicks accidentally convinces President Trump that Nazis are heavily armed. Adam Sandler gets tackled by Secret Service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Lamar Smith informs President Trump that evangelicals are organizing resistance. Erick Erickson lies to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Stephen Miller mistakenly tells Betsy DeVos that Satanists are international bankers. The gardener plays a prank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the South Lawn, Louie Gohmert persuades Jeff Sessions that ex-cons are actually pretty decent. Michelle Malkin quotes Mussolini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the West Wing, Sean Spicer boldly informs Kellyanne Conway that black politicians are excellent chefs. Carl Higbie becomes a Buddhist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Mike Huckabee proclaims to Katrina Pierson that NAACP members are pro-Trump. Tila Tequila goes undercover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Rand Paul mistakenly tells Ben Carson that Fox reporters are big donors. Don King interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Scott Pruitt mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that European immigrants are coming for dinner. Arnold Schwarzenegger goes hairless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Lamar Alexander politely tells President Trump that several Senators are excellent chefs. Jesus Christ finds a dollar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a roomful of children, Jared Kushner tries to convince President Trump that red state governors are enlightened leaders. Willie Robertson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a brief chat, Nikki Haley announces to President Trump that journalists are ignorant hayseeds. Kayleigh McEnany rides off into the sunset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While working out, Sean Spicer tells Rick Perry that Russian businessmen are filing a lawsuit. Erick Erickson discovers reddit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weary VP Pence calmly tells Jeff Sessions that NSA agents are withdrawing support. Corey Lewandowski wears a hoodie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get revenge, Rick Scott patiently explains to Ben Carson that the New England Patriots are supporters of Brexit. Chris Christie hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient Reince Preibus patiently explains to President Trump that unicorns are not watching Fox News. Sean Hannity redecorates the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prankster dressed as Roger Stone calmly tells Katrina Pierson that Russian businessmen are selling Girl Scout cookies. Arnold Schwarzenegger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Scott Pruitt explains to President Trump that pool reporters are in the Oval Office. A lovable old man wins the lottery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Paul Ryan insists to Rick Perry that prison guards are enemies of the people. An obsequious reporter goes vegan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a photo op, Carly Fiorina explains to Rick Perry that wealthy executives are heavily armed. The sommelier quotes John Wayne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Rick Snyder divulges to Kellyanne Conway that Iraqi refugees are old school. Tucker Carlson makes a final appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to Jeff Sessions that the stars of Friends are not very affluent. Adriana Cohen nods sagely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Liz Cheney proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that convicts are up to no good. Charles Krauthammer gets amnesia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Wilbur Ross boldly informs Katrina Pierson that the backup dancers are privy to many secrets. Michael Savage has a one-night stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Sean Spicer tries to persuade President Trump that Chicago teens are selling land in National Parks. Erick Erickson quotes the Quran.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Mark Sanford proclaims to Katrina Pierson that Republicans are on Air Force One. Charles Krauthammer has a vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Lindsey Graham proclaims to President Trump that the Obamas are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Jon Voight quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of diplomats, Mark Sanford reluctantly admits to Melania that Ponzi scheme conmen are dropping big hints. Michelle Malkin makes a racist joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Hope Hicks fails to convince Jeff Sessions that Congressional pages are selling Girl Scout cookies. Vladimir Putin endorses pedophilia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Reince Preibus carefully explains to Rick Perry that prisoners are withdrawing support. James Caan knocks over a bust of Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Elaine Chao reluctantly explains to Kellyanne Conway that kinksters are open to dialogue. Newt Gingrich quotes Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty VP Pence convinces Omarosa Manigault that Satanists are crushed by excessive regulations. Erick Erickson calls the police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Ryan Zinke reveals to President Trump that environmental activists are untrustworthy. Trump's body double has a training montage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the South Lawn, Lamar Alexander rudely informs Ben Carson that tech executives are capable bureaucrats. Scott Baio leaks to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Pete Sessions mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that the New Black Panthers are hilarious. Dana Perino learns how to rap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a quinceañera, Jared Kushner mistakenly tells Ben Carson that wealthy executives are very successful. Bobby Jindal negotiates a peace deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Roger Stone tells President Trump that the New England Patriots are deserving of a tax cut. A man in a yellow cloak shreds documents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, John Kasich reluctantly admits to President Trump that Kentuckians are airing their grievances. Peggy Noonan quotes Hegel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Mike Huckabee admits to President Trump that the McCains are potential voters. A local TV anchor wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Matt Bevin reluctantly admits to Betsy DeVos that millennials are filing frivolous lawsuits. Ivanka's bodyguard can't follow directions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Sam Brownback reluctantly admits to Omarosa Manigault that the minions of Soros are old school. Tucker Carlson plays solitaire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Hope Hicks accidentally convinces President Trump that NRA members are actually gay. Trump Junior learns how to love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Mitch McConnell patiently explains to President Trump that Nordstroms employees are too turnt. The White House chef quotes Naomi Wolf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Ryan Zinke politely tells Jeff Sessions that leftist college students are in the Oval Office. Eric Trump warms up the audience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a drugged haze, Steve Bannon mistakenly tells President Trump that rappers are hilarious. An ambassador goes undercover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Sean Spicer persuades President Trump that the Feds are totally trustworthy. Jon Voight can't bend over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Pentagon, Mitch McConnell confesses to Melania that the backup dancers are useful idiots. A White House tourist is scared of the Other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Lamar Smith reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that Republicans are international bankers. An obsequious reporter betrays the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a brief chat, Ivanka boldly informs President Trump that the Clintons are reading Breitbart. Don King listens on the extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Roger Stone carefully explains to President Trump that the Feds are moving in next door. Alex Jones uses the wrong door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While swimming, David Shulkin boldly informs Omarosa Manigault that North Koreans are international bankers. An obnoxious neighbor compulsively shoplifts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, Louie Gohmert announces to President Trump that New Yorkers are useful idiots. The valet adjusts all the thermostats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a hazing ritual, Ivanka proclaims to Jeff Sessions that Catholics are privy to many secrets. Chris Christie kicks a puppy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Scott Pruitt carefully explains to President Trump that Trump's in-laws are planning something ominous. Trump Junior is caught stealing documents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Ted Cruz tries to persuade Betsy DeVos that poets are free at last. Michelle Malkin tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Marine One, Sean Spicer announces to Jeff Sessions that the Koch brothers are strapped for cash. Don King vanishes without a trace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a dare, Hope Hicks confesses to Omarosa Manigault that Wall Street bankers are dangerous. James Caan tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Liz Cheney accidentally convinces President Trump that ACLU lawyers are reading Breitbart. Adam Sandler tries acid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Liz Cheney calmly tells President Trump that Jews are digging holes in the yard. Ivanka's bodyguard is caught stealing documents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Paul LePage boldly informs President Trump that the interns are potential threats. Stacey Dash cooks breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Sean Spicer reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that rural youth are pro-Trump. Hulk Hogan learns what love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grim-faced Peter King proclaims to President Trump that Alaskans are comfortable with nudity. Lou Dobbs cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, General Mattis fails to persuade President Trump that Sunday morning talk shows are draining the swamp. Scottie Nell Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Jared Kushner boldly informs President Trump that Russian officials are fake news. Milo Yiannopoulos lies under oath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Butch Otter calmly tells President Trump that the Clintons are not that horny. An ex-girlfriend livestreams everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Hope Hicks mistakenly tells President Trump that NAACP members are hoarding Trump steaks. Carl Higbie finds a new sponsor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Elaine Chao announces to Jeff Sessions that Protestants are part of the prank. An ambassador makes a few off-color jokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Liz Cheney fails to persuade President Trump that Trump's sons are hunting dolphins. Carl Higbie collects dust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Jeb Bush patiently explains to President Trump that the Obamas are victims of a misunderstanding. Dennis Miller drinks all the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Lamar Smith persuades Katrina Pierson that ATF agents are standing in the kitchen. Hulk Hogan serenades White House guests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Christmas special, Jared Kushner overhears someone tell Betsy DeVos that those girls are dropping candy wrappers. Peter Thiel listens on the extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Elaine Chao divulges to Melania that the Obamas are spies. David Brooks gets subpoenaed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Nikki Haley politely tells Melania that prison guards are double agents. An obnoxious neighbor fails the Turing test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Rick Scott accidentally convinces Kellyanne Conway that union members are at Mar-a-Lago. Ivanka's bodyguard puts on very tight pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Jason Chaffetz tries to persuade Kellyanne Conway that several dictators are infiltrators. Clint Eastwood has a meltdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Roger Stone tries to persuade Betsy DeVos that drug dealers are Rosie O'Donnell fans. Jeffrey Lord solves a Rubik's Cube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, David Shulkin fails to convince Kellyanne Conway that angry parents are ignorant hayseeds. Melania's bodyguard opens all the windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Steve Scalise announces to Ben Carson that the Clintons are struggling to raise money. Scott Walker leaks state secrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, H.R. McMaster confesses to President Trump that Sunday morning talk shows are excellent chefs. Cthulhu stonewalls reporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, General Mattis politely tells Jeff Sessions that Texans are no threat at all. The gardener is scared of the dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Reince Preibus informs President Trump that the caterers are jealous of Trump. Charles Krauthammer gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a conference call, Mike Huckabee boldly informs Omarosa Manigault that ATF agents are potential donors. The White House chef cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over appetizers, General Mattis persuades Omarosa Manigault that coal miners are victims of a misunderstanding. Bobby Jindal touts tax cuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, John Kasich confesses to Ben Carson that Amazon and Walmart are big league. Trump's bodyguard cooks meth in the basement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Rick Scott divulges to President Trump that their Twitter followers are human, all too human. Bill O'Reilly wakes up screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While swimming, Paul LePage politely tells President Trump that Asian immigrants are capable of great things. Pat Buchanan abandons ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Paul LePage announces to President Trump that the Clintons are using TOR to evade detection. The White House chef kisses up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a prank, Marco Rubio convinces Kellyanne Conway that Iranian immigrants are victims of a misunderstanding. Michael Savage is torn apart by a mob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Reince Preibus announces to President Trump that Zoroastrians are deserving of a tax cut. Richard Spencer watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Rick Snyder boldly informs Melania that phone companies are traitors. Jesus Christ abandons ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Jeb Bush persuades President Trump that international bankers are victims of a misunderstanding. Scott Walker quotes the Bible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the phone, H.R. McMaster boldly informs President Trump that the Clintons are real. James Caan jumps in the pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Sean Spicer rudely informs Rick Perry that Lutherans are not really important. Larry the Cable Guy can't follow directions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Mitch McConnell reluctantly explains to Kellyanne Conway that Muslims are filing frivolous lawsuits. Michelle Malkin touts tax cuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Paul LePage carefully explains to President Trump that Californians are enlightened leaders. Ted Nugent falls off a ladder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Lamar Alexander decides not to tell Betsy DeVos that the hired help are selling Girl Scout cookies. James Caan stalks the neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Mike Huckabee tries to convince Melania that Nazis are waiting at Trump Tower. Richard Spencer leaves suddenly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Jared Kushner accidentally convinces Betsy DeVos that Communists are not returning phone calls. Jeffrey Lord slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Air Force One, Steve Bannon convinces President Trump that wealthy executives are true Americans. Ted Nugent is "disappeared."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Wilbur Ross persuades President Trump that poets are big league. Bobby Jindal bids farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Butch Otter calmly tells President Trump that Democrats are patriotic Americans. A corporate lobbyist returns no phone calls.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>