<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[One of those days where you trip up they steps of The MOD, coffee in hand, sprawled and three men with machine guns run over to you *shame*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @riazat_butt: PAID, year-long internship in BBC's Religion &amp; Ethics AND Factual Television depts. Pls RT .@sunny_hundal  https://t.co/yC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great best practice from @PRCA_UK https://t.co/Zoq9W7jpFz worth a read @mattharescott @salix_sarah lots of ideas for our health group!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @fsb_policy has a new @FSBwomen Twitter page! Let's get publicising their fab report https://t.co/IyyIn3xy4i #WomenInBusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fsb_policy thank you - I admire so much of your media engagement work, which is why the reluctance to shout about this has stung!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has FSB gone weak at the knees on female entrepreneurship? https://t.co/IyyIn3xy4i …#WomenInBusiness #women https://t.co/OsEOUcYwJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Five important business headlines that never were" by @JournalistaLtd on @LinkedIn https://t.co/EpVsWAcYfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow: that was pretty quick. It was pretty crap though. If I want to read that sort of stuff..plenty better available https://t.co/3IEjzm1LCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Entering into an era of complete transformation-data science is going to trump medical science" #health #innovation https://t.co/M19FxAKSDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are some hospitals you can go to in 2016 where it feels like 1946" Prof Sir Malcolm Grant on variation #NHS https://t.co/lwVHaF3RPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“..looks like you’ve had a stroke. No, my mistake – you’re just buffering.”  #JuniorDoctorsStrike @frankieboyle  https://t.co/mRXjPpBLA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Loving watching our chef create our dessert at Salut! https://t.co/ZDEicqSRQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More women cite 'personal reasons' than 'business failure' for exiting their business  -  by @FinStbBoard today https://t.co/L8uQ6idTKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TiernanDouieb: There's something about George in this picture that makes me wonder if he only showed up when it developed. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four foam blocks?! Could they not have chosen something a little more pertinent/interesting/signifying? #royal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlotteSantry: Low levels of public understanding about data use but "considerable" support for anon data use - Caldicott #EHWK16 htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZPBLtd: Learn from the risk-takers: lessons for a digital #NHS #EHWK16 #healthIT @DHCCIO https://t.co/vgPxTZlE9D @HIMSS_UK https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BritishAirwaysT having the term 'head of the household' to exclude me from my own account enrages me. Change your terms to reflect 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hssood advises new tech tariff launched by @NHSEngland today, no official release as yet. Anti-holiday deadline of 16th August! #healthtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesTout: How can we fill the post-Brexit information gap for SMEs? https://t.co/PTgOCfUDnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/wXreba3INm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/70dnWASjcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/faupFmZcz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having bit of a clear out...that's a LOT of crap #email #Google https://t.co/CLl18qBQ3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets have arrived! #wilderness2016 is first festival with the little chap #wilderrides can't wait https://t.co/tAJ1zJ4An0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msclews ah really?! Can't you recreate the couples one with Mr Clews and the kids? Ha ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @Nick_MES @MESsocial https://t.co/FzQlzLXM4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brass Eye or Sky News? You decide... https://t.co/uCPxjN6mHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PRCA_UK launches its gender equality survey today - get involved people! 
https://t.co/4QOvq5aLtR
 #PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markbritnell 's healthcare buzzword bingo - play it on your #healthcare document now https://t.co/9BNFgI5N0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In summary, @markbritnell summarises the best bits of the world's health system #nhs #healthcare #NHScomms https://t.co/zVY8ETs8Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eminent @markbritnell endorses #PR "At your best you're unbeatable" talking at our @PRCA_UK healthcare group. https://t.co/8YiCT9j6xG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bensimms65: Pleased to have quoted @stevedouble support for #UKaid in my blog. Vital we defend 0.7% commitment in coming days. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Id rather a leader that felt comfortable being her true self and cared enough to cry!  https://t.co/iQ9yEJVoBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more than one way to be a leader. Most sense I've heard on @BBCr4today for a long time. Thank you @angelaeagle you've got my vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theipaper they're all joining so they can have a say on who replaces him! Think he's missing the point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_MES: That's all folks! #c2020health has finished. Until next year ... ??? Rt if yay! Thanks everyone  @MESsocial https://t.co/cJEV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to engage? Process, process, process - great step by step diagram by @JessLonsdale1 @VirginCare #c2020health https://t.co/igU5avsUuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently away from desk feeding my son fruit from cocktails. Will check emails - can't guarantee reply. Back 3/07. https://t.co/VNmdXd0C0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_MES: #confed2016 "there are more members of trusts than all the major political parties put together". Disrespectful and daft to i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hate the haters. Be wowed by  resilience and fortitude. Proud to be a citizen of this great world. #JoCox  https://t.co/rrdWc1lqnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sutton_eileen: Bonfire of fax machines please in new integrated urgent care services  https://t.co/dRUFbbGwJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite outfit of #confed2016 so far @lynda_thomas - the NHS' very own Jenna Lyons https://t.co/VJ3ISOq129]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @twhicher: Key to unlocking productivity is improving the technology and re-imagining the way we work. Needs clinical &lt;&gt; tech comms #con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 to dos when using IT &amp; digital to transform patient care from @Bob_Wachter #confed2016 report due Sept '16 https://t.co/OrTc82U52U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mark_Geneix: Sneek Peek @Bob_Wachter's #digitalhealth panel at #ConFed2016. It's all about the importance of clinical led #IT #Projects…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emhough1: Hunt: the NHS is the biggest global purchaser of fax machines. Time for new technologies to enable improved care #testbeds #c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HSJEditor: It's the things they don't say that are often the most telling #confed2016  https://t.co/z1oCmxnAWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @digitalhealth2: We are at #confed2016 where Jeremy Hunt has just said he remains committed to #paperless by 2020 because tech underpins…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShaunLintern: Hunt says he wants to challenge NHS to be more flexible with rostering systems so staff have flexibility on hours #confed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality, quality, quality - that's what @Jeremy_Hunt wants the 10s decade to be remembered for #confed2016 https://t.co/x3IIIkdMqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram friendly freebies? A rare treat #confed2016 kudos to @allocateS for breathing healthcare into their brand https://t.co/B5BgErw3tS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sort out a narrative, get people engaged and show progress in hard facts and figures to deliver #devolution // all PR campaigns #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling reminder from Stephen Dalton that 20 years ago today a bomb went off here in Manchester: solidarity #orlando #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White, heterosexual men your place in the queue is not as secure as it used to be for CEO" Awesome msg to kick-off with. #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPIAndyCowper and @ShaunLintern get good humoured  dressing down at start of Stephen Dalton's speech to kick off #Confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big topic -centralisation- to coincide with day 1 of a big event #confed2016 from @DrFosterIntel on @GdnHealthcare https://t.co/eg5KhH4mZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jamesillman: Search for new NHS England tech chief extended   #Confed2016 £ https://t.co/exHIqzmrk6 https://t.co/WdrBuLtC6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 on site journalists at #confed2016 inc. @BBCNews awaiting @nhsconfed view on #Brexit today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-harmers gain celebrity on web app via @thetimes @oscarholland  https://t.co/fDQPVFHWKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@359benedict pls can you add me on Twitter I need to send you a private direct message re quality of food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day, another 4 carriage train that no on at Crofton Park can get on at 7.29 @TLRailUK disgraceful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work in #NHScomms ? Take MES' quick 5 minute test to find out how engaging you are: https://t.co/AnEweM8dmK https://t.co/q76ulspu0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How can LEPs keep a strong voice against a backdrop of regional devolution?" by @JournalistaLtd on @LinkedIn https://t.co/WeAkJNal1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotwire | Private: Targeting Decision Makers in 2016 - Hotwire https://t.co/7nbZcmT4mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criminotweet: Excellent #news @Hollyonline @jjwood01 Labour's Yvette Cooper "Reclaim the Internet Campaign https://t.co/FtPMc2KLDR http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS I'd like to run in a forest - I'd prefer do said run without pink or glitter on my foot please @Karrimor https://t.co/hRXYuOKjO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StylistMagazine: This is how long it takes to read the world's best-loved books https://t.co/6UoiPCgP4H https://t.co/dXVbj5r7sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wdjstraw: “Britain is more imaginative&amp;more creative &amp; our global creative success would be severely weakened by walking away" https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilgadhok @salix_sarah @PRCA_UK I'll email you the doc - are you guys part of PRCA? You need to join our group :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_ukactive: "In future, it will be the norm and the duty of employers to create active workplaces" @wardsteve now speaking on @BBCRadio4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was Belstaff I'd be asking for my media spend back for the juxtaposition of this ad with the story! The wording of the ad... https://t.co/DCeqEkZfOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May is 'totally nailing' the middle ground...more like lost, stranded and broken down at hard right. https://t.co/IAScrkuLrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is increasing feeling like we're in Black Mirror - the pig voters won, next up foreign worker detectors in our retinas https://t.co/N0GS5eYy3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @KateSwaffer making my mouth water! Delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @THETlinks: Thanks @Hollyonline @AmandaBenDor for joining us today! And thanks @felixjackson @medDigital for the brilliant presentation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JournalistaLtd: As today's #HETT2016 gets underway, how do we shift perceptions on data sharing in the #NHS? Our blog https://t.co/E9cd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @fredds_flowers for this week's beautiful bunch! My favourite so far #ecobusiness #sme #ukbusiness https://t.co/Kke5fzUYi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Points 1-2 the most complicated and even non-sensical (see end of Pt.2) way of making mash I've ever seen #prfail @AbelandCole @thetimes https://t.co/7YodLsJ62j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Boards must make decisions with patients, not for them" #NHScomms #patientengagement #accountability https://t.co/Ce8j6M9EVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @BBCr4today thank you - you too ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely - see @_ukactive calculations on #turningthetide reports https://t.co/BZ69JsJZ0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @BBCr4today yours have more bling though :) great look! I feel 16 again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @BBCr4today they're Bose - never has music sounded so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but these are just too good for @BBCr4today sauntering along to De La Soul instead - much better start to day! https://t.co/2aRJAUSadI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSJnews the link on the HSJ Awards shortlist announcement takes you to where to book a table, not the shortlist https://t.co/hXruTBaTdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blown away by size of @johnlewis in Birmingham Central...question is will there be time for shopping post pitch? https://t.co/CF37tT1Xi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly season still strong - hedgehog sanctuary on garden bridge called for &amp; GP claims ownership of Mars courtesy of @thetimes  #prtips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother and daughter reunited at #nhs16expo any other random family meet ups here? https://t.co/J70dK53wb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V brave woman speaks out on transformative treatment received for BPD power of patients' voices at #nhs16expo is what makes it so special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jamesillman: . @Jeremy_Hunt tells #Expo16NHS last decade NHS sorted waiting times. this decade quality &amp; safety &amp; next decade will b pa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[111 announcement: algorithm currently led by phone call - now also on line. Better than webmd where all symptoms=brain cancer #Expo16NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only one london trust named as a global exemplar of #namethepaperlessby2020agenda #Expo16NHS https://t.co/QGjCEyCePF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No UK hospital IT systems are world class - trusts will need to go at different speeds." #Expo16NHS #namethepaperlessby2020agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindless #nhs16expo musings... Is Lord Darzi the best dressed man in healthcare? https://t.co/4j7sl258Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple effective #prtips David Halpern @B_I_Tweets 'what are the existing comms channels you've got?' Uses eg. Of HMRC for SMEs #Expo16NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPIAndyCowper further evidence you no longer need a physical product for @HSJnews ! You'll all be able relocate to sunnier climes soon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sutton_eileen your moment of fame #nhs16expo https://t.co/uFS0jVOGLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Hunt getting down with the real folk queuing at #nhs16expo hope doesn't escalate to Corbyn-esq train selfies https://t.co/jjxMjt09Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning tweet so far #nhs16expo  https://t.co/ibZeAYaY7i]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>