<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[May not still be in the real world when Mark Hamill is making supervillain references on my best friends' tweets.  https://t.co/dTG0IC0bKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kansasalps: Comey: FBI recommends not prosecuting Clinton over private email server, but using it was "extremely careless" https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, world! Oh you too, Earth. https://t.co/sJ0qLjsWJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, Couch! May your geekiness know no bounds.  https://t.co/qs9kmTPCKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walton Shepherd of @NRDC highlights @GovernorVA's leadership on clean energy this week: https://t.co/4AVl4w3O0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stop going back to look at this Zogby poll on Kansas. Quit messing with me, @NateSilver538. https://t.co/a7saj6Q63O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffvandermeer Jaime. Gotta go for the King/Kin/Queen-slayer hat trick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The window for limiting warming to below 1.5C...  already seems to have closed." https://t.co/lQSUy9s5Tj #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Michal_Rose: @JohnFCross  @ConservationCO staff are all safe. Same with Sierra club, TU, WCF, Rocky Mtn Wild. One female victim, haven'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConservationCO: Conservation Colorado staff is all safe and accounted for. Thank you for voicing your concerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope all the wonderful people who work in/near the Alliance Center in Denver are okay. Stay safe. @americanrivers @ConservationCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: "But VW should also be brought to justice for any remaining civil and criminal violations." —@NRDC's Luke Tonachel https://t.co/7…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GinaEPA: Updated: Proud of our work w/ @DOJ @FTC @AirResources in settlement w/VW to get cars off road &amp; invest in clean air. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: "What's in Your Water: Beyond Flint" press telebriefing starts in 5. Lots on the call--if you are a reporter join us! DM me…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big day for bike policy in DC. Pass the Motor Vehicle Collision Recovery Act! #bikedc @VOrangeDC @kenyanmcduffie  https://t.co/e5AMa4r4CE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Toast is toast, which is to say burnt crisply into our fondest internet memories. We salute you, @mallelis.  https://t.co/9LIcgK80iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rockykistner1: Fading #fishermen: A historic industry faces a warming world https://t.co/NG2oELGLRZ via @HoustonChron #climatechange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if he says these things just set the stage for the eventual Trump News Network. https://t.co/PvGQlJRg7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bayer got in trouble last week for saying ppl can reduce carbon footprint by eating less meat. (Because they can.) https://t.co/ZJeE4UyZoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uspirg: Transportation is a large source of smog – noxious mix of ground-level O3 and PM pollution. https://t.co/1bzjC3NNJE https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Find out if you are one of 12 million Americans who live too close to oil and gas developments. https://t.co/419fJjJzkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DomenicoNPR: .@realDonaldTrump's fav/unfav rating dropped a net of 18 pts in @ABCPolitics @washingtonpost poll - from 37/60 (-23) to 29…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AntOz: Now officially the 9th longest #filibuster in US history (since 1900), and longest of the 21st century; watch live: https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briana9 I would, but my first responsibility is to be at work in the morning getting govt on track on some other things. #actonclimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressed by all keeping @ChrisMurphyCT's #filibuster going, even now. "The opposite of love is not hate, it is indifference" - @CoryBooker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NextGenClimate: France formally signs the Paris climate agreement. https://t.co/R6mKPn4XSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnDingell: #TBT https://t.co/YNEnOHHLYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Harvard study shows a system like the Clean Power Plan could yield $33 billion in net climate/health benefits. https://t.co/Yuhem4AOs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: Delete your account. https://t.co/Oa92sncRQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whaaa? "Literally zero relationship between the strength of the Warriors’ opponents and how well they performed." https://t.co/R8d9X59QXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WPJohnWagner: Seeking to exit on his own terms, Bernie Sanders comes to Washington Thursday, w/ @costareports @eilperin https://t.co/ah…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[83 vacant positions for federal judges, 30 of which have backlogs of cases that constitute "judicial emergencies." https://t.co/spjfxcIJnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great summary of recent findings from @e2org on clean energy jobs: https://t.co/gNSJ8HrrsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pamelalauren: Standard similar to @EPA #CleanPowerPlan could save $33B in annual health costs -- study https://t.co/awv4fz87QF $ @EEPub…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy World Oceans Day! Join the swell of support for #BlueParks to help #SaveOceanTreasures https://t.co/qeLmpmGtQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CITES: Happy #WorldOceansDay! Should all devil #rays be protected by CITES? World's govts to decide at #CoP17 in September https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SierraClubLive: We're at the #WhiteHouse for a press conference to tell @POTUS we want #NoSecretMoney in our politics. Follow along. ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India confirms finalizing commitment to the Paris agreement with U.S. this year  in Obama-Modi talks.  https://t.co/CqWUHWZXAu #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court isn't the only place obstructionism is keeping the justice system from working. https://t.co/5rL9NZemfk #DoYourJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: .@POTUS, protect our coastal communities &amp; ban oil/gas drilling in the Atlantic: https://t.co/Bz72GyAWHl https://t.co/RHHlYawlJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnpodesta: Proud to work for the first Presidential candidate to receive the @NRDC_AF endorsement. https://t.co/Or30jfRCmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why. No. Stop. https://t.co/TgaYp8p4Np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI - U.S. jobs in solar energy surpassed those in oil &amp; gas extraction. https://t.co/BsYZn96zwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's energy speech in ND continues policy of shutting eyes real tight and avoiding reality https://t.co/Gjl8nPgYRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, sorry, no earnest / @ErnestMoniz pun intended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is something way too earnest about the we-need-to-debunk-Stranger-Things tone of this article.  https://t.co/cnHrWtPoFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch That makes spectacularly little sense, on a Dr. Who meets Benjamin Button kind of level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch Good thing time-warping loopholes are in plentiful supply these days. Oops, i mean black holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend Juanita has some thoughts about running, extreme weather, and climate change. https://t.co/5GRtwmKAvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tlongpine: Maybe there is something the 15th &amp; 19th amendment people can do about @realDonaldTrump. Maybe there is. I don't know. #imwi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible - among black voters, Donald Trump is in fourth place. https://t.co/r91wbZCTbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @seungminkim: Wow, that Michael Phelps, he's like the male Katie Ledecky. #Rio2016 🇺🇸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: More than 3 billion viewers were given a stark warning about rising temperatures &amp; seas. https://t.co/6aDhkdrWAR via @sciam #Rio2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Our experts are testifying today on an @EPA program to invest in #CleanEnergy in communities that need it most. https://t.co/rAkt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Seattle for a wedding. You know I'm cool because high on my list is sampling some restored fish populations. @PacificCouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billmckibben: Trump: Windpower 'kills all your birds. All your birds, killed." 
Well, pretty much https://t.co/h8vJKVraAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEPA = critical law requiring review of all sorts of projects' enviro impacts. Now it will factor in #climatechange. https://t.co/FcCyyShJwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY takes historic step with order that 50% of its energy comes from renewables by 2030. #ActOnClimate https://t.co/QGFAknpzEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine is seriously loving these balloons. #DemsInPhilly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can save our planet while creating millions of good paying clean energy jobs" #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that's pretty adorable. https://t.co/tEIYy0ttjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattSepara: PLEASE LET JOE BIDEN BE LEFT SHARK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesGunn: Admittedly, every time I see Bradley I'm a little upset he's not a space raccoon. But I deal. https://t.co/dvSK9m85iq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCVoters: "Are we going to protect polluter profits, or protect public health? Elect a climate denier, or a climate champion?" #DemsInP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But @AaronCouch, what lineup could ever stand up to Bob Loblaw? https://t.co/8CIVd8dBcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: The President of the United States is literally making the case for democracy over authoritarianism. In 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And then there's Donald Trump... Don't boo, vote." -@POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackConnor1 @timkaine ugh. Not that Pembroke is much better, but, ugh. 😛]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kibblesmith: I can't wait for my great-grandchildren to interview me for their reports about President Barack Obama. #DemsInPhilly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patricey oh hey! I didn't realize we were still housemates. But sorry I'm not there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at the DNC: film from James Cameron, Don Cheadle, Sigourney Weaver, Matt Damon  on the need to #ActOnClimate https://t.co/elGsEESMIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will climate change impact summer heat in your hometown? Find out. https://t.co/lNIyk9osQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: For the 1st time on record, all of the U.S. is forecast to see above-avg. temps for the next 3 months: https://t.co/l7bbvsvlBu vi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peak and fall of China's coal consumption now seen as permanent trend: https://t.co/aCyPDCGlsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSanders: Never tweet. https://t.co/DKvAhbDWqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear @MichelleObama's remarks were cribbed *straight* from @MichelleObama's speech in 2016. #DemsInPhilly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to wastewater treatment! @BernieSanders #DemsInPhilly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ActOnClimate #ImWithHer  https://t.co/K5sSfQSZH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: "Hillary will fight to preserve this Earth for our children and grandchildren and we're with her." - @SenWarren #DNCinPHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A stupid wall, which will *never* get built" -Warren #DemsInPhilly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshDorner: Sounded like ten ridiculous people. Anyone shouting down Elizabeth Warren isn't worth taking seriously. https://t.co/ZyJyC0…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait just wait for Rock You Like a Hurri-Kaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jodyavirgan: So, that was enough of an amalgam of reactions that everyone gets to walk away with whatever narrative they want! https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCVoters: Yes! Senator @JeffMerkley: We're #StrongerTogether and calls for more clean energy to help our country combat #climatechange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kansasalps Andrea doesn't hesitate, she exhibits no restraint, she takes and she takes and she takes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: The Paris Climate Agreement is poised to take effect as soon as this year, according to NRDC: https://t.co/hueGwp3zDF via @Busine…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kansasalps Be careful there - two pints of Sam Adams is probably enough for a Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SymoneDSanders: But let me be clear - NO ONE STOLE THIS ELECTION! Team Sanders we did AMAZING WORK. But we lost. It's a hard reality fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of aircraft pollution, we recently created a scorecard on aviation biofuels: https://t.co/slaru1HaVE https://t.co/iOTFsnmfBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GinaEPA: Science tells us aircraft emissions endanger our health/environment. We must #ActOnClimate: https://t.co/AV047blTBT https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Kaine it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colbert: Sanders supporters voting Trump is "like if you ask for a Coke but they don't have it you say 'then just fill my mouth w/ bees.'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eilperin: "And as a Chicago guy I appreciate that, vote early, vote often" @POTUS on @Royals fans swamping All-Star game voting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There were some dark years... some tough decades" says @POTUS. #Royals #Yosted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's go #Royals chant breaks out in the room as soon as they're on stage. @POTUS there now. 
https://t.co/LLwNA1E9th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KC @Royals getting on stage at the @WhiteHouse now: https://t.co/LLwNA1E9th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heat waves look even worse when every month for over a year has been the hottest on record. #ActOnClimate https://t.co/3f8xHBkcAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At RNC show, @ThirdEyeBlind takes a stand "like Bruce Willis drilling himself into the core of an evil asteroid." https://t.co/KVM5CBgxbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job internet, you've created a market for crossovers of political nerdery, news satire and sci fi tropes.  https://t.co/NMbuC8W1pk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never played, but I'd be sprinting out the door in a wizard robe for D&amp;D with Colbert, The Rock, and Aubrey Plaza. https://t.co/zR9FlaOcLE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>