<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nvidia aims to woo business analysts with new software: Graphics chipmaker Nvidia Corp is trying to grab a bigger slice of the business computing market from dominant rival Intel Corp with a new set of software tools released on Wednesday. https://t.co/3YC5ZRKC9E https://t.co/QZ76I59Tpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker Nvidia to supply computer for Volvo's upcoming vehicles: Graphics chipmaker Nvidia Corp said on Wednesday that Swedish automaker Volvo would begin using its artificial intelligence computer to deliver low-level autonomous features in all its… https://t.co/zpoXQWWHPb https://t.co/kCevwjKGRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat announces new scripted shows to win over users: Snap Inc on Wednesday announced new scripted shows for its photo messaging app Snapchat which will launch this fall and struck partnerships with Hollywood production companies and writers in hopes… https://t.co/8cwysHlQRR https://t.co/IedwRYZ8II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank upping bet on loss-making WeWork with possible majority stake: source: Japan's SoftBank Group Corp is in discussions to buy a majority stake in U.S. shared office space provider WeWork Cos, a source said, potentially doubling down on one of its… https://t.co/W6F3eAncad https://t.co/mJL9sPY7Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom to launch commercial 5G operations in 2020: Deutsche Telekom will launch commercial 5G operations in Germany in 2020, as long as enough commercial devices are available, Chief Executive Tim Hoettges said on Wednesday as he pledged to… https://t.co/R9G7zeFWU4 https://t.co/GdEdjtuZcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan's antitrust watchdog ends inspection over Airbnb: Japan's antitrust watchdog said on Wednesday it would end its inspection of the Japanese operations of Airbnb Inc as the U.S. home-sharing platform provider has taken appropriate measures to… https://t.co/0VdCEmaPsi https://t.co/ynnuKuAHts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S., European regulators investigating Google glitch: At least two U.S. states and two European Union member states are investigating a breach at Alphabet Inc's Google that may have exposed private profile data of at least 500,000 users to hundreds of… https://t.co/T2J2O7BeEE https://t.co/LOlY0pjJnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker Micron to invest $100 million in artificial intelligence companies: Micron Technology said on Wednesday it planned to invest up to $100 million in startup companies working on artificial intelligence technologies for use in self-driving… https://t.co/Ju7UZ8lVzH https://t.co/10kNl8ipPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square CFO Sarah Friar to join Nextdoor as CEO: Jack Dorsey-led Square Inc said on Wednesday its financial head Sarah Friar will step down to become the chief executive officer of social networking service provider Nextdoor. https://t.co/C1Ui1XPCjt https://t.co/kFFB2MT0WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple plans to give original content for free to device owners: CNBC: Apple Inc is planning a new digital video service that will provide original content free to its device owners, CNBC reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter. https://t.co/KzytFuZZ9b https://t.co/cQnkrEXbMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position Title Software Developer Entry Level: * Software Developer – Entry Level Location US-PA-Mechanicsburg Requisition ID 2018-11296 Business Area Software Category/Discipline Information Technology/Software Development Position Type Permanent… https://t.co/E5YxEI6YmL https://t.co/BqVQG7gc79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Data Warehousing: Software Developer – Data Warehousing job description | Excell – blog – NewsRoom – Contact – Login – Investors – INVESTOR DASHBOARD – PRESS RELEASES – STOCK – ONLINE INVESTOR KIT – SEC FILINGS – CORPORATE GOVERNENCE… https://t.co/4fHCoq8nZx https://t.co/RE4IEj6R73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli tech women protest men-only meeting with Merkel: Women working in high-tech companies posed around a cardboard cutout of German Chancellor Angela Merkel on Wednesday to protest against a meeting she held with an all-male group of entrepreneurs in… https://t.co/HUI7ROVqTN https://t.co/Z1IBOw93km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon says memo asking for Broadcom-CA deal review is likely fake: The U.S. Department of Defense said on Wednesday that a memo purporting to show the Pentagon asking for a national security review of chipmaker Broadcom Inc's $19 billion deal to buy… https://t.co/HurxcnuW3C https://t.co/LNuc2chZOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital-only banks take sizeable share in France but lose money: regulator: A new breed of digital-only banks has spread in France but still struggles to make any money, a report by France's banking regulator ACPR said on Wednesday. https://t.co/W4NlTwn3ek https://t.co/SxCXEln03V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Professional Services Manager Advanced Technology Services: Senior Professional Services Manager – Advanced Technology Services in Philadelphia, PA – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network… https://t.co/HapybLeZWX https://t.co/L75fp0336o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom says fake Department of Defense memo seeks review of CA Technologies deal: Chipmaker Broadcom Inc said on Wednesday a faked memo, purportedly from the U.S. Department of Defense, had been circulated among lawmakers calling for a review of its… https://t.co/y6wxIEqGVD https://t.co/1I6GaqDJvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Mitek rebuffs Elliott-backed ASG's takeover approach - sources: Mitek Systems Inc, a U.S. provider of financial technology to banks, has rejected a takeover approach from hedge fund Elliott Management Corp's software company ASG Technologies,… https://t.co/SqJP38uEVU https://t.co/jh14JKiukh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom says Department of Defense memo asking for CA Technologies deal review is fake: Chipmaker Broadcom Inc said on Wednesday a forged memo purportedly signed by the U.S. Department of Defense on the need for a review of its $19-billion acquisition… https://t.co/cwjPtHwMTk https://t.co/sD9MMiLJ9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Mitek rebuffs Elliott-backed ASG's takeover approach, sources say: Mitek Systems Inc, a U.S. provider of financial technology to banks, has rejected a takeover approach from hedge fund Elliott Management Corp's software company ASG… https://t.co/26qtkqgMqO https://t.co/ScECjg6M3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's WhatsApp says has fixed video call security bug: Facebook Inc's WhatsApp messenger service said on Wednesday it has fixed the latest bug on its platform that allowed hackers to take over users' applications when they answered an incoming video… https://t.co/dQDSvdR8pn https://t.co/ZhGzN8bsml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France's EDF wants to dominate electric vehicle charging market: French state-owned utility EDF plans to become the leader in electric vehicle charging in Europe, a potentially lucrative, but already crowded, sector. https://t.co/q7Nw635Dxf https://t.co/ngCJDMFD8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany to unveil battery cell consortium on November 13: Tagesspiegel: Germany's economy minister will present plans on Nov. 13 for a consortium to set up a battery cell factory in Germany, supported by 1 billion euros ($1.15 billion) of government… https://t.co/8icUE0HFZU https://t.co/mLLgPMOqTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst CRM: Job ID : 78436BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With revenues… https://t.co/XT6lZdyStH https://t.co/Yn8DeZxPAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei to sell servers with own chips in cloud computing push: China's Huawei [HWT.UL], the world's largest telecom-equipment maker, on Wednesday said it will sell some servers powered by its own chips for the first time, doubling down on efforts to… https://t.co/jK3jjXLPnc https://t.co/3Dd9pDoCm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank in talks to buy majority stake in loss-making WeWork: source: Japan's SoftBank Group Corp is in discussions to buy a majority stake in U.S. shared office space provider WeWork Cos, a source said, potentially doubling down on one of its biggest… https://t.co/QmGiHvuEur https://t.co/InIISEhQxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procurement Operations Specialist (SAP Ariba) – Bilingual (Spanish) Job: COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP started in 1972 as a team of five colleagues with a desire to do something new. Together, they changed enterprise software and reinvented how business was… https://t.co/lIgypUPF81 https://t.co/Qq7VlaOVcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hyVEKuEs54 with Azure cloud: ******* with Azure cloud Ref No.:18-16711 Location: Chesterbrook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 09/14/2018 Job Title: ******* with Azure cloud Location: Chesterbrook, PA Duration: Longterm… https://t.co/IMXBJKK38w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Airbnb rival https://t.co/VwsoHa9lnG raises nearly $300 million from Jack Ma fund: Chinese short-term rental firm https://t.co/VwsoHa9lnG said on Wednesday it has raised nearly $300 million in a funding round led by Jack Ma's Yunfeng Capital, amid… https://t.co/XeXfm0uYxe https://t.co/Gm9G5utTU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon scraps secret AI recruiting tool that showed bias against women: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc's machine-learning specialists uncovered a big problem: their new recruiting engine did not like women. https://t.co/cOMrwbNv3X https://t.co/9hhrVGC2qH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack/Spring Framework Developer Global Trade: For BNY Mellon Full Stack/Spring Framework Developer – Global Trade job – Information Technology – Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who… https://t.co/1rApumVOy3 https://t.co/CmDSWoZBLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Republican senator seeks briefings on reported China hacking attack: The top Republican on the Senate Commerce Committee has asked Apple Inc, https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc and Super Micro Computer Inc for staff briefings about a Bloomberg report that… https://t.co/Zav2LQFLmv https://t.co/ZiLmBrEHur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese short-term rental firm https://t.co/VwsoHa9lnG raises nearly $300 million: Chinese short-term rental firm https://t.co/VwsoHa9lnG said on Wednesday it has raised nearly $300 million in a funding round led by Jack Ma's Yunfeng Capital. https://t.co/wcjtqNojcW https://t.co/WOJJGPyaqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank in talks to take majority stake in WeWork: source: Japan's SoftBank Group Corp is in discussions to take a majority stake in shared office space provider WeWork Cos, a source familiar with the matter said, a deal that would increase one of its… https://t.co/8cWdULA5iS https://t.co/zuGsp47LZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei unveils chips to boost cloud computing at Shanghai conference: China's Huawei, the world's largest telecom-equipment maker, unveiled two new artificial intelligence powered chips to boost its cloud computing business at the company's annual global… https://t.co/gtLVFhhtAt https://t.co/gQeNkJiPPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Entry Level: Local Unit &amp; Position Description DNV GL – Digital Solutions North America is seeking a Software Developer – Entry Level to join our Pipeline Ecosystem Product Development team. This team produces software products for the… https://t.co/Xuk71FD81Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank in talks to take majority stake in WeWork: WSJ: Japan's SoftBank Group Corp is in talks to take a majority stake in shared office space provider WeWork Cos, the Wall Street Journal reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the talks. https://t.co/pTFK8ubsAE https://t.co/gfRtdJSHNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KMONS6eUUI Manager, IT Risk Management- IAM Services: https://t.co/KMONS6eUUI Manager, IT Risk Management-&gt;&gt; Manages multiple teams across business segments in identifying, analyzing, monitoring, and minimizing areas of risk that pertain to… https://t.co/ufucHuIckz https://t.co/EjRfg9jFqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon slow to protect weapon systems from cyber threats: U.S. agency: The Pentagon has been slow to protect major weapon systems from cyber attacks and routinely found critical vulnerabilities that hackers could potentially exploit in those systems, a… https://t.co/DNXVbYvOhD https://t.co/9POTDIRgRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican senator seeks briefings on reported China hacking attack: The top Republican on the Senate Commerce Committee has asked Apple Inc, https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc and Super Micro Computer Inc for staff briefings about a Bloomberg report that the… https://t.co/C9GAvKNPym https://t.co/MvhfjaGIeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: A Technician I will be responsible for resolving escalated issues from first level analysts. This position must have customer service skills with the ability to communicate face to face as well as via telephone to troubleshoot… https://t.co/sq4Xd8dgvA https://t.co/j2PKcDplRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/Pqj6Z1uIIr https://t.co/YxBlvhNWbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Specialist (Information Security/Policy Planning): – Duties HelpDuties Summary About the Position:Information Technology Specialist (Information Security/Policy Planning) position located in the Directorate of Production… https://t.co/qvwHb3z89j https://t.co/vJgc000W2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: SunIRef:it Database Administrator – West Conshohocken, PA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state,… https://t.co/z9BTSv8tdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HNA Technology says in preliminary talks to sell Ingram Micro: China's HNA Technology Co Ltd is in preliminary talks to sell U.S. electronics distributor Ingram Micro Inc, as part of its parent group's efforts to trim operations. https://t.co/M3rtmn7x9S https://t.co/dgIdDCHMVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: U.S. satellite service offers to sell minority stake to Russia: U.S. satellite start-up OneWeb has offered to sell a minority stake to Russia, a move it hopes will allay Moscow's concerns about the company's plan to create a worldwide internet… https://t.co/mgIAfH6PlW https://t.co/ju5AOIx4tV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI Tech: GI Technician- Endoscopy Job ID: 77390 Job Category: Clinical Support Specialty Area: Clinical Support Primary Shift: Day Work Schedule: Day Shift with Call Requirements Penn Medicine Entity: Penn Presbyterian Medical Center Location:… https://t.co/UT6dvWjj9B https://t.co/dSo4rVomk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike-sharing firm Ofo's dramatic fall a warning to China's tech investors: On the sidewalks of Shanghai and Beijing, once bright-yellow Ofo bicycles lie in varying states of disrepair - chains unhooked, wheels buckled and paint starting to fade -… https://t.co/QweGX3hSKC https://t.co/vhTP9Rxb0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us DevOps Engineer Job Attributes Job Id: 22098Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: King Of Prussia, PA… https://t.co/sb3Z2GyIX6 https://t.co/mOyzzMoIrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – Senior – PSH IT Clinical: Penn State Health Shared Services Location: US:PA:Hershey Work Type: Full Time FTE: 1.0 Shift: Day Hours: 8:00a – 5:00p JOB SUMMARY: Penn State Health is looking for a customer-focused individual with technical… https://t.co/oZw1N4XYIa https://t.co/u4bbphkdUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer and Operations: Comcast’s Technology &amp; Product organization works at the intersection of media and technology. Our innovative teams are continually developing and delivering products that transform the customer experience. From creating… https://t.co/MFWkJZXvWk https://t.co/VgD1dOpzau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehouse Developer (Sr ETL Programmer): SunIRef:it Data Warehouse Developer (Sr ETL Programmer) – Reading, PA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title,… https://t.co/lSdz8hgnQQ https://t.co/qPIQPrA7Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer RD Rail Automation: SunIRef:it Senior Software Engineer – R &amp; D Rail Automation – Munhall, PA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title,… https://t.co/lYjJoPaZkC https://t.co/sA9QFGGdVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook gave data on user's friends to certain companies: documents: Facebook Inc let some companies, including Netflix and Airbnb, access users' lists of friends after it cut off that data for most other apps around 2015, according to documents… https://t.co/CO7buFfrLq https://t.co/B8sZi4pjo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook board backs Sandberg's handling of research into George Soros: WSJ: Facebook Inc's board backed Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg's handling of research into investor George Soros, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing a… https://t.co/7SbNfK1fJJ https://t.co/0o38bG365D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Yorkers overwhelmingly support Amazon campus in Queens: poll: New Yorkers by a wide margin approve of plans for https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc to build a massive new campus in the city, although they are divided over terms of a multibillion-dollar… https://t.co/aHSvIpeQNY https://t.co/3y29RwEvnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook gave preferential data access to certain companies: documents: Facebook Inc gave some companies, including Netflix and Airbnb, preferential access to user data in 2015 as it limited services for most others, according to company emails and… https://t.co/1Lus99uTRd https://t.co/yPPx5qCJ60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – Java Full Stack: Sr. Specialist Developer / UI Developer ‘ The position must be filled at this time to address the increasing demand for Wealth Management business solutions.’ We have several business critical initiatives for… https://t.co/UNrWh23hfZ https://t.co/KIQDd9tCZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documents show Facebook gave preferential access to data to certain companies: Facebook Inc gave certain companies, including Netflix and Airbnb, preferential access to user data, according to the company's internal documents released by a British… https://t.co/uFNAqzjfQW https://t.co/A2fQmwm0zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British lawmakers release internal Facebook documents: British lawmakers published a cache of internal Facebook Inc documents, which indicates that the social network gave certain companies special access to user data even after promising to limit such… https://t.co/WyxvHzDUwE https://t.co/tbvU3e8LcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For European chip stocks, business cycle returns with a vengeance: Investors who bet on European semiconductor stocks to profit from innovations being packed into smartphones and advanced vehicles are facing the grim reality that both industries are… https://t.co/QtkVSMiquA https://t.co/GwE1cq1Te7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo unveils self-driving taxi service in Arizona for paying customers: Alphabet's Waymo on Wednesday launched a significant development in its costly, decade-long quest for autonomous transportation: self-driving taxis that actually generate fares. https://t.co/63zNHa0YNo https://t.co/A1cdkU0WGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Waymo compares to U.S. rivals in the race for robotaxis: Waymo, Alphabet's self-driving unit, launched on Wednesday the first commercial automated ride-hailing service of its size among the main U.S. companies vying to dominate the still nascent… https://t.co/71IfLstpL1 https://t.co/jP1GeScu8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finnish game maker Supercell launches free coding school to combat labor shortage: Finland's Supercell, maker of the Clash of Clans mobile game, said on Wednesday it would fund a new software programming school free of tuition fees to be established in… https://t.co/KZnCywXnmV https://t.co/O08oxrjLy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer I: ECFMG is seeking a Salesforce Developer I in the Philadelphia PA office. A self-motivated, independent, detail oriented, and responsible team player, the Salesforce Developer I will utilize various technologies for the development… https://t.co/pmfuyl2Lw8 https://t.co/qrrNzBBefc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BT to strip China's Huawei from core networks, limit 5G access: Britain's BT Group said on Wednesday it was removing Huawei Technologies' equipment from the core of its existing 3G and 4G mobile operations and would not use the Chinese company in central… https://t.co/VTCg4bGcd2 https://t.co/QLEUGONSzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore PM files defamation suit against blogger who shared article on Facebook: Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong has filed a defamation suit against a financial adviser and blogger who shared an article on his Facebook page, Lee's spokeswoman… https://t.co/ZH0Dqho5wN https://t.co/hu5gvXLqZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba signs agreement with Belgium for e-commerce trade hub: Alibaba Group Holding Ltd said on Wednesday it has signed an agreement with the Belgium government to launch an e-commerce trade hub, which will include investments in logistics infrastructure. https://t.co/G098ACd4wG https://t.co/ddNk794WVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Didi announces reorganization plan to address safety: Chinese ride-hailing firm Didi Chuxing on Wednesday announced a reorganization plan aimed at improving safety on its platform, as it works to address public and government concerns raised… https://t.co/DIB0kkqdUT https://t.co/Pv0hFkCTGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Didi announces reorganization plan to address safety issues: Chinese ride hailing giant Didi Chuxing on Wednesday announced a reorganization plan which it said was aimed at improving the safety and efficiency of its platform. https://t.co/d9U3QDuaNC https://t.co/APdKanXIk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BT to remove Huawei equipment from its core 4G network: FT: Britain's BT Group Plc will remove Huawei Technologies Co's equipment from its core 4G network within two years, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday. https://t.co/5mBje6n89v https://t.co/QmGJvCCW7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank's Vision Fund to hire China team, set up mainland office: sources: The SoftBank-led Vision Fund is hiring an investment team to be based in China as the $100 billion investment giant expands in one of the world's most vibrant tech markets, two… https://t.co/t2zmgBSFop https://t.co/0cqqbgA1RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump panel wants to give USPS right to hike prices for Amazon, others: The United States Postal Service should have more flexibility to raise rates for packages, according to recommendations from a task force set up by President Donald Trump, a move… https://t.co/W3fOe9AkZu https://t.co/zIrydsNiX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet unit halts glucose-detecting contact lens project: Alphabet Inc's life sciences division Verily said on Friday that it was putting on hold one of its oldest and highest-profile projects, a smart contact lens designed to help monitor sugar levels. https://t.co/ggeAle12W8 https://t.co/H0zqbgl3hV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer AWS: To provide senior level (Java Netcentric) system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications for Web based systems. We are looking for a JAVA, UI / MIDTIER DEVELOPER who has: * Experience with AWS implementation… https://t.co/DqGQTU44eD https://t.co/mtJz8XrNkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital media company Technicolor explores options including sale: sources: Technicolor SA has been exploring options that include a full or partial sale of the French digital media company, as its set-top box business struggles because of higher prices… https://t.co/OVDlonMkeN https://t.co/6gAZ1NerGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Cloud names Thomas Kurian to replace CEO Diane Greene: Former Oracle Corp product chief Thomas Kurian will replace Diane Greene as head of the cloud division at Alphabet Inc's Google in the coming weeks, Greene announced in a blog post on Friday,… https://t.co/XNRPMU3TMW https://t.co/wkDajKK65l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's life sciences unit halts glucose-sensing lens project: Verily, Alphabet Inc's life sciences division, is putting on hold one of its oldest and high-profile projects, a smart lens to help monitor sugar levels. https://t.co/uRI58LZj9O https://t.co/MThnlIWl5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Applications Specialist: Overview Clinical Applications Specialist – Philadelphia, PA FUJIFILM, SonoSite, Inc . We are an innovative and high performance culture with tremendous opportunities. People who work here are given the unique… https://t.co/lB1ihervJv https://t.co/h1yqwIhKnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's Verily pauses project on glucose-sensing lens: Alphabet Inc's Verily said on Friday it is pausing research on glucose-sensing lens, one of its earliest projects. https://t.co/hcvLnoOCxW https://t.co/boybFXnvZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator settles with tech startups over token sale violations: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday settled charges with two tech companies for improperly offering digital tokens, mandating that they register their offerings… https://t.co/pxJTpWIQql https://t.co/YXT9KRJGiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle veteran Thomas Kurian to replace Diane Greene as Google Cloud CEO: Former Oracle Corp product chief Thomas Kurian is replacing Diane Greene as chief executive of Alphabet Inc's Google Cloud, according to a blog post https://t.co/h9rzndzy5q from… https://t.co/9Wt2j5iBVU https://t.co/FlIFTdGvWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla starts taking Model 3 orders in China: Tesla Inc has started taking orders for its Model 3 sedan in China for a deposit of 8,000 yuan ($1,153.60), according to the electric carmaker's China website https://t.co/0c5OFYOZyn. https://t.co/6dYCVcRrfb https://t.co/Nk3FkExVma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Senate bill vows to get tough on robocalls, up penalties: Two U.S. senators on Friday unveiled bipartisan legislation to toughen penalties on robocalls, make it easier for regulators to crack down on unwanted calls and compel mobile phone providers… https://t.co/WGxpy7Qk9a https://t.co/LPhXyEN9Ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst – Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation: For BNY Mellon Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst – Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation job – Information Technology… https://t.co/Q6xSdcDtIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The egos disbanded? Bridging the great advertising divide: Traditional advertising groups hope that their creative flair will prevail against the technological clout of consultancies encroaching on their business, but there are signs the two sides of the… https://t.co/mS9ukKE7Wy https://t.co/FotuBHl2j3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volkswagen expects to be the most profitable maker of electric cars: Volkswagen Chief Executive Herbert Diess on Friday said he expected the multi-brand carmaking group to be the most profitable manufacturer of electric cars thanks to economies of scale. https://t.co/avo4czPhQ2 https://t.co/wPzU7sbva0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VW embarks on $50 billion electrification plan: Volkswagen plans to spend 44 billion euros ($50 billion) on electric cars, autonomous driving and new mobility services by 2023 and explore closer cooperation with Ford, the German company said on Friday. https://t.co/7u7bDHhqLm https://t.co/QRYdKhPDpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VW says could build up to 15 million electric cars: Volkswagen could build up to 15 million electric cars over several years on its new electric vehicle production platform, the company said on Friday, adding that its Chief Executive Herbert Diess had… https://t.co/156y67Xzn6 https://t.co/tWBCJ4zbmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volkswagen to spend 44 billion euros on electric, autonomous cars by 2023: Volkswagen on Friday said it will spend 44 billion euros on electric cars, digitalization, autonomous driving and new mobility services by 2023 as part of a push by Europe's… https://t.co/oP2akzbY3K https://t.co/rNoV30mjgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply glut mars Turing effect for Nvidia shares: Worries about how fast the computing world will transition to Nvidia Corp's next generation "Turing" graphic chips helped knock 20 percent off the value of its shares on Friday, after results pointed to a… https://t.co/3ovnLi1SjU https://t.co/n9FQZ3vMSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Title: iOS Developer Location: Philadelphia, PA Duration: Contract/ Full time MOI: Face to face is mandatory Skills: Swift Objective – C Architecture design patterns Web services SourceControl Tools App Distribution Agile Unit testing… https://t.co/rZ0qOzmwtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry to buy cybersecurity firm Cylance for $1.4 billion: BlackBerry Ltd said on Friday it will acquire Cylance, an artificial intelligence and cybersecurity company, for $1.4 billion in cash to help expand its QNX unit that makes software for… https://t.co/QqpCsjd9Zv https://t.co/c1CWEriFSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practice Manager, Data Science: Job Description Practice Manager, Data Science Location: US-PA-Pittsburgh Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Position Category: Machine Learning Science Company/Location (search) : Country (Full Name): :… https://t.co/mt1Qj71LRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Crypto hangover' hammers Nvidia's outlook, shares drop 17 percent: Chip designer Nvidia Corp on Thursday forecast disappointing sales for the holiday quarter, pinning the blame on unsold chips piling up with distributors and retailers after the… https://t.co/0E3OvRM59R https://t.co/ufnVrfkvUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook defends Russia response, updates plan to curb misbehavior: Facebook Inc Chairman and Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg on Thursday defended his response to Russian election meddling on the world's largest social media network and issued a new plan… https://t.co/zBJSyOXdKW https://t.co/ND6hPcrIF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slew of electric truck plans may deliver the goods for China's EV ambitions: Having just broken ground for a new factory in the southern Chinese province of Hunan, the head of electric car startup Singulato Motors has grand plans: build up to 50,000… https://t.co/hlymrYCiqI https://t.co/b94tP4M5JT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Platform Technical Lead: The Chief Technology Office (CTO) is committed to identifying, planning and designing strategic technology solutions to support Employer clients. As part of the Cloud Analytics Team, you will collaborate with… https://t.co/nKRbGOtEXV https://t.co/AsUXQctFJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell sweetens tracking stock offer, Icahn drops opposition: Dell Technologies on Thursday raised its offer to buy back shares tied to its interest in software maker VMware to $23.9 billion from $21.7 billion, prompting billionaire investor Carl Icahn to… https://t.co/SSO2AoVewT https://t.co/T84TW9b7zZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Specialist: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the… https://t.co/dYIXbxvIE6 https://t.co/fSe8uJjdiV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>