<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@anxietyissue He doesn't throw punches, he throws books at foes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ali_wants2tweet Hi ali. You have my attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaminoMyWay @UviPoznansky This break bringd rain the next 9 months. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth, like the body, always seeks balance. #outmyfrontdoor http://t.co/xZfTtIVLMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I come here to do my Qigong today. #outmyfrontdoorvancouver http://t.co/BrZLnfFrSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#outsidemyfrontdoor http://t.co/qUJe2FpSP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelKroft: A friend was complaining of waking up to the earthquake. Damn, I tend to pay a quarter for that in the "inexpensive" mote…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@londonswf @RoundTeam #clonearmy. Most popular car in Vancouver these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic nights. http://t.co/d93F1QVLLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affluent Twenty somethings http://t.co/7YmMChBS09 affluence is keeping diversity at bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only reportage of the wanton horror of Ferguson is being covered by a comedian http://t.co/PG9hEy1RgQ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blogdeandy thanks for the follow from the logo man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kapalabhati Yoga Breathing with Andrew Wrenn http://t.co/awXmnnoLd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryFVanucci Sounds like a winner, Gary. Who could resist the buzz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ali_wants2tweet Irish girls rule the kingdom of broken hearts, whom they lured with a few well chosen words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainlady02 i am writing lyrics because the literary mind cannot hold a tune in a bucket. Thanks for the follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalderwoodEric writers, I find, are like cats. Not buddies but equals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No sleep for the dreamer. N http://t.co/luIJ9TOh50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petermcnulty thanks for the follow Peter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ttg0txXWxN  and this is only the prequel of a massive scam that has political consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got : The Rebel! Which Jung Archetype Best Describes You? http://t.co/38RjKeaCdI via @play_buzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Writers Are Opening Up About Money. (Yawn.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCdeWinter: Something to keep in mind… http://t.co/JrKWBct5Cy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penpradeep a lover of pens, especially when I lost mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@go_jaimec The go-to gal with prudent financial advice. What a concept. Thanks for the invite.             27 Followers you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JA_Marx  who wouldn't follow someone with such multitasking-powers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JA_Marx @YouTube thanx for the invite with a nice kinda Sunday vibe. Cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zakzuul cool Zak! Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LordLouis3 thanks for the invite LLG. pretty impressive name to live up do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaTorre whatever you write it will always bring a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaTorre you are being followed. But, hey, you invited me to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An unpunished crime still haunts Three Cups of Tea Author http://t.co/XLrNG26r5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always breathtaking and still. The Aspen never disappoint. http://t.co/vkQvyaQcob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JungKatzBlog Thanks for the follow &amp; very nice work represented by yourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 years ago, as the globe plummeted into the First World War, the Duke of the Abruzzi was being sought to lead... http://t.co/qfKUvUs2lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first printing of the softcover from The Mountaineers Legends and Lore reprint "The Duke of the Abruzzi: An Explorer's Life"  sold out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An article just published in Medium about the Duke's Somalian village. http://t.co/YQE29uinr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “The Life and Death of a Somalian Village” https://t.co/O55xIi8tl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paolo Nutini -totally captures that cool LA vibe: http://t.co/ZxgEI8yL2y via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieCantrell who is busier, the gal in your novels or you? Thanks for the follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In rapture on a warm autumnal afternoon doing Chi Kung. #outmyfrontdoorinKits http://t.co/WcTuxj6hO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I complimented Rachel Lippert’s page at @aboutdotme! Check it out: http://t.co/5asediiXUK @Rlippert22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't stop reading. http://t.co/7TgaHPozeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visit to imternal novels, when there was the time to read and the intelligence to savor words. http://t.co/owwH63YMY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mariannjake. A gift.thanks for following. I'd follow a Kansas girl to anywhere but a church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keidi_Keating thanks for following.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always tugging at my heart to return. http://t.co/EicgZUKcou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson Give me your email address and I'll send you a synopsis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9/11 Firefighter Blows WTC 7 Cover-Up Wide Open http://t.co/mW4H7phDIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LA is suffering a massive heat wave and it's snowing in the east. Here it's just right on another lazy summer... http://t.co/87tbg9bwHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson I found a fully written book under my bed. Will need editor at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In one generation this has happened to the USA. http://t.co/ro4TsSu6Hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Franklin expedition was likely wiped out by scurvy, though the name and cause of their demise was not known... http://t.co/Ki2u1cWI7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeaneMooreBooks a poor person's Jackie Collins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chiara_Micheli A gift Chiara. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Chiara_Micheli: The Importance of Storytelling in Making Sense of the World: - An Animated Essay http://t.co/2KZ7tnO5qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickPolad thnx for the follow,Rick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaguaTiger Because of your secret society instructions of the esoteric martial arts, won't it be difficult to find you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a welcome back from the knomes of Twitterland and picked up a basket full of followers. I will leave more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably surprise a lot of folk. But it's always been the case. http://t.co/brvFePnCfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These will probably surprise many people. http://t.co/eQcroA3yjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a walk at sunset tonight a band of giant bubbles appeared in a park. The 60s all over again for a moment. #outmyfrontdoorkits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There IS a pot of gold at the end of a rainbow. http://t.co/cBgQ8iMRZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. http://t.co/XK9SzkuCr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNAshley who could refuse such an inviting smile. Thanks, Ashley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson really enjoyed meeting you. Neither one of us at a loss of words about writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Social Code” by @hanlonpatrick https://t.co/nWfOwjSFkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinarolsen I remember a chat we had some years ago. You are thriving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cinthiaritchie1 Thanks for the follow and good climbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warm air, warm water. Summer is here. http://t.co/7VLXty9pnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These folks haven't been heard, why should they vote? http://t.co/uZdtXop9Hi via @nytvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These people are smarter than all the pundits combined. http://t.co/wylBisUSN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, apart from high winds and thunderous avalances it's silent. Amazing panoramic view. http://t.co/VWgxI0e6in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Ways to Stop Absorbing Other People's Negative Emotions - http://t.co/PRcyLvkP4v via @Shareaholic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeLehrOZA Enjoyed your writings: I would now label my consulting days as pure &amp; simple mindfulness training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook has made me jaded, but this is truly charming. This bird has talent. http://t.co/rkuTeBsjl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XHLMiSttDm http://t.co/V94RC221D6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too! But that may surprise you. You always were deeply deep. http://t.co/wpzfp5KJI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a full day of sun. People and at peace.
 #kitsatmyfrontdoor http://t.co/TH7AmngEdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has a Girlfriend http://t.co/uGsqrttBz9 via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the man who shot and killed the Islamic terrorist in Canadian Parliament this week. http://t.co/kZMFYrMl6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Ubering While Black” by @jennydeluxe https://t.co/S02eYCxKWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The condition is further enhanced by having a dog, cat,fish and children in the mix. http://t.co/SZtEHwCRyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Psychology Behind Messy Rooms: Why The Most Creative People Flourish In Clutter http://t.co/TYEMQuhKY6 via @EliteDaily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panorama of colour along the block when the sun comes out. #outsidemydoorinkits http://t.co/a8NsL8W6P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@everydaycarry Ain't no way a guy carries this unless he's got a man purse or a female assistant to carry it all. His pants fall down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scariest thing in the news is not ebola or ISIL, it's that Romney is running for prez again for the plutocrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSheltonHamer I am charmed and who wouldn't be. A fun gal who loves words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ir https://t.co/NoDnWvq6Bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article is based on a re-published biography released this past summer, The Duke of the Abruzzi: An Explorer's …http://t.co/WPo7AkzWIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This interview provides some comfort in the face of plutocrats. Real change won't come from a faux president, but... http://t.co/3rtBNQZjYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard Zinn on the Power of People | http://t.co/xE2iRsFh23 http://t.co/igf0dToXbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside look at being "spiritual". http://t.co/PEcbABqIlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The narrative of paying off debt is killing any economic recovery. http://t.co/0cmFy9D3cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most greatful  for Pammy's humor and stories across the years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will have plenty of time to read incriminating mail. https://t.co/pwVyh8t6X2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they are watching us even now. https://t.co/pKW3otlUn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicenteFoxQue @Jugbo Trump won't come out where women might be bleed on him. The rest of the world laughs at this 71-year old man. Pathetic. Bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hSiyGFTQ9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/r6CdL1Y1DO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>