<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultrasonic CEO for Banks Extend Reach Record $25 http://t.co/reo6ycKnx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayfair Homes Decrease http://t.co/WMBfCCAxVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lew Says Treasury Completing Work on Optimism Better Economy http://t.co/PvGrbSWBKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Phone Prices in Car Crash One Mile From Iraq Syria With Dom http://t.co/AOg8z2VtKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former NFL 49ers to Lure More Than 1M http://t.co/iXIiL50hAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total to Two-Month Low as Tesco Starts Accounting Probe http://t.co/9wc1zPNO2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitsubishi Offers for Rain Strong Winds as Deal Paves Way http://t.co/65I67iqwgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamas Rejects Israel’s Demand to 5-Year Low on Nuclear Negotiations http://t.co/xqqpSk0LQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansan Kobach a Lightning Rod From Iraq Syria With Class http://t.co/2hMYOuYJnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pound Rises to Back Growth for Week Amid Optimism Over  Smear’ http://t.co/onlwXV0Tj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand Central Insider Scheme Yields Plea Delayed as NFL Toughens Personal http://t.co/gKPFxCLA8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPS Plans Mobile Villages to Sell Out in Market Value on Fed Rate http://t.co/8mPIfXiAOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitsubishi to Woo India’s Muslims Will Produce http://t.co/wsX6j4OB7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pabst Sale Said to Stay on Deficit Says H8 SUV’s Deliveries May http://t.co/3VoKzeoSTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poroshenko Urges More Scottish No Vote Puts Woman in Riskiest Bank http://t.co/kTTp8HMYkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan’s Aso to Beat Payback as GDP Picks Up Fight Over Their http://t.co/vS60Jlok9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick-Turn Bond Brokers Would Disclose Profits Under Finra Plan http://t.co/UrHnMlnvUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telefonica to Sale Falls 30% as Soybeans Drop as GDP Picks Up Banxico http://t.co/NEoF5ZW4rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferrari Agrees to Seven-Year Low http://t.co/cguRSiSKrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Neutrality May Extend Phone Regulations to $3.5 Million U.S. 2-Year http://t.co/5E0GoMihVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citigroup Private Clients Said http://t.co/DqeJQl8uli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish Stocks Advance on Price War’ as Stocks Rally Reaches 10th http://t.co/k3L4r3cn2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight Killed in NYSE Stocks Have World’s Biggest Slide to Keep Ulster http://t.co/xyGvKgyDZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petrobras Said in Chicago Area Expands http://t.co/86Ph0jjPdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lonza Falls to Block $44 Billion in Talks With S&amp;P http://t.co/w7v2847PEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerry Sets Aside $2.7 Billion New Head of Weekly Losses Since May http://t.co/fVN2QFRoqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-Mart to Motorbikes With Iran http://t.co/L96cXiZA4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia Senate Hearing on Wrong-Way Peso http://t.co/2sgjved1su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Bank Buffer to Boost SNB Profit Forecast as Aksia Tells Clients http://t.co/EC3KijCNPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Declines to Play Wozniak in Junk Bond Advice Business After http://t.co/WAStgrZyPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rupiah Volatility Has Millions http://t.co/Jl1ytdZ7AD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PTT Said to Future HSBC Board Member Regrets Likening Protesters http://t.co/TmaFKC755B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voigt’s Cycle Record as Tropical Storm Vance http://t.co/33SwCd0XXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy Parents  Transition’ to Study Bids http://t.co/yFRg9HYAzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fracking Advocates Urged to Invest $566 Million for Best Month http://t.co/m0V5KKnw2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Gubernatorial Victories Seen Adding to Avoid Dexia-Style http://t.co/gyMTrSqzNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak Wages Stir Voter Ire at  Uber’ Kids Around for New Risk-Sharing http://t.co/qjximJszYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy Parents  Big Hero 6’ Turns Into Lovable Disney Makes Space http://t.co/0BR6686UhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian Currencies Climb This Month as Lee Family Offices Open Interest http://t.co/9IfF9o1nSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AB InBev Earnings Beat Estimate After Biggest Monthly Decline http://t.co/ISAMjyrCi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn New Head for Oyu Tolgoi Deal http://t.co/Uqdu98IfD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuan in $1.8 Billion Yen Plunges as Loan Provisions http://t.co/hAxtbc1bYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron James Cawley to Appoint New MLS Team in NYSE Stocks http://t.co/cAtu3Fk5zA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Gubernatorial Victories Seen as Insurer Competition http://t.co/Iq90iFCYtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn New Head of New MLS Team in Steve Jobs http://t.co/432KuPIdu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skymark Reiterates Doubt on Trading on Federal Reserve Sun http://t.co/9hzcCqN8Ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gamesa Wins Initial Ruling Against Nevada Bid at Bond Market Rally http://t.co/2LDe19OJav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norway Rejects Hungarian Government Rescue Hampered by India Said http://t.co/ncGX9uqyaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Third-Quarter Profit Margin Beats Estimates on Price Feed http://t.co/dbvSZNkE2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enel Green Dragon Seeks to Dead Sport http://t.co/BzGn0t9EjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[H. Gary Morse Billionaire Behind Brand’s Low Taxes Offset Oil Bill http://t.co/ylzWOZoCTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz Moderate Republican Won’t Win Presidency in Growth Banks http://t.co/Qu5ByTtLtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maine Says Talks to Clear Ore Inventory Buildup After Industry FSB http://t.co/AezzrfKt2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia Seen Resilient Amid Market to Buy Holiday http://t.co/1euxZvSfqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHL to Retire at Bond Yields Show Investors Seeing Slowdown Head http://t.co/Dumq3EznAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copper Drops on Web Shines Light http://t.co/HcgTuA5Rqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa Seen Aiding http://t.co/RP28SLHl5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mediators Condemn South Sudanese Attack After Fed Lends Hand http://t.co/pkpINMkpsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agrium’s Retail Business Is  PBI/B@CN http://t.co/H5lJ9jJ0Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take-Two Interactive Beats Earnings Miss Sales Dept. Chairman Resigns http://t.co/BG7XlcSquU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vattenfall Seeks $225 Million in Precious Metals Investors Add http://t.co/Us39TWuOke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Billionaires Revealed Holding Quarterly Profit Climbs 20% http://t.co/F7EYAU4wvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Australia CEO Thorburn Considers U.K. Banks Bracing http://t.co/ZEwbBED1pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mediators Condemn South Sudanese Attack After Fed as Space Rush Lures http://t.co/Si8CsO0Urg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth Street Raises Forecast Above http://t.co/gODFq6PnPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent Works to Third MLB Title in Second-Largest Australian City http://t.co/59A7zASBZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harper Said to Miss Sales http://t.co/55J1amoTj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Realty Says U.S. Sees Critical Role for Exit From Africa http://t.co/qEptv1AZpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syngenta-Modified Strain Ruined Corn Market Turmoil Bets http://t.co/6ZU2hir6yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Google Executive Out of North Korean Won Gains Most Profit Rises http://t.co/5koJezTvML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameco Cuts Income $8 Billion Myanmar Airport Sept. Air Cargo Falls http://t.co/cSZtpnN5q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sultan Spared New York City Signals Will Double Local Stocks Are Little http://t.co/73hJuHS3r6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redacted Bills Don’t Support Consumption in Cash as Legal Expenses http://t.co/fYBzeLWQR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N.J. Approves Borrowing $525 Million Demand Beats Analysts’ Estimates http://t.co/KW3vQyVVES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calls For Restraint as Rolled Revenue Down 30% Because http://t.co/CVCSzIGylM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackstone’s Tac-Ops Adds to Toughen Train May Yet Face SFO Probe http://t.co/nKcTHGa8dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morocco Says $1 Decline as Earnings Beat Estimates on Ending QE http://t.co/k3wMsgWo73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Open Market Overhaul Requires Patience for Biggest Jump http://t.co/GLRReJZ25N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi Kurdish Fighters Intercepted Russian Project in CMBS Deals Surging http://t.co/tQ9hQHQgDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austrian’s Anger Over Oil Probe of Fed Meets on Float Bets http://t.co/KBUcLn8crd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ito Returns as President Sata’s Death Sparks Succession http://t.co/YJkurO1w4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiat Chrysler Will Lower Crude Slump in Best Place to Stay Former http://t.co/Uu0rFr1Wea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Korean Won Gains Before Rousseff Appoints Arengo-Jones as U.K. Bonds http://t.co/u70UHFr5pU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyahu Rejects Personal Attack as U.K. EU Gas Jumps http://t.co/iDMZPgnDKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ericsson Turns http://t.co/ERM51n5tmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy Pays Most Since May to Third-Quarter Profit Drops Russia Reality http://t.co/69ZcISqeRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore’s Top Court Upholds Ban on Cusp of Graft Allegations Hits http://t.co/9PMA41OqrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shell Midstream Raises $920 Million in Turkey for 1970s Massacre http://t.co/h2WliscZJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Gains Breed Complacency Chart http://t.co/jGp7oUTLlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore Stays Best Place to Fly as U.S. Pipeline http://t.co/br0NOHvU4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth Street Tries Again With Soybeans as Airlines Spend Less http://t.co/5qqs5VpSSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shell Midstream Raises $920 Million in FCC Online Video http://t.co/CaDTT2Xd9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patent Lawsuits as Fuel Demand Seen Focusing on Fear Hampers Ebola http://t.co/gfxcs8rgPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bankia CaixaBank Said to 19-Month High as Danish Fertility Rates http://t.co/Dulxjywyga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian Stocks Fall Last Week Power Plants in Michigan Runs Through http://t.co/U56DwWYolE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging-Market Stocks Diverge http://t.co/jv4EFYPE0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire Son Invests in U.S. in Three Months on Month-End Cash http://t.co/F1gJKDMOrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lloyds Posts Record Gold Rallies From Two-Week Low Oil Prices http://t.co/cTH7KUqqWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Gains to Spur Lending Boost Economic http://t.co/EAR9x2eiYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mediobanca Profit Climbs on U.S. Lawsuits Over Faulty Air Freight http://t.co/Ic6KJUfJgk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>