<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Reform Lowers Costs for Businesses: 
	You might have heard about a partisan report on how the health care... http://t.co/smJavAKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks to Students in Iowa about Student Loan Rates: 

    President Barack Obama listens t... http://t.co/Ykg2jNXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 7.4 Million: 

	Approximately 7.4 million students will rack up an additional $1,000 in debt i... http://t.co/zMlbXRFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Budget Threatens Health Coverage and Insurance Protections: 
	This week, Republicans in Congress are ... http://t.co/Pjs2rsrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Dr. Biden at a Joining Forces Commemoration Event Live: 
	Dr. Biden participates in a Joining Forces anniv... http://t.co/NA5Qsw7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strengthening the Violence Against Women Act: 
	This week, the Senate will consider bipartisan legislation, intr... http://t.co/SdW293bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Visits the Everglades: 

    Vice President Joe Biden, Senator Bill Nelson, and Congre... http://t.co/pcwJK1J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Next Generation of Girls in STEM: 

	“Knowing that your ideas…might change the future is something that I ... http://t.co/pdh52wrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combating Sexual Assault in the United States Military: 
	Sexual assault is a pervasive problem in the United St... http://t.co/MqkeDeI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks at the U.S. Holocaust Memorial Musuem: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks... http://t.co/9K6uNc95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $1,000: 

	If Congress doesn’t act, interest rates will double on July 1 for more than 7.4 mil... http://t.co/RcwCwbCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Office Hours: Severe Weather Week: 
	Every year, thousands of people are impacted by severe weather thre... http://t.co/fp0xW4Hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline Tomorrow: Nominate a Hero for the Citizens Medal: 
	Over the past two years, President Obama has awarde... http://t.co/lEvilapK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pipeline Modernization Plan Means Safety and Jobs: 

    U.S. Department of Transportation Secretary Ray La... http://t.co/swShNijb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Child Deserves a 5th Birthday: 
	Today the U.S. Agency for International Development (USAID) and several p... http://t.co/8a5bE1u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preventing and Responding to Atrocities: An Interactive Discussion: 
	This morning, President Obama spoke at the... http://t.co/wXgo8GDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: The Obamas Visit Yellowstone National Park: 
	In the summer of 2009, President Obama took his... http://t.co/abKa37UD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup Stories: Fast Forward, With a Few Speed Bumps: 
	"Always be humble and don’t let anybody say you don't w... http://t.co/qsLdLW5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presenting the First Green Ribbon Schools: 
	Today I had the honor to name 78 schools as the first-ever U.S. Dep... http://t.co/wS4paiVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting the Air You Breathe: 

	Did you know?

	To better protect the health of American families and the a... http://t.co/9VzscZFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating National Parks Week: 

    Young girls hike a trail at the Olympic National Park, which is west... http://t.co/3eHM7Rxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Calling on Congress to Prevent Student Interest Rates from Doubling: 
	President Obama believes ... http://t.co/AB1pGG1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's Message to the People of Sudan and South Sudan: 

	In these videotaped remarks, President Ob... http://t.co/2s95s5nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes the Wounded Warrior Project's Soldier Ride: 

    President Barack Obama cheers on... http://t.co/UAMyOmrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: “All We Have Is Each Other”: 

	A quick look at everything that happened this week on WhiteHouse... http://t.co/NOPcwsdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Establishes Fort Ord as a National Monument: 

    President Barack Obama signs a proclamat... http://t.co/22bRzTqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the Conversation: Honoring the Pledge of 'Never Again': 
	On Monday, April 23, President Obama will speak a... http://t.co/krHPYEvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a Small Business that has been helped by SBA? Don’t miss our National Small Business Week Video Contest:... http://t.co/8mLiYzPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connecting Grads to Resources to Help You Start a Business: 
	Ed note: This is was originally posted on the Smal... http://t.co/lRyygx0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 4/20/12 or "Roll Tide": 

	This week, the President visited one of the Sunshine State's largest ... http://t.co/uGgA4fTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crimson Tide Rolls Into the White House: 

    President Barack Obama is presented with a jersey and helmet... http://t.co/KPDB0ctT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning the Unemployment Program into a Reemployment Program: 
	Ed note: this post was originally published on W... http://t.co/Yd54CAlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 4.05 Million Records Released: In September 2009, the President announced that -- for the first time... http://t.co/ZxhgKGjmwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking Off Military Family Month: Throughout our history, members of our military have put their lives on the... http://t.co/8RRcnSQj5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Plans and Making Progress: How the Federal Government Can Lead by Example: 
Five years ago this month, ... http://t.co/NUTgpzf7OX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About New Rules to Protect Students from Poor-Performing Career College Programs: Yester... http://t.co/J55t1AIUDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama on Immigration Reform: "I Am Not Going to Give Up This Fight Until It Gets Done": 
Watch on Yo... http://t.co/UoVpg02j04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chart(s) of the Week: American Manufacturing is Growing Stronger Every Day: "When our manufacturing base is st... http://t.co/eWPjOzYkXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow Along: The Cabinet Visits Manufacturers Across the Country: Today is National Manufacturing Day, and mo... http://t.co/09PyNLbn3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in September: With today’s report, America’s businesses extended the longest streak o... http://t.co/vTRAZ4lgwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 10/03/14 or, "If the Body is Strong": This week, the President convened summits on global publ... http://t.co/m1N0mh2icn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring 9/11 Through Service: 

    President Barack Obama greets volunteers at Food &amp; Friends during a ... http://t.co/fL3nySIuDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Provides an Update on the Latest in Iraq and Ferguson, Missouri: This afternoon at the White H... http://t.co/wSXchEDtOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join a Tumblr Q&amp;A on the President's New Executive Order to Protect LGBT Workers &amp; Expanding Opportunity for t... http://t.co/GL8Sx7FHWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Apollo 11 Mission: 45 Years Later: Forty-five years ago today, two American astronauts -- Buzz Aldrin and ... http://t.co/zP9RZjQScJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The First Significant Legislative Reform of Our Job-Training System in a Number of Years:: 
Watch on YouTube
W... http://t.co/NxZa2j3231]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Case You Missed It: LGBT Pride at the White House: 
Yesterday, for the sixth time since taking office, Pres... http://t.co/z4XWT8ogWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court's Hobby Lobby Decision: 
Watch on YouTube
Today, the Supreme Court ruled on the much-publici... http://t.co/B3twSFDyHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks on Immigration Reform: 

    President Barack Obama, with Vice President Joe Biden... http://t.co/UKWbjUASeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring Dr. Maya Angelou: Dr. Maya Angelou, whose timeless works such as I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings enco... http://t.co/9hetgaffwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Supporting America's Students: In this week's address, President Obama underscored the importa... http://t.co/qAi3r99CjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap-Up: POTUS in Europe, OK Go, Power Plants, and More: There was a lot of action this week, both in W... http://t.co/PKkCEUCJ2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks at 9/11 Museum Dedication: "A Sacred Place of Healing and of Hope": 

    Presiden... http://t.co/NWF2dBawNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President and Vice President’s 2013 Financial Disclosure Forms: Today, the President and Vice President re... http://t.co/g9IcfBUFED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Is It So Important to Rebuild America's Roads and Bridges?: 

    President Barack Obama delivers rem... http://t.co/jSgJfL0lsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marking the 50th Anniversary of the Civil Rights Act at the LBJ Presidential Library: Ed. note: Tune in to whi... http://t.co/nD7BjoDpZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vice President and Dr. Biden’s Support for Community Colleges and Apprenticeship Programs: 

    Vice... http://t.co/9WrzbvLoxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We the Geeks: Women Role Models: 

    Ma’kese Kesley takes a picture as President Barack Obama delivers ... http://t.co/THMh0oi52z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Economic Case for Raising the Minimum Wage: In his 2014 State of the Union address, President Obama announ... http://t.co/WwA8IQ7NjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 01/03/14: Best of the West (Wing Week) 2013: As we move into 2014 we'd like to take a quick loo... http://t.co/fR0AlajsRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: The 2013 National Christmas Tree Lighting: 

    The National Christmas Tree is illuminated d... http://t.co/A8yyABHUmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States Releases its Second Open Government National Action Plan: Since his first full day in office... http://t.co/PJxw8L0Pgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 12/05/13 or, "Olde English": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's hap... http://t.co/uWd80ogTVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in November: With solid job growth in November – in addition to strong data on manufa... http://t.co/d9Zy9YQQfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Delivers a Statement on the Passing of Nelson Mandela: This afternoon, from the White House Br... http://t.co/GI8W8BqqhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Time is Now: President Obama Meets with Business Leaders on Immigration Reform: 

    President Barac... http://t.co/QxI6RAcgbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Celebrates Diwali at the White House: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama joins stu... http://t.co/fPCOivFxK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Let’s Get Back to the Work of the American People: In this week’s address, President Obama dis... http://t.co/KfdXCvc6gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Security Advisor Susan Rice Speaks on Syria: Tomorrow evening, the President will address the nation ... http://t.co/upgN6pmtN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing the 2013 Presidential Medal of Freedom Recipients: 

    President Barack Obama talks with f... http://t.co/2XRjZzdmHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcasting a Message of Gratitude: 

    President Barack Obama greets U.S. troops following his remarks ... http://t.co/DypVxY5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Honoring Our Fallen Heroes this Memorial Day: 
	President Obama pays tribute to our men and wome... http://t.co/p95Ywbud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Corps: Helping Feed the Future: 

    Feed the Future kits that Peace Corps volunteers utilize in the... http://t.co/FtozBkDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Remembers: 

    Vice President Joe Biden and Dr. Jill Biden address the Tragedy Assistance Program... http://t.co/3oKdG43k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: President Obama Tweets to America: 

  Click here to see the video. 

	Here's a quick glimp... http://t.co/dbBlwfun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.3 million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/L8Uia2ZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 5/25/2012 or "We Are Not Meant to Walk This Road Alone": 
	This week, the President announced a ... http://t.co/HbcCrZPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Thirteen Presidents Mark Memorial Day: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	Memorial Day ... http://t.co/bliP8LRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Big Week for Joining Forces: 
	Through Joining Forces, Americans continue to step up and respond to the First ... http://t.co/68H6SvM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Cybersecurity Capability in the Electricity Sector: 
	Yesterday, in partnership with industry, we took ... http://t.co/aOlOEZDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statement from the White House on Berthing of Dragon Spacecraft with the International Space Station: 
	Followin... http://t.co/voZyKI8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Talks Clean Energy in Iowa: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks urging Congress t... http://t.co/JNdpqlyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out with Small Business Administrator Karen Mills: 

	Yesterday, SBA Administrator Karen Mills, and th... http://t.co/LKHU0wwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Talks #CongressToDoList on Twitter: 
	Yes, President Obama was on Twitter today – taking your qu... http://t.co/xlaehsjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Job Seekers to Job Creators: 
	In his 2012 State of the Union Address, President Obama stated his goal to t... http://t.co/ga2uHiGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Step Forward in Fighting Food Stamp Fraud: 
	At USDA’s Food and Nutrition Service we are committed to keep... http://t.co/AePx9nMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Case You Missed It: Broad Bipartisan Support to Extend the Production Tax Credit: 
	Tomorrow the President wi... http://t.co/9YS2VZo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Touts a New American Century to Air Force Grads: 
	Four years ago, when President Obama made his... http://t.co/ZRkaqA4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SBA Announces National Small Business Week Video Contest Winners: 
	At the U.S. Small Business Administration, w... http://t.co/a0z6pbuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Nancy-Ann DeParle: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government ... http://t.co/O2CQmrmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone can find a Way to Honor our Service Members: 
	This op-ed by Dr. Jill Biden was first published in The ... http://t.co/jljj2PO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2010 Census: On-Time, Under-Budget, and Extremely Accurate: 
	Ed note: this was originally posted on The Commerc... http://t.co/cJjschGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roadmap for a Digital Government: 
	When the Internet revolution arrived in the 1990s, the U.S. Government embra... http://t.co/MIk7b4Yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted: A Few Good Women and Men to Serve as Presidential Innovation Fellows: 
	Today, we are very excited to be... http://t.co/vYwRm3Ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ongoing Commitment, a Bright Future: 

    Darla Armstrong is one 25 AmeriCorps members still serving in... http://t.co/UWKYeIg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask an Entrepreneur:  How Do Small Businesses Benefit from Federal Research Grants?: 
	Ed note: In honor of Smal... http://t.co/o2aR7wVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number of the Day: 82 years: 

	Of all the incredible stories to... http://t.co/MqaCjaoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Andy Katz: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to work ... http://t.co/Y4PimojY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JudyCare: Focusing on Fighting Cancer, Without Fear of Lifetime Insurance Caps: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted... http://t.co/Ob0LfAWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Returns to Joplin: 

    President Barack Obama delivers the commencement address to the gr... http://t.co/zF41m1I5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>