<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gd question! MT "@BoughtonLaw: Why would a U.S. resident renounce Cdn citizenship? http://t.co/5EJR4jvv2R by @tonywilsonlaw #citizenship"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danke Natascha!"@lawyer_marketer: Legal Marketing-Radar is out! http://t.co/DCoxKroYrI Stories via @lawyerPR @StefanieMarrone"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx Colin! "@lawyerPR: Should legal marketing be outsourced? http://t.co/Nc0d8VF1ed #bclaw #bclegal #legalmarketing"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should legal marketing be outsourced? http://t.co/WmDD6w1Kkp #bclaw #bclegal #legalmarketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I happened upon this little sign in my 'hood. Made me smile. http://t.co/V1Ksieq04c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend or Scrimp? How to best use your marketing budget http://t.co/WmDD6w1Kkp #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! "@nhouseinsight: NHOUSE INSIGHT From Marketing Pros is out! http://t.co/SsL1P4ZfZ3 Stories via @rsigroche @lawyerPR"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do we get our lawyers to develop business? http://t.co/WmDD6w1Kkp #bclegal #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law Firm Marketing - Are you getting business from your efforts? http://t.co/WmDD6w1Kkp #bclaw #legalmarketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CityofVancouver: Holiday garbage piling up? Help is on the way: city crews are doing extra pickups Dec 26 &amp; 28. http://t.co/fuQbY0RnUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahhh :) "@GlobalBC: Metro Vancouver to see snow overnight and into Friday morning http://t.co/BgtvYXYGu4"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinokeefe: Ill-timed tweets by prosecutor don’t merit reversal, appeals court says - @abajournal http://t.co/XqykDfYCYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Osler_Law: @legalpost recognizes Osler’s Calgary office for its $30,000 donation to the flood-ravaged Calgary Zoo last summer.  http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Garin: "Without deviation from the norm progress is not possible." 

~Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McQuarrieHunter 's COO Catherine Jacobs a finalist in @SBofT #SurreyWIB awards corp leadership! So very proud of her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverSun She *is* Greg's replacement, so I'm good, tx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverSun Greg Ryan's replacement. Called Shakuntla in mktg dept directly + she connected me to Janet. Diff to find humans at Sun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @VancouverSun why so difficult to find the replacement for a departed display ad rep?? Frustrated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LienY: Advice for young women: grow skin like a rhinoceros, take criticism seriously but not personally, when rejected - get back up #v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful "@JaredLeto: In case you missed it, here’s my #Oscar speech in full, as I wrote it. - http://t.co/AxChcLsBxt"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefJimChu Wonderful!! I'd call it a home run tonight, then! Keep up the great work :) !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefJimChu Evidently you sure do! Sure hope the VPD also felt the love tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefJimChu Congrats on a terrific night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChiefJimChu: Sarah McLachlan performing with #VPD Pipe Band at #NightPatrolGala http://t.co/cpM2nbUQfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBA_BC: CBABC 2014 Directory - comprehensive &amp; up-to-date listing of all lawyers in BC - Available In print or Online - http://t.co/y7T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VPD Foundation Gala's 1200 attendees spell bound by Sarah McLaughlin performance tonight. Gifted. Talented. Perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Police pipe band bring a lump to my throat. So special and moving. http://t.co/rjsZ1Y8hoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Pipe Band - 1st in canada + 3rd in world - perform at Vancouver Police Gala. Celebrating 100 yrs. Impressive! http://t.co/NyxsVYJ3Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Police Gala about to start with sold out crowd! http://t.co/bHHt8ucwX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx @Lexpert -- appreciate the link!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best ski weekend EVER! Realized tho... Borders are like puppies. They go, go, go and just drop + stop in place when tired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganNewsYVR Volume of wine consumed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kingsgatemall: Any one of our 4 parking lots make a great place to sit in your car and cry and ponder how your choices in life lead you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law firms glued too! "@TheEllenShow: My staff was glued to the Olympic hockey game. Congrats, Canadians! An epic performance. #USAvsCanada"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AluvionLaw Thanks! Hope you enjoyed this piece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! Part II up next @slaw_dot_ca "@bLegalMarketing: Legal Gift Cards &amp; Legal Asst Mktg http://t.co/7Drt2LAzOZ (thx @AttyMktng &amp; @lawyerPR)"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paddleink: "Play Like Girls." #hockey #sochi http://t.co/b7pRVI2s8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx @lexpert mag for the interview on law firm branding. Julius wrote great (subscr. only) piece in Feb issue. #bclaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drivebc what's best route from vanc to vernon today - via hwy#1 or #3? Asking for a friend. Thx!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power coming on very soon says crew! Thx @bchydro. Source was loose tree branch at my neighbour's house. http://t.co/mfGTw7vX1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WanderlustMegan thx Megan!! Very helpful. Cool map.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power out :( btwn 25th + 13th Cambie + Ontario. You're working on this right @bchydro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBA_BC: Deadline extended for the upcoming Annual Women Lawyers Retreat! http://t.co/RtYoZhx2bP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow and the call today @proctor_jason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esilawsoftware best if I call you. What number is best?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know of a CRM (client database software) system that plays nicely with @esilawsoftware?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapped lips? Coconut oil spells immense relief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillRako: Whoa. MT @ohioaj French journo Agathe Logeart (in Ohio for a story on capital punishment) said France used guillotine for las…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ontraccoach: LEGAL FUTURES Unprecedented consolidation, ABSs and only the global or niche surviving - http://t.co/mfJEp5QCqt #thelawyer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @news1130traffic: #SkyTrain problems heading into Downtown Vancouver http://t.co/lrfHUU8JtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawsonLundell Loved it! You knocked it out of the park today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the @lawsonlundell ad in today's Van Sun, pg C3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning approach to @LawsonLundell partner anncmt ad!  Congrats to my colleague Susan F + team (SW, too)! http://t.co/2NOmPCl75M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @news1130traffic: 9:09 There's a crash on the #LionsGate Bridge southbound in the middle lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tla_bc: 7 different stages of what your injury claim may have to go through.  http://t.co/0FleDl29HX via @InjuryLawyersBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: Olympic statue finally installed in downtown Vancouver four years later - http://t.co/BoPhs2PIPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeffreybgray: My story from this morning's paper: Troubled Heenan Blaikie says it is going through a 'major restructuring'  http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessiJohnson: “You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough.”  ― Mae West]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @news1130traffic: 1:37 #BCHWY1 westbound in #VANCOUVER watch for DEBRIS before the Cassiar Tunnel. There is a door on the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MillerThomson: Minimum Wage in Ontario to Rise to $11.00/hr. Alex Heaslip comments in our Labour and Employment Blog. http://t.co/ktOau…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JJESearch: New exclusive #legalmarketing career opps in San Fran &amp; San Diego for @Orrick &amp; @DLA_Piper! Here's the scoop: http://t.co/oo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CLEBC: Sale Ends Today! Supreme Court Chambers Orders - 20% off - http://t.co/ZFpivAk20D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bday card for my nephew cracks me up and makes me uncomfortable. Those faces!  (Credit: Close to Home) http://t.co/iFnlFmd1oO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use a mktg pro to help u evaluate advtg sales pitches for similar reason we advise clients to get a lawyer for a car accident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WestCoast_LEAF: Check out #equalitybfast sponsor @Canadianlabour first national study of impact of domestic violence in the workplace h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawSocietyofBC: Law Society welcomes public input as it considers new law school at Trinity Western University. http://t.co/obfps7B05B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithhardie @MEKowalski Exactly! Wondering what the mktg strategy is (or isn't!) to warrant such massive spend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breath-taking - large law firm ads still in yellow pages book. Some must be spending $150k+/yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers: Involve your assistant to tip scales in your favor http://t.co/6hgVlqO3UY #bclegal #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arg. Service @cibc for this 30 yr+ client w perfect history substandard. Policies shld not prevail over risk-free requests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No worries @tonywilsonlaw - it was well worth it! A very fun read indeed (even if at yer own expense!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ditto! "@Kariboyle: Happy bday Tony -here's to many more! RT@tonywilsonlaw: A life half-done or is it half-started? http://t.co/JNI0MlM01k”"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverSun frt pg story about loss + @RoyalColumbian so sad for all. Infant survival rates v high at RCH. Thoughts w Rivas family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is handling your online content marketing? Most firms can't keep up on the own. Get help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UinvitedU: Creativity takes courage.

~ Henri Matisse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD  Go fetch!!"@CBCNews: Dog thief caught on camera at Vancouver tattoo parlour http://t.co/QAwhREjjPd"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattyMC22 just tryin' to woo you west, my friend! Happy Easter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattyMC22 O.M.G. Brutal! Here's what I picked from my backyard last weekend! http://t.co/9fM4cuMt99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AirCanada: Want to win 2 tickets to any @AirCanada destination? Use #ACGoFar to enter and see how far you could go! Details: http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Pattymc22 how you enjoying the snow? :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lining up now!"@Miss604: Army and Navy Shoe Sale - Coming Up April 30th http://t.co/DazFD0Apm2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BIVCommunity: BIV welcomes Tako Van Popta, Lawyer, @McQuarrieHunter as moderator of our Sry BES:  Business Growth Breakfast May 6 http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OsgoodeNews: We're offering a Free LSAT Prep Course again. Know someone who may be interested? Please forward them our link: http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mediatebcsoc, you just proved my point *beautifully*! ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great team! MT "@mediatebcsoc: Admin Coordinator Mediate BC Roster Family Support &amp; Admin Coord. ADR #mediation #job http://t.co/AZTxX5mGiZ"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZahraAlani: #Vancouver Know this couple? SD card found. Let's get theses pics back to them! @CTVVancouver  @VancityBuzz http://t.co/7Hj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview (no surprise!)"@CKNW: Right now - @simisara980 chats w @LaineyGossip about her novel, 'Listen To The Squawking Chicken'."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: Presenting the Maddies: Five very real ad campaigns from the world of Mad Men http://t.co/bnCZxuYbQt From @GlobeArts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CKNW: BC Law Society gives green light to law school at TWU http://t.co/y7sEu6NdSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @christyclarkbc: My Canada includes Quebec. Congrats Premier-elect @phcouillard! Looking forward to working with you. http://t.co/gT6WUc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CLEBC: We're hiring a temporary Customer Service Representative. Apply by April 8! http://t.co/2H4XZL4rqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kdawg39: We're hiring at @globalnews Interactive Developer, Global News at Shaw Communications http://t.co/kY66wflpR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GinaRubel @KHRsolutions Great topic! Sorry to miss it. #LMA14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @audrain: we're hiring a Publicist at Penguin Canada - any PR experience/background welcome! More details here: http://t.co/lHz9jBurAg @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MEKowalski: Hahaha :) "@ScottHierath: This is funny whatever your leanings might be. #ableg http://t.co/RH4TCNAtDU"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcfifth: If you have a story you think needs to be told, get in touch with us by email at fifthtips@cbc.ca #cbcfifth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OptinetSystems Sure does. Same goes for twitter - should be part of a biz listening strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OptinetSystems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OptinetSystems Yup! So funny, but sadly still so true. I'm still having this discussion w *some* clients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mjcastonguay: MISSING: KARL BRESLAUER last seen Fri 8300 blk Beatrice St. Has Alzheimers. See him, stay with him call 911 pls RT http:/…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>