<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/sGJJUtfxPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/Bzq7bITQ28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/OheBwEeQY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/jiyo6LeIGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/GVRWEVgwHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/zGgkf1op5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/Fr9ccTyEOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/M9rEnvITYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/LbvfNj9ftz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/CDoZV6DB0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/gVFYMIRVRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/6FeFUXlXbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/DhZnUnq1dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/JttLTjH8tT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/e1yve9NjIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/oCn88xIczy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/4XKMwwWTxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/kzhHfC0DBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/EP1lAB6oPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/ADCumjj8Ip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't tell how much spirit a team has until it starts losing. - Rocky Colavito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/F3WNqGzR5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/Hgy48EX1cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/TOccdaxgpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/Whkx61aqXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9m44uunrFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/sR74J6SBuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/w8Q9VHt8sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/dRDYMdYYgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/oZ6aU34mAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/9qY19NsVG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/zAGChxgvS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/mR0fhg0DLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/yZGmmlTw7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/vgzoqPggZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Cicerone Beer?  http://t.co/NWOetp5Xh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/S6Cc5GRq2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/aZGiDlmVGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/sdKKQgNTQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Setup an iPad Speaker System  http://t.co/IAAo39LfKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/Pmm1XITniP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/txiUoUJL68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/Uy5Q6E2sl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/H13t35Cgsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/soMsq8BUtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/ixqkfiLz9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/8EsXZBRt8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/6xBig5O4Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got rock 'n' roll in my blood. - William Shatner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/8GRfYtO506]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/sLNmgZETZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/SgxIPxMQNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/xM1BZ4zLxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>