<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/x1QS5Qab5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/g2eHA4VSyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/yHJrlPcJIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/ecoYKYFN8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/GF51uldsCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/QhjGFOBvCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/Lc4ODqN5sP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/gXKai8b6Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/9bGNS7vpvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/xz2K3IiUNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/IKmsJ3Xs64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/phHPl9z2vS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/LSHZjBT3va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/kl61Ivlxx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/1sMP9sov5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/QavW73j5jM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/7bYBiJZGuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/HNvoQSg5f2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/g1Zv5hHaxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/WrgjcCGUdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/CSxGD4tXp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/ICifDZwWgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/4HPauqwKBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/tgMxagZyJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/pN15GDDbWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/fNNyAhj571]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/4d2xa71Cgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/p1WBLGG9U5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/n2JFzFdKGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/uco579LIf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/oQbCy3CyES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/ptG1zKMFZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/LpwCc9H2KA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/Ghsio8Zlcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/B63Q7p3h4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/MWbJyXuho7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/hMTMktKnnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/uQVFVdXwDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/g2eHA4VSyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/wKU5Wx0p0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/ybrfmtsSL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/7OZWvYAeA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/lKWGB2dYAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/prlUKja5My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/MO3JtgNrys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/LSHZjBT3va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/PwzX666ndk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/oKXEPykdPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/C3RBomDcyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/KPB0lVO3IR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>