<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/E7BBPk6Ti1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/cW3scpEBGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/iWsDHnvfTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/rdeFOyxUdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/fQAeROwB8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/Kqyzwl5NNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/ffcR4cVDH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/QOeCw2YqfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/wxONwLbN7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/rgLhyq34hJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/LWWaYBcdDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/dNjIIU2pDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/6Fidkn6K8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/xR5bj0keGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/2xEbLENReR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/KJAUZ9VfBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/bkpMYdtA2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/CkFcLoxzp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/X2KIr827Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/2nvPvw5PRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/mPhgGVmHg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/GW6uABfi1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/4LKM6zdzbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/KQCIsCQndZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/6LdvQ7cnDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/KuQ9BjLI5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/2fnM3PSPPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird of paradise alights only upon the hand that does not grasp. - John Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/zpzbNTTTE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/3Wc6YorQoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your time...don't live too fast, troubles will come and they will pass. - Simple Man - Lynyrd Skynyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/0n2K99ehYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/5sbIFbgAFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/5AsoMwmGWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/6dqZwYC3PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/DpzbM1fyiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/aqieZNOWCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/b4FOwbDMqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/LDST1A6E1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/a0E4E7sABV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/Kw0zK40Tiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/GSpwBoWkok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/5W9mPrB7l9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/K02JbhRDQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/9bcMy6WCNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/HjrMHyd3Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/MjMW88e8JJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>