<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/Oe5Kb2UbjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/UsFPJ23M42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/UmPEoQD5ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/lc9rJmmi6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/Glmac1yYeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/M2a4ETmUVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/eCiXZ2ibt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/iZjsaPmxOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/8zZpXugLDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/aGo7VffyzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/wrvZn3dusH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/YWIdFgUJOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/UmPEoQD5ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/lsBRgZNjvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/hVNo5zsZKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/lDjweC0hEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/vwEG0cgYZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop earning when you do what you love. - Asha Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/QYcZSopMBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/jIGTfjmPQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/hpXe0eBdUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/cp0iaYLBkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/cPHqvHhGQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/lDjweC0hEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/2ZjBLr7bee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/WF8uIF5wzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/uDUXgZKUPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/z7cSS3JueE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/dssreWyVbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/iBZv5739XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/D8y3rMc4tY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/886B7FrXb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these spooky skull candles!  http://t.co/uKhUCL6cA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/aT5wzB0g9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/a4h7zZ001e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/OLtzOzZX6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/UmPEoQD5ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/JujnBhkMzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/cKPcsqgOCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/iZjsaPmxOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/WkTsQcrnjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/YAuakjlRTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/jFqtkBALb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/DMoJAG367m]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>