<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThermalByline That is one #cutestaffy ! Do you know about the search for Britain's cutest staffy?! find it here http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amy_lauren_xx Is Teddy a model?! He should enter our search for Britain's cuttest staffy #cutestaffy. Enter here http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethHutton_ Duke is one cute dog! Is he a staffy? If you should enter him in this contest to find Britain's cuttest http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbiejaynex OMG that is such a #cutestaffy. We are looking for Britain's Cuttest Staffy - you should enter him! http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlyenever09 thats a #cutestaffy! have you entered it to online comp  http://t.co/yRDtzaZg ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryCloudfoot hi Harry, phone cut out, let me know when is good on sunday? Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightowl400 adorable! I used to think these dogs were unfriendly now I love em! #cutestaffy did you enter online??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper fine ..except I'm in airport going to India and they tell me I have wrong visa!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At airport about to go to India to help stray dogs and I find out I have no visa. I AM IDIOT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pocketouthouse @DogsTrust so cute!!! http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper hey, thanks for tweeting as always!!! How things??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feelgoodprizes @DogsTrust @markbisset_83 thanks greg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PricklyEmu @DogsTrust what a great cross! his speckles match the ground! Loving it! thanks for posting! http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rockyrover30  ahhhhh too cute!!! thanks for posting! http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedogreporter thanks for mentioning!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mahonjayne @DogsTrust ha!!! this is great!! Did you enter online http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  ?? #cutestaffy He looks so blissed out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedogreporter: fav dog photographer @MartinUsborne is having an awesome photo contest to help #staffys in the UK!http://t.co/ixgsYm ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gillsybear @marcthevet PS.. did you enter this on the website? so good! http://t.co/fqQJH5oR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAngDarling Loving this! Did you enter online? (I'm the photographer running the comp). thanks for posting! Tell all!  #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireGoodi adorable!!! #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet @shorehamshinobi Gorgeous dog. Thanks for posting for tweeting marc!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fitzroy_Boy: @Jarbysaj Look - RT @DogsTrust we're looking for Britain's Cutest Staffy to raise awareness. Please RT! #cutestaffy htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gillsybear @marcthevet OMG, I helped set up the campaign and love this! I made a book of dogs in cars, see my twitter page! #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlyenever09 @marcthevet adorable!! #cutestaffy (I'm the dog photographer helping to run the staffy campaign). Thanks for posting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@windsorclaire Susie is a cutie! I'm the photographer who is running the campaign. Hope I can photograph her!!! #cutestaffy, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightowl400 he's a cute one! #cutestaffy I'm the photographer who helped start this campaign. Thanks for posting!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kanesmammy03 @marcthevet WOW!! that is one #cutestaffy Even with out the jumper. I want to photograph it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crow release!! After 4 days in a chimney and 1 week fattening up at recue centre #yeartohelp http://t.co/Xen8Sa9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to pick up and release that crow that was stuck in chimney #yeartohelp . Pictures in few hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice! I took a photo of woman's dog for rehoming. Not only has it got a home now she's fundraising for me! #yeartohelp http://t.co/j2S75wIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaGavin sure thing. Send me your address and will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crow that was stuck in sooty chimney (last week) has made full recovery. I shall set him free thursday in Waterloo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogsTrust we're looking for Britain's Cutest Staffy to raise awareness. Please RT! #cutestaffy http://t.co/fqQJH5oR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for Britain's cutest staffy dog. Prizes! Enter pic here http://t.co/fqQJH5oR : or twitpic #cutestaffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLBGallery @ParisPhotoFair yes, was a great fair, all the books we had there sold fast! Thanks to all for coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tackybeats thank you Paul!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaGavin thanks for the kind post! Hope you enjoyed Paris Photo, let me know if you want a book to review, see you soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to photo panel discussion I'm on today at a group show - animals and art - hackney picture house, mare st, 2pm today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Publishers say all Dogs in Cars books gone - after 4 weeks! I have remaining signed copies http://t.co/yqo03VJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book signing in ParisPhoto, stand ee3, final copies, print run almost sold out http://t.co/mIhjA2OZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am feeling like an aching sick rat after flu jab. Thought it was a cure. Just Say No to needles, kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darlingdog oh no not on my site, go to http://t.co/SNqb82sv ! Let me know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Broadbentius @sophiebindloss thanks for mentioning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsMeOrTheDog am big fan! Just launched campaign to find cutest staffy dog to raise awareness for abandoned staffs http://t.co/fqQJH5oR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upload a pic of your cute staffy to http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  or twitpic #cutestaffy. Looking for Britain's cutest staffy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/KQDXrjzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsMalone OMG she would be perfect...and in the knitted top! Can you enter her to the site http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kazster1981 SUPER CUTE!!! Can you upload to the website??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darlingdog thanks for that!!! brilliant. All money raised goes to helping rehome dogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking for britain's cutest staffy dog. It's a photo comp anyone can enter http://t.co/fqQJH5oR  pass the word on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be signing copies of my new photobook about Dogs in Cars at ParisPhoto this thursday 4pm, stand EE3, see you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and nice in BW too... http://t.co/VzJs4XaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autumn on the Heath this weekend. INSANE colours. http://t.co/EVbCgUFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crow is safe at sanctuary and expected to make full recovery. White wings reveal it was runt http://t.co/MK2syowU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoKelion done. Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stuck in traffic and rain and darkness on streatham high st with dying crow on seat-  my new life of compassion! http://t.co/EXtqSRRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crow out of chimney. V weak. Off to sanctuary bloody miles away. Wet monday http://t.co/4lxvdVwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to rescue a crow stuck in my friends chimney - and that's not a euphemism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 birds saved, better than nowt http://t.co/XyThlGBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught two more birds, did one interview on itv news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two saved so far http://t.co/K6VyhH8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far spotted 5 dead birds but nine alive http://t.co/RwAkckve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arriving in Dorset to rescue seabirds covered in oil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day of insanity:  police, suitcases and broken teeth. http://t.co/pWwpKDkZ #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarkingBlondes thanks for being judges! Cutest Staffy winners now announced here! http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterEgan6 thank you for your wonderful help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterEgan6: Here are the results for the competition http://t.co/xn6Xk0oZ all who entered are winners as far as I'm concerned, even  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcthevet cutest staffy results announced here! thanks for being a judge http://t.co/yRDtzaZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROOF: Staffies are gorgeous dogs. Winners of Britain's Cutest Staffies announced here! http://t.co/yRDtzaZg Thank you for entering..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Albert dock , liverpool , so pretty on second most depressing day of year http://t.co/qsWKCuSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jon_tonks ha!!! Too good... Posed or found?? Hope all well. Any update on book?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a little snow in London.... http://t.co/TDymAdNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M00seline thanks for this. Truly horrible but powerful. Are you involved in this at all? China is tricky for a westerner to investigate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SHADOWWABBITS8 thank you for reading it. Moose is covered in snow and sends his woofs! Glad you enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CUsborne I don't believe it ....you're on tweeter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Joseph. 86 today! But back in hospital again. Will get out tomorrow. Video here http://t.co/nVO2fNZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first dog painting. Of Duke, Ann's familie's dog http://t.co/kst1rHaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stellakalaw you are most welcome! thankYOU for your support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Janetarrant glad you love!! Merry Xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julienewton_ @lostinagoodway @tlbgallery see you there, should be great! Wonderful gallery in west London]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Robbiegittins: All I want for Christmas is 'The silence of dogs in cars' by @martinusborne
Looks major. Not sure if he is the Daddy  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last chance to enter BRITAIN'S CUTEST STAFFY -competition closes xmas day, win a professional photoshoot with your dog! http://t.co/EEIS0zZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhotoAdvocate: Photographer's Portfolio:
Martin Usborne  @MartinUsborne
http://t.co/cJ2pMiqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAY 97: MAGGOT DOG IS SAVED!!!  read here http://t.co/8RrKEUgW http://t.co/iFUfG0Fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiegittins yes it is!! All books sold out, second print run in 2013 but you can get signed first editions from here http://t.co/GeByS3qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when you meet a mass dog-killer and he smiles at you? http://t.co/UYW48zVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithHopkin glad you like!! Thanks for all your support! Merry Xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAngDarling  no...but you'll find out what happens in my blog in next few days...quite a story!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring a motorbike and pursuing a tipoff about place that dogs are allegedly killed in India- may just be hearsay #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great Dave" needs your help! Check him out http://t.co/MM9HUwI9  #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAR_updates thank you, very kind to say so. Maybe in a small way it helps....here's hoping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dragonfly_Laura thank you from Moose and me!!! Woof woof Laura!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dragonfly_Laura: I just read My Name is Moose by @MartinUsborne and I nearly choked from laughing so much. Brilliant. The funniest a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAR_updates thank you for posting this, it makes all the difference. It's damn tough out here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IAR_updates: Brilliant post about the stray dog situation in India, worth a read: A Year to Help » Day 85: Angry http://t.co/BJzxF7N ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonkristinsson Yay! You are most welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute pup found by side of indian road - making recovery http://t.co/dwbHFhqo http://t.co/kjVjDf7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pawsandpurrs thank you for mentioning!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Pawsandpurrs: RT @martinusborne do you know a #cutestaffy? If so please tell them to enter comp to find Britain's Cutest Staffy http ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent most of day in forest looking for this dying dog - argh, back tomorrow. We think it has days left...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>