<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Watching television and surfing the Internet are really excellent practice for being dead." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything you do is a self-portrait." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't know what you want, you end up with a lot you don't." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." - Charles Bukowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @chuckpalahniuk @BretEastonEllis @WelshIrvine @DougCoupland @CraigClevenger @stephengjones72 @xDisappearHerex @brandontietz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is just what human beings do--turn objects into people, people into objects." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious 'American Psycho' parody with Hewey Lewis &amp; Weird Al Yancovic...  http://t.co/cnSURED3tE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By the time you read this, you'll be older than you remember." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first time you meet that someone special, you can count on them one day being dead and in the ground." 
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are always spraying the air with their moods. Their car stereos, broadcasting their grief or joy or anger all over the neighborhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Torture is torture and humiliation is humiliation only when you choose to suffer." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Please fasten your seatbelts as we begin our terminal descent into oblivion." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes your best way to deal with shit is to not hold yourself as such a precious little prize." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @imanaboat: @PalahniukQuote #invisiblemonsters http://t.co/VJp8bUcw41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are not special. We are not crap or trash, either. We just are. We just are, and what happens just happens." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would pay snakes to bite her." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Scratch any fortune and you'll find blood only a generation or two back." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to waste your life is by taking notes. The easiest way to avoid living is to just watch." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am nothing, and not even that." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brittanyrucklos: @PalahniukQuote #lullaby http://t.co/C6MNlP6kBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We've taken the world apart... but we have no idea what to do with the pieces." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People have to really suffer before they can risk doing what they love." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShellySometimes: @PalahniukQuote RT @ShellySometimes: This is your life - and it's ending one minute at a time. http://t.co/shG1YbUj4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your birth is a mistake you'll spend your whole life trying to correct." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @benbelzer: @PalahniukQuote charcoal http://t.co/PrOKIIWUt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Real smarts begin when you quit quoting other people." - Pygmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @codename_rondo: @PalahniukQuote http://t.co/mAxZIwVpog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A girl calls and asks 'Does it hurt very much to die?' 'Well, sweetheart,' I tell her, 'yes, but it hurts a lot more to keep living.'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff so far. Keep the Palahniuk inspired fan art and tattoos coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoshJorges: @PalahniukQuote #fightclub http://t.co/saJYBYW12m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Buster Casey #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/yTdZib29HR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe it's our sins that give God consolation when he finally has to give us cancer."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Art never comes from happiness." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hannahemerald: @PalahniukQuote invisible monsters tattoo! :) http://t.co/ptdG28eFxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, send me your Palahniuk inspired tattoos and I'll tweet them out periodically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention artists: If you have any cool Palahniuk inspired art projects, tweet them to me and I'll periodically retweet the better ones. Tks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: You can also check all my posts here: http://t.co/xU8lO4o5wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: In case you were wondering, I’ve been keeping up w/ the @Reddit #AMA, answering questions every few days - http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your past is just a story. And once you realize this it has no power over you." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Choke' fan art. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/HtyByiQsVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You grow up to become living proof of your parents' limitations. Their less than masterpiece." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These stories are ghosts, bringing people back from the dead. Just for a moment. For a visit. Every story is a ghost." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes, working jobs we hate so we can buy shit we don't need." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is bullshit. Emotion is bullshit. I am a rock. A jerk. I'm an uncaring asshole and proud of it." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you keep looking for someone perfect, then you'll never find love. Because it's how much you love them that makes them perfect." Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How is it you can keep mutating and still be the same deadly virus?" - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anymore, no one's mind is their own." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyler Durden #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/c1f0hOhzml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is it you feel like a dope if you laugh alone, but that's usually how you end up crying?" - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A book is as private and consensual as sex." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have no Great War, no Great Depression, our war is a spiritual war, our depression is our lives." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In truth, the degree of anyone's success depends on how often they can say the word yes and hear the word no." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With everyone's imagination atrophied, no one will ever be a threat to the world." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the living are haunted by the dead, then the dead are haunted by their own mistakes." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Ok, just finished @chuckpalahniuk's new short story 'Cannibal' and it's absolutely brilliant. Pick it up in the May is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most heralded women starve themselves or cut themselves or poison themselves. Or they find a man who's happy to do that for them."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without access to true chaos, we'll never have true peace. Unless everything can get worse, it won't get any better." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I let go. Lost in oblivion. Dark and silent and complete. I found freedom. Losing all hope was freedom." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Parents are like God because you want to know they're out there, but you really only call when you need something."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The problem is, if you never weep in public... well, the public assumes you never weep."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @averous_92: Gonna do some reading. @PalahniukQuote 
#fightclub
#choke
#author http://t.co/Z6trnDg6GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone's in their own personal coma."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find good in what the world says is evil."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we can leave all of our stories behind. Our being villains or victims. Only then can we maybe rescue the world."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In truth, the degree of anyone's success depends on how often they can say the word yes or hear the word no."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The things you own end up owning you."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's sex and what's death--I can't tell the difference."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people are just born human. The rest of us, we take a lifetime to get there."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeDoerer: @chuckpalahniuk @PalahniukQuote #fightclub http://t.co/m4qnb5Snkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On a long enough timeline, the survival rate for everyone drops to zero."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Invisible Monsters #ChuckPalahniuk... http://t.co/uBtS6FUd0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Conditions change and we mutate."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAmacyLee: "The biggest factor that makes you a saint is the amount of press coverage you get." @chuckpalahniuk @PalahniukQuote #Su…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All human beings search for either reasons to be good, or excuses to be bad."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People fall so in love with their pain, they can't leave it behind. The same as the stories they tell. We trap ourselves."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Oh, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me. I'll be anybody you want me to be."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A salacious lie will always trump a noble truth."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ask yourself: What did I eat for breakfast today? What did I eat for dinner last night? You see how fast reality fades away?"
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you can just crumble up and throw your past in the trashcan, then we'll figure out who you're going to be."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @madeleineisme: just rea guts by @PalahniukQuote and maybe i shouldn't have right before dinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @perezelizabeth: Just read Guts by Palahniuk..... All I have to say is, wow. @PalahniukQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who wants to read 'Guts' can click the link in my bio. Not for the faint of heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Guts' Art #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/CSzbFcbeih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A sperm meets an egg and your soul gets sucked back to live another tedious lifetime. On Earth: Planet Hurt. Planet Conflict. Planet Pain."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's us against us. You, the victim of yourself." 
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is static."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is calm and sunny, but the air is full of bullshit." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How sweet! You still believe in death... that's just so... quaint. Well, sorry to pop your death bubble, but there's no such thing."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's the best revenge of all: happiness. Nothing drives people crazier than seeing someone having a good fucking life."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a tumor, I'd name it Marla... #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/FTUfx12Crl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We love drama. We love conflict. We need a devil or we'll create one." 
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Katherine Kenton remains among the generation of women who feel that the most sincere form of flattery is the male erection." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAmacyLee: About to plunge into this bad boy. @chuckpalahniuk @PalahniukQuote #Survivor #Palahniuk http://t.co/B0I4eoYEYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People turn up their music to hide yours. You turn up yours again. Everyone buys a bigger sound system. This is the arms race of sound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's still a thousand places I haven't gone to die." 
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deliver me from Swedish furniture. Deliver me from clever art. May I never be complete. May I never be content."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First your parents, they give you your life, but then they try to give you their life." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Since change is constant, you wonder if people crave death because it's the only way they can get anything really finished." - Survivor]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>