<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Product Developer – Java/JavaScript/React/Node: Join our elite IT team as a Full Stack Developer – Java/JavaScript As a Full Stack Developer, you will be a part of the Product Services team.  At CARFAX, we create products for our consumers and… https://t.co/yqcTiu0OSf https://t.co/uXArYdjVI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/svHeqHu2v2 https://t.co/Uu692KHTCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump vows to help Chinese tech giant https://t.co/Fr52qTeCQv https://t.co/7H1OzyPhDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared (Req# 00013): SENIOR JAVA API DEVELOPER (JAVA, REST API, JS) Title: Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified… https://t.co/f5AA9P2gwW https://t.co/7YdgUBbdB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: TECHNOLOGY Senior Java Developer London, UK Apply Job Description We are looking for a Senior Java Developer with 4+ years of experience in Core Java and 2+ years of experience in multi-threading. Responsibilities * Design and… https://t.co/puAcpKxdRb https://t.co/bAEx9nql7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Software Engineer (JavaScript, Solidity) – TOP10 Computer Science University!: This client is a team coming out of Stanford, Palantir, Google, and Berkeley, funded by Founders Fund Angel, Stanford-StartX, and BlockTower Capital, building a… https://t.co/axkInQjEy9 https://t.co/Im4Bov47vm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer, Secret Cleared (Req# 00002): SENIOR JAVA ENGINEER Title: Senior Java Engineer Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified applicants MUST have an ACTIVE DOD issued SECRET security clearance, and by virtue… https://t.co/3I0ASAbiYW https://t.co/iEVVBQlInF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanoid robot runs upright; could run after you: Boston Dynamics released new video of two of the company's robots, Atlas and SpotMini showing off some new features like running and autonomous navigation. https://t.co/JPQ3twEiQI https://t.co/MttoQisOBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Join our team of Java Developers and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Application Technologies: Spring,… https://t.co/IjUIXP5zOj https://t.co/V6a6XypKmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's key safety representative leaves for Waymo: Tesla's executive team isn't done with turmoil following the loss of its Autopilot chief and its engineering lead's sabbatical. The electric car maker's "primary technical contact" with American safety… https://t.co/vPHREiSCUI https://t.co/dCsOhxwLcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Groovy / Grails Developer: JAVA Groovy / Grails Developer Primary Skills JAVA,jQuery,SQL,AJAX,SDLC,BOOTSTRAP,DB2 UDB Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking JAVA Groovy / Grails Developer for location Fort Worth, TX… https://t.co/ND7ChIPQOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Applications Developer: Seeking a candidate with 5 years applications, JAVA, UNIX application development. * This is about upgrades, enhancements, code changes to new and existing application * We do not want Middleware Administrators with… https://t.co/kzlEkv6BDw https://t.co/2bq666bPyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer-Back End: Req ID 96692BR Business Title Java Developer-Back End Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed None Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is seeking an experience Java… https://t.co/mksq1yR48E https://t.co/2W95Nm6mMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – DHS Public Trust Clearance: Herndon, VA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today We are a government IT consulting firm based in Herndon, VA. THsi is a full time permanent opportunity requiring a DHS Public Trust Clearance. What You Need for… https://t.co/LG6C2YUhTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: 113933BR Java Developer VA – Herndon 113933BR Java Developer Raytheon is seeking a quality Applications Developer to develop, enhance and maintain enterprise/departmental IT systems. This position requires in-depth hands on experience… https://t.co/ateSbLubw2 https://t.co/GyEEZl8CVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/J2EE Developer – to 100k: job detailsJob Number:1219324Job Title:Java/J2EE Developer – to 100kJob Type:Full-timeLocation:New York, NYHours:Post Date:Apr 18 2018Salary:DOEDetailed Job Description: Great Java/J2EE Developer full-time position in NYC.… https://t.co/Uow4gxm15O https://t.co/fe7wbe7AFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Enterprise Java Engineer 100% TELECOMMUTE: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $300k Posted Today We currently have offices in San Fran, Santa Monica and Miami but are open to hiring telecommute people if you are a strong match. We need 2 – 3… https://t.co/1FZRRCPnJp https://t.co/yNpbBevxNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr – C++, Java: Req ID : 427983BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : The Enterprise Modeling/Simulation team of LM Space in King of Prussia, PA is looking for talented Software Engineers with recent and… https://t.co/wTJY7Gbvf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three days in, life with the Android P beta has been mostly painless: The first public preview of Android P is finally here, and as you might have guessed from the jam-packed keynote, there's a lot going on in this new build. As Google tells it, Android… https://t.co/ivVra4Bp0V https://t.co/mguSyZMiNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Senior Java Developer – Suitland MD The Developer will be a pivotal member of a team that assists in the requirements collection and analysis, software design, development, debugging, and implementation and enhancement of new and existing… https://t.co/4z6NEACTkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA – Security Apps- Developer: JAVA – Security Apps- Developer Ref No.: 18-19967 Location: Sunnyvale, California JAVA APP Developer – Security Apps Sunnyvale, CA JAVA/J2EE core development exp. is required Hands-on with developing security applications… https://t.co/yP8cUeeBO7 https://t.co/2WXHgVCwNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment… https://t.co/3dtC7xlR1d https://t.co/5VoMWTBNxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Cloud Dockers Consultant: Java Cloud Dockers Consultant Ref No.: 18-20306 Location: San Jose, California Job Title: Senior Java Cloud Dockers Consultant Location: San Jose, CA Duration: Fulltime / Permanent (or) Contract Job Description: – Java… https://t.co/v11Bm6BBxd https://t.co/4ORhCrDvPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – Market Risk IT – Market Data: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/aKbMjNRHD8 https://t.co/ZGEzqXjEfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Product Developer – Java/JavaScript/React/Node: Join our elite IT team as a Full Stack Developer – Java/JavaScript As a Full Stack Developer, you will be a part of the Product Services team.  At CARFAX, we create products for our consumers and… https://t.co/8GOw9ViVLN https://t.co/H4Ni0MjNoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Ref No.: 18-20111 Location: Whippany, New Jersey Position: Senior Java Developer Location: Whippany, NJ Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Strong experience Core Java with MQ Messaging and Unix https://t.co/69QFr2IYfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/Dicgnpdr01 https://t.co/ihThn9lNTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Brooklyn Nine-Nine' canceled: The most painful time of year for TV fans has claimed a major victim. https://t.co/gGst9FXwyB https://t.co/QMAS4oKs2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Engineer, Java, Javascript: Req ID : 430520BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Are you a highly skilled Software engineer who is ready for a new challenge? Lockheed Martin is a global technology leader… https://t.co/7LEcYHaa5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – Market Risk IT – Market Data: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/GUik0V8q7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft isn't giving up on VR and AR yet: Whatever happened with Microsoft's Mixed Reality platform? Headsets from partners launched with surprisingly little fanfare last fall alongside the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update. And for the most part, they… https://t.co/2ViVG207dR https://t.co/aK4Zn4SpA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer – Mobile Web Engineering: For American Express Java Engineer – Mobile &amp; Web Engineering job – Digital Commerce, Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation American Express – Life at American Express – Our Company –… https://t.co/bZcptODe3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows truck take out light poles on highway: A pick-up truck loses control on a highway in Wisconsin and takes out two light poles. No injuries were reported. https://t.co/o7OsqanIZ3 https://t.co/rDnumKr9Qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: JOB TITLE: Java Developer PROJECT OVERVIEW: We are seeking a mid-level Java Developer to join our agile team. You will develop web-based analytics software in a multi-disciplinary environment which include; technical analysis of… https://t.co/p9HOFjPeFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager,Java Development: PROJECT MANAGER, JAVA DEVELOPMENT RESPONSIBILITIES * Hands on development experience with Java and DevOps * Architect, design and develop systems * Hands on experience with TDD in Junit, FitNesse, Cucumber, etc. *… https://t.co/TVIz2INUaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why some Americans are obsessed with Harry and Meghan: On a Monday afternoon, the Pig and Whistle begins filling up before it's officially quitting time. Happy Hour starts every day at 4 p.m. and the bartender is pouring pint after pint of Fuller's and… https://t.co/EciD47B3lB https://t.co/Z4CSlsWCul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18007388) Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18007388 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/Lw1acdNuZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-06734 Location: West Chester,, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/12/2018 Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills: – Java EE Technologies, Foundation : Java Web Services. – Good knowledge on… https://t.co/IaSEIM8jUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final design of SpaceX’s Falcon 9 rocket launches today (update): SpaceX's launch that's scheduled for this afternoon may appear to be a routine launch to deploy a satellite, but it's actually anything but. Bangabandhu Satellite-1, scheduled for a… https://t.co/c8gU0Xr165 https://t.co/rZrhuztCWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Falls Church, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/16/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/e59CdsDHuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Our client is the creator of a fast growing software product that addresses security concerns that arise with complex enterprise level software development projects. Consistently rated as one of the best companies in Central Texas… https://t.co/LSfeC8pkei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Democrats release over 3,500 Russian Facebook ads: Today, Democrats in the House of Representatives released over 3,500 Facebook ads that were purchased by Russia in order to influence the 2016 presidential election. In a Twitter thread, Rep. Adam… https://t.co/W3SdZj1yOF https://t.co/zzzFdtpEe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Javascript UI Engineer: Nuvi aggregates hundreds of millions of pieces of social content that are created every day via Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, and just about every internet publishing outlet on the web. We help the worlds leading brands and… https://t.co/UJzAx42A69 https://t.co/w2Nblow57N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python/JavaScript Developer: Muster is a cloud based web platform that enables customers to create online advocacy campaings with analytics. We are seeking an experienced developer to help build and maintain our web application, written primarily… https://t.co/IBcDuISDBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrome will let you have AR experiences, no app needed: Google believes that 2018 is the year the web turns a corner and starts becoming more immersive, and the company's new WebXR API is at the heart of its efforts. Long story short, WebXR provides a… https://t.co/KT8PBbvFeF https://t.co/XU9dCsDrOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Full Stack, Java (Treasury): Job Description Job ID: R41969 McLean 1 (19050), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by… https://t.co/3sLL2wbwTm https://t.co/668zOk6BCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Job Title: Java Architect Location: Mt. Laurel, NJ Job Type: Contract Main duties and responsibilities: * We need a Manager tech level person who has retail banking experience. * We are looking at that person as the lead solution designer… https://t.co/TwPLvhKfjf https://t.co/813WcaRkjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Java Developer: Skylight is at the forefront of a civic movement to reinvent how the government serves the public in a digital world. Were looking for experienced developers to join our talented team of technologists in driving this movement… https://t.co/6qSjM2qEOn https://t.co/T0H5QY3XYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI JavaScript Engineer: My client, a highly successful and profitable computer software and SaaS company specialized in Cyber Security computer software, is currently exhibiting exponential growth. The Front- End tribe is looking for a Senior UI… https://t.co/uUEVyM25JV https://t.co/BKjCnSzex9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java programmer: Java programmer st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 04/17/18, Posted Date – 04/17/18 Primary SkillsJava,DevOpsTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard skype linked in MasterCard just released another role for a JAVA… https://t.co/4SwaifYRMK https://t.co/l5ReUwFr9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EA is going to keep putting loot boxes in its games: Electronic Arts will "push forward" with loot boxes in its future video games, despite admitting that "all loot boxes are gambling." Yeesh. In an investor's call, CEO Andrew Wilson said that EA has… https://t.co/dL4ods4lN9 https://t.co/LXrgVwJiM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Enterprise Cybersecurity Software – Javascript): We’re looking for a highly talented Javascript Software Engineer for our El Dorado Hills office. As a Javascript Mobile Application Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers… https://t.co/OzMvIiVEVZ https://t.co/6NrowSEWZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ JEE Developer (Senior): We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Java Developer to join our team in Kingstowne, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Responsibilities: – Design and… https://t.co/D88uQkBiZN https://t.co/ayCBOxpG9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist UI Developer (NEXEN) AngularJS JavaScript, Java, SQL: Specialist UI Developer AngularJS/Angular2, JavaScript, Java, SQL Asset service technology at BNY Mellon has an immediate need for web developer with Java application development… https://t.co/ceuSPUtuh7 https://t.co/GuInYiv05Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: 1. Initial contract is set for 6 months. 2. Hiring Manager is only targeting candidates with a Green Card or have US citizenship. 3. Scope: Hiring manager wants a strong, hands-on Java developer that can balance multiple projects at… https://t.co/fatlZznbob https://t.co/wfA146U48W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-22139 Location: Plano, Texas Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: Spring Boot-L2 (Mandatory) FULLSTACK JAVA-L3 Java-J2EE-L3 As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a… https://t.co/tF5LIUxFaE https://t.co/d4thSGYOM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer in Carmel, Indiana, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core… https://t.co/tChO9vwxsg https://t.co/tgsqMMrwsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohen files restraining order against Stormy Daniels' lawyer: President Donald Trump's personal lawyer Michael Cohen filed for a restraining order late Thursday against Stormy Daniels' lawyer, Michael Avenatti, to prevent him from speaking to the press… https://t.co/kk0EFMBZr9 https://t.co/p95saiPUSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Applications Dev.: Sr. Java Applications Dev. RESPONSIBILITIES * Engaging with Enterprise and Application architects to promote collaboration on the development of solution architecture; Reviewing architecture and ensuring alignment with… https://t.co/FoptL0sXIB https://t.co/0F2Ug7o5Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Drools Developer: Java Drools Developer Ref No.: 18-21594 Location: troy, Michigan Hello, Hope you are doing great… This is Vishal from Enterprise Solution Inc. and I am writing to you regarding an excellent job opportunity based out of. Position:… https://t.co/1fUnyt4wwc https://t.co/MjBX0AhfJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full-Stack Developer: Java Full-Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-22207 Location: Tampa, Florida Job Description:- Position : Java Full-Stack Developer Location : Tampa, FL Type : Contract (12 Months) HTML5, jQuery, CSS, Java, Angular JS, Bootstrap, REST,… https://t.co/jVDybqd3CI https://t.co/u0kM6pr5zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Development Lead (Java/Grails): We are looking for a Java/Grails Development Lead to steer the development of the APIs powering our successful own-brand and grey-labeled products. The position involves about 30% leadership and 70% hands-on technical… https://t.co/xHo4PeVMiy https://t.co/xnIKLkFukM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer – XP: Job ID: JR-******* Description: As the healthcare industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable healthcare for our… https://t.co/1CwsaKOSl4 https://t.co/2llsdbUKAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Location San Diego – CA, US Level Master Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 4/13/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Electrical Engineering, Design Engineering Background Software Engineering, Information Technology,… https://t.co/7lUiZcgYsJ https://t.co/erK66lxvME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer / Consultant, San Jose: Are you looking for new challenges in your career? Would you like to work in an international environment with the newest web technologies, in a company that is world-known for its open source products?… https://t.co/1hPYBIe7yy https://t.co/iD1MIPNc0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java lead: Java lead st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsJava,LeadTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard linked in face to face you can submit h1b This is a lead JAVA developer role, must be… https://t.co/bhtD5RL1hX https://t.co/QHSW06gn7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-12054 Location: Irving, Texas Description: The candidate for this position will be responsible for providing development, and second line production support for Telecommunication’s application security tools… https://t.co/E9en8LFGZn https://t.co/miBed7bnvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML: Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML Tracking Code ******* Job Description Do you have great ideas about how to create user interfaces (UIs) that are intuitive… https://t.co/XJvz4BG1GE https://t.co/p1y69tGHFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Full Stack Java Developer Ref No.: 18-20727 Location: Syracuse, New York Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 4 Not contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity… https://t.co/aHOECO5B74 https://t.co/l22d7Q8VFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer – 2:   Job Description – Java Software Engineer – 2 (18011163) Java Software Engineer – 2 Requisition ID : 18011163 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/fijGFfCDiO https://t.co/iUK6WA37T8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Join our Information Technology team where you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our customers’ needs and make it easy for them to do business with us. You will work fairly… https://t.co/fP7lGkRwdS https://t.co/WX430FnXob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer: Vienna, VA Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are an experienced java developer, please read on! Based in Vienna, VA, we are creating a comprehensive mobility platform and providing products for mobile app solutions,… https://t.co/3BkFlYqKTN https://t.co/dvQ6cg9kAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adblock Plus creator hopes blockchain will help spot fake news: The creators of Adblock Plus, eyeo, have an uncommon solution to the fake news scourge: rely on one of the tech industry's biggest buzzwords. They've introduced a beta Chrome extension,… https://t.co/HpSJ6NH54J https://t.co/vVvecHTkEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment… https://t.co/8gYx9JIoxc https://t.co/boXEBLbadC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Level Java Developer: Careers @WilmerTech WilmerTech provides a complete and effective employee orientation program involving induction, domain-related training sessions, cross-cultural training, and personality development for new recruits.… https://t.co/KxtXU9uMI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Visualization Software Engineer: AnaVation, LLC | Careers |Java Visualization Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability… https://t.co/YfnEbjHw15 https://t.co/g1W9NvSDIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Join our Information Technology team where you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our customers’ needs and make it easy for them to do business with us. You will work fairly… https://t.co/2d8CGzLQEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Architect: ALIS Software is currently seeking a Senior Java Architect for a contract opportunity located in Austin, Texas. Required qualifications: 10+ years of experience in enterprise architecture, analysis, design, and hands-on application… https://t.co/8ooqK3YCcf https://t.co/sgWtBnSNQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More national parks close as Colorado fire grows: Nearly 1,400 homes have been evacuated in Summit County, Colorado as the Buffalo wildfire burns nearby, according to Summit Fire &amp; EMS. https://t.co/YxLkhxGMXU https://t.co/CdHmjFHHDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA DEVELOPER: JAVA/J2EE DEVELOPER JERSEY CITY, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 05/21/18, Posted Date – 05/21/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverview Job description TDA Rate: 65 ( Candidate rate on C2C) A strong developer with Java and… https://t.co/HbN7DlKrBo https://t.co/0I6KQ4atw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer Ref No.: 18-19100 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 32 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.)would like to share a job opportunity asSr. Java… https://t.co/9Y5A1gENt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico releases records of deaths since Maria: The Puerto Rican government on Tuesday released to CNN and another news organization a database of information on all deaths that occurred after Hurricane Maria, which pummeled this US commonwealth on… https://t.co/drw0qVdqje https://t.co/HOpD8nWwHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API Developer (LOCALS ONLY): Java API Developer 3-6 Month+ Contract Boston, MA In person req. Keys: * Spring/Boot OR Spring MVC * REST APIs * Strong Mid-tier &amp; back-end cloud microservices development experience * Exposure to AWS environment (2… https://t.co/JeWHvsPgzp https://t.co/BfqiPq5dc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Developer: Java Web Developer Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is… https://t.co/bo8dnFdots https://t.co/3EzXj8c9lK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer: We have an open position for a Java developer with one of our clients. The prospective candidate will be responsible for designing, developing and implementing software applications for the capital markets team using Core Java,… https://t.co/zm0yMgWCos https://t.co/xQYKfeohGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Fortnite' comes to Nintendo Switch today: The rumors were true: Fortnite has arrived on the Nintendo Switch. As of 1PM Eastern, you can play Epic Games' battle royale shooter at home or on the move using the same console. It looks to be up to date, too,… https://t.co/fuWaKxfSGS https://t.co/nlho3la989]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Meade, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/ljxFFBBqy4 https://t.co/KrFdE2Rnzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# ColdFusion developer w Java Cherry Hill, NJ: TITILE: Senior ColdFusion Developer Type: Contract Duration: 6+ Months Location: Cherry Hill, NJ Key Skills: ColdFusion with Java backend Requirements * BS in Computer Science or related field of study. * 6… https://t.co/dxsCyyjvuY https://t.co/wr4oeQhnRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: First Student is a leader in transportation of children K-12. As the largest provider of student transportation in North America, First Student is more than twice the size of the next largest competitor. Industry-leading safety programs,… https://t.co/Xe3XJay1GD https://t.co/xoJTegV8Ki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer (Java / Web Services): Company Description About Visa Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind – making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is… https://t.co/VmSk9mA3ZU https://t.co/fuyyDXsr0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (Full Stack Java/EE, Spring Framework Developer): Sr. Specialist Developer (Full Stack Java/EE, Spring Framework Developer) The ideal candidate would be a full stack developer understanding the SDLC best practices, interested in… https://t.co/g3BgsnZHcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java / C# Software Engineer – Entry Level: Summary: Software Engineers will work on developing the user interface (C#) and/or related server side systems (Java) of the Charles River Investment Management System. Positions involve highly technical… https://t.co/4xsLw1CmVK https://t.co/JN7JKSy7p3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump made $82 million in 2017 https://t.co/yhQVCQONWe https://t.co/7mv30YD92S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Java Applications Developer: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/Y2jZ1PrykX https://t.co/LDYbp2rMOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer: What does it take to protect and maintain the most sensitive data for over 220 million people and 25 million businesses? What does it take to meet daunting challenges and shape solutions that pioneer industries and improve lives? At… https://t.co/0i7i2Ymd2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java UI Developer: Lead Java UI Developer for a growing Electronic Trading group in the FX space across multiple functional areas including pricing, credit, and automated trading. Candidate is responsible for the full lifecycle of UI development… https://t.co/2xBvDRKFWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer – AI Java Platform: Our close client, a FinTech startup, is on a mission to enable companies to attract, engage, support, and transact with their customers via human-like, intelligent conversations, anytime, anywhere. Their… https://t.co/O4EQL1B7jw https://t.co/rydg5yc8TG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Enterprise Java Engineer 100% TELECOMMUTE: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $300k Posted Today We currently have offices in San Fran, Santa Monica and Miami but are open to hiring telecommute people if you are a strong match. We need 2 – 3… https://t.co/WVZMXFCZGi https://t.co/LTxfHhkpDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Backend Developer (Java &amp; Node JS) | Urbandale IA| 6 Months| Position- 1: * ISGs Digital Solutions group is seeking back-end developers to help support the data platform (Enhance) process streams of data from machine sensors. * Looking for strong… https://t.co/flntVNjAKv https://t.co/lymPu0BQ7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Square Enix's E3 keynote right here at 1 PM Eastern: How do you catch the news as it happens from Square Enix's E3 media briefing if you aren't in LA? You watch along with the publisher's livestream embedded below starting at 1PM Eastern,… https://t.co/M3CSES3tc0 https://t.co/M8gDw92mSR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>