<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant #SS1970: UXC Eclipse USA, a DXC Technology company, in Bellevue, Washington seeks Technical Consultant. * 5 years experience with at least 1 year experience Structured Query Language, X++, C#, .Net, Json, Azure Cloud required. * Must… https://t.co/XMaXLpWu4w https://t.co/HnNZDr4BMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scm/Devops #MP6334: Senior Scm/DevOps Engineers (Calabasas, CA) Be part of team responsible for development &amp; support our continuous integration/ deployment infrastructure which consists of automated software version management, software build,… https://t.co/e46qjVf2Uk https://t.co/wxI9vuP9a3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/oWvo5sBBLf https://t.co/O20TcE6C29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Design Engineer: Senior Staff Design Engineer (Job location is Seattle, WA)  Develop software solutions utilizing JavaScript, CSS &amp; HTML. Develop content pipeline to design &amp; develop video streaming applications. Create new technologies to… https://t.co/UeZ8JWXSjO https://t.co/yuhg1u8QAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager: Teradata Operations, Inc., Santa Clara, CA: Resp. for mng project dev. in multiple methodologies from initiation to closure. REQS: BS or foreign equi in CS, Info Tech, MIS or rel. &amp; 8 yr prog., post-bacc. exp. or, MS in CS, Info Tech, MIS or… https://t.co/Ys78osuG88 https://t.co/UkcwmUpHDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineers: Careers At Raytheon One Global Team Creating Trusted, Innovative Solutions to make the world a safer place. Use your engineering skills to make the world a safer place with a career at Raytheon. We partner with our global customers to provide… https://t.co/qBJoMv1gDq https://t.co/tIRGG3JDuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R43424: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall tech design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer apps using existing &amp; emerging tech… https://t.co/YlB5mu1NLl https://t.co/ODJ9jHyPKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity, Application Developers, Help Desk Specialists: Job Fair Delta Resources has an impeccable reputation as a leader in the government services industry. Delta Resources is actively recruiting professionals with technical backgrounds and… https://t.co/569em7OEji https://t.co/J80Y15sLUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: You will collect, maintain, manage and interpret data from internal and external sources; work with business users and subject matter experts to clarify business needs, develop report specifications, and test results to ensure business… https://t.co/aU8DDTqfvD https://t.co/ngKVorOk7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information and Technology Specialist: The School District of Glenwood City is looking for an Information and Technology Specialist to support the learning environment for students and staff through leadership in technology. The successful applicant will… https://t.co/t0Ca0OPYKR https://t.co/ByPXaQ9sH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gently Breathing Somnox Robot Cuddles You to Sleep: The Somnox is a fuzzy, bean-shaped robot that mimics human breathing to help the human holding it fall asleep. https://t.co/zFiWghMITT https://t.co/HZy36Llm7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Administrator: ORACLE DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR ADT LLC has an opening in Irving, TX for an Oracle DB Administrator. Help manage &amp; maintain Oracle EBS R12.x.x apps. &amp; DB, &amp; other non-ERP Oracle DBs. Provide tech. &amp; oper’l DBA support for… https://t.co/4HXSO9efIe https://t.co/Gl2YWSRRv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Development #JSWM: Senior Manager of Development (https://t.co/6tTWQ1Ax8j, Inc., Midvale, UT) Multiple openings available. Lead multiple teams working on significant &amp; critical projects, provide tech &amp; team leadership &amp; mentorship. Work… https://t.co/mNA8i5IHjh https://t.co/yB3vIAMW2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer: If you are enthusiastic about safety and security with a strong technical IT background, Bell Bank is seeking experienced candidates for their Information Security Team that can lead security team initiatives while… https://t.co/QdV9yMfSDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description: Job Summary: This selected individual will be part of an integrated team engaged in planning and implementing solutions in support of multiple geographically distributed systems in a complex network environment. He/she will… https://t.co/hPNdikyiFV https://t.co/mq3IyfhpQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Systems Engineer: This position is located in El Segundo, CA Position Summary: The Senior Software Systems Engineer will provide direct support to the Air Force Space and Missile Systems Center in the development and operation of large… https://t.co/HV6z7PB68W https://t.co/fj0Nq8AcSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer: Sales Engineer ID 2015-6104 Category Technical Support Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities https://t.co/Mvg1vyKmrJ seeks a bright, self-motivated Sales Engineer (SE) to join our “startup within an established company” for our global… https://t.co/mrTgKkiHNr https://t.co/U5tdUXfX8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Director, Corporate Finance &amp; Accounting:   Job Description – Senior Director, Corporate Finance &amp; Accounting (38788) Job Description  Senior Director, Corporate Finance &amp; Accounting-38788 Description  Company: Hitachi America, Ltd. Division:… https://t.co/kMk20i44fQ https://t.co/SCOTVjyo1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal SC Business Ops Spec (BPE) (IND): 111678BR Principal SC Business Ops Spec (BPE) (IND) CA – El Segundo, CO – Aurora, FL – Orlando, IN – Indianapolis, TX – Richardson, VA – Dulles Raytheon IIS Supply Chain (SC) is seeking a high-performing… https://t.co/NbB0FgIo1w https://t.co/pKzXPvollF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Data Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here,… https://t.co/Sxq05nLcmv https://t.co/j1RabxwWMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software II: Engineer Software II for Tridium Inc. (Honeywell co) (Richmond, VA) responsible for development &amp; testing software as part of Agile team for Tridium’s Niagara Framework. Requires Master’s in Electrical Engineering, Computer… https://t.co/8fHIL4UMDo https://t.co/hU6tXHwjLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Specialist IV: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/4n4pQ5oUp6 https://t.co/MyIAGIWilS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Check If Cambridge Analytica Could Access Your Facebook Data: Facebook has released a tool that lets you see if you were caught up in the Cambridge Analytica fiasco—and what other apps know about you know. https://t.co/HCUv7yrg1U https://t.co/YXgNDE7XYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Strategic Data Analyst – Multiple Locations: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward. We need attention to every detail with an eye for the points no one has considered.… https://t.co/Rpr65PgZUR https://t.co/BNq4eBC4Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vistex Consultant: Vistex Consultant. F/T with Denken Solutions, Irvine, CA. Position based out of Irvine, CA HQ, but may be assigned to various client/project sites anywhere in USA. Configure/design/assist with Vistex-based admin &amp; analysis of complex… https://t.co/Xn41mnxpbs https://t.co/5zJgJPYvwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineering Senior: Description: Job Summary Leidos was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes “Americas Top 500” list. The company is growing quickly, and is looking for new talent. Leidos is offering a $2,000 bonus for… https://t.co/n5PQVKLk4H https://t.co/42qIKZhh5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) Systems Administrator: ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) Systems Administrator Information Systems Technology. Chesterfield County is currently recruiting for the above.   An Equal Opportunity Employer Committed to… https://t.co/tdG4v511sg https://t.co/U36K6VriZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG Developer: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/KSxeaHZYzP https://t.co/EyCXcAZNY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk/Technical Support Specialist: FHLBank Topeka’s products, services and programs help our member financial institutions provide affordable credit and support housing and community development efforts. We are accepting resumes for the position… https://t.co/T6xHHAYy0L https://t.co/FbJYscMNXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager ITS Applications #7661: Manager – ITS Applications Job #7661 $100,000 – $135,000 depends on qualifications. Basic Responsibilities:  Manages the utility’s Enterprise Asset Management (EAM) systems program and team performing software… https://t.co/hx257ovSt0 https://t.co/5238EVh5SB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Data Analysis Manager #R43299: Associate Data Analysis Manager – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Perform quantitative &amp; quality analysis of economic data, relating constants &amp; variables, restrictions,… https://t.co/GSiqYZMFj0 https://t.co/9JE8tQvQEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Architect: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/nWwwBQOJMQ https://t.co/a94RE4JZkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: * Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. * Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/NbF5cfWBYh https://t.co/7EoKrXvARw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Application Developer The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL backend coding,… https://t.co/t6yn18RAaB https://t.co/Lw4Rrm9Zef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121): Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121) position available in San Diego, CA. Equal Employer Opportunity: Race, Gender, Veteran, Disabled. recblid 56wccihcu8q14vj7mvweuvxmcz4e1u https://t.co/irYcw7ikup https://t.co/ThOusD3q1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Best Smartphones of 2018: Guide to Android, Samsung Galaxy, iPhone: If you're on the prowl for a new Android, Galaxy, or iPhone, read our full guide to the best smartphones of 2018. https://t.co/fIFranvuLF https://t.co/NPxQj7VJWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: https://t.co/xz8dnMELdb Services, Inc. and A2Z Development Center, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Quality Assurance Engineer I, Job Code AZ0078: Adopt best practices in software engineering to test code at… https://t.co/3CxvxEaNEp https://t.co/PdoVc4LCSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Job #:180028444: Job #:180028444 Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Duties: Provide quality technology solutions that address line of business needs by contributing to writing Pega applications, developing stored procedures and general… https://t.co/9bJVKeXgXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Community Enhancement: Director of Community Enhancement  Chesterfield County, Virginia (Richmond-Metro Area) is seeking an energetic, collaborative, strategic thinker who can articulate a clear vision for community enhancement and… https://t.co/srv7yETAXV https://t.co/JEUSiV5Aqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Cumberland): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/kqcIlp7vbW https://t.co/HaprosOayP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer 16392: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology,… https://t.co/1HRcuHGFra https://t.co/T4xHC1F2m7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Senior: Req ID : 414403BR Job Code/Title : E1463:Systems Engineer Sr Job Description : Lockheed Martin Rotary and Missions (RMS) is seeking a Systems Engineer professional to join our team in Valley Forge, PA. This position is in the… https://t.co/RzEz0fcQ4n https://t.co/E26SvudYyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Application Development: PROJECT MANAGER – APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT 120VC exists to enable our clients to complete their Projects efficiently and cost effectively; to light a fire under innovation and crush the cost boundary, ensuring a… https://t.co/bgJYm9clFO https://t.co/X8Y4Sm1a5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analysts: Business Systems Analysts Ref No.: 18-10459 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Role: Business Systems Analysts Loc : Pittsburg, PA Duration: FTE 1. Create Agile user stories and acceptance documentation 2. Participates in all… https://t.co/hGS7CRMUsJ https://t.co/LJGOkVAgV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[END POINT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR: University of Washington Location Seattle, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category Administrative / Office,Bio-Tech / Sciences,Customer Service,Domestic Care / Services,Health Care Job… https://t.co/8lPOrnKKWQ https://t.co/HOFxQ4V6hh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer with Linux: Hi, Greetings from Macropace Technologies !! We have a job opening with suits for you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested for this position Automation Test Developer Hillsboro, OR… https://t.co/UTWJDuue3Y https://t.co/YnSTol0ro7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Data Feature Engineer: IT Data Feature Engineer Job Description IT Data Feature Engineer jobs at Kimberly Clark Information Technology jobs at Kimberly Clark Location: Roswell, GA or Neenah, WI Summary of Position The Data &amp; Analytics team is… https://t.co/vfPoLn28T5 https://t.co/PdbSDweLoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Arnold, MO Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/6/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than… https://t.co/TiphuiSZk3 https://t.co/SXw90cpBcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Apple, Quitting Intel Won't Come Easy: It makes all the sense in the world that Apple wants to leave Intel behind. Where it gets tricky is how it gets there. https://t.co/RYlyyZKcPu https://t.co/ZyHV8VqpgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Digital Technology Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/NrVGy6yUI8 https://t.co/pn1Nfp7MCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Data Analyst: Our Pharmaceutical client has engaged us to provide a Data Analyst contractor to support operational data analysis and support. The ideal candidate: * Provides support to the organization in regards to the processing and… https://t.co/X5hCSTHpt8 https://t.co/osqjt8sPgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMO Project Manager: The PMO Project Manager will lead the Project Management Office for a Design Development and Implementation of multiple MMIS modules in the Medicaid Enterprise strategy. The Project Manager will be responsible for performing,… https://t.co/xkeL7j5g5M https://t.co/rrgBqj2b4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Analyst I Moline IL I 3 years: Local candidates preferred asON-SITE INTERVIEW REQUIRED. This position may require the person to work any one of 3 shifts in a 24×7 environment. What skills you need: This is a Security Administration and… https://t.co/yvzHys9IaR https://t.co/HEfn5Fd1vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Content Developer: . Join our team and make the world better for developers! We are building the Developer Relations dream team in Azure engineering. Our global team is maniacal about making the world amazing for developers of all backgrounds.… https://t.co/0AnH2pTcxL https://t.co/77RmqTl1VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior EA Modeler/Developer- OBIEE/ODI Developer: POSITION SUMMARY: Leads and performs application development, configuration and unit testing of Oracle Business Intelligence (OBIEE) applications including Oracle HCM Analytics ETL, Dashboard and Reports… https://t.co/2knoHEJnZD https://t.co/yvcnkZ8nP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of User Experience Research: Description Our mission at Glassdoor is to help people everywhere find a job and company they love. We are disrupting an industry by changing how people search for jobs and how companies recruit top talent. About The… https://t.co/bGIl5pIMxN https://t.co/deiMCuXOrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test: TVision Insights is a hyper-growth television attention measurement company pioneering the way brands, their agencies, TV networks and OTT platforms determine the true value of their video content and advertising. The companys… https://t.co/JOvXKUI3rT https://t.co/sgL8Bo9Q1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Mobile Browsers: Microsoft Edge, Firefox Focus, Google Chrome, and More: Surfing the web on your phone is about to get a whole lot better. https://t.co/TbMvIpBgh3 https://t.co/QePvNBAHLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dir, IT Production Operations – MHC Production Assurance Leader: This position is a visible technical leader who owns and takes accountability for operations within a specific IT Service Area. This individual is well versed in running IT operations in a… https://t.co/ufii6JsSgc https://t.co/bqiiidsRfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed… https://t.co/0khoi8w2qj https://t.co/FcN1MrPmaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patient Access Process Consultant – Telecommute (Mountain or Pacific time zones): How do we make headway in the quest for better health care? We make disruptive revolutions happen every single day. As a Business Process Consultant, you’ll shift your… https://t.co/9feYTDIsQn https://t.co/nkIjSGXv7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Great Weekend Tech Deals: Nintendo, Apple, Tile, Eufy, Vive Pro: This weekend, ramble around a VR world of your choosing or smartify your coffeemaker with these tech deals. https://t.co/CffjM8AB4P https://t.co/2cqctRiF8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Executive: BPS World are a global resourcing specialist who have been nominated for the ‘REC best company to work for’ three years in a row, placing us in the top 10 most desirable recruitment organisations in the UK! We are… https://t.co/0BCsS8zb41 https://t.co/XrhLzjahKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Systems Engineer Level 3 16413: Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/Wnf1CIVcHp https://t.co/kJX5s7ki3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Machine Learning Delivery: 101139BR Software Engineer – Machine Learning Delivery MA – Cambridge U.S. Citizenship status is required as this position will need a U.S. Security Clearance within 1 year of start date. Help us bring… https://t.co/V2M5Lop9Dx https://t.co/TJjieyvNUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Attn: West Coast Based Full Stack Developers Full Time Remote position with Inc. 500 SaaS Healthcare Software Company. We are one of the fastest growing companies in America, recognized 3x by Inc. Magazine, VitalWare is a fully… https://t.co/gdA5wAdelB https://t.co/G7xWl1HP7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical / Systems Support Specialist For Software Co.: Do you want a meaningful role with a company thats making a real difference? Do you want to be involved in one of the most important resource areas in the world today: water? Then join our… https://t.co/qsnSktGnLQ https://t.co/KDqG5pQqdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial Automation Engineer: Country: United States Work Location: Estherville State: Iowa Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do The Industrial Automation Engineer will plan, direct, and coordinate… https://t.co/4QTJjssfwq https://t.co/VSwu9yKXDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Tester/QA Analyst (VISIO, HP ALM, JIRA, JAMA, REMEDY): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity… https://t.co/eQRYmqMAmB https://t.co/LazWhsNdb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Architect: Responsibilities: * Develop a variety of user-oriented applications to deliver analytic content in intuitive and innovative ways, through applications, and web interfaces * Work in cross-disciplinary teams with the industry… https://t.co/726ASOK2qu https://t.co/vhdrIkOqtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: The (Near) Future of PCs: Laptops are getting mobile processors and behaving more like phones. How will that change the way we use them? https://t.co/Igp8D9P1o4 https://t.co/gK5uri6OMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Services Insurance Business Analyst: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/n8CQTX2TlP https://t.co/akB4aC9jJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology UI Engineer: Blackhawk Network, Inc. in Pleasanton, CA seeks: UI Engineer (Job code 78805). Participate in designing, coding, &amp; testing mobile web UI templates. Build fluid, responsive layouts that function across a wide array of mobile &amp;… https://t.co/Ckqqb8AC3q https://t.co/ZOhJhZPImz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information and Technology Specialist: The School District of Glenwood City is looking for an Information and Technology Specialist to support the learning environment for students and staff through leadership in technology. The successful applicant will… https://t.co/4b7voSJiwd https://t.co/7kyqjpmu20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting Analyst: Senior Reporting Analyst Freedom Mortgage Corporation seeks a Senior Reporting Analyst to perform research and information gathering necessary to define, design, create, and document business requirements and specifications as… https://t.co/ArfheHftJ2 https://t.co/KgPXUVOqvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Engineer Systems Integration: Location: Granville, Ohio – United States PURPOSE OF THE JOB The Sr. Engineer (SE) is a key leadership and execution role for delivering outcomes that are aligned with the Global Manufacturing Technology (MT) portfolio.… https://t.co/1maFr265Ql https://t.co/ZH5hZGBPTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer: iOS App Developer needed for minor updates to major feature builds. Part time/Full time. Looking for someone who can work "outside the box" as we We currently have an office in Phoenix AZ with our main office currently being… https://t.co/fuaUvOh3Zm https://t.co/P5mDNpMuF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer #7788: Data Engineer Job #7788 $64,000 – $80,000 Annual (Salary DOQ) Basic Responsibilities: Provide analytic support and services across the organization. Support the development of new analytical models and business intelligence solutions… https://t.co/h3OTt3C9fc https://t.co/pJfK7dDjo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Development #JSWM: Senior Manager of Development (https://t.co/6tTWQ1Ax8j, Inc., Midvale, UT) Multiple openings available. Lead multiple teams working on significant &amp; critical projects, provide tech &amp; team leadership &amp; mentorship. Work… https://t.co/tla931LfBA https://t.co/9ZPXdEQHk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager With Masters Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science, or Computer Engineering, and 1 year experience in job offered. (or) Bachelor’s Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science,… https://t.co/2YAX4HgbwA https://t.co/YGHM5hYiQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Expert II (DCS ULN Build Engineer) #69406: Technical Expert II (DCS ULN Build Engineer) Austin, TX. Duties: Install &amp; config Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6.x, 7.x, SuSe Enterprise Linux 11.x, 12.x &amp; Solaris 11 servers as per requirement. Config &amp;… https://t.co/dXvvqtDOZu https://t.co/iKhpY1dg7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Technical Program Specialist (Mountain View, CA) Define feature sets to ensure that the technical aspects of Google programs satisfy the business needs of Google’s clients and users. #1615.19122 Exp Incl: data analysis, stat modeling,… https://t.co/BLgFfdpAFF https://t.co/e0SwhmrdAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liquid Studios – Embedded (C/C++) Developer: Basic Qualifications: * Minimum 2 plus years experience in development in Linux, Python and node.js. * Good familiarity with APIs SOAP REST * Deep knowledge in MQTT, Pub sub, web socket, ESB and JMS Preferred… https://t.co/bUiitY6EuI https://t.co/6ApYNyCCeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build a PC: Building your own computer yourself is a lost art—one due for a revival. https://t.co/E8PPWWCkii https://t.co/wVqdFyaeIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant #SS1970: UXC Eclipse USA, a DXC Technology company, in Bellevue, Washington seeks Technical Consultant. * 5 years experience with at least 1 year experience Structured Query Language, X++, C#, .Net, Json, Azure Cloud required. * Must… https://t.co/lyN6WR9uyQ https://t.co/JK6EFzfrIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sales engineer: Principal Sales EngineerLocation: Salt Lake City, UT This position can also be worked remotely. The primary purpose of the Principal Sales Engineer is to provide direction and specialist knowledge in applying the technology/software… https://t.co/uKcFIGos9M https://t.co/PHtK7fnpAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Program Analyst: Ausley Associates is pleased to recruit for the newest member of our premier team; Software Program Analyst. This position supports an ACAT I NAVAIR program that is driving requirements definition, resource allocation,… https://t.co/U29XUFxcaf https://t.co/UGBvguwC3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SMT Machine Programmer: Kay and Associates is an engineering services firm located in Buffalo Grove, Illinois and has been in business since 1960. Our division specializes in Engineering, Information Technology and Manufacturing related positions on a… https://t.co/avz8grFSLn https://t.co/EmjfKUWnWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCCM Desktop Support Engineer: An international law firm with offices in Washington, D.C. is seeking a qualified Desktop Engineer. The engineer is responsible for the support of all desktop applications, integrations, and the efficient delivery and… https://t.co/ORvIM9dogW https://t.co/lZXCSUbYtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Senior Analyst Programmer – Limited Tenure: City Rochester State Minnesota Telecommute No Department Information Technology Why Mayo Clinic This Senior Analyst – Programmer position is classified as a temporary / limited tenure position, which is… https://t.co/j1BqKwPpWY https://t.co/7Knie6YrEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Project Manager: 1st Shift, Monday – Friday, 8:30am – 5:30pm Logistics done differently. You are always looking for a better, more efficient way to improve productivity. We are looking for people who can effectively incorporate strategies to help… https://t.co/907vKkGdTc https://t.co/f4enWMGzxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: * Recommending or performing complex actions to correct problems using remote diagnostic, remediation technology and tools or at user locations to install, modify or make repairs to computer hardware and/or software. * Support… https://t.co/pUFxmwMHdv https://t.co/9xBZumTPD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Security Engineer: *25-50% travel required* Prestigious Professional Security Services Firm is currently seeking a Sr. Network Security Engineer with a strong Cisco routing and switching background. Candidate must have the ability to solve… https://t.co/RdKymn1CCH https://t.co/1pdQVkLm8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's New Data-Sharing Policies Are Crashing Tinder: Users can't log into the dating app after Facebook adjusted its app integration policies. https://t.co/l7kaCMYwRZ https://t.co/3eZHKELJAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager of Network Services: Manager of Network Services Central Bucks School District is accepting applications for a Manager of Network Services.  This full-time administrative position offers excellent benefits and competitive salary in accordance… https://t.co/eaNbMrNKa4 https://t.co/bDP35TF4jR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #R42195: Software Engineer  Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA   Details: * Multiple positions available * Perform technical design, development, modification, and implementation of computer applications using existing and… https://t.co/pVZDCgGANX https://t.co/ls07nXJ5ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer:   TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center… https://t.co/DURimZo4FE https://t.co/tkvnuWNPMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Title:                      DevOps Engineer Category:             Exempt Department:       User &amp; Systems Support Benefits:               22 Days Annual Leave, 15 Days of Sick Leave, 3 Days Personal Leave, 15 Paid Holidays Tuition… https://t.co/7sZfqWMxCU https://t.co/nsrOulqgIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. * Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work challenges. * Lead design research education to… https://t.co/x2xIrPeT80 https://t.co/kvgMBFcKsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Product Manager: Imports Assistant Product Manager burton + Burton. Burton, the world’s largest balloon and coordinating gift distributor, has opening for a trainee position will work directly under Imports Product Managers (PMs) to assist and… https://t.co/ZWGV3y5oJO https://t.co/NLB0t8bJK9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>