<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/6A6jlH5gxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/GdKalk7XaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/nIezZs4a9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/7OkvYwmIdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/fsLHN2vbcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/hPZbQ2q9Gv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/WOKt7ZW5W1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/8icZWywN1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/krUHs9KBGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/c9M5sprBZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/d2tCNElsom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/Y9hHDW5jK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/vJUXTwsSVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/P6OAI2nNWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/BKVdZ1oQyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/qhVb3TNpt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/ZgAvS6fMJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/ytorxoXZbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/D7vKskDwqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/jyRsIQWcLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/IGsHIt1jHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/L19cFUK3Ln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/ytorxoXZbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/DnraMHTLP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/XfkROe8xRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/DkDRtWxxmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/PoMvAnxrmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/bRarnVTxjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/e98kIil2w5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/vDXxrSdXrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/HyiCZ4MSGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/7FU6h51bbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/pMsIdloGWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/JV9MJKIqMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/lTRZUibeP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/wK2tiJWXlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/Ss0xeTN1aD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/3S80A1035t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/a4Ct84InVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/YBKzq18yM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/Tg25DFdM7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/s9G9M6C4vu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/ZMJeqBQXEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/up1BDlm5FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/2kThhTxkwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/HCo8wFFpvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire character. Train skill. - Peter Schutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/agiB18V1da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/45kbZiPdxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/XKo3sYw3dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/JUT7MeMGwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>