<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Java and Microservices Developer: Java and Microservices Developer No. of resources required: 2 Location: Milwaukee, WI Technical Skills: Java, SpringBoot, Angular, MongoDB, Kafka, Jenkins, Test Driven Development Job Description: The client is looking… https://t.co/RrLWDLTqQm https://t.co/lVkvOiP3kJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer – Entry Level: JavaScript Developer – Entry Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA – Careers – / –… https://t.co/BXjF3f6ymk https://t.co/Uuz9o1ZfNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dick's sales soar without assault rifles https://t.co/BdZYtDzSZh https://t.co/eZGGEn2e6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-19657 Location: Long Island City, New York Job Title: Java Developer Location: Long Island City, NY Position Type: Fulltime Interview Type: F2F Key skills required for the job are: Accountable for all phases of… https://t.co/1nwLbfIJPM https://t.co/5Ed5C4jZj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Core Java Developer: Risk Quants Core Java Developer has the unique opportunity of supporting a major financial services organization in the Capital Markets space seeking to bring on senior professional talent for server side core java… https://t.co/Uhm07ziVuH https://t.co/MLLN8I1Ob0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Enterprise Cybersecurity Software – Javascript): We’re looking for a highly talented Javascript Software Engineer for our El Dorado Hills office. As a Javascript Mobile Application Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers… https://t.co/tyYU94c4T6 https://t.co/ctbFFXMjHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman sued for writing 1-star Yelp review: A New York woman who gave a one-star review on Yelp to a gynecologist is being sued by the doctor for $1 million. https://t.co/UIU1cj1YGf https://t.co/jSjKhkyGbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Java: The Software Developer is responsible for analyzing business requirements, designing architectural solutions to problems, developing superior software solutions, and continually assessing and improving upon performance of… https://t.co/7qcjlBOPB2 https://t.co/lTgGi07Bgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer (RTB, AdTech): Our client is looking to grow the engineering team supporting our Exchange by adding developers who are; smart, get things done, communicate well, understand computer science, take pride in engineering, and want to… https://t.co/hMwJaU1ggO https://t.co/66mu5wKiyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-19565 Location: Bufallo Grove, Illinois Role : Java Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Buffalo Grove, IL Job Description : " – Experience onf J2EE – Experience with Front End(HTML, Javascript), JSF,… https://t.co/gztAbzjdTi https://t.co/AP94ggWBPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don Lemon: Barr faces consequence. What about Trump?: CNN's Don Lemon discusses ABC canceling the "Roseanne" reboot after Roseanne Barr's racist twitter rant today, and explains that the issue stems from a normalization of racism in the United States. https://t.co/MOPmgrm2BP https://t.co/jmepzwtWrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level-Java-Developer—DoD: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service orientedMid LevelJavaDeveloperto join our team atFT. Belvoir, VAto begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this role you will… https://t.co/yHv0UCSP5j https://t.co/D2ZdBhcUl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer: Embedded devices test engineer Ref No.: 18-20222 Location: Lake Forest, CA, California, California Job Title: Embedded devices test engineer Location: US- Rate: Duration:[Invalid Variable] # of Positions:1 Overview: Embedded devices test… https://t.co/VOSkJ0Yr1X https://t.co/LMLdgyk3ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confluence Moderator/Java Developer: The Confluence Moderator/Java Developer (Confluence Moderator), with 11 years of relevant experience, shall primarily oversee Confluence, but shall have experience in software design and development. Expertise in… https://t.co/RtKqYZ4fTd https://t.co/e11Ryz40Wq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greitens scandal looms large in Missouri's Senate race: On a recent tour of a mid-Missouri manufacturer, state Attorney General Josh Hawley was eager to talk about job creation and vocational training, the themes underpinning his visit. And the… https://t.co/Rpd7Vw5Glq https://t.co/41PKQYq4Ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer (Java) – Air Combat Training: Location: Cedar Rapids, Iowa Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Instructors &amp; Trainers Requisition ID: 8229 Want to work with some of the most talented, dedicated people on the planet?… https://t.co/nP6XPizfyp https://t.co/SnCbdh4Q8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (JAVA Developer): Cardinal Health at Home is a best-in-class provider of medical supplies to patients in the home. It is comprised of two separate operating segments: Edgepark, a leading direct-to-consumer (DTC) medical… https://t.co/6zsOSCvwlA https://t.co/UZRrAKBuzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java developer: java developer Ref No.: 18-20596 Location: Weehawken, New Jersey Role: java developer Location: Weehawken , NJ Strong in Java and must haveexperience on SpringMVC, Spring Boot,Hibernate, JPA. Good knowledge on DevOps,Jenkins Good… https://t.co/uOMctYyOIk https://t.co/ni6so0rjyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Why I blew the whistle on Starbucks: I do not consider myself to be an avid sports fan, but last fall, an NBA coach got my attention with remarks he made that were shared on Twitter. It was Gregg "Pop" Popovich, the seemingly surly but… https://t.co/O7bgkYVENg https://t.co/JrMJeDIBxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was the muse of Yves Saint Laurent: For more than three decades, French fashion designer Yves Saint Laurent turned to his muse Loulou de La Falaise for inspiration. On most days, she could be found at his Paris studio, offering counsel and designing… https://t.co/6vss0Gw8Ko https://t.co/8FJaFXoqRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: RealPage Careers – Browse and Search Openings Consumer Support Client Portal Contact – 1.************ Search Careers Company Services Contact Sales Cancel 1.************ Support – Asset Optimization – – YieldStar Overview – About Us –… https://t.co/SXeniTuslJ https://t.co/6887taJ9Da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-18991 Location: Arden, Delaware Position: Java Developer Location: Arden, DE Must: Java, Redux Scripting, XRE, Java script, CSS, HTML and unit testingGood to have:Mobile – web / app development experience"… https://t.co/ZZQWPdINFv https://t.co/VoEsLVYv9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump just put the 'Me' in his Memorial Day tweet: Memorial Day, for politicians, is a no-brainer. You express thanks to those who have served and condolences for those who have been lost. That's it. That's the statement. https://t.co/nDhO897H6r https://t.co/Y4jX4vMgBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer – What We Do Featured Tips for Building AI into Mobile Apps In the News – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work – Financial Services – Software &amp; Hi-Tech – Energy &amp;… https://t.co/nWhFl7aJGa https://t.co/Nk2htRpYwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test w/selenium, Java, SDET: Automation Test w/selenium, Java, SDET in Newark, US-DE, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant –… https://t.co/3F5cOUNEBc https://t.co/yNH0dS5KFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge orders Trump admin to consider releasing asylum seekers: A federal judge on Monday became the latest to rebuke the Trump administration for its immigration practices -- this time ordering the administration not to deny asylum seekers potential… https://t.co/YzFxjshI4k https://t.co/yCFzAn32Ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Enterprise Java Engineer 100% TELECOMMUTE: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $300k Posted Today We currently have offices in San Fran, Santa Monica and Miami but are open to hiring telecommute people if you are a strong match. We need 2 – 3… https://t.co/YjnWNyysLV https://t.co/prtqPbjjh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey says a 2020 presidential run 'would kill me': Oprah Winfrey is again dampening speculation that she may be planning to run for president. https://t.co/M88mmcpKZb https://t.co/JZsg3kckHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-25695 Location: beverly, California Title:- Java Lead/Developer Location:- Beverly Hills CA Duration:- 12 Months + – Java/JEE Experience: 6 – 10 Years – REST Services – Spring Boot – Microservices – Cloud… https://t.co/WFJKISXSBh https://t.co/0VNRECGbeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer Java/JavaScript APS: For BNY Mellon Sr. Specialist Developer – Java/JavaScript – APS job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking –… https://t.co/yh6FWPwoFv https://t.co/dVXCBDGwrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JAVA/JEE Web Developer: Req ID: 21790 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our… https://t.co/rGp9XZ03Nv https://t.co/cVKcYnTsEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Python Scripting: Java Developer with Python Scripting Ref No.: 18-25729 Location: Buffalo Grove, Illinois Title:- Java Developer Location:- Buffalo Grove IL Contract Role Python scripting Thanks and Regards Tarun Arora Sr. IT… https://t.co/SFv6DAM6tm https://t.co/osJ2fBDaMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developer: Java developer Ref No.:18-10434 Location: Arden, Delaware Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/11/2018 Proficiency with JAVA application development – Should be expert in Micro Service related development. Should have hands on… https://t.co/BQnmzeHSRs https://t.co/mdYY1Ieze4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Full Stack Java Developer Ref No.:18-00387 Location: Plano, Texas Start Date / End Date: 06/18/2018 to 12/28/2018 FULLSTACK Java Developer 50/50 Plano, TX 6 Months+ This is 50/50 front and back . 2 openings 1. 6-8+ years Java… https://t.co/McgL7FUa01 https://t.co/AIQy1HCel4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Customs seizes 108 fake Super Bowl rings https://t.co/Wk9GolnAOy https://t.co/EEZGvFiQAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a Java Developer to analyze, design, develop, implement, and support code; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as assigned. PRINCIPAL… https://t.co/8dayGJvUu4 https://t.co/5XFhD5BAoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer with Spring Boot: Core Java Developer with Spring Boot in Menomonee Falls, US-WI, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About… https://t.co/6MCVtYxgUU https://t.co/k8NdSjUsgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See moment divers reach teens in cave: These are the first images of rescuers locating twelve boys and their soccer coach after going missing for nine days. https://t.co/datwWJWdRq https://t.co/G4OjcOgHsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Experience SSO Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be responsible for providing software design and development, and second line production support for our external customers’ single sign-on suite of applications supporting… https://t.co/943jyqNMVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Tech Lead: Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food retailing, with a growing base of loyal shoppers.… https://t.co/9U7VmEzkOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Location US-CA-Encino Posted Date 1 month ago(5/10/2018 6:53 PM) Job ID 23599 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Republic Indemnity is a subsidiary of Great American Insurance Group – we market… https://t.co/htIbADzqY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything MoviePass does just makes things worse: I purchased a MoviePass membership back during a promotion. I paid $90 for a year of one movie a day, and got a MasterCard in the mail that I could use to purchase a ticket at the box office after… https://t.co/wGSHq97Nl6 https://t.co/7vfozHylsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer -Equities Tech: JOB DESCRIPTION CORE JAVA DEVELOPER The team is working on an various trading engines that supports algorithmic trading, smart order routing and crossing engines which serves the AMRS as well as global electronic… https://t.co/c4rsSC0Kvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microservices Java Developer (2-3 years experience) – Detroit, MI: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Microservices Java Developer (2-3 years experience) – Detroit, MI Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies… https://t.co/o3swRqudxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roseanne says she's fielding 'many' TV offers: Roseanne Barr says her TV career is not over. https://t.co/pwGrQShjS8 https://t.co/m5Z7H3dXBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cop stun-guns man sitting on sidewalk: Lancaster, Pennsylvania, police are investigating a video showing an officer using a stun-gun on an unarmed man sitting on a sidewalk. https://t.co/Mrj1BbtTZ9 https://t.co/nAq4YOCEbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer: Java Fullstack Developer Ref No.: 18-26112 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey Role : Java Fullstack Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Secaucus, NJ Job Description : Full-Stack Software Engineer- Frontend experience Backend… https://t.co/qPuJMXvtJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV station cancels newscasts after trespasser enters building twice: KRQE, an Albuquerque, New Mexico, TV station and CNN affiliate, canceled two newscasts and evacuated its facility Sunday night after a trespasser came into the building twice. https://t.co/TvVP6ptjPB https://t.co/ZkMVEo8NQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/akhnjxpBhY https://t.co/v3uEfFxFPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Join our Information Technology team where you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our customers’ needs and make it easy for them to do business with us. You will work fairly… https://t.co/QjUkAv5VGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Java (Web Services): at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Waltham, MA Constant Contact, Inc. helps small businesses and nonprofits connect with their customers, clients, and members. Constant Contact® champions the… https://t.co/nxYN7EIskX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27312 Location: pheonix, Arizona – 8+ experience in advanced Java Development – Extensive technical experience and development expertise in Spring-boot, Micro services, And APIs – Demonstrate strong written and… https://t.co/CNQfpO5BXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27983 Location: Farmington hills, Michigan Key skills required for the job are: Hibernate As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of analysts, developers, testers or engineers and drive delivery… https://t.co/dxYKwEV5LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation – Java: QA Automation – Java Ref No.: 18-28564 Location: Irving, Texas Knowledge and experience with automation development techniques, methodologies and best practices. Understanding of the SDLC process and principles. Understanding of… https://t.co/IdPJKOIgHu https://t.co/hcDfaAUtKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Microservices Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, Senior Java Microservices Developer to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a… https://t.co/9nxSYhCKLC https://t.co/zth77mhBXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA legend's mansion on sale for $19M https://t.co/z9i63Y2rQA https://t.co/mt74E4iii7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Primary Skills JAVA,J2EE,JAVASCRIPT,Angular,JSP,CI/CD,Test Driven Development Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Full Stack Developer for location Dallas , TX… https://t.co/9yZD47u7cz https://t.co/gQbiRLmGtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers Overview… https://t.co/bG7DB6ZHZp https://t.co/b5TSTiQGc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Position: Full Stack Java Developer Job Description: Arrow Electronics, Inc. a Fortune 150 company with global headquarters in Denver – helps the worlds best technology companies think Five Years Out, working together to… https://t.co/ZlAQXiupvh https://t.co/ip7t55SVN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test (Java): Software Developer in Test (Java) | Asurion Careers – Why Asurion? – Departments – Corporate – Customer Solutions – Device Repair – Supply Chain – Technology &amp; Product Development – Work At Home – Job Listings – Why… https://t.co/wGM9WeZUWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/uX64AAX4FG https://t.co/JjGfthPC0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ webservice product specialist: Java/ webservice product specialist in Woodbridge, New Jersey, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant –… https://t.co/yy89QiwLEn https://t.co/AESdflKNtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air pollution linked to 3.2 million new diabetes cases in one year: Levels of air pollution well below what is considered safe by the US Environmental Protection Agency and the World Health Organization are causing an increased risk of diabetes… https://t.co/US4mRwlF7W https://t.co/Nhpcj6wkyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans are mad at one of the biggest 'League of Legends' teams: Winning a professional League of Legends title is tough. Keeping fans happy, one esports organization has learned, can be even tougher. On June 13th, Cloud9 benched three of its best players:… https://t.co/GONIfWSs0O https://t.co/a6oD9YK7Nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Principal, Java Development: Job Description – Consults with internal business groups to provide application software development services or technical support. – Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior… https://t.co/509k1WOmVz https://t.co/DI8jwnWikE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vivo's all-screen NEX S is a frustrating glimpse of the future: More than anything, Vivo's NEX S is a fascinating machine. From a distance, it seems like any other big-screened smartphone. Look more closely, though, and the ambition becomes strikingly… https://t.co/wHKY3NP015 https://t.co/oRLAw22M07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job TitleJava Developer – ID:31170 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsJava, Oracle LocationIrving, TX Date Posted03/06/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking forJava, Oracle, to join their team… https://t.co/a2rSIvKGCt https://t.co/dp3SUAy6gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest plane in the US military turns 50: One of the largest airplanes in the world -- a jet that forever changed America's military and airline industry -- is turning half a century old. https://t.co/odXtYwg4jN https://t.co/zL7qdZHbMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Job in Plano, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA – Careers – / – Search Jobs – – IT Jobs – –… https://t.co/UV0KLJbVe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer (TS/SCI) – Herndon, VA for CACI in Herndon, VA 20171(map) Job Description CACI is seeking a Java Developer to be a part of our DTRA team in Herndon, VA. What you’ll get to do: Responsible for researching, designing,… https://t.co/OMpMYXyl5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a Mid-level Java Developer to analyze, design, develop, implement, and support code; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/P7HTHsMljB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java developer: Job ID 2018-3829 Location US-CA-San Jose Category R &amp; D About the Job Senior Java Developer- CPaas 88 is seeking a talented Java Developer to join our growing technology team. This is an exciting opportunity to become a member of… https://t.co/6EiFbAUjTM https://t.co/kZSi5awWDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Microservices Developer: Lead Java Microservices Developer (5 positions) Location: Cedar Rapids, IA Duration: 6+ months contract Strong Java Microservices exp. NoSQL databases like mongo is a plus Aws is a plus Insurance background is a plus.… https://t.co/OOsigVcOdU https://t.co/CAbnx8xywL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer $120-125K +Bonus McLean, VA Senior Java Developer will be part of development team supporting new and ongoing development efforts on suite of Pricing Applications within IT organization. Our team is made up of… https://t.co/bwAk7yjSgg https://t.co/DYbULef7pE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Memphis, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 06/05/18, Posted Date – 06/05/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverview Phone and skype. Location- Memphis, TN Rate- 50. Duration- 6months Java, J2EE – Servlets, JSP, JPA,… https://t.co/EXTxep2VXn https://t.co/4pksGmIRe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are your credit card perks shrinking? https://t.co/ZbvSCSSNl2 https://t.co/FKFcQGZjvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Microservices Developer: Java Microservices Developer Jersey City, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 06/06/18, Posted Date – 06/06/18 Primary SkillsJava 8Tax TermsC2COverview Job description Java Microservices FTE/Contract Jersey City, NJ… https://t.co/cgaxvVwgUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer (JAVA) – ArcSight – Provo, UT: Sr. Software Engineer (JAVA) – ArcSight – Provo, UT Tracking Code ******* Job Description Micro Focus is looking for software developers to work on its ArcSight Enterprise Security Manager (ESM)… https://t.co/dJXCdhPRKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr./Principal Java Software Engineer – Data/ETL: Summary: CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our new data services product offerings. We are in need of a senior level Java/ETL developer to work on data processing interfaces. Positions involve… https://t.co/Yw81lmQwAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Service Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Web Service Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Web Service Developer who is responsible for the web services design and… https://t.co/HjpBwKXhhe https://t.co/iqankjjEJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosenstein and GOP clash in fiery hearing: House Republicans sharply took aim Thursday at Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein and special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation in a heated hearing that came at the same time the House passed a… https://t.co/iuqzoarjK2 https://t.co/zxkZ6WimB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: 118015BR Job Description: Raytheon is seeking a Full Stack Developer to be an integral part of a Java Web Application development team to support both Raytheon products and customer programs in one of the following locations:… https://t.co/CMHJnfAYYX https://t.co/aYt2u6YzQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27983 Location: Farmington hills, Michigan Key skills required for the job are: Hibernate As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of analysts, developers, testers or engineers and drive delivery… https://t.co/h63fg5oUmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java Developer: At CoBank, our Software Engineer will be responsible for the planning, design, development and maintenance of integration solutions in support of the CoBank’s service-oriented architecture and Enterprise Service Bus… https://t.co/YSCN4dnDkp https://t.co/6ly02aYsiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL fines ex-owner $2.75 million after probe https://t.co/fewQ7rYpRl https://t.co/OnhuSIKNLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java IVR Developer: What you’ll be doing… If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and find ways… https://t.co/BYzMv6iWBq https://t.co/DeZeafQdBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Poll: Americans think Russia investigation is serious and should continue: Most Americans continue to believe that the Russian effort to influence the 2016 presidential election is a serious matter that should be investigated, but the constant… https://t.co/Yq4lMK7Dd0 https://t.co/Oy520xfpsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops with Linux/Unix and JAVA: Devops with Linux/Unix and JAVA Ref No.: 18-23750 Location: Timonium, Maryland Job title: Devops with Linux/Unix and JAVA Location: Timonium, MD Duration: 12 months Independent consultant – Expertise using Linux command… https://t.co/rdPvWhwyYl https://t.co/luxRRpPf81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla wants former employee's data from Dropbox and Facebook: The saga of Tesla and its case against former employee (and alleged saboteur) Martin Tripp continues this week with a subpoena against tech companies that include Facebook and Dropbox, which… https://t.co/slbdv36oTo https://t.co/bFMkCwmS44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer – Javascript / Node.js / Angular: Careers @WilmerTech WilmerTech provides a complete and effective employee orientation program involving induction, domain-related training sessions, cross-cultural training, and personality development… https://t.co/amsvJbiaba https://t.co/WPnnXl3n1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET – Selenium, Java: SDET – Selenium, Java in Morrisville, North Carolina, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know… https://t.co/cGQNb18BXG https://t.co/KlxqZ7haV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr./Principal Java Software Engineer – Data/ETL: Summary: CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our new data services product offerings. We are in need of a senior level Java/ETL developer to work on data processing interfaces. Positions involve… https://t.co/qBpTdro9SX https://t.co/XU7DKmYaX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Spark Developer: Java Spark Developer Ref No.: 18-26124 Location: Tampa, Florida Job Title: – Java Spark Developer Job Location: – Tampa, FL (On Site Position) Job Type: – Fulltime Job Description:- Hadoop Developer with string programming and SQL… https://t.co/bkcypjautj https://t.co/55MwuhoFIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: This feels like a tipping point on marijuana legalization: Voters on Tuesday in Oklahoma -- Oklahoma! -- became the latest in the US to approve broad access to marijuana when they approved one of the most permissive medical marijuana… https://t.co/TVUmz2Tn0L https://t.co/jbY6qQHm2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java: java developer-****** Ref No.: 18-27514 Location: o fallon, Missouri 1. strong java, webservices, micro services who can understand business quickly and provide solutions 2.Excellent communication skill. https://t.co/NI00YYHsXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-28012 Location: Phoenix, Arizona Position: Java Full Stack Developer Location: Sunrise, FL, Phoenix, AZ Full stack java/j2ee developer ( 5 or more years )with expertise in REST,… https://t.co/McyBu4vNLZ https://t.co/uBxgisS0rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's Keyword Snooze will help you avoid spoilers in News Feed: Last year, Facebook introduced a "Snooze" option that allows you to mute a friend for 30 days on your News Feed. Now it's extending that feature to keywords. According to Facebook,… https://t.co/GB587emACt https://t.co/fYrYf7ejtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer with networking: Core Java Developer with networking Ref No.: 18-24310 Location: San Jose, California Competencies Foundation: Advanced Java Concepts, Core Java, GUI &amp; Rich Clients, EIS: Network Engineer Essential Skills- Core Java… https://t.co/K96mNQHHiD https://t.co/8EvEMZF6kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer | must be certified as Sun Certified Java Programmer, Oracle Certified Java Associate, or higher cer: Java/J2EE Developer | must be certified as Sun Certified Java Programmer, Oracle Certified Java Associate, or higher certification… https://t.co/HKxC3rhWzm https://t.co/VYBEMvme3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defending World Cup champ Germany eliminated https://t.co/F1EceLwqg9 https://t.co/TTAFLN6H3r]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>