<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/mhXbcjR2tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/xqCWJ0Qabi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/X2iu1Xde9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/iTMPgQfvYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/IhomTdGrKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/3EEsdismWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/68pDCQkHfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/566R7fvXw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/gQJx9twNOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/RMDhH1j3EM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/3FkX4Bagmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/UyV64KtUmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/h6rITzVPio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/uHc64mP3S3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/2lh3mm5hpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/lXdQZ8wziS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/qiT7QxD99K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/WTIOdYCVjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/9yk8CNlxzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/JFIRQl6WaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Introduction to Ray Bradbury  http://t.co/3qNcihauvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/vdC6QGViKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/d3h3oYxDsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/py7UO4hHy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/BEeqmZmefR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/JZ4vbOMy55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/aqirL5EJw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/UkQ4ikH1hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/BEeqmZmefR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/ZwC0pLGbh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/LbOaafFAxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/HmYW9FH8wB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/zEzhnzq6pP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/iNRfcoqPca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/L7pexWkDgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/W5bTVjyMAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/L0i3qgW2cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/vjQCALsMmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/WHvZAvugTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have heard of Bitcoin?  Read these 10 important things you should know... http://t.co/uLuHVeeUMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/vJljllvR2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/XkZNPdxlW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/lPD0zNZX9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/iWB3NRlBYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/GCwFtwg8Zl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/uIFRSlZoQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/2y9J4JxLGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/UqJYb1SKNF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>