<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/5AirzzyMmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/7eiIwptDQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/wf9C3Ak7pQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/CboAjM840G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/aOE7clM8cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/ghg6o3Mfpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/V3AAJ6DnBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/p9h0wTAu6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Out why Facebook is great for Your Business  http://t.co/Z2zhslOvnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/gibBVbYuh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/0l3fzqP1VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work is the presentation of our capabilities. - Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/B2EmXDNK0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/xtIgIy0sG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/4jzR7jyVkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/I8tQsUn7zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/XKSTP13ykh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/RIWlzjBNPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/C0K9RdV8TP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/Ilu7rM6Khw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/DA2bnR9YCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/2uhCs68sBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/6ZbmLAFco8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/y7toM5jdSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/FGhMGZN9KA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/pPKFlrWh5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/Sr230s5vPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/soqGHh8mWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/CGHH54t3JC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is good for nothing unless you know the value of it by experience.  P.T Barnum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/zHHwT70EXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/IFKMGAMNch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/2siLAhKfhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/VJLN9JaQlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/vZHg2Agitr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/Uc2CrxXmOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/ke8FmOqJxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/msCgHefEvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>