<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnJHudak: The president is now touting the repeal of the individual mandate. Meanwhile, for the first time since ACA was passed, more…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece. "'There Isn't A Just #Housing Choice': How We've Enabled The Pains Of #Gentrification" - https://t.co/UV4Tes41wk via @NPR https://t.co/tRMntxTbae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What People Mean When They Call Dockless #Bikeshare a 'Nuisance' - https://t.co/6YvsaPhp4z https://t.co/kxnMDYIq4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FT: Facebook to ban ads for cryptocurrencies, ICOs https://t.co/uiasgvwgqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is winning by @ezraklein - https://t.co/NcYAAfEc70 https://t.co/lOIJ2JfLZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jennymarder: "Between 1965 and 2013, presidents made 33 policy proposals on average in each State of the Union address...Congress passe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arstechnica: Cisco drops a mega-vulnerability alert for VPN devices https://t.co/X8vTAMKkEg by @thepacketrat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mathematician Cathy O'Neil (aka @mathbabedotorg) says #algorithms embed existing bias into code — with potentially destructive outcomes. Everyone should question their fairness, not just computer scientists and coders. https://t.co/jJA5I4T2E0 https://t.co/O8hnqj42cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No One Wants Your Used Clothes Anymore - https://t.co/cg5JCxoqNr https://t.co/JYn6FnmOUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @data4democracy: check out the latest going on in the #D4D community. https://t.co/3oM64qzAhm https://t.co/IOzlnZHPPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @opentotrade: The @usmayors holds a panel discussion on #trade policy at its annual winter meeting in Washington, D.C. -
 https://t.co/a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @knightfdn: If you share our passion for the fields where we invest, we want to hear from you. Apply: https://t.co/yXL1OactOk #jobs #now…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewsHour: Before tonight's House Intel vote, we asked @MarkWarner about the Nunes memo. "I actually hope, if there's a way to get the c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The battle over #immigration and #DACA continues - https://t.co/SZ0nYZdsYF via @washingtonweek #politics https://t.co/FIwfMk9LZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathonmorgan: I'm excited to announce that @NewKnowledgeAI has raised $1.9M in seed financing to defend public discourse https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathonmorgan: @NewKnowledgeAI I talked with @TechCrunch about why we decided to raise, and the urgency of fighting back against onlin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HauntRRR: Looking for a freelance UI/UX designer.. Non esports related project.. Great pay and for reputable company.. RTs appreciated…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @18F: "When bringing DevOps into government, making it DevSecOps instead may be the difference between failure and success."  https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childish Gambino's 2018 Grammy Awards Performance - https://t.co/rjkj9SQ6Ef https://t.co/36RypDxjsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HenryJFoy: Billionaire behind hard Brexit lobby group buys himself Maltese citizenship - so he’ll keep EU benefits even as his organisa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you providing customers a great experience on your landing pages? This quick video shares why you should work hard to delight and not frustrate users. - https://t.co/6JTnS484Of https://t.co/D3bk36EtkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wallpapermag: Derrick Adams explores African-American travel in the Jim Crow era https://t.co/DsTxqilMlA https://t.co/dLOCTjMs1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rrhoover: This short video might shed a new understanding of materialism: https://t.co/OXMs9zrHbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic #DavidBowie! "Andy Warhol" - https://t.co/r0oIxL8zSF https://t.co/MaC09YZfyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow @ProductHunt Ah, bing rewards. Duh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see more of @alison__wright on @SneakyPeteTV. She's such an incredible actress. Love her on role on @TheAmericansFX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sxsw: Can Small-Donor Progressives Win Local Elections? The Intercept's DC Bureau Chief @ryangrim will discuss with @BetoORourke at the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller gathers evidence that 2017 Seychelles meeting was effort to establish back channel to Kremlin - https://t.co/uk0xyULHNk https://t.co/uQTX4yCf06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-OMB Director Stockman Says #Steel Industry Found 'the Biggest Sucker of All'
 - https://t.co/Y3ybYu2UuL #steeltariffs #tariffs https://t.co/Xv64yo9cf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Police Officers In Schools Really Make Them Safer? - https://t.co/G2a9dGhVd8 https://t.co/DDIWD6DJn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshuamarch: Love violent games as much as you want, if you don’t have a gun you can’t shoot someone https://t.co/Xj32xZjsUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @opengovpart: Are you in Washington, D.C. and want to know more about the state of #OpenGov? Join 
@SunFoundation and OGP on March 15th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Congress moves to drop #tariffs, some U.S. firms cry foul - https://t.co/S1WKE80LdI #trade #politics https://t.co/AWwh9lYQJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlishaOutridge: 'Each time you learn something new—you have reached success. Don’t ever forget that.' @startupsco @khalidboukdid https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arstechnica: Iceland's “Big Bitcoin Heist”—600 mining computers stolen from data centers in four separate burglaries between December 2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine Chao Confesses #Trump Personally Pushed to Kill #NYC's #gatewayproject - https://t.co/F5fKb31BpZ https://t.co/asdSVKBeq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StevenCiobo: Signing #TPP11 - an FTA that eliminates 98 per cent of tariffs in a trade zone with a GDP of $13.7 trillion that spans the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: Avoiding corruption in overseas trade has many ethical, as well as legal &amp; ultimately financial, pros. Here's why: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveThirtyEight: “People mistakenly assume you have to like something to do it over and over again." https://t.co/7bQEPQxMam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Once Ruled the Computer World. When Did Silicon Valley Become Brotopia? - https://t.co/2ogtc7ena4 #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/xWNAY30Dcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GovLoop: Learn how Data Center as-a-Service can optimize mission-critical applications in a timely and cost-effect manner. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jack: International Women's Day 2018 #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/Q4KbZ0qQjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BizCouncilofCan: Encouraging women to pursue careers in #STEM will help close the gender gap and promote growth. See new report from Ca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wallpapermag: Check out Conny Freyer and Eva Rucki of @Troika_London as part of the Wallpaper Power 200 list this #InternationalWomensD…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GovMattersTV: Digital transformations are underway. Find out the challenges that lie ahead from federal IT leaders and private sector e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boilerroomtv Who played the Theremin better? https://t.co/pNoOtOqdIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How #Trump’s Hudson Tunnel Feud Threatens the National #Economy - https://t.co/NNRM6DQD1J https://t.co/O8z2pJnTIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallpapermag FYI: Images on this article aren't displaying. https://t.co/0ERGOq5QYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @knightfdn: Social media offer an opportunity for journalists to be more transparent with readers. How is that playing out on #BlackTwit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @techreview: Many people might not realize that they’re making use of machine learning, but apps like Google Maps and Spotify are full o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Tomorrow, a New York district court will hear arguments in Knight First Amendment Institute v Trump, a case with huge ramification…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Given the pervasive use of social media among government officials and agencies, the First Amendment prohibits the exclusion of in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daringfireball: Alexa Is Laughing at People, Unprompted: https://t.co/Y3ELg7aRIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteveCase: How Zendesk, Switch, and Zillow look for talent outside Silicon Valley https://t.co/e4axoaNiqD "We realized none of us was o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveThirtyEight: Americans in general have not loved the press for decades and decades! 

According to Gallup, the most trust we had in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WWF: Big news for wildlife! Starting today, the world’s largest social media, technology, and e-commerce companies will work together t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Balkrishna Doshi, 90, wins Pritzker prize for architecture https://t.co/5v2iD0POvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewsHour: 2 Republican lawmakers ask for new special counsel to investigate DOJ, FBI https://t.co/j8dgaXgju8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FunkParade: It is with great sadness that we have to announce that Funk Parade will most likely not be happening in 2018.... https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndersonHouse: Join us for a one day spy camp at the Anacostia Community Museum March 17th  to learn about the diverse people who acted…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ocasio2018: Everyone in New York needs to check their voter registration *right now.*

We are getting reports of additional purges.

Co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: How can #exporters stay on top of fluctuating #Currency rates? What is a forward rating? Answers here: https://t.co/S9lRg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's make a good point Gary Cohn. So were tax cuts more important than standing on the wrong side of history? https://t.co/Ra2NNNY6kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @business: The U.K.’s trade with 70 nations is in danger of falling off a "cliff edge," lawmakers say https://t.co/ZvOoEoRD2B https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveThirtyEight: How much does the president’s mood (a frequent topic in the media) actually matter? https://t.co/tu1CR4ipk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jdawsey1: WHO? https://t.co/UXb6gUoXqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @knightfdn: How might journalists improve trust? Transparency, re-examining how stories are covered and sourced, recruiting and retainin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phone Makers Are Embarrassing Themselves By Copying #Apple’s Ideas - https://t.co/hCTkW960p0 #gadgets #tech #android https://t.co/OMEvsyHW7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulsingh: How to know when you're ready to start a business https://t.co/9Zx3GvcoTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamuelMarcLowe: UK-US Open Skies talks hit Brexit turbulence https://t.co/Pjcr3QjkUl https://t.co/isEPCKOhcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FT: fastFT: US trade official says tariff announcement expected in next few days https://t.co/T2959QsksF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckRossDC: People should step back and ask whether Nunberg would be likely to know this even if it was true.  https://t.co/1vTiACfY9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @knightfdn: When it comes to journalists mining Twitter for stories, users from marginalized communities are often concerned about lack…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @business: A tunnel predating World War I is key to 20% of America's GDP https://t.co/Tsn3WDTc1D https://t.co/DTEspewy5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daringfireball: Christopher Steele, the Man Behind the Trump Dossier: https://t.co/5yx1q0vWj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FinancialTimes: The US is offering Britain a worse 'Open Skies' aviation deal after Brexit than it had as an EU member https://t.co/apx…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: America's government is finding it hard to compete with the tech sector for talent https://t.co/e934vSNItQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With more and more Americans retiring, the "#Trump’s Social Security budget offers more work, less staff, longer waits" - https://t.co/1upTxP5CfP #politics https://t.co/yjuQsUUWO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pierce I hate touchscreens. They screens obviously attract fingerprints which I hate on my monitor. Keep your fingers off of my screen. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: Trump’s tariff war nudges Cohn toward White House exit https://t.co/qz34e2YyZH https://t.co/lxx8m9sjAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politico: Pruitt tapes revealed: Evolution's a 'theory,' 'majority' religions under attack https://t.co/VJTSU3cXja https://t.co/pCuH3TQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @business: The U.S. industries that could be most impacted by Trump's proposed tariffs https://t.co/zFmYflQyK6 https://t.co/45lCNgpq8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Hears Fiery Arguments In Case That Could Gut Public Sector Unions - https://t.co/0RTEEl7VwM #scotus #unions #politics https://t.co/NTTKHio2Lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday on the @NewsHour...

Trump declares "trade wars are good." Also: The unimaginable destruction of a Damascus suburb, women face retaliation in the U.S. Forest Service, and Shields and Brooks on the week's news. - https://t.co/Zo0id2eTVr https://t.co/ZZsAh10mkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: #Incoterms play a key role in international #shipping but how can you as a business ensure you're using the right ones an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: How does invoice discounting work? What is factoring? Here's a great guide on solutions for international payments: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mims: Median Uber/Lyft driver in U.S. makes $3.37 an hour, new MIT/Stanford study finds. 30% of drivers actually lose money.  https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: Our next #webinar is on what #exporters need to know about #AEO - Authorised Economic Operator status - with Vartan Consu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: Considering doing #business in #China? A Doing Business in China guide may be of assistance - read it here: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @opentotrade: Dutch PM Rutte Seeks United European Response to #steeltariffs - https://t.co/YPk1vx5KvZ https://t.co/oGZviugSyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Capitals: U.S. women's hockey team to attend PreGame at #StadiumSeries! #ALLCAPS 

https://t.co/s6iW0Sypg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High winds hit D.C. region, closing federal government and some area schools - https://t.co/XnkbiIpfr7 #dc https://t.co/hhwhqz3Ylt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattLaslo: Wow. Trump may be walking back his NRA comments any moment. https://t.co/xkeSGqLyB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Atomwaffen As It Celebrates a Member for Allegedly Killing a Gay Jewish College Student -
 https://t.co/tVPZMJax3j https://t.co/PXQcTy5K4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SBECouncil: SBE Council on @realDonaldTrump's tariff announcement: "Unfortunately, this move to impose tariffs will have unintended con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @noreaster: Meet the 25 Startups Competing at #SXSW Startup Night 2018 https://t.co/2AY1DztExj  #startupofyear #sxswstartupnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Digital_Gov: Join us on Weds, April 11, 11-12pm ET for an honest talk from @gerrymcgovern on identifying, prioritizing and continuously…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FT: Video: What the EU's fallback Brexit plan means for Northern Ireland https://t.co/0NG3jf3Lcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nickvegas: It’s easy to complain or say something negative. 

It’s hard to make something beautiful and on budget.

Keep doing the hard…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpentoExport: Are you a service company looking to sell internationally? This guide covers two key concerns: #VAT and #IP https://t.co/…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>