<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And then, if Republicans win big in LITERALLY ANY PRESIDENTIAL YEAR, they can increase it to 21 or 55 or Eleventy Gillion and One. This is a stupid idea that, once started, will escalate to absurdity in record time. https://t.co/2h0X4WwcOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wxgeek @senatorshoshana Assuming a highly seasonal wardrobe (Willie Brown, another political clotheshorse recommends three navy blazers, one for each season); he could easily spend $600,000 on suits alone. That leaves $200,000 for other rare accessories like high end watches and handmade shoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wxgeek @senatorshoshana It's not hard to spend $800,000 on clothes if someone wants expensive fabrics. A bespoke suit with high-twist (Super 180s and above) wool will be $10-20k from a high-end tailor. Vicuña and other Veblen good fabrics can run as high as $50,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wxgeek @senatorshoshana Trump's tie length is awful and while he may intend a longer tie to cover his girth, it only draws attention by moving the eye lower on his body. To look slimmer, he should consider suits with a vest or a rolled three button jacket with minimal darting a la J. Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most importantly, state affairs associate Brian Jencunas is available for the definitive opinion on politicians' clothing choices. Need someone to trash Trump's tie length, call me. Need someone to explain how Paul Manafort spent $800,000 on clothes, I'm your man. https://t.co/eGlGBSQNcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @IAaboutCA @mpetricone I just use these lists as helpful collations of places to avoid, so a broader net is fine by me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordylancaster If we work hard I'm sure we can get above 50% by 2028.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alex_Roarty: very interesting thread on immigration poll numbers, indicating the subject -- even in light of the child-separation polic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaayleyCoates Clearly you haven't fully processed the magnitude of giraffes being fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjciaramella: Imma let Scott Pruitt finish, but the greatest EPA grifter of all time was the guy who convinced his superiors that he wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Noahpinion: And I'm not just talking about "Jeb!".

I'm talking about George W. Bush's attempt to give amnesty to undocumented immigran…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Noahpinion: The most underrated event in American politics was the struggle for the Republican party between the Bush family and a nati…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Noahpinion: The flip side of this article is that if the GOP stopped nominating leaders who demonize Hispanics, they could probably be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hailhayes Alcohol can help, insincere compliments are good too since we'll just believe you really think we're the greatest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexNowrasteh: Lots of bad things were radical too:

The USSR was radical.
ISIS was radical.
European Imperialism was radical.
Eugenics…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeschlossDC: When billboard industry felt threatened by newspapers, 1917: https://t.co/0unml1Gs77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbuhl35: I still say it's BS that my wife dresses up my son in cargo shorts but makes fun of me when I wear cargo shorts. "He's just a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elliosch: New Gallup poll: For the first time Dems are more positive about Socialism than Capitalism https://t.co/vcSEZmwC4K https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be the first time "the Vineyard" and "middle class families" have appeared in the same tweet. https://t.co/9YJ2I6G0dZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lymanstoneky: I never knew what it was like to be worshipped as a God until my 7 yr old nephew watched me get to round 12 of Duck Hunt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HotlineJosh: America, 2018.

If you think Dems won’t go the celebrity route against Trump, all bets off... https://t.co/27PLT7Ok6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MilenaRodban: Cool, someone buy ads urging for Saudi to stop violating human rights and for UAE to release imprisoned activists and see…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanCrespo: Ok if it’s gonna be Space Force then we gotta rename the other branches so it all matches up.

The Navy is Water Force.
The…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjane87: I think about this often. https://t.co/PrMpbfE3D8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dick_nixon: She is right not to debate Shapiro. I don't care who she is. She won one election more than Shapiro ever will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johngizzi: Thinking about Paul Laxalt &amp; how history would've been different if Reagan had named him as a running mate: George H.W. Bush…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulSzoldra: Also, DoD’s budget this year is 700+ billion dollars and the generals constantly talk of “readiness” issues, as a disturbi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulSzoldra: Meanwhile, the Coast Guard has been warning of the militarization of the arctic for years as Russia is so far ahead, and C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulSzoldra: Reminder that we have to rely on private corporations and/or Russia to get astronauts into space these days, but now we’re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you think of her politics, Pelosi is a tough pol. @dick_nixon would approve. https://t.co/JPi1BDfx1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaitlynKiley I'd believe you've been replaced with a Black Oil or Yeerk control system before believe that happened. Come on Kaitlyn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan You know a reporter from Hartford is going to hit you with a chair at the next forum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is literally indistinguishable (besides the diction) from a Know Nothing Party pamphlet in the mid-19th Century. https://t.co/Ag2x3BO7eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntownCartoon @mattklewis Nixon didn't use TelePrompTers. His speeches were almost all memorized, a skill he'd trained as a young pianist who couldn't read music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattklewis: "Always give your best, never get discouraged, never be petty; always remember, others may hate you, but those who hate you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattklewis: "...greatness comes not when things go always good for you, but the greatness comes...when you take some knocks, some disap…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattklewis: "We think that when someone dear to us dies, we think that when we lose an election, we think that when we suffer a defeat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickZaiac But at least we'll be making stuff in America again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These have nothing in common. One is smart, hardball politics (the Kennedys recruited a janitor with the same name as JFK's first Congressional opponent, a popular councilman) the other a crime. https://t.co/7d7BsFHxg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to riding on these in 2033 after five cost overruns. https://t.co/UlpaXv6v9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iowahawkblog: Twitter conservative, or 1973 International Workers of the World newsletter? You make the call
https://t.co/IlHieoAuQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll never understand how propping up the exploitive, racially discriminatory, mobbed up taxi industry became a liberal shibboleth. https://t.co/RipVlpAwi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @redsteeze: Weird. It’s almost like voters don’t go for what’s popular in Brooklyn patreon podcast circles. https://t.co/o57OuHJRZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexburnsNYT: This might be the clearest echo of the Tea Party. The revolution never loses or retreats. It only advances in a different…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lieutenant_lady: there’s a woman walking around my coffee place with an honest to god snake on her shoulders and I just hope I’m that m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @goodrica: It's never good when Erin Brockovich calls #scituateMA water quality, worse than Flint, Michigan.  @PatriotLedger #mapoli htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @senatorshoshana: It's always oversight for thee, but not for me. They demanded action from Facebook. Facebook took action. Now they're…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @senatorshoshana: "Strategists raise alarms about Facebook delays in approving Hispanic political ads" https://t.co/FTIYI9mD9S

Stop. TH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAtheTeapot @Starbucks @harrahsnola You can't win if you don't play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @senatorshoshana: REMINDER: Prisoners who fought California’s wildfires cannot be firefighters once they are released https://t.co/nd4Qp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan Say what you want about Buddy Cianci, but he would have rolled out the red carpet for someone who wanted to invest in Providence and create jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mims: working on a startup called new car pass, you pay $1 for a new car and I run out of VC money in 3 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lyndseyfifield: Buried lede: there is a British Sandwich Association because of course there is. https://t.co/8hbR3lxY2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lyndseyfifield: Cold. Case. Killer. Leaps. From. Cold. Case. How could you screw up this headline IT IS A LAYUP. https://t.co/Y8NYw1uhOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*I = me and the great team of policy people, researchers, and California's Favorite Teapot, @IAtheTeapot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketplaceFair @RSI @Uber @lyft @Instacart @DoorDash @Postmates @TaskRabbit @Square @TSYS_TSS @Handy @josheidelson @business @IAtheTeapot The vast majority of freelance workers prefer their arrangement to a 9 to 5 job, that's documented by survey research we cite in the paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see work I've done making an impact in the real world, great sign for the policy team here at @RSI https://t.co/JwZ6o9OdE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCameronSmith @Reagan_Airport @Uber @lyft @RSI When I came in for the all staff I gave up on finding my Uber after the second one cancelled, took a cab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HayesBrown: It’s wild to think about how future historians will talk about football or basketball the way we learn about things like jo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylehmann: An appropriate promotion. Being a Mets fan will certainly drive you to drink. https://t.co/dYnKy4wJno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbarro: What I take from the Texas senate race polls is that Ted Cruz may be in a lot of trouble for re-election in 2024.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xan_desanctis: it seems many people remain incapable of distinguishing between "I think this is a good thing to say" and "I think peopl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Kristol's transformation from neocon Sarah Palin booster to woke NeverTrumper is one of the many bizarre aspects of contemporary politics. https://t.co/VhMONrScr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @miss_knierman: [wedding]

“Anyone know why these two should not be joined in marriage?”

Me: (from the back) THEY’RE DOING A CASH BAR!!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveThirtyEight: Blacks made up about a quarter of the Democratic Party, but Rs estimated the share at 46%. Rs thought 38% of Dems were…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidmackau: honestly..... this would totally be me as a spy https://t.co/YPh2Hb5IC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DamonLinker: FTR, I have no objection to the NYT statement about Jeong. I don't want her fired. But I do find pathetic the tendency of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana @IAtheTeapot @ne0liberal @calebwatney As a card carrying shill, I've never seen Shoshana as a kindred spirit. She has....beliefs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenDezenski @The_HorseRace @skoczela @HannahChanatry This could be a stock photo for "Oh? Really now?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aubsneal Doesn't this poor soul know that vodka goes so well with orange juice? (I may have a different takeaway from this than most.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickRuffini: 1) Russian meddling happened 
2) It wasn't that influential
3) It's probably an inevitable downside of an open, global…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickRuffini: Russian meddling is another instance the-terrorists-win-if-we-freak-out-and-change-how-we-do-things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickRuffini: So, the Russians glommed on to Abolish ICE. Would anyone say that this wouldn't have taken off without a few bad Facebo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickRuffini: “Medicare for All” is like MoviePass for health care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Noahpinion: We should definitely take a second look at subsistence farming, hunter-gathering, feudalism, nomadic pastoralism, and the o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylehmann No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: High-End Persian Rugs Attend Trial In Show Of Support For Paul Manafort https://t.co/9SrOOnEM9i https://t.co/GdopJo4EWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarcM_Morris: How to get those "savings" according to Bernie himself:

Pay doctors and nurses 40 percent less. 
Ban all brand name drug…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @senatorshoshana: Why the fuck would I just pretend my name is Shoshana if it isn't

Do you know how hard this shit is at Starbucks? htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelZfox @MargieOmero @KSoltisAnderson @ThePollsters Oh those halcyon days of "War-Chester County"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad polling alert: Attn @MargieOmero @KSoltisAnderson @ThePollsters https://t.co/NehHTaFmbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skoczela: I checked and it turns out there were some issues with weighting by region in the 1863 presidential approval poll. Also, cont…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @redsteeze: From the @perlberg Buzzfeed piece about McElwee... And Sean McElwee https://t.co/eczquK8mVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Redistrict: By my math: in 2016, 72% of Trump voters &amp; 66% of Clinton voters lived in precincts where most of their neighbors voted the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sgtjanedoe: People smarter than me: The Disney/Fox merger is worrying due to the creation of a potential monopoly.

Me: The Disney/Fox…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katrosenfield: It’s beach season and my shelves need clearing out, so how about a #giveaway? Get your hands on my creepy sea story, INL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @epicciuto: I think I need to start a new headline thread. The theme of this thread is SCIENTISTS WHO HAVE OBVIOUSLY NEVER SEEN A HORROR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Noahpinion: 1970s dystopian sci-fi premise: "There's a supercomputer in your pocket, and it knows everything you do, and you're addicte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @tstruble @jeffreywestling @RSI Start yelling cat fun facts. No context, just loudly interrupt with one every few minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daveweigel: What if Anthony Bourdain but evil https://t.co/SRRQfD1t2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @baseballcrank: Scandanavian countries have a unique culture that can't be replicated without Scandanavian demographics. https://t.co/Pu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is completely true and horrifying for the future of the country. https://t.co/ixOHzmfWHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyFratto: TRAVEL TIP: sometimes you go to a town &amp; avoid the “tourist spot” because you just know it’s going to disappoint.  The Old…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilusasha @jneeley78 We'll write when they throw you in Alcatraz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NoahCRothman: In a world in which outrage is not currency, which is everywhere but here, this is called dark/off color humor. Stop pret…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jessesingal: 2/ This is a PRIME example of how many on the left are full of shit when they say "I listen to marginalized people!" Reall…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jessesingal: Was just having this convo two nights ago with a friend who emigrated with his family from the USSR very young and gets in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MilenaRodban: Because they allow everyone to virtue signal- people who hate nanny states, people who love recycling, people who are fig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am the only one who thinks it's bizarre the FBI was trying to flip a boss to testify against his functionary? Isn't that the opposite of how it's supposed to work? https://t.co/bh1DgApWCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ianbremmer: I’m really glad I missed this. https://t.co/21tuultlwb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>