<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Rail Car/Bus and Equipment Instruction: Job Description Department Marketing Statement: The Manager of Rail Car/Bus and Equipment Instruction is a critical role within the Bus Maintenance organization of WMATA. The ideal candidate will lead a… https://t.co/L64980XOcx https://t.co/Szrh12RD2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-27412 Location: phoenix, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day! We have an urgent requirement for .Net Developer in Phoenix, AZ. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/s1kzTWEWhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth – Other U.S.… https://t.co/0cUsUfe5U7 https://t.co/lOOsKJFnJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SAP: Job Description Tracking Code ******** Job Description Toro is seeking a highly motivated individual for position of SAP Finance Business Analyst. The position acts as an intermediary between the business and IS to collect, clarify and translate… https://t.co/qLU2nz8Vw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Test Automation Engineer IP Telephony: Job ID 2018-3917 Location US-CA-San Jose Category R &amp; D About the Job Staff Test &amp; Automation Engineer – IP Telephony 8×8 is looking for an experienced Test Automation engineer for IP Telephony who is… https://t.co/HAV3fRABRw https://t.co/Ao6b7lWTCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Software Developer C#, https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, JavaScript: Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Design, build, test… https://t.co/gjmm3KBaBp https://t.co/AYRVR3yFuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Chatbot Developer: .Net Chatbot Developer Ref No.:18-10175 Location: Secaucus,, New Jersey Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/06/2018 Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills – Responsible for the development and design of web applications and… https://t.co/WPfgTB8JmQ https://t.co/C6VMlZ88mp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02186 Ref No.:18-02186 Location: Folsom, California Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Viplove Singh at ************. If… https://t.co/bX6JnBZCwt https://t.co/HwAYCdxVeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2kJvz5wZku Developers: *********** Developers Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/07/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex Systems, the nation s 2nd largest Information Technology… https://t.co/2KylvJmGwC https://t.co/DwV6Ie2Fcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Senior Developer Big Data, Pacific Investment Management Company LLC, Newport Beach, CA. Requires: Master in Computer Science or related plus 5 years experience. Background check &amp; drug screening required prior to employment.   recblid… https://t.co/VBFWFvmTzq https://t.co/VahOtw7PyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-24808 Location: Dallas, Texas Role: .Net Developer Location: Dallas, TX Duration: Full Time Permanent Skills Required: .NET development (C#.NET, WPF, Entity Framework, *******, *******, MVVM, MVC) .NET Web… https://t.co/AFeFx4YoHO https://t.co/F1hPKYuvmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/31/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/vEFsxaWpuE https://t.co/DFvgeSN5IP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Analyst: SAP Analyst MS CS, Engineering or closely related + 2 years experience or BS + 5 years experience or any suitable combo. SAP MM/EWM, WM/ BOBJ/LE, SD/QM/PP/FI. Travel required.   recblid 54i422d4mlobick2cefhfgs3cph63c https://t.co/czgLEcZO8g https://t.co/MQou2YBnYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Design Integration Specialist III (Aerospace/Aircraft) – System Integration: Individual will work within the Environment Build Service in the Product Systems organization. This position administers the application environments for Boeing… https://t.co/FMq4ayEWcP https://t.co/kO77M0Q1l8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Title .NET Developer State Texas Description Connection Services has a fantastic opportunity through our technical staffing division in Dallas, TX. We are looking for a Senior IT Security Officer. This is a full time contract… https://t.co/FREkFlbAGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Arlington, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/22/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/RThUFHJa3b https://t.co/EejAtQ6oTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Do you have Project Management Experience? Do you want to work at one of the top employee voted best places to work in St. Louis? Please inquire below!! Apex Life Sciences is looking for a Project Manager to work for a manufacturing… https://t.co/FfCyBuakWF https://t.co/fjXCki31Hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with Application Support: .Net Developer with Application Support Ref No.:18-09885 Location: Fort Lauderdale, FL Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 06/01/2018 Job ********* Developer with Application Support Relevant Experience… https://t.co/4qWytMLwm8 https://t.co/Nnq60Aw2aD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockbuster Chinese tech IPOs face bumpy ride as trade tensions rise: HONG KONG (Reuters) - Chinese tech titans preparing to float in Hong Kong and New York are likely to face a bumpy ride if trade tensions between the world's two biggest economies… https://t.co/zKS1cwMUzq https://t.co/g0rq3CEO3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Applications Developer: Senior .NET Applications Developer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10309 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Senior .NET Applications… https://t.co/hEHIDv6FFh https://t.co/hGcW1mVrrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon wants to foster small independent delivery fleets: SEATTLE (Reuters) - https://t.co/lpiTRnheas Inc on Wednesday said it would offer incentives to entice entrepreneurs to set up their own small package-delivery businesses as part of Amazon's latest… https://t.co/p85dVZ8ipB https://t.co/G82z312lA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Summary Perform software development of new requirements, support development on existing code base, and optimize a highly complex application built in C# *******. Perform work within an agile development and apply a systematic approach… https://t.co/hmAqbE5iZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Vision/ Machine Learning Software Developer: Job ID: ********-10630-TL Company Name: Verisk Analytics Description: Computer Vision/ Machine Learning Software Developer Geomni, Silicon Slopes tech-company located in Lehi, is currently seeking… https://t.co/4zZke4H3hL https://t.co/r01wBNnCwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10298 Job Location United States Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and product development team. We design and… https://t.co/mxdkmgcnNp https://t.co/afpwiHpaDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: The .Net Developer will be responsible for web applications. Role will be developing new applications and upgrades and supports existing applications. Responsibilities: 1. Support existing applications. 2. Develop new applications by… https://t.co/iX5hRSUlo1 https://t.co/qGgjMmHVHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer (Full Stack): SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER (FULL STACK) HIGHLIGHTS LOCATIONS: Houston, Texas JOB TYPE: Contract-to-hire or direct hire SALARY: BOE JOB SUMMARY GTN is seeking a Sr. Full-Stack Software Engineer to join our fast growing… https://t.co/1nod6TbMwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (C# /.net / Cloud) Build Modern API’s – A FORTUNE Top Best Small Workplace: Careers – REPAY Skip to content – Careers – ************ – Log In – Request a Demo REPAY Realtime Electronic Payments – REPAY Solutions – Products – Credit… https://t.co/jHAouEVKUh https://t.co/yld7g6n2VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Data Scientist: Climate Data Scientist Palo Alto, California Data Science Full Time One Concern is a startup which specializes in Artificial Intelligence for Natural Disasters. With our team of global disaster scientists and engineers, we have… https://t.co/XVqht3qxDZ https://t.co/Qx5hWTYMvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer, Willis Towers Watson Job #******YM, Philadelphia, PA Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Glassdoor – Linkedin – Twitter – Facebook – English – Espaol – Franais (FR) – Franais (CA) – Join Our Talent Network – English English en – Espaol… https://t.co/fok5WreS6p https://t.co/z8w0tOJnls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Job Description Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May… https://t.co/M8HXq75m6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer | analytical, problem solving, and decision-making skills, including the ability to identify technologica: .NET Developer | analytical, problem solving, and decision-making skills, including the ability to identify technological and other… https://t.co/iR2YC28EuZ https://t.co/rHVAHVUKMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Winston Salem, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Our client is looking to expand their development team in the .NET Space to help enhance… https://t.co/QEFLAVVBmD https://t.co/XISwH3WLC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst-.Net,IIS: System ************,IIS Ref No.: 18-20635 Location: Mt Laurel, New Jersey 5+ years of experience working in .Net Framework which includes IIS Good Hands on working with windows &amp; Sql server Should have very strong communication… https://t.co/IOCu3pYDO3 https://t.co/hXwvANTkKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Title .NET Developer State Texas Description Connection Services has a fantastic opportunity through our technical staffing division in Dallas, TX. We are looking for a Senior IT Security Officer. This is a full time contract… https://t.co/Uat0ECuDjO https://t.co/LFbHaiB1V0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) knowledge: .Net Developer with MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) knowledge Ref No.: 18-24207 Location: Lakewood, New York Role: .Net Developer with MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems)… https://t.co/rP1Mkt4MOe https://t.co/fZirWA9WzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Full Stack Engineer: EXPERT FULL STACK ENGINEER Looking for an experienced Full Stack Engineers to be responsible for the development, testing, and implementation of innovative customer-facing native mobile and web applications and be the… https://t.co/FJ2aLzrHoA https://t.co/6Gc6xnXf0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI developer: ******* developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview 1. 1. 6-10 years experience developing in ******* 2. MVC, C# 3. SQL 4.… https://t.co/kTsg0La3uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer I, II Phoenix, AZ: .NET Developer I, II – Phoenix, AZ Job no: ****** Work type: Full Time Regular Location: Arizona Categories: Banking, Information Technnology The .NET Developer I (Software Developer I) assists in improving the Bank’s… https://t.co/aBhbpIopJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Description HI’s client is adding an ASP/C# .Net Developer to its teamin NYC. The role will design and develop web based n-tier applications that will be used by end clients as well as internal teams. REQUIREMENTS: * Strong C#/ASP .Net… https://t.co/eDcjhfRzPM https://t.co/DxHGBrGduc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You’ll work in Application Support as a crucial role in the DevOps model Verizon Wireless is utilizing. You will be monitoring, analyzing and supporting a new project which is part of the Smart… https://t.co/lZnI4yJ6we https://t.co/23vwUtAVhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – Enterprise Data/Content Mangement – C#, https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v,: Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time… https://t.co/ilmc6Q5eUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer – Python: San Francisco, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Engineer with solid analytics experience, please read on! Based in beautiful Downtown San Francisco, we are a unique and highly innovative… https://t.co/IZlGNKW5M2 https://t.co/G6M3kZDySZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Developer – Corptax: Employer, a CSC company, is transforming the business of tax through technology and business process expertise. Offering the first and only single platform solution on the market, Employer handles an unlimited… https://t.co/AN7dp7swl1 https://t.co/oWY8X51T8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Architect/Developer: .NET Architect/Developer Ref No.: 18-01530 Location: Chicago, Illinois Position Type: Contract Start Date: 06/12/2018 Roles &amp; Responsibilities Re-architecture project of *********** they have 9 products that need re-platforming… https://t.co/a653VC5xbf https://t.co/ycFFxTKSNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer in Chantilly, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us – What… https://t.co/zhqdhx9ktt https://t.co/klEp9e8PIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer FTE: .NET Programmer Job | .NET Programming Job | .NET Software Engineering Job | .NET Developer Job Consulting Training Blog Careers About Us Contact Us CONSULTING TRAINING BLOG CAREERS ABOUT US CONTACT US ********** ******************… https://t.co/86f0VjiOc5 https://t.co/hcMcJi0KMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Norfolk, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/13/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/xpeTJIf8Uw https://t.co/vBJUvh8THf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-01046 Location: Irvine, California Position Type:FullTime This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional offices in… https://t.co/auCmq0UuAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer/Lead: Sr .Net Developer/Lead Ref No.: 18-24951 Location: pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Hello, Hope you are doing great. This isVishalfromEnterprise Solution Inc. and I am writing to you regarding an excellent job opportunity based out of.… https://t.co/WkeW4JHFsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-27412 Location: phoenix, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day! We have an urgent requirement for .Net Developer in Phoenix, AZ. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/8tFqtqQugH https://t.co/WBiY2Q6Enw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / Dotnet Software Developer: To discuss in more details about this opportunity feel free to reach me soon on #************ or email your resume to ******************************* ROLE : .NET SOFTWARE DEVELOPER III LOCATION: 440 S. CHURCH ST.,… https://t.co/LKtw5FUcAw https://t.co/bktbiNuuKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-level .NET Software Developer: At Experian Health, our employees have the opportunity to shape more than products – they shape the future of U.S. healthcare. Experian Health is a pioneer for innovations leading the way in revenue cycle management,… https://t.co/ULHVE6ZMGq https://t.co/QWGnx305ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer w/Azure: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Senior .Net Developer with Azure experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that… https://t.co/W9jsP7hpA3 https://t.co/9TTtsgP9fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02186 Ref No.: 18-02186 Location: Folsom, California Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Viplove Singh at ************. If… https://t.co/sGrwDLmKA1 https://t.co/toOypH3LwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/HNGuAXR2cG https://t.co/n7RsNwqVpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with MES: .Net Developer with MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) knowledge Ref No.: 18-24207 Location: Lakewood, New York Role: .Net Developer with MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) knowledge Location: Lakewood NY Duration: 12… https://t.co/E0yuKroJd2 https://t.co/ybjjMwpAgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#.NET Developer: Our direct fortune 500 client is in need of C#.NET programmers to join their dynamic team. Contract and Contract-to-Hire positions available. Required: – 5+ years C#.NET experience – 3+ years SQL programming experience – 3+ years SQL… https://t.co/0SgzV2VR1l https://t.co/bAyJImUTqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: North American, UK, Asian regulators press EU on data privacy exemption: WASHINGTON/BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Financial watchdogs from North America, Britain and Asia are urgently seeking a formal exemption from the European Union’s tough new data… https://t.co/UlY8YFyGGh https://t.co/GuGMpdWWOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#/.NET Engineer AWS: Senior C#/.NET Engineer – AWS at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive –… https://t.co/zZpESP016d https://t.co/isrMmN5l96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Senior Developer for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dev focusing on dsgn, cdng, qlty assrnc of cmplx prdct features in a dev team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd &amp; 6 yrs exp req’d. Will also acpt Master’s dgr &amp;… https://t.co/ISSAizwYHl https://t.co/K9OLyGIvt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Description – .NET Developer Job LocationUS-MD-Rockville | US-IL-Chicago Job ID10268 Job LocationUnited States Alternate locations DC1, IL2 Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm… https://t.co/IO4TdcfQwa https://t.co/XJZMIrpWuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: .NET &amp; C#: Our Chicago based client is seeking a Full time Lead Software Engineer who is passionate about technology and software development. The Lead Software Engineer position will challenge you and provide you opportunities… https://t.co/hNxpeqrdzB https://t.co/bcU9z7gywr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2kJvz5wZku Developers: *********** Developers Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/07/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex Systems, the nation s 2nd largest Information Technology… https://t.co/5PKPQaVF1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Specialist 2: Business Title GIS Specialist 2 Requisition Number 35553BR Salary Plan ENS Grade 128 Division Telecom Employee Type Full Time Training and Certifications Technical Discipline-Related Training preferred, if applicable. Visa Sponsorship… https://t.co/2QmTgLqD1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer – C#, WCF and AngularJS: Senior .NET Developer – C#, WCF and AngularJS in Teaneck, US-NJ, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – –… https://t.co/bJHCNhToNB https://t.co/ZjBARbCt7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software https://t.co/ajsyo2JfPd – TS/SCI – Tampa, FL: Designs, develops, codes, tests, and debugs complex new software products, and makes significant enhancements to existing software. – Researches and integrates design strategies, product… https://t.co/v0ZbhoiInz https://t.co/Rpplsn5ayG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Engineer: San Francisco, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted 06/21/2018 If you are a Front End Engineer with streaming experience, please read on! We are a movie streaming company located in the heart of San Francisco! We have been growing… https://t.co/m7RTXyioBm https://t.co/pB5anMFCWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software QA Engineer – Network RD (Graduate): Systems Software QA Engineer – Network R &amp; D (Graduate) Description at Aruba Networks Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Home Search Search Jobs Keyword CountrySelect CountryCanadaChinaCzech… https://t.co/LTiO45vbIJ https://t.co/T2JHajyJ73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/nbLrnWxi1H https://t.co/P12a9DiSr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer for .NET Cloud App: Join a high-powered group of people who write amazing graphics software for project planners around the world. Our customers love us because we make communicating project plans so much easier. We are an… https://t.co/gQGvJyju4x https://t.co/6VDklQWaNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Irvine, CA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/18/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Development and maintenance of software applications built using Microsoft… https://t.co/yxOWLv9jnD https://t.co/qdz7IYC0dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging the status quo for PAC management solutions. We do healthcare differently and we are changing… https://t.co/h0ILlxi49S https://t.co/ysq5YfqlcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Peter Thiel: big tech directors miss shareholder meetings: BOSTON (Reuters) - Some small investors who want to give a piece of their minds to big tech company directors are losing their only chance: many board members are skipping annual… https://t.co/khyUdgSb9R https://t.co/3oWdHoH1gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#.NET Developer: *********************** LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of Bed Bath and Beyond, offers a wide selection of high-quality, personalized gifts for all recipients and occasions. Position Summary: If you like to stay current with… https://t.co/0TBw042uoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: We are currently on a hunt for a .NET SOFTWARE DEVELOPERto join our team in Philadelphia. YOUR RESPONSIBILITIESINCLUDES: * Drive software architecture decisions for firm-wide critical data systems. * Develop solutions using… https://t.co/FKhO4ZY6J6 https://t.co/uxhoViLc6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-18928 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested for, send me updated resume along with best time to contact. Position : Sr. .Net… https://t.co/WZrWsby5f9 https://t.co/64FGl1kxXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Reporting Analyst: – BI Reporting Analyst Company Rockloans Marketplace LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Who We Are RocketLoans, a Quicken Loans company, is an online platform revolutionizing how individuals get a personal loan. Every day, more and more… https://t.co/DXri0FcY7z https://t.co/uSHs7QF2vh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#.NET Developer: Great opportunity for strong C#.NET developers from intermediate level all the way up to lead level to join a fortune 500 company located in the Cleveland area. 6 month and 12 month contract-to-hire/permanent positions available.… https://t.co/w9qhj954VX https://t.co/8zguRa9Vn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Software Engineer (Molecular Biology): Careers Center | Research Software Engineer (Molecular Biology) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including… https://t.co/fguqKwNx9r https://t.co/yvOgXr0LMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/FmZBbd0dPJ https://t.co/7GWc1LXdA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/41AqhwiRpY Developer: We are excited to bring a new Salesforce Developer to our team in the Washington D.C. and Alexandria, VA area. Please note that this role has special requirements, including the requirement for US citizenship and you… https://t.co/h8Y2yWFTWn https://t.co/CZgr4hlUKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.NET Engineer: C#/.NET Engineer Job Responsibilities: – Translating product requirements into software solutions – Ensure software development lifecycle is followed which includes architecture, design, code, unit test, code review, etc – Work in… https://t.co/6doFGg0woI https://t.co/CuGlsp3EWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS, DB2 job – Asset Servicing – Jersey City, New Jersey Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation –… https://t.co/hWByShMjsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator ===================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: Public TrustClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Duties and… https://t.co/qacjxn3MLO https://t.co/mhvw9QipC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer (Angular&amp; C#/.NET) 420 Friendly /100% REMOTE: Seattle, WA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today *** DISCLAIMER!!! You must be comfortable working for a company that is in the Cannabis Industry*** If you are a Sr. Full Stack Engineer… https://t.co/izI7wDuPAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: US Citizens and GC Candidates only Description Client is looking for a C# developer responsible for building a C# application, including anything from back-end services to their client-end counterparts. Your primary responsibilities will… https://t.co/MsLR0m4HmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Quality Coach: Only candidates who submit a resume and complete the full application will be considered – anyone without a resume will be declined automatically. For assistance with your job application please use our External Candidate… https://t.co/Pma2nR3IUa https://t.co/4EspTMrOFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Programmer: Description of job: The Nonproliferation Systems (NS) Group, within the Nuclear Security and Isotope Technology Division (NSITD), Oak Ridge National Laboratory, seeks to hire a .Net programmer to join its Software Development team. NSITD… https://t.co/cVcZQrInjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c#,.net and web security: Job Titlec#,.net and web security – ID:31901 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsC#, .net, Telerik, Ssis, Web Security LocationTemple Terrace, FL Date Posted06/11/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications… https://t.co/tnFE7IrvBj https://t.co/9TOBDeLsin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr level .NET Developer: Jr level .NET Developer in Norfolk, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network –… https://t.co/I9BZgoUeNW https://t.co/tLYwNK0ZPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Arlington, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and developing web… https://t.co/X2NyQ4xdW4 https://t.co/0JgXOvJsrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Hyattsville, MD Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/12/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/lIjqkR66Vv https://t.co/YkwFgaw8t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Manager, Appl Development (Ruby, C#, .NET, SQL Server): Group Manager, Appl Development (Ruby, C#, .NET, SQL Server) Manages a medium to large-sized or multiple small teams responsible for all phases of the systems development and implementation… https://t.co/3VP48spNmZ https://t.co/YCpuXZUU8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer (C#, F#, VB, ASP): As a Senior Level .NET Developer, you will be filling a role at Huntington Bank to support, assist, and enhance new vendor based applications being installed, enabling capital optimization and pricing decisions… https://t.co/PuIHGJv4oS https://t.co/v8fCmcLVjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (C# /.net / Cloud) Build Modern API’s – A FORTUNE Top Best Small Workplace: Careers – REPAY Skip to content – Careers – ************ – Log In – Request a Demo REPAY Realtime Electronic Payments – REPAY Solutions – Products – Credit… https://t.co/oxJLbDULuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer 3: Digital Experience Engineering – Full Stack Software Engineer 3 At Asurion, we don’t just redefinewe reinvent. We began by establishing a culture that rewards results and isn’t confined by a hierarchy. As a result, we have… https://t.co/MMa8rwjPNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan's Foxconn calls Sino-U.S. trade spat a 'tech war': TAIPEI (Reuters) - Foxconn, the world's largest electronics contract manufacturer, on Friday said the U.S. and Chinese governments are engaged in a technology war, not a trade war, describing the… https://t.co/ikVIIj9pVd https://t.co/XECOs2E1hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Glen Allen, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Richmond, VA .NET Developer Required 5+ years of application development and implementation… https://t.co/zWcAsJwgmc https://t.co/UrlUI4p9mN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 9301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers,… https://t.co/PVy2EtsV4R https://t.co/m41TFECHcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Operability: Senior Software Engineer – Operability at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Who? You’re someone who is enjoys being directly accountable for the reliability of a business-critical, large-scale enterprise… https://t.co/i1pMOHsEX8 https://t.co/puqNmitrNG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>