<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Object Oriented Developer: Object Oriented Developer st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 03/29/18, Posted Date – 03/29/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard skype linked in The need is for a strong developer with… https://t.co/fFUt82C6Bl https://t.co/bU9uv0ALYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Required: Applicant MUST have two solid years of Django application development. Applicant MUST have solid knowledge of Python. Solid knowledge of the principles of class-based object-oriented programming. Solid knowledge of standard… https://t.co/84eBY3CjW4 https://t.co/8RNDM8siym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Developer/Python Developer: Job Description We are looking for a Python web developer with following responsibilities Write well-written, self-documenting code that follows best practices and design patterns Design and implementation for… https://t.co/1joLxTefRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Our Company: ThreatQuotient believes that the foundation of intelligence-driven security is people. The companys open and extensible threat intelligence platform, ThreatQ, provides defenders with the context, customization and… https://t.co/dczAkUH6Ua https://t.co/XeRejTmxF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Python Developer: Jr. Python Developer Ref No.: 18-19686 Location: Sunnyvale, California – Candidate should have strong hands-on developmentexperience in python scripting – Should have hands on experience in modelling in Python – Should have… https://t.co/7tGvAl6jjG https://t.co/exLzcFYxCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SOFTWARE ENGINEER: POSITION PURPOSE The Sr. Software Engineer is responsible for joining a product team and contributing to the software design, software development, and overall product lifecycle for a product that our users love. The engineering… https://t.co/HQHlgG2B6A https://t.co/ebi35LlMuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description:Leidos is looking for a Software Developer to join our Corporate Computer Information Systems Group.   This position can be supported as 100% telecommute. In this role, you will work on building out a big data system to… https://t.co/srUqhBhEl7 https://t.co/xW90NwPVBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI/Machine Learning Senior Engineer (Java &amp; Python): AI/Machine Learning Senior Engineer (Java &amp; Python) at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Twilio Understand is the brain of Twilio’s natural language understanding (NLU). Twilio Understand,… https://t.co/rS3YxRjqcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): 106428BR Software Developer (Python/Django) VA – Herndon 106428BR Raytheon Intelligence and Information Services (IIS) – Raytheon Cyber Solutions(RCS) is looking for an experienced Software Developer to advance several… https://t.co/M73TxtIrlC https://t.co/otb7rqSViF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE ENGINEER PRINCIPAL: POSITION PURPOSEThe Software Engineer Principal is responsible for joining a product team and contributing to the software design, software development, and overall product lifecycle for a product that our users love. The… https://t.co/bPteYbGVzB https://t.co/ZGwNWB1dgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python – TS/SCI with polygraph required: DESCRIPTION: ABOUT EMPLOYER At Employer, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/aDpY9eA5dl https://t.co/3SHobWPMLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Information Security Analyst: Join our Winning Team as a Senior Information Security Analyst At CARFAX we are constantly EXPANDING our product and technology offerings!  This means we are continually bringing new, innovative products to market… https://t.co/tZip9XlXlx https://t.co/3yRTPnMJ23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python C++ Developer Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging skills,… https://t.co/rz1CCorJKI https://t.co/QbBv7cM4JQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II w/Python: NO SPONSORSHIP Network Engineer II Salary: $100k to $110k to $120k + 3% bonus Location: Wilmington, DE – Hagerstown, MD – Marietta, GA Looking for a Network Engineer not an operational support person with large enterprise… https://t.co/bNjKn9BEJZ https://t.co/f7PbOGN7Iu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/km7VNWhyyF https://t.co/52Pkd6Qa8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. DevOps Engineer: Sr. DevOps Engineer Santa clara, California – United States Job Start Date – 05/09/18, Posted Date – 05/09/18 Primary SkillsDevOps,CI/CDTax TermsC2COverview Position: Sr. DevOps Engineer Location: Santa Clara CA Duration: 6+Months… https://t.co/yMdNrUQ757 https://t.co/e1gh80PmxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Product Developer – Java/JavaScript/React/Node: Join our elite IT team as a Full Stack Developer – Java/JavaScript As a Full Stack Developer, you will be a part of the Product Services team.  At CARFAX, we create products for our consumers and… https://t.co/Y0wblzVxjQ https://t.co/DQXpnPNUIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate – Application Support #180045983: Associate – Apps Support Columbus, OH. Design, develop, create, administer &amp; maintain computer apps software or specialized utility programs. Provide production support, troubleshooting production apps issues… https://t.co/CQ1bNhE2Hy https://t.co/sCHpdTNm3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: Are you an experienced Python/Django/Full Stack Developer looking to do work that matters? Forum One is looking for a Senior Developer to join our team and work out of our office in Washington, DC or Alexandria, VA. What you’ll… https://t.co/M5R0qGYe7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime Position Responsibilities: * Should be able to understand the test infrastructure and Test Framework * Good knowledge of OOPS concept. * Should have hands on experience on… https://t.co/f0cYPiBPhd https://t.co/lJ6gcwjprK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular TypeScript HTML CSS NodeJS &amp; Python SQL Full Stack Web Enginee: ANGULAR TYPESCRIPT HTML CSS NODEJS &amp; PYTHON SQL FULL STACK WEB ENGINEER MULTITHREADING NEW YORK Qualifications: Bachelor’s Degree educated, or higher Hands-on coder with lots of… https://t.co/6B6W2Tq4GZ https://t.co/Ay2Lo9WIqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Software Developer: Everyone communicates. It’s the essence of the human experience. How we communicate is evolving. Technology is reshaping the way we live, learn and thrive. The epicenter of this transformation is the network—our passion. Our… https://t.co/jlGPwZcrbA https://t.co/X6HTUDtYKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/HuBsVnXnWV https://t.co/mfO0mBRs0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Backend Developer/Engineer Professional: Looking for a Financial Developer/Engineer Professional that has Python Backend Developement Salary: $100-120k Location: McLean, VA 1-2 years plus hard core Back End Server Side development in… https://t.co/92Tc9EVffN https://t.co/MhOih8vbxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – (C++, Linux, Python- Proficiency): Req ID : 430589BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Member of the Military Support Programs (MSP) Flight Test and Simulations (FT&amp;S) team that operates, develops and… https://t.co/cGK1P7TkDO https://t.co/9kgZqqkP0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: Are you an experienced Python/Django/Full Stack Developer looking to do work that matters? Forum One is looking for a Senior Developer to join our team and work out of our office in Washington, DC or Alexandria, VA. What you’ll… https://t.co/FJVHu9QHOb https://t.co/m3VkamlZA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Policy Orchestration Engineer: Armor, Inc., the leader in Managed Detection and Response, is looking for a talented and highly motivated engineer to join its Security Operations Department. The Security Policy Orchestration Engineer will be… https://t.co/XNJhwJ42GR https://t.co/xFezoNH1fG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineering – C/C++, Python, Java, Matlab: Req ID : 430677BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : We are seeking a Software Engineer to join the dynamic and growing Space Protection Programs Software… https://t.co/Pk24SYQH0J https://t.co/HSNbIHwd9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Manager (Java/Python): The ideal candidate can manage a team of engineers and participate in software design and coding. About the role Collaborate with team members in crafting technical vision and establishing best practices Work… https://t.co/zFo5NLEcNB https://t.co/Fa0AhycXFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Developer – Python: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-130K +bonus Design, develop and support systems within the financial modelling and research area. Design and develop new code and review existing code changes to ensure… https://t.co/WMKD3Vn23o https://t.co/V27GisKZpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splunk Developer: Splunk Developer Ref No.: 18-18132 Location: Pleasanton, California Hi, Hope you are doing great Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Splunk Developer with the client based in… https://t.co/RvG3mUT0ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI (Business Intelligence) Intern: At GoReadyMade, we are building the next Food Tech unicorn. We’re offering a career kick-start for entrepreneurial minded, data driven grads. Backed by a major global food tech company, were a fast growing startup based… https://t.co/yswn6enJOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Consultant 3 – Secure Infrastructure Services: AT&amp;T Security Solutions is a division of AT&amp;T (a Fortune Global Top 10 company).  AT&amp;T is looking for an information security practitioner with technical experience for the position of a Senior… https://t.co/8bAXGb7o5I https://t.co/ylMF9NG2OP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job TitlePython Developer – ID:31445 Duration6 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job Skillspython, SQL, AWS LocationBloomington, MN Date Posted04/10/2018 Qualifications Python, Relational Databases, HTTP APIs, Data Formats (JSON, CSV, XML),… https://t.co/mZUKEQWXxa https://t.co/VOdgL3NMSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python C++ Developer Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging skills,… https://t.co/NLT3DAdFDw https://t.co/mgdI9hscjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/UJ9AF2sxAb https://t.co/QssOkiFCJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Description:Leidos Corporate Information Security Group has an immediate opening for an experienced and motivated Sr. Software Developer to join our Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center (CSIRC) in Gaithersburg – MD.  … https://t.co/oVL4e7WvdB https://t.co/nOQ21nF6lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 30971BR Domain Others (Please specify in the Requisition notes) Skillset Linux , PYTHON , Country USA State / Region / Province Arizona Work Location Phoenix, AZ Company ITL USA Job Description… https://t.co/bkfqJv8anj https://t.co/REK58YyOhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/fo00CVEaix https://t.co/xt5xqeg1jB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Intelligence Analyst Manager: Description:Leidos Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center has an immediate opening for an experienced, and motivated Cyber Intelligence Analyst Manager.   Reporting to the Director of the Cybersecurity… https://t.co/ag4voazklw https://t.co/0jCtX9FmzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/FfDTThQGbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/ZCavC8NVRh https://t.co/GSdyiDVm1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/74vWkUnGwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/fhskXIk9NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA Python Engineer: MySQL DBA/Software Engineer with Python Need a strong MYSQL DBA with good python knowledge to automate tasks. You will need server tuning, strong Bash or Python Scripting skills along with DBA tasks Responsibilities: Performs a… https://t.co/IpquGdVOVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/lDSI6tAg4L https://t.co/Mhq5NINJ1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Pinterest personalizes millions of experiences by using machine learning algorithms to sift through our catalog of a hundred billion Pins to find the best content for each Pinner. To provide high quality data to build these algorithms,… https://t.co/sHY6iCIALu https://t.co/FdQYC5UAgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Ref: PH00811 Role Summary The Senior Software Developer will be responsible for the technical implementation of project work by working closely with other team members to ensure scoping and delivery of projects runs smoothly… https://t.co/SbwjFE7gDt https://t.co/vDoxdiOzyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Engineer: If revolutionizing healthcare excites you, join our growing team and help us achieve our mission to build better software for doctors and patients and improve healthcare for all. drchrono was founded and is led by two software… https://t.co/fQRmTiPOlP https://t.co/4mX7N0U0js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer Analyst: Aon Hewitt has announced BCAA as a 2018 Canadian Gold Level Best Employer    Business &amp; IT Solutions   BCAA’s Corporate Home Office in Burnaby has an opening for a regular full-time Senior Software Developer Analyst –… https://t.co/nykDZ7IIgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java and Python (back-end): Software Engineer – Java and Python (back-end) | Maxta – Newsroom – Events – Contact – Request Demo – Free License – 2018 Software-Defined Data Center 50 – Adwords_Nutanix_Freemium –… https://t.co/L9GClArUSp https://t.co/P19Qgk5xvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Analyst: Computer Programmer Analyst HV-NTP-905 Applicants are being accepted for the following vacancy on the Non-Teaching Professional staff of Hudson Valley Community College, 80 Vandenburgh Avenue, Troy, NY. In order to be… https://t.co/5S23WYoYZp https://t.co/BF1rxaAdwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Developer (Remote OK. $90-125k): Full Time Role (40+hrs/week) Onsite in NYC, or Remote (US Only) Croscon plans, builds, and grows digital products and services that help companies become leaders in their industry. Our clients range from… https://t.co/yWkdljPIjk https://t.co/YGj6RPyUI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/todp7M9coa https://t.co/Zj6TcvwH4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java, Python, BDA, C++: Req ID : 431266BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Space Systems Company (SSC), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the… https://t.co/7CfqRjD7rI https://t.co/db745pugmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer, Senior: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and engineering… https://t.co/gBZKKgyO1l https://t.co/HPKA78CuGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NIC(Network Interface Card) QA Engineer: NIC(Network Interface Card) QA Sunnyvale, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Manual Testing methodologies and Agile process * Troubleshooting knowledge of NetApp Hardware and RCA * Basic Understanding on… https://t.co/vGNee1LLnO https://t.co/J2bCF2Dgix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): Software Developer (Python/Django) Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture… https://t.co/0NyR5M6nKw https://t.co/klfJctZ6fl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/SSLv7eR8lk https://t.co/EB4jpmwIax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Python Software Engineer IoT: TVision Insights is a hyper-growth television attention measurement company pioneering the way brands, their agencies, TV networks and OTT platforms determine the true value of their video content and advertising. The… https://t.co/VMlxdozArV https://t.co/hLMAZ9HzIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join our… https://t.co/brTzJa6ZFS https://t.co/BcvNhXoBAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Developer: Automation Test Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position 2+ Yrs Job Description: Candidate must have at least 2 years of experience developing C++ test framework and test cases OR C++ application development experience… https://t.co/PaAj9b9CBi https://t.co/f3pNkYJA9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeking Application/Systems Engineers and Systems Architects – TS/SCI w/Favorably Poly Required: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: Suitability: Job Family: Engineering &amp; Sciences Job Description: As the… https://t.co/TsYDs0kx5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/DUabPZ0G0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – EDS Guardium Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/lMS8AvzU2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join our… https://t.co/QVQHS2EAEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer III – OSS Applications: Client Reference Code: 217626Job Scope The Systems Engineer III – Linux is part of a team involved enterprise-wide Operations Support Systems (OSS) applications, the operating systems, and their associated… https://t.co/IwwG4shGXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: ASRC Federal System Solutions was recently awarded a seven (7) year program supporting the FAA in Oklahoma City. This position will support the FAA’s Terminal Flight Data Manager (TFDM) systems used by Air Traffic Control to provide… https://t.co/Itu7kghJoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analytics Consultant Sr: Position Overview As a Business Analytics Consultant Sr. within PNC’s Corporate and Institutional Banking organization, you will be based in Pittsburgh. You will be joining the Data Analytics and Solutions team, to work… https://t.co/FalSEr6Liy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 4 – Lumeta NVA: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we… https://t.co/M0Z905DCSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python C++ Developer Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging skills,… https://t.co/5mdV2B8lXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer IV– Spectrum Enterprise, Network Implementation &amp; Operations: Client Reference Code: 217016 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology… https://t.co/xIEt3TexNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer IV, Network Developer – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 216980 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving many… https://t.co/M0Aay9rlef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/jqEEiU6A51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Build &amp; Release Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime position Job Description: 5+ years of software development, build infrastructure engineering experience Expertise in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery Experience with build… https://t.co/nYfRxdbB6G https://t.co/buw2UNNZCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/Ansible Developer: Oasis Systems -Python/Ansible Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/dtEr21jz0F https://t.co/yVvYYSKiep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain Software Engineer: New Alchemy is an advisory and investment group specializing in tokenization and blockchain technology. One of only a handful of companies able to offer a full spectrum of guidance from tactical technical execution to… https://t.co/TX7TK2rmno https://t.co/Lx7gRVipF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Analyst: THE POSITION We are looking for a GIS Analyst to join our team in Arlington, VA. The successful candidate will be both independent and collaborative and possess the desire to continuously learn and teach others about the newest technical… https://t.co/LYkm3noxhJ https://t.co/dbGygLwmOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Data Science and Engineering: The Advanced Analytics team at Decision Resources Group (DRG) provides productized and semi-custom data and analytical solutions to some of the largest biopharmaceutical and medical technology companies… https://t.co/vHoilpioNa https://t.co/G20dkKnGTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS/Python/Unix Developer: The Oakleaf Group – Careers -SAS/Python/Unix Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/Yi2dSf0IWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: Position Title: Senior Web Developer Position Type: Permanent Position Location: Mid West RESPONSIBILITIES: Our client is looking to add a strong developer with great UI experience in E commerce. The need is for a strong team player… https://t.co/g7kNBWEb5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst / Developer: Data Analyst / Developer Date: May 26, 2018 Location: Jersey City, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co Apply now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Apply Now EmailStart Please wait… New York Life… https://t.co/mmPPTEgTfo https://t.co/CfBnsCfV3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps AWS Engineer: Looking for a Junior and a Senior DevOps Engineer – Developer and Infrastructure NO SPONSORSHIP Experience with AWS, CPP and/or Azure, security infrastructure, DLP, Frameworks for managing Infrastructure code, cloud formation,… https://t.co/tePqesWd0n https://t.co/R39bXhQ4RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Reston, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/6/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/UOr5xOfZ8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Our client is currently seeking an experienced DevOps Engineer (with Software Engineering experience) to join our Engineering Operations team, a team driven to understand and apply leading technologies to our Software Delivery pipeline… https://t.co/Rhlh6k7CvU https://t.co/MqC7Un9Xm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineer (TS/SCI required): DESCRIPTION: Immediate opportunity as a Cyber Software Engineer located in McLean Virginia. This position willsupport the Department of Homeland Security, which provides cutting edge Cyber, InformationAssurance… https://t.co/rt0hb2U419 https://t.co/3ZL2ujJCg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/Java Developer: Python/Java Developer Ref No.: 18-21731 Location: ca, California Need Python/Java Developer with Integration experience for Sunnyvale, CA location Duration: 12 months + extension possibilities / Rate-$60/hr. corp-corp. Basic… https://t.co/nNuTNMkZBB https://t.co/ibGHGOIaqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: SymphonyCare, a Symphony Corporation product development company, is a provider of population health and patient engagement solutions, combining best-of-breed digital health tools and a variety of support services aimed at improving… https://t.co/lWHvw5mgKu https://t.co/0yApxJThYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIM Programmer: Contract/Freelance Project Description Job Title BIM Programmer Job Location Hillsboro, OR Department HIL3396 – AT Basebuild Eng Design Tech – Hillsboro Position Type Contract / Regular Full-Time Position Summary: Seeking Full time… https://t.co/UyvzvXLCmx https://t.co/CzMFbDbDaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – AMAZON ALEXA MACHINE LEARNING TEAM- Cambridge, Massachusetts: Job Description Software Engineer – AMAZON ALEXA MACHINE LEARNING TEAM- Cambridge, Massachusetts Job ID ****** Location US-MA-Cambridge Posted Date 5/3/2018 Company… https://t.co/W4pAn2PhoS https://t.co/lyGmJ6IVCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist – Prescriptive Analytics: Job Description What you’ll be doing… You’ll be part of a leading-edge advanced analytics team helping us bring the best possible experiences to our customers by helping us to identify what they like,… https://t.co/1I4sGrjR98 https://t.co/gCdpUnLZEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Software Developer: Job Description AWS Software Developer Job ID ****** Location US-WA-Seattle Posted Date 5/14/2018 Company ********** Services, Inc. Position Category Software Development Recruiting Team .. Job Description Amazon Web Services… https://t.co/3IcBbjD3Ll https://t.co/tVMrz3Zon2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Scientist – Deep/Machine Learning and Image Analysis: Redwood City, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Research Scientist – Deep/Machine Learning and Image Analysis with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing More… https://t.co/NlgpEAq37I https://t.co/DYRA2JWSfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/yhJBSr0uRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services – Software Developer: Job Description Amazon Web Services – Software Developer Job ID ****** Location US-VA-Herndon Posted Date 5/14/2018 Company ********** Services, Inc. Position Category Software Development Recruiting Team .. Job… https://t.co/Lje5dE8ElD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Engineer w/ DevOps Background (WORK FROM HOME): Austin, TX Full-time $120k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Python Engineer with a DevOps background, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 1. Based in Austin, TX, we are a thriving… https://t.co/TK2tqDhtY9 https://t.co/0bdarrmkdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: 113091BR Full-Stack Developer CA – Pasadena 113091BR Looking for two Full Stack Developers who are comfortable in software development, delivery, and processing involving GitHub, JIRA, DevOps Apache Spark and Cassandra. Successful… https://t.co/dGmN2kxFUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer- Cryptocurrencies: Job Details – Akuna Capital – Your Career – The Team – Our Culture – Get in Touch – Your Career – The Team – Our Culture – Get in Touch Python Developer- Cryptocurrencies Chicago, IL Python Developer- Cryptocurrencies… https://t.co/kgECIcFl6i https://t.co/VyqzaXhjAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers and Architects: Job Description Senior Software Engineers and Architects Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you are helping to create a better world. Your day-to-day management will touch the lives of… https://t.co/VuxfVzVrHc https://t.co/RRgRGJFDNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Systems Engineer/Programmer – IBM MQ: For BNY Mellon Lead Systems Engineer/Programmer – IBM MQ job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client… https://t.co/qkeOfor3VP https://t.co/ZfxVnhD3Es]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>