<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Shine accepts top White House job: President Donald Trump and Bill Shine have had several serious discussions in recent days about him becoming the next communications director, a source with knowledge of the situation tells CNN. https://t.co/xYchyFS76q https://t.co/5iugAjZ7y9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourth of July Party Picks: Yeti, Weber, Biolite, Hydro Flask: Happy Fourth of July! Let us upgrade your Independence Day bash with premium coolers, stomping rockets, and 12 other great products. https://t.co/H7wLGgOyyz https://t.co/dfBokezYpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior User Experience Designer: Description The Sr. User Experience (UX) Designer will work on the Digital Banking team to create best in class digital experiences. The ideal candidate should have an eye for design and possess superior UX/UI skills.… https://t.co/KxthVKOFPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: IT Project Manager : 18-01152 Ref No.: 18-01152 Location: Walnut Creek, California Primary Skills: Cisco SDN, Project Management, Healthcare Systems Location: Walnut Creek CA Duration: 12 Months+ Contract Type: W2 Only [1099 or… https://t.co/tRSRZZLWJZ https://t.co/6nULg03bGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Associate Software Engineer at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High Tech… https://t.co/QcPP5ViS9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Governance, Risk, and Compliance (GRC) Manager: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a… https://t.co/8tXlGqWFrX https://t.co/OwNr4xPETs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLM Support Analyst 2:   Job Description – PLM Support Analyst 2 (18009193) PLM Support Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18009193 Location : United States-Florida-Melbourne US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/XPQNSkFAEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Medicare Supplement: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Milwaukee, WI Job Type: Product/Pricing Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/17/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Responsible for leading the planning and implementation of… https://t.co/KHm0GZVbvh https://t.co/ZSNOoT5iMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: TITLE: Systems Administrator LOCATION: DAYTON, OHIO DURATION: FULL TIME CLIENT- FEDERAL AGENCY JOB DESCRIPTION The contractor shall provide a team member that demonstrates a proficient understanding of medical software testing and… https://t.co/bYv0it2OUD https://t.co/gBUnz2ue6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court: Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court =================================================== This role provides basic-level software support for Tyler clients in the use, functionality, and… https://t.co/fVlWcVmfsn https://t.co/0flBugEP6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The concrete that can trap CO2 emissions forever https://t.co/MZgi1iumw5 https://t.co/MZFXTH5k0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG C8 OLED 4K TV: The Best-Looking TV of 2018: When it comes to picture quality, LG's OLED 4K TV lineup beats all comers. https://t.co/kpaKJESrSc https://t.co/gVCZ0SpSns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dementia complicates US gun ownership: There has been vigorous debate about how to prevent people with mental illness from acquiring weapons. But what about firearms in the homes of aging Americans with impaired or declining mental faculties? https://t.co/Qu7tcUkTBO https://t.co/zsTuKCGkER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: About MeduitMeduit, a growing national healthcare revenue cycle management firm has an opportunity for an Office 365 Systems Administrator located in its Charlotte NC corporate headquarters. Job ResponsibilitiesWorking in… https://t.co/mGeziyRCNc https://t.co/00v23p6SrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer 3: COMPUTER: Stanford Univ/ SLAC seeks Software Developer 3 (Sr SW App Dev &amp; Architect) to design, dev. &amp; deploy controls infrastructure SW apps for advanced scientific instrumentation &amp; research. Reqs BS in CS/CE + 8 yrs exp, incl 4… https://t.co/9SJoTFIWRB https://t.co/KQrJwCkyOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Staff Member: COMPUTER/IT Research Staff Member, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Dvlp new technologies at frontier of storage softw. Work on high velocity data, extreme scale storage &amp; globally distrib. in areas of cloud srvcs, analytics, healthcare,… https://t.co/4g5rXCRmor https://t.co/Jbk8jVTe04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Killer Tech Deals on the Bitdefender Box, SNES Classic, and More: Two Nintendo consoles are on sale this week, along with a secure router and other great tech! https://t.co/6oRAQNyfnt https://t.co/cr646bPBTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electrical Engineer, ITS: Job Title:Senior Electrical Engineer, ITS Description: **Business Line** Transportation **Position Title** Senior Electrical Engineer, ITS United States of America – Virginia Richmond **Job Summary** The New Jersey office… https://t.co/wli5EIvPKl https://t.co/U1KOhygJlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actor Terry Crews tells Senate more men need to talk about sexual assault: Actor Terry Crews called on men to speak more about sexual assault -- both as victims and their roles perpetuating sexual violence -- in order to lessen the stigma survivors face… https://t.co/c9kN1CBFLP https://t.co/K0I9ZMM8Mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers Gather for the International Workshop on Emoji Understanding: Linguists and data scientists see a new way to study language and communication in our little digital ideograms. https://t.co/ipnQb99LnL https://t.co/YbeWvN5r7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Network Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/5/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/7aKDkfzIqf https://t.co/FNCuGrqnaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multimedia GIS Data Manager: Job Description The Multimedia GIS Data Manager designs and delivers operations research applications (databases, websites, tools, and products) that are geospatially enabled to support a multitude of intelligence issues.… https://t.co/7GwkebXQpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Hi to the first Hello Kitty-themed bullet train: There are two things that will never get old in Japan. Hello Kitty -- Sanrio's adorable mouthless character -- and bullet trains. https://t.co/EE4GhgFACs https://t.co/c2TLAn8UcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Onsite – Joliet Area (CHI: Chemical Project Manager – Onsite – Joliet, IL Area Functional Role Description: The Project Manager (PM) is fully responsible for the overall development and execution of small- to medium- (typically up to… https://t.co/dQI8JwFRUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Infrastructure Open Source Enablement: Job ID #: 12804 – Job Category: Marketing &amp; Communications – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Infrastructure – Department: Infrastructure Marketing – Primary Country: USA –… https://t.co/i9U51RGjrG https://t.co/EvCTd2NmIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The real winner in Court's decision: At last, the Supreme Court has spoken. After 17 months, hundreds of pages of lower court rulings and three versions of President Donald Trump's travel ban, the high court has ruled on the ban, upholding… https://t.co/Tf6wrHlfFT https://t.co/Y3dQ0ZllFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology – Multiple Positions: TECHNOLOGY Atlassian, Inc. seeks to work in Mountain View, CA: 1) Software Developer, Mobile to develop reusable software components and libraries as well as consumer facing network based mobile applications using latest… https://t.co/pccx2T28ie https://t.co/sAwGy3m3D0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Japanese subculture cruising 'low and slow': Parked in a row, their undersides almost glancing the asphalt, these ornate and outsized American cars stand out in a sea of Hondas, Toyotas, Nissans and Subarus. https://t.co/fOWjLKKGOZ https://t.co/9W8S01vgg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphic Designer #SA-0721: Graphic Designer position in Redwood City, CA.   recblid o9fohpu0ql663inkawkuxmaced8dbh https://t.co/0cMH2TrmgY https://t.co/totz16FtXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer in Arlington, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us… https://t.co/vovxgQBA8k https://t.co/QdBUOGxxMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Engineer: UI Engineer: 18-02157 Ref No.: 18-02157 Location: Santa Clara, California Akraya is looking for an UI Engineer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Viplove Singh at ************. If… https://t.co/pivJJjXOaX https://t.co/WC82VUGba1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Principal Architects serve as the technical design authority and architectural expert for sales opportunities across multiple vertical and geographic regions, in support of the… https://t.co/O2Yit0bauO https://t.co/BneNbl04Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entire police force of Mexico town detained after mayoral candidate's assassination: The entire police force of a Mexican town in the state of Michoacán is being questioned in the assassination of a mayoral candidate, the office of the state's attorney… https://t.co/VBrthZT9Nq https://t.co/NoiNtkJKub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure Active Directory Architect: Azure Active Directory Architect Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3399 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services… https://t.co/Z6rJerElOw https://t.co/SoJxrLBxgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Quality: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the… https://t.co/I1YekEoB5R https://t.co/bZssOl7WMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer: Our firm needs a professional Web Designer with experience in WordPress Content Management Systems (CMS) to assist our client transition their existing webpage into a more fresh and modern Word Press webpage. Were looking for a candidate… https://t.co/RbufONo7rc https://t.co/xi9j7uDoxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She got bad news from her doctor and went to the pharmacist. His words left her in tears: An Arizona woman has criticized Walgreens on social media, saying a pharmacist at the chain refused to fill her prescription for a medicine prescribed to induce… https://t.co/vesPIlTOjK https://t.co/D8tygMbIxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst (Certified Scrum Master) ================================================= Req #: ******Location: Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance… https://t.co/5qn5VVtb0u https://t.co/zw0yTn1RCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fujifilm Instax Square SQ6 Review: Simple Square Shots: Fuji's first square analog instant camera is finally here. Was it worth the wait? https://t.co/TkY35I9CnI https://t.co/7ZPV7Xxj4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst – The Greentree Group – Home – About – Services – Project Management – Business Analysis – I.T. Services – Quality Assurance – Configuration and Deployment – Government Contracts – Texas Contracts – Employment – Contact… https://t.co/P3hJDGqg6b https://t.co/GQJMs9q0bu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Project Manager: Customer Project Manager-004IF6 Description Schneider Electric creates connected technologies that reshape industries, transform cities and enrich lives. Our 144,000 employees thrive in more than 100 countries. From the simplest… https://t.co/E7pmj6YlCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Technology Systems – Learning and Development: Job Description Job Description This position is responsible for configuring/maintaining enterprise MetroPCS HR Learning Management systems including but not limited to updating/creating business… https://t.co/ivebjceUXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Pricing Project Analyst: TTEC is seeking an experienced Senior Pricing Project Analyst to join our Enterprise Services teamat our Global Corporate Headquarters, based in Denver, Colorado. OurPricing team brings significant value and contribution… https://t.co/k78qKFc6nL https://t.co/TcfBsyb3jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – New Hampshire Office: Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – New Hampshire Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc. (Loureiro) has an immediate opening for a Project Manager/Environmental… https://t.co/I6NHy3yDp2 https://t.co/YR7Jssgmjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star considering quitting Egypt national team: Mo Salah is considering quitting the Egyptian national team due to his unhappiness over what has happened in Chechnya, where the team was based during the World Cup at Russia 2018, a source close to the… https://t.co/rmgbAqMbsc https://t.co/5reOKtGdqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Description Senior Project Manager Senior Project Manager (******) About UsAt HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are most well-known for adding beauty and… https://t.co/o5dahiv8KV https://t.co/5OHJKG3mi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Engineer: Overview Clearwater Paper manufactures quality consumer tissue, away-from-home tissue, hard roll tissue, bleached paperboard and pulp at manufacturing facilities across the nation. The Company is a premier supplier of private label… https://t.co/WBneVIpcFI https://t.co/0SxDlz29J9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect Enterprise Integration Services: Solution Architect – Enterprise Integration Services Date: Apr 21, 2018 Location: Clinton, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now… https://t.co/wRCedCDYwa https://t.co/6RRajMAHRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN anchor to Trump supporter: He created this policy: What began as a new Trump administration policy, enacted in mid-April, has turned to a crisis that resulted in the separation of immigrant children from their parents. CNN's Victor Blackwell… https://t.co/ezheKbkiaI https://t.co/qzqc8RGbGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Solutions Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Alexandria, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/15/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/7YYcItO5It https://t.co/cTQUCly6iY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Munis: Software Engineer, Munis ======================== Tyler Technologies is experiencing significant growth and we are hiring developers of all skill and experience levels who will help us meet the needs of our clients and our… https://t.co/BnB0dNMYt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer: ***ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply*** General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT), a leading provider of systems engineering, integration, IT service operations and support solutions, is seeking… https://t.co/fGSUhouVlG https://t.co/FDw7qutcdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Every great idea begins with a problem. Ours began with a struggle to get what our bodies wanted, when we wanted it. We’ve been fortunate that life has taken us many places; remote descents in the backcountry, last-minute goals on the… https://t.co/ZytDeDYR32 https://t.co/NYeyFZ4Ktr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpdesk / Service Desk Supervisor: Help Desk / Service Desk Supervisor Los Angeles, Ca 90032 Contract to Hire Opportunity IMMEDIATE NEED for a Help Desk / Service Desk Supervisor to join a world class Healthcare client. Responsibilities : * Supervise a… https://t.co/uFPD6ngqRk https://t.co/fjNRhy6kYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Application Architect Corporate Business Systems: Company Description Visa operates the world’s largest retail electronic payments network and is one of the most recognized global financial services brands. Visa facilitates global commerce… https://t.co/v1d0g5HZhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power Systems Scientist / Developer Optimization and Unit Commitment: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina,… https://t.co/4hRUDcWdVf https://t.co/7t2zZiU3gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Salesforce: Senior Project Manager/Salesforce Waltham MA 6 Month+ Contract Our client is building out technology capabilities for a new Go-To-Market strategy. Developing a Business case for Process Redesign, Sales Systems… https://t.co/Z7EezjcQNz https://t.co/UBAb55VWZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer job in Hudson, New Hampshire, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp;… https://t.co/j7UtNa3Hzu https://t.co/ZMlaHmis8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activity Security Representative III: Req ID 97836BR Business Title Activity Security Representative III Group MCIS Location USA DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA Washington Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Security Job Duties and Responsibilities Activity… https://t.co/K11W9Ln9pt https://t.co/DB0fB7HMAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 422951BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : Software C/C++/Java Software Engineer. Duties to include parser, and XML schema development as well as Network Protocol integration. Must work well in a high… https://t.co/yOmf0vLBhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania, that jacket! https://t.co/FVYECl7iqQ https://t.co/R0xxFhQ4wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: The Project Manager administers and directs plans, organizes and controls space planning, deferred maintenance, renovations of spaces and construction management. This position works under direction of the Director of Facilities.… https://t.co/dMsDc79fNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL stars: Why people deserve a clean slate https://t.co/6vHfaI9MGV https://t.co/kkw0S9nGCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Primary Skills Security+ certification,VOIP,Secret Clearance,Private Branch Exchange,Nortel Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Network Administrator for location Alpena ,… https://t.co/cUDcF37eec https://t.co/Ln9lMT3y6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include… https://t.co/F5rS9De5jX https://t.co/WItRFBRnOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect-Enterprise Networking: Careers | Cisco Service, Enterprise Networking &amp; Unified Communications | ABS Technology – About – Overview – Blog – Company News – Careers – Our Partners – Our People – Our Clients – Healthcare – K-12 – Higher… https://t.co/csqT3vtSTx https://t.co/MKu1EnjdcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Required Skills and background – Extensive hands-on experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and cross-browser coding practices. – Extensive hands-on experience HTTP, AJAX, JSON, REST, C++ and server-side processing. – Experience with… https://t.co/GXFVHVu0Qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaf prisoners are trapped in frightening isolation https://t.co/9DpTQddrmN https://t.co/u5gjCnbMp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/Hvoa8mSPio https://t.co/mNXrctfxmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect – Intelligent Routing API: Architect – Intelligent Routing API at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Because you belong at Twilio The Who, What, Why and Where Who? As a very hands-on Architect at Twilio, you are empowered to create… https://t.co/Q46kZnMjcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BK apologizes for bizarre World Cup promotion https://t.co/c5fM9m9zaK https://t.co/qRh01FthRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Specialist: Information Technology Services at Iowa State University is seeking qualified applicants for a Data Center Specialist. The Data Center Specialist will be responsible for supporting ISU’s data center infrastructure, and data center… https://t.co/fMmLPN7KyQ https://t.co/ksuLuVklGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS SUPPORT ANALYST III: Applications Support Analyst III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Build a strong understanding of applications and be able to support each at a subject matter expert level. Apply at https://t.co/5CW6XFiqmv, Req #… https://t.co/7y7c0aGaen https://t.co/bvepsxSOiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops, Trump almost had a $125 billion border wall: House Republicans had to scramble late Wednesday night to fix a drafting error in a conservative immigration bill that would have accidentally given President Donald Trump $125 billion for border… https://t.co/YuF8WQyMXq https://t.co/XzfkxmBCiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: TECHNOLOGY Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Application Engineer (Req #8E11011) interact with Process Tool Development teams to help define Design of Experiments, req’s domestic &amp; int’l travel 20% of time;… https://t.co/ybP6gNfG24 https://t.co/D6Ih9XIshT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Planning Analyst Integrated System Planning Team: More than a career – a chance to make a difference in people’s lives. Build an exciting, rewarding career with us help us make a difference for millions of people every day. Consider joining the… https://t.co/lK5zCBu3h5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's the first world leader to give birth in office since 1990: New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern, the first pregnant world leader in nearly 30 years, has been admitted to the hospital to give birth, her office said. Her expected due date was… https://t.co/gxkLpC268F https://t.co/FH7xsWMUrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer: Job Information: Associate Software Developer – ******* Job Email Opening Title Associate Software Developer – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon University is an Equal Opportunity Employer/Disability/Veteran. Description… https://t.co/spccmbSOoa https://t.co/Ttr8G4AV9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Quality Assurance Engineer: Careers – Cengage Learning -Content Quality Assurance Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/y6L0jxcfp4 https://t.co/vhCfpK05n7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Server-DBA: We are hiring a SQL Server DBA Location: Columbia, SC Duration: 12+ months (with a possibility of extn) Candidate Type: W2 Only; Unfortunately NO Corp-to-Corp or 1099 DAILY DUTIES / RESPONSIBILITIES: – Identify the requirements for the… https://t.co/ZCh32EA3OR https://t.co/uZa2iBUMRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator ===================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: Public TrustClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Duties and… https://t.co/56sn3RjEsW https://t.co/RxGQqQMWQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Engineer: Req ID 96417BR Business Title Chief Engineer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Systems Development Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is seeking a motivated, career and… https://t.co/vahfGNzaWJ https://t.co/YDdeTNb8XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electromagnetic Design Engineer 5:   Job Description – Electromagnetic Design Engineer 5 (18010789) Electromagnetic Design Engineer 5 Requisition ID : 18010789 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes… https://t.co/QlNirk9m1b https://t.co/DBEq2ZV3kZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coordinator – RN Data: Loma Linda University Medical Center (Loma Linda, CA) requires a Coordinator – RN Data. Must have a bachelor’s degree in nursing or a related field and 12 months of experience as a clinical nurse in a direct patient-care setting.… https://t.co/bsyMiGDSKV https://t.co/75ujVsKUeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead System Analyst: IT Project Mgrs, Lead Software Devs, Lead Sys Analysts, Comp Sys Analysts &amp; Software Devs sought. Manager &amp; Lead positions req Master’s or equiv in CS, Comp Apps, Engg or rltd &amp; 12 mos’ relevant indus exp. Will also accept Bachelor’s… https://t.co/bMtBvQetO6 https://t.co/PS1lQMvTHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Account Development Manager: Use Data To Build The Next Generation Of Sales Professionals: Periscope Data’s mission is to provide the fastest data visualization tool on the market. As a Senior Account Development Manager, you will be responsible… https://t.co/RLiUZ9t8oY https://t.co/eqxnryk08U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Software Engineer III sought by Accolade, Inc. in Plymouth Meeting, PA. Job # 58808. Resolve complex technical issues and deliver innovative solutions that improve user engagement, system availability, resiliency, and performance.… https://t.co/PmpIOHmBKX https://t.co/G18wiyuXKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotics Engineer: Robotics Engineer (Murrieta, CA) Draft, analyze &amp; assemble automation systems for FANUC industrial robot equipment. Develop real-time robotic software programs &amp; vision-guided robot applications. Master’s in Mechanical or Electrical… https://t.co/c7G8zeQHgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice and Network Engineer: Voice and Network Engineer ========================== Req #: ******_80225Location: Denver, CO USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: Public TrustClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description What You… https://t.co/3YHYDV6EkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Project Manager (FIre Alarm Domain): Job Description Field Project Manager (FIre Alarm Domain) (WD***********) What you will do Leads moderately complex projects that generally have been assigned a medium to high corporate priority. Provides… https://t.co/oVeJUpdLzb https://t.co/U8PBfOmUho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Services Solution Architect: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Application Services Solution Architect to join our team in Reston, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems.… https://t.co/c8ZvS2QXWZ https://t.co/RzIEqmWpG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Basis Administrators: SAP Basis Administrators: Frisco, TX Resolve any operating system, Oracle database and SAP system related issues and take care of the Data Center operations and Management. Investigate and resolve operating system related… https://t.co/bvkdgfdUGL https://t.co/GUEM7D30Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Marketing Manager — B2B SaaS: Oakland, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted 10/19/2017 Based in beautiful Oakland, we are a growing and innovative mobile start-up that is already turning heads in the sports industry. Although we… https://t.co/4HLFkofg1h https://t.co/HMOEArgiS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ground Systems Engineer RF Design 3 – SCI:   Job Description – Ground Systems Engineer RF Design 3 – SCI (18009357) Ground Systems Engineer RF Design 3 – SCI Requisition ID : 18009357 Location : United States-California-Manhattan Beach US Citizenship… https://t.co/hT5dcPdmzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teams trade player twice -- in one day https://t.co/tAYPAl0YZD https://t.co/uAmUe6icY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst, SAP BPC Consultant: Data Analyst, SAP BPC – Irvine CA – Consultant A top-tier commercial real estate company is seeking a talented DATA ANALYST for a 5 – 12 month engagement. The ideal candidate is a talented DATA ANALYST with Big Data… https://t.co/u7JGFlrkkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Support Engineers: EchoStar Corporation (NASDAQ: SATS) headquartered in Englewood, CO, with additional locations world-wide, is a premier global provider of satellite solutions and technology services. Together with its major… https://t.co/7H1dOCIOUf https://t.co/tW1WIczXLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Senior Consultant: IT Technology Senior Consultant Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword… https://t.co/QMZNe25q4k https://t.co/60nUB8Mixc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Project Manager ID 2017-2209 # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MA-Boston Category Management More information about this job Responsibilities * Meeting with clients * initial project scoping, proposal preparation * staff… https://t.co/RnvmoxolYz https://t.co/M2hT8dVUDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Planning Systems Administrator: As a Mission Planning Systems Administrator, perform systems administration supporting the operation, maintenance, and installation of Mission Planning Environment (MPE). Provide user support for numerous devices… https://t.co/tVHzrR5ypX https://t.co/vRBbsvxTBn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>