<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up.... Do I take too many supplements? http://t.co/LtVQhx2OmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved "The Show" this weekend @GatewayPeople http://t.co/vyYJ84hWzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you walk in love, you give up your right to be right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about SEX. Nov 7-9! http://t.co/aGYtyuM7mV
Don't miss it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a photo from 1966...on our way camping with Mom and Dad. Photo credit goes to my sister Linda Dudish.... http://t.co/k39PInQMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you God for iPads and coffee. http://t.co/05r2369QCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all Men! Come be a part of the Call to Arms Mens Conference Nov. 7-9 in Broken Arrow, OK. I'll be speaking... http://t.co/jb1OJ6BWBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's another link to the video! http://t.co/XrA8NUFPjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I holding this knife?? Watch the video below and hear about my career as a knife salesman!... http://t.co/pH6jZ2ylgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't connected with me yet on LinkedIn here's my link: http://t.co/f5TwUGEb2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever go camping? In a pop-up camper? In the rain? Watch this short clip and see what I learned from... http://t.co/NrBgB8gO9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With my gorgeous wife Teri... http://t.co/7J2J3jynvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever consider professional wrestling? http://t.co/ib9IqSzKGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a professional wrestler? http://t.co/sd8S8tFJXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever feel like giving up? Don't stop Dreaming!! http://t.co/Vkm1PwNBXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Life is far too important a thing ever to talk seriously about.”
- Oscar Wilde

#livelifeloudly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genebailey: "Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time." -Thomas A. Edi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time." -Thomas A. Edison #courage”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brentthebigdog  im watching! way to go!! Good Stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billydawson1 Love the new tune...you rock bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good when you realize what you want isn't what you wanted before you wanted something better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“How to go from self-published author to a six-figure advance: http://t.co/33ccj4t06U”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be silent or let thy words be worth more than silence. - Pythagoras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad and Mom still got it going on... http://t.co/HR0PjE5uDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were on a cruise ship when Hurricane Karen came by...! http://t.co/NOY6h4SLQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;iframe src="//player.vimeo.com/video/76835065" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen... http://t.co/qvOHiA2T1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WisdomQuotes25: Silence does not always mark wisdom.-Samuel Taylor Coleridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joeslaughter: Happy is the man who finds a true friend, &amp; far happier is he who finds that true friend in his wife -Franz Schubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HusbandMentor: Not happy with where your #marriage is today? Take time to examine what you have been sowing (Gal 6:7). That's what you …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyAndrews: I have checked every single episode--black and white to color--and I cannot find a single example of... http://t.co/O9nwcc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRobertD: RT @bradlomenick: Be who God meant you to be &amp; you will set the world on fire. - Saint Catherine of Siena (via @dave_lomas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: God &gt; My fears
God &gt; My insecurities
God &gt; My worry
God &gt; My everything”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SkyBox seats at The Eagles Concert...Priceless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch me today as I host a special webcast LIVE at 2:00Central at http://t.co/pqDlzdHeA4 ! I'll be there with Dean... http://t.co/2acSZkCpAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch special webcast today at 2:00Central at http://t.co/bJCFwyLiV0! I'll be there with Dean Tad and more fun! #rbtclive @RBTC_USA Join In!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheZigZiglar: "What you feed your mind determines your appetite."- @TomZiglar #Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever notice someone? Roger noticed me!

http://t.co/FTFInoGhg4 http://t.co/p93NA0oCYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger noticed. Will you? http://t.co/MBiKtYiv86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger noticed. http://t.co/iwbjmvFieb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My career beginning as a male model. Or I was just ready to leave!! http://t.co/vJl8XHVwVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DavidBartonWB: 10 Commandments Monument Toppled in Washington http://t.co/XLv9BKqJQB” unbelievable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenTedCruz: Congress should be bound by the same rules as everybody else #MakeDCListen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon Cruz! #StandWithCruz #MakeDCListen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "You can't change the past but you can change now." #goodstuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today...
I am a man of action. I take responsibility and seek wisdom in every area of my life. I choose to be happy and show forgiveness wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today...
I am a man of action. I take responsibility and seek wisdom in every area of my life. I choose to be... http://t.co/u60bMeU7qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never mistake motion for action." ~ Ernest Hemmingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreatestQuotes: "Never mistake motion for action." - Ernest Hemmingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DLoesch: Flashback: Debunking The 14 Biggest Gun Control Lies http://t.co/aupsf9biSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you're a bug, some days you're a windshield.  ~ Price Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pioneer is generally a man who has outlived his credit or fortune in the cultivated parts. 
- Benjamin Rush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @successmagazine: “Live out your beliefs and you can turn the world around.” — Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DavidRoads: Don't make excuses for why you can't get it done. Focus on all the reasons why you must make it happen.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anger is never without reason, but seldom with a good one." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @foxnewsvideo: Shepard Smith takes on new role at Fox News http://t.co/VYpllSclMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@BillyHallowell: Exercise good character. Everything else will fall into place.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember happiness doesn't depend upon who you are or what you have; it depends solely on what you think. ~Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@9to5mac: Apple quietly adds $59 AppleCare+ for iPod touch and iPod Classic(!!) http://t.co/0v5lS1NIJJ”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember happiness doesn't depend upon who you are or what you have; it depends solely on what you think.  ~Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@AndyAndrews: Something funny for your Saturday: http://t.co/VrWaZtfkjR” I heard most of these too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are here on earth to do good to others. What the others are here for, I do not know.
- Matthew Arnold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat Scratch Fever by Gene Bailey http://t.co/GO4sBwIJBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever have someone that didn't like you? Or a pet ..like a cat?? http://t.co/WLCjiOMWIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Quote Zig gave me: "Don't worry Gene, even Moses was a basket case."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch me today as I cohost a special webcast LIVE at 3:00Central at http://t.co/pqDlzdHeA4 ! I'll be there with Dean Tad and more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me live on Rhema.tv at 3:00pm Central for #rbtclive !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a great pic to start your day... http://t.co/J1bgi37PVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A pessimist is one who makes difficulties of his opportunities and an optimist is one who makes opportunities of... http://t.co/WBbynhzru4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good way to start your day with this thought: http://t.co/g0YUDvHRsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last meeting with Zig Ziglar...and his parting advice! Also...@TheRobertD weighs in. https://t.co/vAhUfFMIrN?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheRobertD: @genebailey Great post!!!! Fantastic reminders. Thanks for the 20,000 Days mention.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If people aren't anticipating your message, they'll just tune you out." —@jeffgoins http://t.co/az543y3YIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JohnCMaxwell: Effective communication is 20% what you know and 80% how you feel about what you know. -Jim Rohn”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friendship is a plant of slow growth and must undergo and withstand the shocks of adversity before it is entitled to the appellation." ~ G…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friendship is a plant of slow growth and must undergo and withstand the shocks of adversity before it is entitled... http://t.co/GJRl5oPU5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@ChrchCurmudgeon: Nobody on his deathbed ever said, "I wish I'd spent less time eating nachos and watching football."”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking at CTA Conference in Oklahoma this week!!  http://t.co/9HaTW4hotG http://t.co/8ntGSNZjaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheZigZiglar: "Lack of direction, not lack of time is the problem. We all have 24 hour days."- Zig Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What you do speaks so loud that I cannot hear what you say." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@toddstweets: Stay inspired!!!! http://t.co/RZFYrI8ds0”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look past the view and see the masterpiece! http://t.co/jFl9I2SQ3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TomZiglar: "Sometimes adversity is what you need to face in order to become successful." - Zig Ziglar”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A GREAT LEADER must first be a GREAT LISTENER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last meeting with Zig Ziglar...and his parting advice! Also...@TheRobertD weighs in. https://t.co/vAhUfFMIrN?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast with Zig http://t.co/knVDU7iyO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karyoberbrunner: Do not waste your life in friction when it could be turned into momentum. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Addictd2Success: "Most of the important things in the world have been accomplished by people who have kept on trying when there seemed …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah.... me and Don Gatlyn working the TV crew in the 70's. Definitely a #tbt http://t.co/V55VVNxqpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah... I was working it. #tbt http://t.co/4XKhzWj4cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay away from the dream killers and the negative thoughts. Evict those thoughts from renting space in your mind!... http://t.co/D4cgWlF1si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay away from the dream killers and the negative thoughts. Evict those thoughts from renting space in your mind! Remember what goes in you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay away from the dream killers and the negative thoughts. Evict those thoughts from renting space in your mind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JoelOsteenShake off doubt, disappointments, self-pity, little dreams, little goals and make room for a flood of God’s goodness.”excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is an amplifier. Whatever is INSIDE you WILL be amplified with more money. Make sure what's inside you is worth amplifying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is an amplifier. Whatever is INSIDE you WILL be amplified with more money. Make sure the inside is worth amplifying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is an amplifier. Whatever is INSIDE will be amplified with more money. Make sure the inside is worth amplifying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@OrganizeHacks: You can use hand sanitizer to remove ink stains from fabric.” Whaaaaaat???!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@GoVisionary: Surround yourself with people who motivate and inspire you to be better.” Good advice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GatewayPeople: "If you've had prolonged illness and sickness, there may be an open door in your life." (@PsRobertMorris)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never too late. Just proclaim a "Do-Over"!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>