<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["I am not a witch" seems almost quaint now https://t.co/hc68a1k7TI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reddy: Female aides said Rep. Trent Franks suggested intercourse to impregnate them https://t.co/E7OYkzjg5N via @politico's @rachaelmba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @passantino: AP Exclusive: Former aide says GOP Rep. Trent Franks offered her $5 million to carry his child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepRickLarsen: As a member of @TransportDems, saw this coming. Nothing, so far, is helping achieve $1t infrastructure goal, leading to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCantwell: I'm calling on @Interior Inspector General to add @SecretaryZinke's use of taxpayer-funded helicopter rides to the ong…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianschatz @johnmdonnelly It's a Friday that feels like a Monday, so sorta both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: After Hurricane Maria, as many as 1,000 more people may have died in Puerto Rico. The official death toll is 62. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @seungminkim: .@realDonaldTrump signs the two-week funding bill into law, per White House. Shutdown officially averted (for two more wee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyRomm You can catch it at $150 DC-NYC, but have to book pretty far in advance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Neda_Semnani: Literally had this conversation last Friday with a friend and we decided it wasn't worth it while looking for work https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kurtbardella: #RoyMoore was the last straw, I'm throwing in with the #Democrats via @USATODAY @USATOpinion https://t.co/283hRC1z0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, why https://t.co/oKbdNvk23W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @perezpena: Amazing: National Weather Service calls SoCal fire danger EXTREME from  Ventura to Mexico.
California Fires Live Updates: Mo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steph_Beasley @TSA I kinda want to collect these cards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: Everyone meet Marlon, the frisky @TSA bomb-sniffing dog. https://t.co/jYDr5lNJhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had monkfish at Salt Line tonight. It was about the size of a lemon. Is this what $30 buys you now?! Martini was good though. #getoffmylawn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliemason Julie feel free to swoon over me. I mean check me out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @axios: BREAKING: Al Franken will resign tomorrow, according to Minnesota Public Radio https://t.co/w8ALFm8fj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brigurciullo: .@USTravel is throwing its muscle and money behind lobbying on issues like PFCs, Open Skies and flags of convenience. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thedailytexan https://t.co/ishY0trgkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: "I never thought that I'd be at a moment in time in which the Committee to Protect Journalists would cite the United Stat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NHTSAgov: Come one! Come all! There are only 15 minutes left before our #BuzzedDriving Twitter chat begins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#peebeat https://t.co/A1WTEP30fo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The POLITICO Journalism Institute is now accepting applications for its fifth session! Spread the word. https://t.co/JojzlPDjIN  #PJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbudoffbrown: Great reporting here from @heatherscope: Another woman says Franken tried to forcibly kiss her. As she hastily left the r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JakeSherman: FRANKEN will make an announcement tomorrow.  “More details to come."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brigurciullo: 185 followers and counting! https://t.co/uV2sg0sOCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clairecmc: Al Franken should resign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steph_Beasley @TSA But did you pet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FlyGirlsSeries: Yesterday, we lost a dear friend. 

Fly High, Edna. We will always be inspired by you. ♥️♥️

Edna Modisette Davis, 1921…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta say, without enlarging that photo, the top of the "sword" looks kinda like a Swiffer. https://t.co/HsElcgKYdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: German police say several people injured after a passenger train hit a freight train near Duesseldorf. https://t.co/dfOgWKlaXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JDiamond1: Bannon predicts infrastructure will be “the big fight in ‘18.” https://t.co/dUfugsOuGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rachaelmbade: THIS is why women on Capitol Hill are afraid to speaking out. Meet Lauren Greene, who did so -- naming Blake Farenthold -…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @si_vault: Fun Fact: Warren Moon operated a chocolate chip cookie store in Edmonton while playing in the CFL. #NationalCookieDay https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NateMonroeTU: BREAKING: Sentences for ex-U.S. Rep. Corrine Brown and conspirators:
Brown - 5 years; 3 years of probation.
Ronnie Simmon…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjane87: As a child, Harriet Tubman had her skull crushed in by a slave owner, was left w/o medical attention for 2 days, + then was re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StevenTDennis: Biggest winners in tax bill:
Stockholders
Business owners
Heirs of estates &gt;$11M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Filth800: so last summer i randomly met this 80 y/o woman on words with friends. we played 300+ games together and she actually ended u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GarrettHaake: Democrats on the floor right now arguing that a late-add to the tax bill benefits ONE college in Michigan, whose biggest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clairecmc: This is so bad. We have just gotten list of amendments to be included in bill NOT from our R colleagues, but from lobbyists…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alweaver22: Boxes on boxes on boxes of pizza being carried into the Senate GOP caucus room. Seems like they’re bracing for a long night…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @USMC: Semper Fi, Gomer Pyle. 

Rest in peace Jim Nabors, one of the few to ever be named an Honorary Marine. https://t.co/B3m3RYAbPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ruth_A_Buzzi: Nobody was more thoughtful, loving and special to his friends and family than Jim Nabors.  The many laughs and journeys w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rachaelmbade: CANCEL YOUR CHRISTMAS PLANS! GOP leaders announced in whip meeting 2day the double CR strategy. 1st CR will go to DEC 22…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexcguillen: American Airlines right now https://t.co/QPRrepD3v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: Acting @DHSgov chief Elaine Duke says dept has "stepped up" efforts to protect soft targets after the Las Vegas shooting…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatherineBScott: "There is no longer a home game and an away game," says Acting DHS Sec Elaine Duke re: counterterrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @byaaroncdavis: NEW: Conservative activist who failed to plant fake news with WashPost worked for months to infiltrate media in DC and N…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: I've got the deets on the latest development in a back-and-forth between @TSA and @GOPoversight. https://t.co/HAwaFkVLGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Raniaab: Meanwhile, many journalists in the field (including war zones), &amp; especially freelancers, are living on unlivable wages/per-pi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @petridishes: WELCOME TO THE FLIRTING CHAMBER i intone, pressing the button on my desk that makes the steel cage drop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JakeSherman: I’m standing outside the house side of the Capitol and they’re not allowing anyone in the building. Heavy police presence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness, I also brake for tacos https://t.co/d1X5HXPwCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samstein "News is a flirty business?" What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SuzanneStrug: .@CNN @CNNPolitics or other journalists who still want to raise a glass on Friday in an environment (and a bar) dedicated…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ABC: NEW: Radio-TV Congressional Association withdraws RT's press credentials, effective immediately; the move comes after RT registere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has already been a weird, jarring day. Enjoy this corgi being vacuumed. https://t.co/biWVuvEbTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SCourtneyDC: My scoop on the Senate #AV bill being floated for unanimous consent, now with a link outside the paywall: https://t.co/dnB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scottpwaldman: Lots of attention to Kathleen Hartnett White, who claims fossil fuels ended slavery, at CEQ today. Few reporters at NOAA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: So the tweets aren’t a game we should all ignore? They have real consequences as statements from the president? https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidMDrucker: "I guess somebody likes me." =&gt; https://t.co/Th2b5vIupI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EamonJavers: @JakeSherman True story: the late Sonny Bono once walked into the Speaker’s Lobby schnockered and asked me which way he wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @POLITICOPro: Drone strikes could be worse than bird strikes, study says. @brigurciullo has the rest here: https://t.co/axIG7guSeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SarahMMimms: Congresswoman Who Oversaw Complaints Against Members Says She Didn’t Sign Off On Any Sexual Harassment Settlements https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elisewho: We just got word that our recently-named @NPR Exec Editor (who was promoted by the former VP of News, the one ousted for sexu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting my small town’s staff acquainted with open records laws. Whee! #FOIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @martinepowers: literal text to a work friend: “omg we work with a bunch of f—ing ninjas” https://t.co/4KOABhQJ2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GPollowitz: Prince Harry's kids will be Americans. What if one grows up to be president and is in line for the throne at the same time?…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mkraju: Trump, who golfed with Tiger and Jack Nicklaus over last couple days, is back at one of his golf courses today for the 82nd tim…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinwilhelm @connorobrienNH “Sith Beats” would be a dope band name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Comey: “Our liberty depends on the freedom of the press, and that cannot be limited without being lost.” - Thomas Jefferson,  Jan. 28,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally 0-60 #dcweather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scottwongDC: SCOOP: DARRELL ISSA, who said yesterday he won't seek reelection in CA's 49th district, is talking about running in DUNCAN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapeworm. Enjoy it. https://t.co/1vFnBjHKoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brigurciullo: Both @SenJohnThune and @RepSamGraves said they aren't expecting to see that "detailed infrastructure principles document"…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Woellert: It’s official! I’m proud to join @politico’s crack White House team. Everyone pls send story suggestions and tips! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MoiraDonegan: In October, I made a google document. My life has been strange and sometimes frightening ever since. I wrote about it for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized I’m following 777 people. Scared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: .@SenRonJohnson says he expects senators to roll out DHS reauthorization soon. https://t.co/ERXDRNkJM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nancyscola: Totally stealing the occasion of Issa’s retirement to repost this Q&amp;A I did with him a bunch of years back — but only becau…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: A new FBI report casts doubt on the initial theory that Americans in Cuba have been hit by “sonic attacks.” https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna need this vessel after today https://t.co/LpQz9Oi4Pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwpetersNYT: BREAKING: BANNON STEPPING DOWN FROM BREITBART NEWS. Story to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChadPergram: Rules Cmte Chair Sessions says GOP won't lose House over earmarks. Plans two days of hearings next week starting January 1…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: .@GDouglasJones has been assigned to @SenateHSGACDems, replacing @jontester who is moving over to @SenateCommerce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just two bros workin' on cars https://t.co/1v4faEQIvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahnferris: I see that earmarks is now (oddly) trending in D.C.

In that case, here's the story I wrote today about why an earmarks r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JFKucinich: I can’t wait to skip the 30 for 30 about the majesty of Nick Saban. I’m sure Shawshank or Bride Wars will be on that day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByronTau: With Royce leaving, that Republican chairmen/chairwomen of:

-Foreign Affairs
-Judiciary
-House Administration
-Space, Scienc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @POLITICOPro: FAA Administrator Michael Huerta heads for the exits, his next chapter still open. More from @brigurciullo: https://t.co/U…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond You’ll be fine. Carry some credit cards or a checkbook (seriously) and be prepared to answer questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Titans can take a long walk off a short pier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @laura_nelson: I always learn something interesting from @Nataliekitro’s stories, and this piece on NAFTA and trucking is fascinating: h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just stroll through #stablegenius for a bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gardner_LM CQ is kinda like getting a shot of recombinant DNA...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gardner_LM: The CQ in me doesn't allow me to write this ever. https://t.co/vNwyN3IM1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steph_Beasley: Got a little scoop for y'all. Roster will likely include bills calling for @TSA to review its aviation security policy a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wmata: Metro reminds customers SmarTrip cards will not allow negative balances starting Monday https://t.co/t5fmi8tkLq #wmata https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shocked that I didn't see anyone once tweet about the #bombcyclone being "the bomb." Did I miss it?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>