<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Architect: – Technical Solutions Architect Job Locations US-VA-Reston | US-DC-Washington, DC | US-MD-Bethesda Req No. 2018-4573 Category Sales Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience, Cloud Networking, and… https://t.co/qUQmMNQ9GY https://t.co/HwvfrRE19H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptography Analyst: The Crypto Analyst is responsible for change and maintenance of existing application cryptographic services, eg Central Authentication Service, CertificateNOW, SSH Universal Key Manager, PKI platforms, HSM (standalone and farm) and… https://t.co/l3jX1sc4lo https://t.co/HWEww3y4mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia Democrat Lucy McBath elected to Congress following tight race: Georgia Democrat challenger Lucy McBath has defeated Republican Rep. Karen Handel to be elected to Congress, CNN projects. https://t.co/6RLJJDFtBD https://t.co/ObaMVXje8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospitality Manager (Technical – IT Department): Technical Hospitality Manager (IT Department) Location: Uxbridge Salary: £45’000 per annum Days: FT Monday – Friday Contract Duration: Permanent (or contract with intention of permanency) Technical… https://t.co/oJZ7C0SEn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer – Leading Technology Firm: Senior DevOps Engineer required to join a highly successful and talented IT team at one of Edinburgh’s most successful Software companies who work hand in hand developing new products for some of the… https://t.co/bkJPuGQRwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Operator – IBM, iSeries, OS400: Computer Operator – IBM, iSeries, OS400      -Excellent opportunity for a Computer Operator to work in a highly technical, progressive environment. -Chance to work for a well-known, established Technology provider… https://t.co/EQONpS0I6B https://t.co/pFBceFcO4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Product Development Lead: Software Product Development Lead East Midlands A fun household brand, offering valuable services to millions of customers. Fabulous offices, with open space for collaboration and also quiet spaces when you need to… https://t.co/j2TDJ3v7js https://t.co/xvpxc2iFiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite a strong Q3 earnings report, Square’s Q4 forecast disappoints investors: Despite a strong third-quarter earnings report, Square’s forecast for the final quarter of this year gave investors pause, sending its share price down 6 percent in after… https://t.co/JtUvLYrDr6 https://t.co/kMJLPU59g2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Witness describes watching gunman enter bar: Multiple people were injured in a shooting at a bar in Thousand Oaks, California, authorities said. https://t.co/E9ImQ4G89P https://t.co/MvYWKNztzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer – Firewalls, Applications, Operating Systems – Salary £35,000 – £45,000 + Benefits – London The company: An award-winning provider of cloud-based solutions with offices across the globe. Due to… https://t.co/NerGHwytC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power BI Developer: Business Intelligence Developer opportunity at a global aviation company based in Farnborough. You will develop varied solutions for multiple large corporations and independent businesses. Working within the group’s Business operation… https://t.co/QEMru33QFo https://t.co/yOcJa56H4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside history's most opulent English houses: When it came to depicting the timeless beauty of England's historic homes, interior designer David Mlinaric faced a tricky question: "Where shall I begin?" https://t.co/A9AkJP31m0 https://t.co/h3hNWrZvj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer (Tech stack: DevOps Engineer, AWS, Azure, Linux, PHP, SQL, Bash, Python, CentOS, MySQL, Nginx, Jenkins, Travis, Teamcity, Octopus, Docker, Kubernetes, Rancher, Swarm, Ansible, Puppet, Terraform, Git, Grafana, Prometheus,… https://t.co/4TVQy20q8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing a… https://t.co/MM5b8tlpE4 https://t.co/JGRiJS14vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer – Front-End Developer- Frontend Developer: Front End Developer – Front-End Developer- Frontend Developer – Angular – Node – Javascript – FED We have fantastic opportunities for Frontend Developers to join an international consultancy… https://t.co/MV4537cEzG https://t.co/9dkb83oiKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior/Mid Level Full Stack Developer: Are you looking for an opportunity to progress your skill set and naturally grow within an organisation? If so I have the perfect position for you! I am working with a company who are looking to bring on a developer… https://t.co/ukjVIvnENy https://t.co/1M2s2rKtvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House pulls Acosta's pass after contentious press conference: Breaking news update: https://t.co/ABGsN68FV9 https://t.co/0SY83bUbXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Financial Officer (Rail): Become Part of Our Team As an industry leader Balfour Beatty offers employees a comprehensive benefits package that includes competitive salaries, comprehensive medical, dental and vision benefits, paid time off and… https://t.co/dW7L1zLFGu https://t.co/s5bbOXtIu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript UI Developer: JavaScript UI Developer – £40k – £50k + Shares – Reading – Remote working available Avanti Recruitment is currently working with an exciting start up based in Reading town centre, a short walk from the train station. Their… https://t.co/cb8TqsWKt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer Education: Sierra Consulting Inc. seeks Business Intelligence Developer Education: masters in Information Systems Management or related field. Duties Producing quality analytical and reporting solutions that support the… https://t.co/vZxCUh8xHZ https://t.co/qbXxBJrI0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend Engineer – React – Instant market insights (AI): Frontend Engineer – React London Imagine if we could access data on-demand that would give us insights into people and the places they visit. A platform powered by AI and Machine Learning of… https://t.co/nbz81Yyfpe https://t.co/G9OeafToBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is facing an EU data probe over fake ads: The UK’s privacy watchdog has asked Facebook’s lead EU regulator to look into ongoing data protection concerns about its ad platform — including how its platform is being used to target and spread fake… https://t.co/I64E2tyfdZ https://t.co/zfDh6t91M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Republicans' secret weapon was Kavanaugh: Republicans lost dozens of House seats and the majority in that chamber Tuesday, while simultaneously expanding their control of the Senate. https://t.co/m8M1huUNKu https://t.co/WP822s4xHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projct Manager / Business Analyst: HR Project Manager / Business Analyst – HR systems process design, implementation, project management methodologies, project lifecycle – cost / risk / planning, strong analysis skills with understanding of business and… https://t.co/Ug2ebsKdpl https://t.co/VOrMUMp6RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he has 'never used racist remarks': President Donald Trump on Wednesday strongly pushed back against claims he has made racist remarks, as alleged by his former lawyer Michael Cohen. https://t.co/j9pRVEGCYp https://t.co/uwdv0uFbOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer (C#): Senior Software Developer (C#) Product and Technology Innovation award winner £65k base + Bonus and Flexible Working hours Southampton We are seeking a talented Senior Software Developer (C#) to take an influential role in… https://t.co/hV6K49QfrR https://t.co/Wp4m3GUiTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Data Analyst Contract (Great Day Rate): Digital Data Analyst Contract (Great Day Rate) Our leading client is looking for a Digital Data Analyst to support the growing demands of it’s expanding workforce for an initial 12-month contract which is… https://t.co/hPGvPX3f5s https://t.co/mfLcFf0rP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Capita IT Resourcing is partnered with an exciting software company based in Bracknell. They have enjoyed significant year-on-year growth again and are now looking to grow their software development team. The Software Developer role… https://t.co/QXO46ubIvi https://t.co/DmVmsen4Qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems' House victory gives Mueller key protection: The Democratic Party regained control of the House of Representatives as a result of Tuesday's midterm elections, while the Republicans held firm control of the Senate. While a Democratic-controlled House… https://t.co/5gn64PAH6H https://t.co/MSd9FhMZVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Developer Contract: C# .Net Developer Contract My client is ramping up for a major New Year project and as a result needs to increase the capabilities of its Microsoft based project delivery team with a C# .Net Developer Contractor (BizTalk… https://t.co/e5GnUVf6OS https://t.co/yWrgZsWOHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect – Bristol: Technical Architect – Bristol – J2EE / .NET – AWS – £65,000 An excellent opportunity has arisen to join a leading IT Consultancy with offices around the UK as a Technical Architect. They are offering up to £65,000 +… https://t.co/PA3vToVSIu https://t.co/rdmn01l6Yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Democrats will do once they're in power https://t.co/gGgqvQHBH0 https://t.co/I2owsHSmAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: JOB PURPOSE: ·Build the front-end and/or back-end of various products (mostly greenfield projects) ·Build units for existing tools that are vital to the company expansion ·Coordinate with the product manager and director of… https://t.co/k8O4V98657 https://t.co/EbD7AleBoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: EBSoft Consulting Inc: Careers EBSoft Consulting Inc Your Business Technology Partner Oracle Partner – Home – Services – Solutions – Clients – Partners – News Room – Careers – About Us – Contact Home Careers – Overview EBSoft… https://t.co/FlvEmFWBcy https://t.co/pWDZdeUZuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original Content podcast: We’re left a little cold by Netflix’s new ‘Chilling Adventures of Sabrina’: It seemed like the ingredients were there for “The Chilling Adventures of Sabrina” to win us over. After all, at least one of the hosts of the Original… https://t.co/tiP9e9y5Km https://t.co/hN3mbsM9S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These children have high risk of being stabbed on way home from school: Children are most likely to become victims of stabbings as they walk home from school, a London study has found, as its authors warn of the "endemic" nature of knife crime among… https://t.co/1TaKdhmwG4 https://t.co/ex0S8PQqfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Web Developer Job description The Web Developer role is a vital part of the development team responsible for creating, designing, maintaining and implementing small to medium software projects. You will also be involved in the full Agile… https://t.co/fxxMxPMp4i https://t.co/Hy4sJPhzYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Analyst – Bath: IT Support Analyst – Bath Leading Consultancy Next to Bath Spa train station Up to £23k We are currently recruiting for an IT Support Analyst based in Bath. Our client is one of the world’s leading construction, architect and… https://t.co/9rNy69w3UG https://t.co/Oc7vk3JHM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager, Healthcare IT: Healthcare IT Project Manager PACS &amp; RIS Healthcare IT Systems £43K – £48K + Bonus + Car or £5,400 Car Allowance + Pension + Healthcare + Phone + Laptop + Full and Comprehensive Product Training **An excellent… https://t.co/d7idOzYLOj https://t.co/tp4fegyEKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Midterm results that will shape America's future: Before the midterm elections, CNN Opinion asked commentators to weigh in on the races they were watching most closely. We have asked those commentators to assess the outcome of those races -- and what… https://t.co/2FEUY0DOq3 https://t.co/yrDE3e4VHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C# – Global Record Label – London: NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C# – Global Record Label – London (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, WCF, RESTful, Web API 2, SQL Server… https://t.co/posw1smAto https://t.co/RsJFstrlzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test and Operations Engineer: Do you have experience working in the media industry as a Tester? Does working with entertainment products excite you? If so then read on, because a company based in Central London are seeking a Test and Operations Engineer… https://t.co/zwVa2jtWUH https://t.co/AmiAvnjx6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our… https://t.co/ru2RD09Ldp https://t.co/HKcd1PBTRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Architect: Test Architect – Midlands l Based in the Midlands l Rate competitive Are you an experienced Test Architect who wants the opportunity to be part of a huge transformation replatform for a leading retailer in Midlands? If so, Vantage… https://t.co/65q1fqP0gX https://t.co/nBjRE0ZrJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect fought for the steering wheel before killing 3 Girl Scouts, prosecutor says: A 21-year-old driver struggled with his passenger over the steering wheel before driving his truck into a group of Girl Scouts, killing three and one of their mothers,… https://t.co/y4Nb35viwJ https://t.co/xGORp5EZBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position earning from £18k per annum? * Are you technically minded? * Do your family… https://t.co/EnvJyYgbGg https://t.co/FUTDY6bLc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colorado man pleads guilty to killing pregnant wife and daughters: A Colorado man who killed his pregnant wife and his two young daughters pleaded guilty Tuesday as part of a plea deal that allows him to avoid the death penalty, the office of Weld County… https://t.co/Y6MoyIZa7A https://t.co/sMRoYtbzeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support: Applications are invited for the position of IT Administrator. Reporting to the Group IT Manager, the IT Administrator will provide IT support at Gloucester and provide additional assistance at all sites as required. Principal… https://t.co/K3dJx1UWzJ https://t.co/HdCW9U7Bt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer; .Net; Delphi; North Wales – £50k / £400 pd: Software Developer; .Net; Delphi; North Wales – £50k / £400 per day Software Developer is required by one of North Wales most dynamic and entrepreneurial design agencies. The company work… https://t.co/r54bPVvFIJ https://t.co/LTm283fRZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasmo pivots to scooter cameras that keep them off sidewalks: GPS is too inaccurate to tell if a scooter is being driven or parked in off-limits areas. But as scooter startups compete for permits from city governments, they need a way to prove their… https://t.co/iCplgb2qSV https://t.co/USgMWii4qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measles outbreak in Israel prompts warning in NYC: Measles has been diagnosed in 17 children in the Orthodox Jewish community in the Williamsburg and Borough Park neighborhoods in Brooklyn, the New York City Department of Health stated Friday. https://t.co/IeROxG6gSw https://t.co/yaDvuZFgsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure Engineer: Are you a Web Hosting Engineer with excellent knowledge of Microsoft Azure? Looking for the opportunity to ensure that an award-winning software company can provide exceptional software and service to their global clients? And… https://t.co/ljlttgnLXq https://t.co/qjNZRh9vbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sage X3 Consultant: My Clent is currently resourcing for a Sage X3 Consultant, on an ad-hoc basis, to resolve their day to day issues within Sage X3. The Project is currently ongoing and is being completed by my client's support partner. What my client… https://t.co/gvGOtzSP5w https://t.co/tcm38r1qD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager (Temp to Hire Position): IT Engineer (Temp to Hire) Magellan has been a pioneer and leader in GPS technology and products for business and consumers since 1986. Along with a host of firsts and award-winning products, Magellan is credited with… https://t.co/Pxtsy37PBV https://t.co/ARpIGmg2Ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CI/CD Consultant (Cloud &amp; DevOps): CI/CD Consultant | Stockholm, Sweden |Flexible Salary Based on Experience Type: Permanent Location: Stockholm, Sweden Salary: Competitive and Flexible based on Experience Working for an Amazon Web services ‘Advanced… https://t.co/Qx7Q3mQG0Z https://t.co/x1UGiMjxfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News staffers express outrage over Hannity's rally appearance: Fox News journalists were outraged and disgusted after Sean Hannity, the network's star host, campaigned with President Donald Trump on Monday night ahead of the midterm elections, more… https://t.co/A0cJxhmswV https://t.co/vJqzxf63yQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer: Are you ready to take the step into a Senior Java Engineer role? Do you want to work with cutting edge technologies including Machine Learning, Big Data and AI? We are hiring talented Java Developers and Engineers to join a… https://t.co/XVYHt4cVw2 https://t.co/TwQ0Z63Qsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Portfolio Manager (Web, Mobile, Retail): Digital Portfolio Manager (Web, Mobile, Retail) £65,000 + Car Allowance + Bonus + Benefits West Midlands (Commutable from Birmingham, Worcester, Stratford upon Avon, Leamington Spac, Coventry) Are… https://t.co/xlaSxr77AF https://t.co/Yr0dflzZL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer: The ideal candidate will have over 5 years of PHP programming experience and be confident working with Javascript, HTML and CSS. You will be responsible for migrating a Drupal System to Laravel, so experience with these… https://t.co/FqM8i4KzGR https://t.co/NO2VImmRUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Display Software Engineer Intern: Job Details Req ID 18126 Title Display Software Engineer Intern City Burr Ridge State Illinois Job Function Product Development &amp; Engineering Salaried / Hourly Hourly Job Description Through its people and brands, CNH… https://t.co/QLv1yiZRk3 https://t.co/IHhPWzAPok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In pictures: Americans cast their ballots: People across the United States will be voting in the midterm elections Tuesday, but more than 31 million have already cast their ballot. https://t.co/UhEKdeeqUt https://t.co/LsxIr9us6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Systems Analyst Technical Specialist: Req # 2018-51388 Category Engineering # of Openings 1 Job Location US-Washington-DC Clearance Top Secret Overview Every day at Perspecta, we enable hundreds of thousands of people to take on our nation… https://t.co/waISMGs6w1 https://t.co/Gz42tMWMPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: Established in 1984, Uniserve are the largest British privately owned international freight and logistics company in the UK. Working with an unrivalled network of professional partners across the world. We are experts in all major Global… https://t.co/A4nXdTTlwE https://t.co/3iRGRO9UIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Atlassian Consultant London £70K: Our client is a fast-growth market leading consultancy specialising in BDD, DevOps and Test Automation. You will provide hands-on technical experience and enable teams through leading by example and coaching… https://t.co/YJCP57YOqi https://t.co/RR43daLEBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The (Final) Forecast: Democrats, GOP will both be happy: The 2018 campaign (mostly) comes to an end today. If the polls and our forecasts are right, the Democrats and Republicans will each have something to be happy about. https://t.co/h8zT6WC9MI https://t.co/9P4apxVhds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principle Data Engineer: Principle Data Engineer South West As a trading fund of the Ministry of Defence (MOD), our client, founded in 1795, provide world leading products and marine geospatial data to support global maritime decision-making. Responsible… https://t.co/UpoL0fstzk https://t.co/VK4PJfByph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hours before U.S. election day, Facebook pulls dozens of accounts for ‘coordinated inauthentic behavior’: Facebook has pulled the plug on 30 accounts and 85 Instagram accounts that the company says were engaged in “coordinated inauthentic behavior.”… https://t.co/lQE2TP3QjG https://t.co/ymfiQ86k96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator I: NGP VAN is seeking a system administrator who will plan, implement and maintain hardware and software in support of our internal office environment as well as public-facing web applications. Candidates will provide end-user… https://t.co/jgpEa3ImqS https://t.co/WHQBTvClai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead C# Developer (Digital Design): Job title: Lead C# Developer (Digital Design) A fantastic new opportunity for a C# Developer at a Lincoln City Centre based Digital Design Agency, who are working on exciting, bespoke and cutting edge software… https://t.co/HNcmShVPUJ https://t.co/nV0oO319cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Scrum Master: Project Manager / Scrum Master required for one of the largest Utility companies. They recognise that investments in both employee development and working environment drive them forward as a modern, innovative and… https://t.co/qLf2wGB2Fz https://t.co/I6oi5ZRcMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: This is an exciting opportunity for a talented Data Analyst working for a market-leading restaurant group, offering great benefits, such as 10% bonus, 25 days holiday and 50% off discount across the restaurant group. The role will be based… https://t.co/ufSAGCE8fB https://t.co/DqKUpSjXJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Networking/Internet Gurus: We have an exciting position available for an exceptional individual to join a start-up company with ground-breaking technology which is making the internet a far safer place. Duties and responsibilities: * Developing a… https://t.co/FjcbE4KV2e https://t.co/D2VGMnPQ7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity said he wouldn't campaign on stage at Trump's rally. Hours later, he did exactly that.: Sean Hannity defied his own words on Monday. https://t.co/fW1lrieMLx https://t.co/1lv6ARoTi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OCONUS Construction Manager: 120443BR Job Description: Job Description: Raytheon IIS is seeking a Construction Manager to provide oversight and management of construction projects and renovations at OCONUS government facilities. Position… https://t.co/QCGQfGUkhN https://t.co/ugvzdg6oxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Director: Solutions Director – London – £60,000. Are you currently working as a Technical Project Manager? A Technical Business Analyst? Or a Senior Solutions Designer? Good – then this you’re in the right place! I’m working with a marketing… https://t.co/w4U7jk7RQD https://t.co/Gmnrzdh06q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Description BAE Systems in Washington DC is seeking a software programmer with Java experience. The candidate will work in a small team environment located in Washington DC. The candidate will participate in all phases of the… https://t.co/u8pm6PVtTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Application Architect + Initial 6 month contract based in Derby/Nottingham + £450 to 550 per day + Leading Application Solution design Ability to deliver solution architectures conformant with a TOGAF 9 defined Enterprise… https://t.co/cRukaYXQEz https://t.co/FkMfqeWpOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: ABOUT US: BBS Securities Inc. (BBS) is registered in all Provinces and Territories of Canada as an Investment Dealer, and is a member of Regulatory Organization of Canada (IIROC) and the Canadian Investor Protection Fund (CIPF).… https://t.co/k9rI6Z7kV7 https://t.co/V8GSmakOfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Brian Kemp stood by his decision to level claims of attempted hacking at Democrats, turning their objections into an election eve selling point: With the clock winding down before Tuesday's vote, Georgia's chief elections officer, who is also… https://t.co/9VHv792X0t https://t.co/EH9OVxHO1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position with excellent earning potential? * Are you technically minded? * Do your… https://t.co/XU44DQSvT1 https://t.co/yHyfI7xbx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist/Engineer Service Operations:   Job Description – Specialist/Engineer Service Operations (27441) Job Description  Specialist/Engineer Service Operations – 27441  Profession : Service Operations  Work Location : Europe-United Kingdom-London … https://t.co/jtGJj2Kodw https://t.co/KHYI6BZR7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says 'I don't care' if Dems go after my tax returns: President Donald Trump shrugged off the prospect of Democrats going after his tax returns if the party wins control of the House in this week's midterm contests, suggesting Monday he was… https://t.co/kRwLZiKjX4 https://t.co/fm8MtPuc8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS DevOps Engineer: AWS DevOps Engineer – London – 6 months – £600-£650 per day Currently on the lookout for a DevOps Engineer to join my client, a leading online retail company, on an initial 6 month contract with possibility to extend. You will be… https://t.co/NVOwPNOkBB https://t.co/RYlthFtQjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 Midterms: 4 resources every voter should know about: Voting in the U.S. can be confusing. By design, every state is different. On top of that, disinformation meant to discourage voting is rampant this election. Cut through the noise, arm yourself… https://t.co/gK9CFLigUv https://t.co/zspB9rMGMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Contract- React: I am looking for a Software Engineer with strong React skills for a Market Leading SaaS Organisation company based in Manchester who boasts year on year growth in size and profitability and as they continue to corner… https://t.co/1k6VFu3Auh https://t.co/EZldMX0jzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: I am currently recruiting for a Data Engineer to work in Leeds, for a 6 month contract. This opportunity will provide exposure to the AWS stack as well as working with big data tools, an outline of the role is below; – AWS Stack (EC2, S3,… https://t.co/8ebhUdZ6pu https://t.co/Ya1vncE3RV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ate a slug on a dare, became paralyzed and died: It was just a silly dare among teenage boys. What could it hurt to eat a small slug? https://t.co/yb87iG0P0Z https://t.co/Chqjdxglln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior BI Developer: Senior Business Intelligence Developer / BI Developer A BI Developer is required for an innovative organisation in central London who are genuinely making a difference to the world in positive way. The successful BI developer will… https://t.co/xXbb85wVV2 https://t.co/056p1Rn7fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Relationship Executive (Entry-level): Client Relationship Executive (Entry-level), London Our client are a company focused on delivering exceptional customer experience strategies and solutions. They offer is a unique software that helps… https://t.co/uBQ59dnPjX https://t.co/H6SzLdGTl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoga studio shooting survivor tells ABC he fought off the gunman with a vacuum: A man who survived the deadly shooting at a Tallahassee yoga studio may have saved his own life -- and the lives of others -- when he apparently confronted the attacker with… https://t.co/CdI0bKd1On https://t.co/r0JxaPJ5QD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHAREPOINT CONSULTANT – £55,000 – Flexible Working: SharePoint Consultant – £55,000 – Flexible Working Are you interested in working for a Microsoft Gold Partner? Do you want to work at a company that has an award winning culture and a reputation for… https://t.co/KA7ZlJICSk https://t.co/RBSqon6c21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Full-Stack Developer: World leading Data Analytics company based in Cambridge seeks a Graduate Full-Stack Developer to build new internal and customer-facing solutions to support the pharmaceutical and healthcare markets. This is a new position,… https://t.co/CVG0PvXiMo https://t.co/n7sqKP1CZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lowe's is closing 51 stores: In another sign of the times for retail, Lowe's is closing 51 North American stores. https://t.co/ukCZz0NMG4 https://t.co/S9Uc5Ih7Nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Recruitment Consultant: Job Title: Graduate Recruitment Consultant Location: Poole, Dorset Salary: £20,000 (£27K OTE) REF: J3161:SW Sector: IT Recruitment This IT recruitment company has built a name for themselves in their market, and have just… https://t.co/RthuitD7Ii https://t.co/9tY1bKGwB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer – Vue, Node or similar, Agile: Full Stack Engineer – Vue, Node or similar, Agile £50,000 to £70,000 Based in Central London Client: With over 500,000 users across 190 countries, this app is considered to be a "gamechanger"…and given… https://t.co/qMktKEDjI7 https://t.co/XnalMiyowE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support/2nd Line: Desktop Support/2nd line Support – Cambridge 12 month STC Immediate start Salary £22500+ An experienced 2nd line/Desktop Support Analyst is required for an immediate 12 month FTC post with a global company with prestigious… https://t.co/XmC3eIahpb https://t.co/zBFRiBZCda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELA Test Developer, Alternate Assessment: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10813 Job Location United States Alternate locations Washington, D.C. Category Test Development/Content Overview AIR Assessment is one of America’s leading K -12 educational assessment… https://t.co/gZEIvc0Q2K https://t.co/RnXWElDwd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Midterms road map: 10 races to watch on Election Night: There is a lot up for grabs Tuesday. https://t.co/pPIC94eej3 https://t.co/QvgAX0Scbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: A specialist software based in Fareham company who work with the very latest technologies are searching for a Software Engineer to join their team. As a Software Engineer, you’ll be working on an interesting mix of products and… https://t.co/zu2FnJVVIB https://t.co/UIPDjXCicw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More.X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact Sheet Principal… https://t.co/kdRiqjeGLQ https://t.co/Th85x8V6mN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>