<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where the world's highest bungee jump will open: For those who have successfully overcome their fears and walked the world's highest glass-bottom bridge in China, it's time to take things up a notch -- and bungee off it. https://t.co/VOcxR33wv3 https://t.co/WVc4w4bJva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First same-sex kiss in US campaign ad: A new television ad showing a gubernatorial candidate kissing his husband is the first political spot in US history to feature a kiss between a candidate and their same-sex spouse, according to LGBTQ Victory Fund's… https://t.co/JbkH1kS3g8 https://t.co/i96z5sFGaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Software Engineer, Performance: Job CategoryProducts and Technology Job Details We are seeking a UI Software Engineer, Performance to join our R &amp; D, Tech &amp; Products team. As the 4th largest software company in the world, and the leader in the cloud,… https://t.co/7Pwmdlmmwt https://t.co/WndCKYLCDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Server BI Developer: MS SQL Server BI Developer in Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join… https://t.co/jCEWHoMdQd https://t.co/gvwWk0iPcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Texans watched Hurricane Harvey from boats: During a FEMA briefing on hurricane preparedness, President Trump said one reason the Coast Guard was so busy rescuing people during Hurricane Harvey was that "people went out in their boats to watch the… https://t.co/ZyY9PW7HCb https://t.co/vxslHuOL5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: Position Title: SQL Server DBA Position Location: Oklahoma RESPONSIBILITIES: Work with other team members collaboratively in understanding and resolving database issues including database performance problems Installation of SQL Server… https://t.co/wZPy89Ztod https://t.co/isXUoaOesX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice Johnson: Why Kim Kardashian wanted President Trump to free me https://t.co/LVx6K0bn1Y https://t.co/oy0MjDxplS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL-SQL Developer: PL-SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-23125 Location: Fountain Valley, California Role: PL-SQL Developer Location: Fountain Valley CA Type: Contract Key skills required for the job are: PL-SQL-L3 (Mandatory) Oracle SQL-L3 As a Senior Developer,… https://t.co/PAPaK5WxUW https://t.co/L2yOj8xPv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Script Developer: SQL Script Developer – Chicago Software Tech Jobs at Milyli Inc. – – Products – Overview – Blackout – Blackout Homepage – End to End Native Excel Workflow! – Introducing Native Excel Redactions with Blackout – Broadcast – Broadcast… https://t.co/SlOBS0J9ju https://t.co/OMZjeLVGuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer in Alexandria, Virginia, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers… https://t.co/xzYnuZ8XfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Application Development Advisor: Job Description Job Description As a SQL Server Software Developer, you will be responsible for end to end, full-stack development of both internal and client facing applications for Wellpartner’s Contract… https://t.co/XjIWxiVjKY https://t.co/ZxnG7Tya8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passwords at work could be on their way out https://t.co/wlF5GUceL1 https://t.co/5zYa1KK3FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-21163 Location: Bangor, Maine Position : PL/SQL Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Bangor, ME Job Description: Experience Required 1. Excellent knowledge in Pl/SQL programming language 2.… https://t.co/H0Wv3tKdkt https://t.co/0aLAx1kOHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Programmer (Plymouth): SQL Programmer (Plymouth) – Job Listing – Loc Performance Jobs Search Jobs | Submit an Application | Home SQL Programmer (Plymouth) Salary Range:Negotiable Exempt/Non-Exempt:Exempt Benefits:Medical, Dental, Life and Disability… https://t.co/aGbDd3L6C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer (C# / .NET 4.0 / JavaScript / SQL ): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity –… https://t.co/4B8Lw3Gm1T https://t.co/hGz7Udm2ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL PL/SQL Developer: An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified ETL Developer with TS clearance to join their growing team. This person will be responsible for the data warehouse design… https://t.co/B6d5TrlaY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: PROPOSED AD Portland, OR. Sr. Database Administrator. Draft and maintain procedures and documentation for databases. Manage database configuration including installing and upgrading software and maintaining relevant documentation.… https://t.co/2AatEGCL4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump dunked on Sessions in the most vicious way possible: It's no secret that President Donald Trump loathes his attorney general, Jeff Sessions. The reason it's no secret is because on a weekly basis -- and sometimes even a daily basis -- the President… https://t.co/CpLVCWuC8S https://t.co/TJVdwPfGy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job ID: ********-10050-LEK Company Name: Argus Description: LCI is an industry leader at analytical and technological services to the financial industry. Founded over 25 years ago, we handle over 1.3 billion accounts a year for the… https://t.co/8OpvEcBidJ https://t.co/l0MoPBE7nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – KnowledgeBase (Java, Python, SQL): 17000BR Job Description and Requirements About Synopsys – Black Duck Software, Did you know that Synopsys acquired Black Duck Software? Together we help organizations around the globe secure… https://t.co/hbGpJ4Zyrm https://t.co/nSSjIpqXyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-24152 Location: Johnston City, Illinois – Installation and Configuration of SQL Server 2008/2008R2/2012 on Standalone and Clustering. – Experience in SQL Database Up-gradation &amp; Migration – Experience in Good Backup &amp;… https://t.co/PbkAL4BDxN https://t.co/hiBeVL0vz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Data-Developer-Analyst: This is a 4-6 month contract opportunity for a Data Developer/ Analyst (SQL). This opportunity will likely become a long-term engagaement for the right person. You will be working on a six man team with a major pharmaceutical… https://t.co/M8KAiHH7SA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK rates of ancient STI reach record high: Cases of syphilis reported in England have reached the highest level since 1949, according to new data on sexually transmitted infections (STIs) released Tuesday by Public Health England. https://t.co/tQpNSOv5bu https://t.co/PtMO3BcHZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The stark reminder in Kate Spade's bewildering death: Fashion designer Kate Spade's death by apparent suicide, discovered Tuesday by a housekeeper, has hit a tender nerve, particularly in New York. On Tuesday I saw media crews and onlookers… https://t.co/7gPLeWz7a5 https://t.co/MTWHS0jCtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort could be in big trouble: Paul Manafort could be in big trouble. The cozy house-arrest situation of the former chairman of Donald Trump's election campaign may rapidly change to confinement in a federal correctional facility if a judge in… https://t.co/JdjxmvTanT https://t.co/0cHYwnHHCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: SQL Server Database Administrator Ref No.:18-00251 Location: Washington, District of Columbia SQL Server Database Administrator Responsibilities: – Provide SQL Server 2016 infrastructure Database Administration (DBA)… https://t.co/O9Re43iFA9 https://t.co/4Sjcy4dSrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parkland survivor David Hogg's home swatted: The family of Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School student activist David Hogg was the victim of a "swatting" incident Tuesday morning. https://t.co/V6LP3JMGdR https://t.co/QLVS6RQyUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer – Senior: SQL Developer – Senior Job in Scottsdale, AZ | CVS HEALTH ************* Main menu – About – About – Our Services – Retail Pharmacy – Pharmacy Benefits Management – Clinical Services – Specialty Pharmacy – Digital Services –… https://t.co/C98g9JVJN9 https://t.co/smDJnZgW1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black women are running for office in record numbers in Alabama: A record number of black women are running for office as Democrats in Alabama. https://t.co/qzcUOFsFSv https://t.co/b37zsWI6fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that… https://t.co/lxcCV7ncGy https://t.co/igtLRAnmgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Manager, Appl Development (Ruby, C#, .NET, SQL Server): Group Manager, Appl Development (Ruby, C#, .NET, SQL Server) Manages a medium to large-sized or multiple small teams responsible for all phases of the systems development and implementation… https://t.co/DiVwOiICzy https://t.co/HXJVv1Wkgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolly Parton snags Netflix deal: Dolly Parton clearly works much longer than 9 to 5. https://t.co/QaSubeqinx https://t.co/7Yv4FpVRoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Performance Engineer: Optimization of existing data services and SQL Database, analyze performance bottlenecks and system failures. Primary role in smaller, low risk projects. Improvements on security of services, creation of data integrity monitors… https://t.co/9zlYa8acDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Consultant Senior: Job Description Job Description Are you looking for a role that is technical and analytical and makes a big impact to a Fortune 10 healthcare leader? If so, here’s your opportunity. CVS health has an exciting opportunity for… https://t.co/eQLhWBntDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz silent for 18 seconds after question: Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX) was speechless for 18 seconds before sidestepping a question from a reporter about whether Trump can pardon himself. https://t.co/pZDnSJVtmI https://t.co/nv9F2TDmC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS, DB2 job – Asset Servicing – Jersey City, New Jersey Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation –… https://t.co/BPRyrzfJ75 https://t.co/Ht5blezePC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Engineer: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-IL-Lincolnshire Posting Description Aon is looking for a Senior SQL Server Database Engineer As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by… https://t.co/Swb6q8gwjO https://t.co/CFa3lfyjiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer – Healthcare ***2 new openings!***: Full time, direct hire position in Huntington Beach, CA for a Sr. SQL Server ETL Developer with healthcare experience. Position offers a great work environment with a competitive salary, bonus, and… https://t.co/hgPM7UTPL9 https://t.co/z2kds9ISgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook defends sharing user data with phone makers https://t.co/PDtuiyx5Fa https://t.co/C9NpItWx0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL DBA: Senior SQL DBA west palm beach, Florida – United States Job Start Date – 05/30/18, Posted Date – 05/30/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Company: PBSO Position: Senior SQL DBA Location: West Palm Beach, FL 33406 Duration: 6… https://t.co/BQ44wfRN1l https://t.co/LpEOUFj2SN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sea level rise is pushing property owners to higher ground: Despite the apocalyptic drumbeat from climate scientists, most Americans remain skeptical that climate change is the "most urgent threat facing our entire species," as actor Leonardo DiCaprio… https://t.co/IaG27857Eu https://t.co/i7WsYdEzCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Engineering Leader / Application Architect: Staff Engineering Leader / Application Architect job description at VMware Skip Navigation MENU VMware Search Jobs – MENU – Home – Life at VMWare – Careers – Sales – Engineering &amp; Technology – University… https://t.co/NaLyIXx7DG https://t.co/NBuq5A2kXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL – PL/SQL Developer (Top Secret Clearance Required): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified ETL Developer with TS clearance to join their growing team. This person will be… https://t.co/6ln1ZCgSQY https://t.co/zNeW14tKNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Data-Developer-Analyst: This is a 4-6 month contract opportunity for a Data Developer/ Analyst (SQL). This opportunity will likely become a long-term engagaement for the right person. You will be working on a six man team with a major pharmaceutical… https://t.co/xpnfV5dQ4J https://t.co/cJ1tcZAlPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: SQL Server Developer Ref No.: 18-21416 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position: SQL Server Developer Location: Washington, DC – More than 5 years of SQL development project. – 5+ years of relevant experience as a DBA in… https://t.co/nGMKHhNh8e https://t.co/WqPXrxlvUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL PL/SQL Developer: An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified ETL Developer with TS clearance to join their growing team. This person will be responsible for the data warehouse design… https://t.co/NdRUbQJHEE https://t.co/oWFhJ5TSjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Lead SQL Server DBA: Job ID 13713-2018 State Maine Shift First City Freeport Overview Leon Leonwood Bean (L.L. Bean) founded his business on a passion for the outdoors, a profound belief in honesty, and an unwavering commitment to quality and… https://t.co/64gitAyTce https://t.co/L6l6EPxVid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis player crushes ball boy at French Open https://t.co/6ZEhog4Bki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Full stack + Angular or React + AWS + NoSQL; CS Degree strongly preferred: Kore 1 Jobs Page ************|************** – Services – Workforce Planning – Software Development – IT Strategy – Staffing Solutions – Technology Staffing –… https://t.co/uI8WhOex1W https://t.co/3KaUpiHsgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-23801 Location: Waukegan, Illinois Role: .Net Developer Location: Waukegan, IL Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required – Proficiency in .NET1.1/2.0/3.5,*******,Classic *******, SQLServer2008 and SSIS Jobs.… https://t.co/gasF4tCqIs https://t.co/FJZlhCcugH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corker says the aim is to limit the President's use of authority in ways that are damaging to US and allies: Sen. Bob Corker said Saturday that he is working with other Senate Republicans on an effort to "push back" on President Donald Trump's use of… https://t.co/F4j8Cle9LP https://t.co/U74NIoqkHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: SQL Database Administrator SQL Database Administrator Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked… https://t.co/lXnP8GuqRE https://t.co/IaZuUOymFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: SQL Server Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 05/21/18, Posted Date – 05/21/18 Primary SkillsSQL ServerTax TermsC2COverview SQL Server/MySQL ServerDBA. This role is long-term and based in Charlotte, NC. Skype Hire EAD… https://t.co/Adspv32Iy3 https://t.co/xtaDQO6pMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooper calls out 'double standard': CNN's Anderson Cooper points out the hypocrisy of President Trump tweeting about Samantha Bee's vulgar language, but remaining silent about Roseanne Barr's racist remarks. https://t.co/HBxNxefEKL https://t.co/RonGmMBJGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSNBC anchor apologizes for blog posts: MSNBC anchor Joy Reid apologized after a number of incendiary blog posts from more than a decade ago resurfaced. https://t.co/foY3q35jSg https://t.co/puyrpYhhaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL SERVER Developer: SQL SERVER Developer Ref No.: 18-21243 Location: Whippany, New Jersey – Candidate should have 10+ years of experience in SQl Server development – Should have extensive Pl SQl development experience and should be adept in medium to… https://t.co/GupraM7iBK https://t.co/OKXfDrMvFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's trade war is self-defeating: We have repeatedly heard from President Trump that the United States' main trading partners are taking advantage of the country. Trump administration advisers have argued that trade deals result in trade deficits that… https://t.co/qjFGVblQce https://t.co/2n1nGwsy8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (DBA)-SQL: Join our team of SQL Professionals and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Experience with SQL… https://t.co/aEoJEVDbr0 https://t.co/wyrZ6bdQE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Professional Services Performance Consultant: – Professional Services Performance Consultant Job Locations US-DC-Washington, DC Req No. 2018-4557 Category Professional Services Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience, Cloud… https://t.co/rWwZZufqY1 https://t.co/P3qTwBaybX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/VmbhnryzJt https://t.co/aYyAvAXF4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Report Developer: As a Report Developer you will be focused on supporting the needs of our clients who currently utilize reports and tools developed by the Client Services team. The selected candidate will be a key player in delivering high quality… https://t.co/x3mVznTqC5 https://t.co/d8agInBzjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst (PowerCampus ERP OR SQL): Programmer Analyst (PowerCampus ERP OR SQL) Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 1 Role Description Design IT solutions for higher education! At Ellucian, we deliver a broad portfolio of technology… https://t.co/xq6KNEKWxF https://t.co/7UQf809FbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron's 51 points not enough to steal Game 1 https://t.co/KTBKDxBs7u https://t.co/yA9CX1y8jz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NoSQL Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, NoSQL Developer with Java skills to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a strong developer… https://t.co/UG443p0tXu https://t.co/b3oa7m8rP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need cash? How to access your home's equity https://t.co/ZGF9zb94et]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer With Strong AWS and MySQL: Are you a software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you want to work for a lifestyle brand powerhouse that is highly profitable and backed by some serious technology? If that sounds like you then check this… https://t.co/AFa50J7Q5h https://t.co/S7bT9AekRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist UI Developer (NEXEN) AngularJS JavaScript, Java, SQL: Specialist UI Developer AngularJS/Angular2, JavaScript, Java, SQL Asset service technology at BNY Mellon has an immediate need for web developer with Java application development… https://t.co/eCy50TnzbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas teen wins National Spelling Bee: Karthik Nemmani from McKinney, Texas, has won the Scripps National Spelling Bee. https://t.co/L2LsUvmDFa https://t.co/vF8K38YWM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL PL/SQL Developer: An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified ETL Developer with TS clearance to join their growing team. This person will be responsible for the data warehouse design… https://t.co/r8cHOiR3vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – SurePayroll: Title Senior Software Developer – SurePayroll ======================================== About the Organization Paychex, Inc. (NASDAQ: PAYX) is a leading provider of integrated human capital management solutions for… https://t.co/xE7DPnXJNo https://t.co/TVNpxf8YTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audiotapes of Michael Cohen threatening a journalist are released: Lawyer Michael Cohen told a journalist, "I will take you for every penny you still don't have," in 2015 after the reporter wrote a story about President Donald Trump and his first wife,… https://t.co/H16bsdIIMY https://t.co/ZDPurpcGGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer in Plano, Texas, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values… https://t.co/t1fE7fPJCz https://t.co/rLI9NQX2wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She left Colombia during the drug wars. Now she runs a major fashion magazine https://t.co/7r8bUcTOBt https://t.co/CX7DdOmxTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Arnold: We have a racist President: Tom Arnold, actor and ex-husband of Roseanne Barr, speaks out on President Trump's reaction to the cancellation of sitcom "Roseanne." https://t.co/GuEtGjekh9 https://t.co/Bq6KhEzffS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Why Amazon Prime should be free to everyone: If you were looking for proof that Amazon is leveraging its ever-expanding shipping and distribution capacity to clobber every last competitor and become the go-to seller of everything, here is some:… https://t.co/3FnPlRnl4q https://t.co/KES3MemojJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eminem and Nicki Minaj dating?: Is there a new rap supercouple? https://t.co/Gh7pSmvilF https://t.co/vx2IudjBgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Administrator: Job Description "We are inspired every day by the dedicated professionals we serve. Your work is why we’re here and we offer sincere thanks." Karla Bakersmith | President &amp; Founder What began as a two-person… https://t.co/YaHuhI2FFd https://t.co/6sNqB8YCxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS amp; SQL Data Analyst: SAS &amp; SQL DATA ANALYST * Performs data collection, analysis, validation and reporting. * Designs, tests, and documents processes, and SQL queries. * Extracts and analyzes data from various sources, including databases, manual… https://t.co/gT5mYR6hgD https://t.co/G86tXQhyAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim K. and Kanye West's relationship with politics: Kanye West is on board to make America great again. https://t.co/ZJNVSJOH5P https://t.co/VqLSp3e4YL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Web Developer 3 C#, https://t.co/SEom1RP7Sa, SQL): BI Web Developer 3 (Angular4, C#, *******, SQL) Ref No.: 18-20870 Location: Redmond, Washington Role: BI Web Developer 3 (Angular4, C#, *******, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: Full time Job… https://t.co/4Tth4r9UBS https://t.co/rQSPPI0XLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is owed an apology, White House says: The White House insisted on Wednesday it was not defending Roseanne Barr for the racist tweet that ultimately led to her sitcom's cancellation on ABC. https://t.co/0zRNpnalJm https://t.co/9nM3VUT0Gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL): .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Ref No.: 18-21691 Location: Redmond, Washington Role .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: FTE Mandatory Technical Skills A… https://t.co/WdMlQSzjtN https://t.co/LM0owDKdbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This drive shows how badly Puerto Rico was hit: Fallen power lines, flooding, debris ... obstacles litter roads in Puerto Rico after Hurricane Maria ripped through the island. https://t.co/sdv2tMRaCa https://t.co/xaZwL20FUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer – DBA: Date: May 23, 2018 Location: reno, NV, US, 89509 Year: 2018 Company: Arvato Digital Services LLC – Arvato FS USA Requisition ID: 20052 Reporting to the Onshore Technical Project Manager and working closely with the Offshore… https://t.co/iHN6LFZ1cU https://t.co/fr395hNE7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior AWS Engineer With Strong MySQL For Massive LifeStyle Brand: Are you a Sr. Software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you view infrastructure as code? If you want to help take our DevOps culture to the next level, then read this! WHAT IS THE… https://t.co/ZXUDI3DPzW https://t.co/6Nrwxliwlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump gives terminally ill patients a lifeline: President Donald Trump signed the "Right to Try Act" Wednesday, a measure aimed at helping terminally ill patients access drug treatments that are yet to be fully approved by the Food and Drug Administration. https://t.co/5xIURMc92k https://t.co/NgcMgT3l2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer – Java / MySQL / AWS: We are looking for a highly talented Backend Software Engineer for our El Dorado Hills office. As a Backend Java Application Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers products (Consumer, B2B).… https://t.co/MegmS2IcvI https://t.co/F6aRylIvLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Careers | American Institutes for Research |Data Analyst (SQL) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/i0h25CZ1R1 https://t.co/Q1a0jPyZGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Fitness International is a well-established, respected fitness company with over 600 state-of-the-art sports clubs throughout US and Canada. Based in our Irvine headquarters, our IT department is expanding to support new… https://t.co/OPYk1Ak1SH https://t.co/8T544NBXVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr–Data-Migration-with-Oracle–PL-SQL: SR. DATA MIGRATION WITH ORACLE, PL/SQL HOPEWELL, NJ Project Description: A seasoned data engineering consultant is needed to design, develop and deliver high quality data migrations and data integrations for… https://t.co/3ra4gBzHjH https://t.co/6aktjACq9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Walking Dead' star leaving show: "The Walking Dead" star Andrew Lincoln is reportedly leaving the show after season 9, according to several reports. https://t.co/BIMMfC5fxe https://t.co/lcIrlGMjsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA – Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/MuImNsu6cQ https://t.co/YGA3c6s7ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/SSIS Developer: As a SQL/SSIS Developer, you will be filling a role at Huntington Bank to backup an application lead, support, assist, and enhance new vendor based applications being installed, enabling capital optimization and pricing decisions… https://t.co/86WXwcVCa2 https://t.co/ApApA8ryJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL SERVER DBA TYPE: FULL TIME, DIRECT HIRE LOCATION: EASTERN NORTH CAROLINA (AHOSKIE, CAMDEN, GREENVILLE, JACKSONVILLE, OR WILMINGTON) SALARY: $70K-$80K/YR + EXCELLENT BENEFITS SQL SERVER DBA SUMMARY This is a technical and… https://t.co/ylowEwHIjP https://t.co/pwqoBO7bjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The horrifying irony of Trump's tweet https://t.co/oDSASt8TPM https://t.co/MsOu5oyaKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL SSIS Developer: MS SQL SSIS Developer Ref No.: 18-23310 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- MS SQL SSIS/SSAS Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More… https://t.co/gmt4JMNlZa https://t.co/5N0ur9F3oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SQL Database Developer: As a Senior Database Developer, you will be responsible for the creation of stable and reliable relational databases, according to our company’s needs. This is to include managing input of various data sources, definition of… https://t.co/Sk2wxoEJbu https://t.co/vast6zgTjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was rejected from dozens of investment banks. Now she's the CEO of Vimeo https://t.co/bos666GR8H https://t.co/4Zx2EFC9Rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer Ref No.:18-08870 Location: Bangor, Maine Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/14/2018 Job TitlePL SQL Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs)6-8 Technical/Functional SkillsPL/SQL Developer Experience… https://t.co/9dNrNqbjIT https://t.co/M22AaNu6Ev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Design Engineer – SQL/VB Developer Database Architect: The SQL Developer will be responsible for developing applications and integrations using the Microsoft SQL Server platform. This will include reports, vendor exports, data warehousing tasks… https://t.co/5D13ylzIQC https://t.co/uvOnz14ACi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>