<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL DeveloperDSS86528656*Richmond, VA*ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very important. … https://t.co/y3SPQER5Nd https://t.co/BpXILMEBdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dodger Stadium Gondola Is Just LA's Latest Wild Transit Idea: Flying people to baseball games is exactly the kind of thing LA's Office of Extraordinary Innovation was meant to consider. https://t.co/LPZIhvLlus https://t.co/ERrYQ6LlDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Mobile Tester (QA): Job Title: Sr. Mobile Tester Location: Chicago IL Duration: 3-6 monhts Rate: $60-70/hrMarket/hr. (best possible) Contractors: 2 Requirements Skills Required: Our client is looking for a Senior Mobile tester who have tested on both… https://t.co/LJkxOgxdSS https://t.co/emWjh8n3eN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Cloud, Big Data: Division: Siemens HealthineersBusiness Unit: ServicesRequisition Number: 217240Primary Location: United States-California-Mountain ViewOther Locations: United States-North Carolina-Cary, United… https://t.co/GHNPao7G8n https://t.co/pfL3BBdcBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Specialist, Principal: Software QA Specialist, Principal ================================= Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Engineering and Technical SupportSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must… https://t.co/LDYA3tZfLM https://t.co/qRfT8Dt9nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail Supervision Principal: Retail Supervision Principal Job ID  2018-17116 Primary Location  California, San Diego Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  .. Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this job This role coordinates and… https://t.co/MIVVmOYDtR https://t.co/AkLwDGVIRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer: Principal Developer-&gt;&gt; Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior… https://t.co/nbSbe7wUp8 https://t.co/4MseIVGYmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car Intall Technician/ME Leader (MECP Advanced), Geek Squad: Our technicians are passionate electronics experts and are especially energetic when talking about the connected car. Whether the request is to install Wi-Fi, entertainment, or a security… https://t.co/zOzkyHEitQ https://t.co/TylPqg1d5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Consultation Agent: Geek Squad Consultation Agent Our Agents are the first point of contact for clients and command the check-in and check-out experience of client devices. They ask the right questions, listen to client needs, take detailed… https://t.co/q4VOxOm104 https://t.co/ezlIm4Otj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPad Apps Pilots Use in the Cockpit: No Words With Friends for British Airways pilots, it's all about fuel calculations, safety notices, and maps. https://t.co/QJVndrQ7PL https://t.co/GN9iXJ0EMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer: UI Designer Lisle IL Responsibilities: * Keep the interface beautiful and easy to use. Direct the visual appearance of all new features and enhancements on our software application * Initiate, suggest, and spearhead major UI re-factorings… https://t.co/9MonXUtVli https://t.co/E7GgCamERC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Job for Humans: The Robot Assault on Fukushima: The 2011 earthquake and tsunami in Japan triggered a devastating catastrophe in one of the country’s largest nuclear power plants. The cleanup will take decades, and it’s no job for humans. https://t.co/kPuKdiztSh https://t.co/90n6JAH0hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 414651BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Turkish Utility Helicopter Software Supplier Management position to oversee software supplier activities. The applicable candidate will reside… https://t.co/2mL1Nspu9l https://t.co/Oo42dmVmBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Scott Pruitt Leaves, Will EPA Science Change Course?: Advocates say attacks on science and deregulation would continue under the agency's number two. https://t.co/XXEgLk5b1z https://t.co/ualJ9m1zqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Engineer – JavaScript: Phoenix, AZ Full-time $120k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Senior Front-End Engineer with JavaScript experience, please read on! Operating in Phoenix, AZ, right down the street from the Phoenix Convention… https://t.co/xSPZfk3vcC https://t.co/Zyg4jfd0Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Web Developer – Job Location:Headquarters – Alexandria, VA – Job Status:Full Time – Position Type:IT – Web Development – Date Posted:2/15/2018 – Location Address:880 S. Pickett Street Alexandria, VA 22304 – – Job Description: – BoatU.S., a… https://t.co/D6mHVvcXxn https://t.co/S8vVbBU1Rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Design Engineer III / Automation Specialist: Optimization of existing data services and SQL Database, analyze performance bottlenecks and system failures. Primary role in smaller, low risk projects. Improvements on security of services, creation… https://t.co/XrKOTDV9yF https://t.co/0nf5CiIkqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Handmaid’s Tale' Season 2 Looks Eerily More Familiar Than Season 1: The writers are moving beyond Margaret Atwood's book—and into familiar territory for news junkies. https://t.co/5OQj90z0Rp https://t.co/oo892UaexS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst DHS77558611*Des Moines, IA*The Senior Business Analyst will participate in all phases of the systems development lifecycle from Requirements, Design, Development, Testing, and Implementation to meet business… https://t.co/6oacamxBGX https://t.co/cAitzqi9x5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project ManagerIUB75557293*Des Moines, IA*Position will be working on a major multi-agency initiative to streamline information and workflows for a system that is currently based in Oracle UCM.CLIENT MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS: (APPLY ONLY IF… https://t.co/EBQdtebIoT https://t.co/WLNt2zGvXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member Technical Staff Consultant #KSA1-N: Member Technical Staff Consultant at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Responsible for software analysis, design, development, documentation, implementation and unit testing. recblid jluqt7se0qfklmnqbybdcunz4mguf3 https://t.co/LUpuTciqM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager II #AZ0082 / Senior Technical Program Manager #AZ0111: Information Technology positions available at the following California locations: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc… https://t.co/OcJeKmcBbM https://t.co/ZBUs7gAoKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (North Andover): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/RrqtQu6rKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Geotechnical Engineer, Krakow (Poland): We are seeking a Graduate Engineer for our Krakow office, working on projects world-wide as part of our Global Design Center. You will work within a team to deliver geotechnical services within a large… https://t.co/PFxl01cyXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29982BR Domain Banking Skillset Database , Java EE , Design Patterns JScript , Java script Middleware , Oracle , Programming/Mark up languages , HTML5 SQL Server , Web services , REST Web… https://t.co/aIkWzNZ6ER https://t.co/M0XTkytoay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Professional Services Performance Consultant: – Professional Services Performance Consultant Job Locations US-DC-Washington, DC Req No. 2018-4283 Category Professional Services Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience,… https://t.co/liiJbhMQ1J https://t.co/rTWuIZCz9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Comics to Read Before You See 'Avengers: Infinity War': Marvel fans have had Thanos thirst for years. These comics reveal why. https://t.co/NQaOafuZUh https://t.co/BlGYtH2Ywc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member Technical Staff Consultant #KSA1-N: Member Technical Staff Consultant at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Responsible for software analysis, design, development, documentation, implementation and unit testing. recblid jluqt7se0qfklmnqbybdcunz4mguf3 https://t.co/4Snz1z2cu0 https://t.co/0asXHWyPKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Applications Developers, Overland: Enterprise Applications Developers, Overland Park, KS: Des., dev., &amp; modify sw apps like Oracle ERP Financials &amp; SCM. Utilize scientific analysis &amp; mathematical models to predict &amp; measure outcome &amp;… https://t.co/MYffyCJwTS https://t.co/QUCKZA95Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/XqD9vZouyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USC Wide Receiver Josh Imatorbhebhe's Crazy Floating Jump: Is this normal physics, some type of optical illusion, or just plain magic? https://t.co/zMwW4BxD9q https://t.co/bve5YD8QoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENTERPRISE APPLICATIONS DEVELOPERS: Enterprise Applications Developers, Overland Park, KS: Des., dev., &amp; modify sw apps like Oracle ERP Financials &amp; SCM. Utilize scientific analysis &amp; mathematical models to predict &amp; measure outcome &amp; consequences of… https://t.co/2nZlgAR2ML https://t.co/8txPJiWZC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ORACLE DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR: ORACLE DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR ADT LLC has an opening in Irving, TX for an Oracle DB Administrator. Help manage &amp; maintain Oracle EBS R12.x.x apps. &amp; DB, &amp; other non-ERP Oracle DBs. Provide tech. &amp; oper’l DBA support for… https://t.co/sd0UnWPWFu https://t.co/XmJgNzVpLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer, Lead: LYONSCG is the industrys premier Commerce Digital Agency, serving brand, retail, and B2B organizations with tailored eCommerce solutions that maximize online potential. Headquartered in Chicago, the firm offers a full range of… https://t.co/a1LuMM74qK https://t.co/YHeRUUDkO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Web Developer: At Modern Message our focus is on building great products that solve real-world problems for our customers. Our core product Community Rewards [************************ an engagement platform for apartment residents, and our… https://t.co/XPROwyuYL5 https://t.co/kOoPQkoKiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer Sr / Flow Battery Testing / Cambridge, MA: Req ID : 423068BR Job Code/Title : E1473:Research Engineer Sr Job Description : Lockheed Martin Energy Storage is commercializing a new flow battery technology for low-cost, grid-scale energy… https://t.co/OfZ3NN6otQ https://t.co/8VWiPJIaN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN Staff Developer: RN Staff Developer Description at CareMeridian Skip Navigation – Facebook – YouTube – Twitter – LinkedIn Search Keyword Search City, State, or ZIP Search radiusRadius5 miles15 miles25 miles35 miles50 miles Search by Map Start Matching… https://t.co/8ib6swCxd4 https://t.co/LDGBU2CDjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Focused Systems Analyst: Job Description Provides mission partner training on all phases of RF, to include service ordering. Responsible for managing the DGOC Telecommunications Seminar, and providing ad-hoc virtual training, as well as on-site… https://t.co/95MDEThogY https://t.co/zCSdTZMJW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Analyst: Conagra Brands has the most energized, highest-impact culture in food. Our people persistently challenge and disrupt marketplace/business conventions and we are respected for our great brands, great food, great margins and… https://t.co/pqxWZvSpte https://t.co/nH0zMooXQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC Is Redesigning Its Slow, Old, and Unpopular Bus System: It's also introducing double-decker buses and all-door boarding. https://t.co/Vbaeenz3qH https://t.co/SzBKOwGh6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator I or II #485: Basin Electric, our employees are the heart of our organization. Together with our subsidiary, Dakota Gasification Company, we employ more than 2,300 people across multiple Midwestern states. In addition to competitive… https://t.co/6PlQ7kwooB https://t.co/ssWXCZqiDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why So Many People Make Their Password 'Dragon': The mythical creature's popularity says a lot about the psychology of password creation. https://t.co/vMAaJx4rn4 https://t.co/dDyLZNMlc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Web Developer – https://t.co/hyx3lfhSKU: ********** has entry level programming positions for recent college graduates with science, math, or engineering related majors including multiple programming courses. We will provide advanced web… https://t.co/MjioCXBCeC https://t.co/NMSM3qYA2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Implementation Project Manager: Who We Are We help architects and engineers find, share, and manage knowledge. Our intranet solution helps over 100 firms in the Architecture, Engineering, and Construction (AEC) industry achieve a wide range of… https://t.co/GzoSzsRjUH https://t.co/kZ3x4Z0vD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator 2/3:   Job Description – Systems Administrator 2/3 (18006627) Systems Administrator 2/3 Requisition ID : 18006627 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/BnOtK7dERJ https://t.co/I49Jbd0dCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer-Wireless: What You’ll Do You’re extremely motivated Software Engineer and passionate about learning and contributing to the team and the business with ‘can do’ attitude. – Strong design/programming ethic. Knowledge of designing… https://t.co/tk4ZqKlB5A https://t.co/pmZOLRUSPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logistics Configuration Analyst I (Shore ATC Systems): Job Description BAE Systems Inc. is looking for a logistics configuration analyst to join our team supporting shore-based Air Traffic Control and Landing systems, including the civil Instrument… https://t.co/BAP6f7lRgf https://t.co/7OFZTlmVkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Development Engineer #KP1-N: Senior Product Development Engineer at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Responsible for the design, development, and unit testing of Middleware and User Interface (UI) components for set-top boxes and consumer… https://t.co/hyVpZjtrSW https://t.co/o1mPFZM4yK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley's Latest Revolution: Cutting Out Wall Street: Companies like Uber and Spotify don’t need IPOs anymore, and that's turning the finance industry on its head. https://t.co/zyn9yWqDDA https://t.co/0LUK1nqAld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer Application Software: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV… https://t.co/Nl1VFA2E1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: SOFTWARE ARCHITECT. Netsmart Technologies, Inc. Raleigh, NC. Design, develop &amp; implement Netsmart Homecare &amp; other post-acute SW solutions. Work M-F 8a-5p, on call &amp; overtime as needed. Reqs at least Bach degree in Comp IS/ Comp Apps/… https://t.co/DSRNauynGt https://t.co/RcKGduEsph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning’s ‘Amazing’ Ability to Predict Chaos: In new computer experiments, artificial-intelligence algorithms can tell the future of chaotic systems. https://t.co/MWArVG62al https://t.co/0jmgM93mta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Business Systems Analysis: Vice President, Business Systems Analysis, Research Affiliates, Newport Beach, CA: Review, analyze, &amp; evaluate processes, systems, &amp; user req’s for software development projects involving business applications… https://t.co/tINzuAkZeo https://t.co/d4Htp3PxPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer II: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/4xGiejpvrg https://t.co/pm4q1TXmBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASIC &amp; FPGA Design Engineering Member of Staff: Req ID : 398084BR_2 Job Code/Title : E2524:ASIC &amp; FPGA Design Eng Stf Job Description : Digital Processor ASIC/FPGA Designer: The Staff ASIC/FPGA Design Engineer will be working in the RF Center of… https://t.co/VRi99468uQ https://t.co/dswi4IHur5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 421621BR_2 Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Our world is a dynamic place, more so today than ever before. Come join us in Space System as we design and build vital satellites, develop new… https://t.co/cDY4IViBaI https://t.co/33vVNaCkL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23andMe Wants You to Share Even More Health Data: On a new health portal, 23andMe encourages customers to share how they manage common health conditions. It’s not hard to see who gets the better side of the deal. https://t.co/89awoeIG1R https://t.co/1Otnp3381n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Labor Counsel/Attorney – Original Content, Legal and Studio Affairs: Sr. Labor Counsel/Attorney – Original Content, Legal and Studio Affairs Job Number: 113660189 Culver City, California, United States Posted: Apr. 17, 2018 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job… https://t.co/cBVKPmcriW https://t.co/UE0RKWY7Ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Life Sciences: Project Managers at Precision For Medicine implement and manage new and existing projects that support unprecedented acceleration in medical research and the explosion of biomarker and translational sciences for our… https://t.co/UB3t01OTz7 https://t.co/MDB2ZszYNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – eDiscovery: KLDiscovery, one of the largest national eDiscovery providers, is currently seeking a Project Manager for our Ambler, PA or McLean, VA location (or remote East Coast). The Project Manager is responsible for the overall… https://t.co/Lj6WA5qRky https://t.co/v5pKgVrKqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: The Project Manager plans, directs, and coordinates activities of designated projects to ensure that the goals and objectives of the project are accomplished within the prescribed time frame and funding parameters. Essential Duties &amp;… https://t.co/a4DwrrPd5v https://t.co/H75X4Jlrwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All You Need to Saddle up for Westworld Season 2: Whether you're a black or a white hat, this is all stuff you'll want. https://t.co/UizLP2jJiH https://t.co/jwQexkDSWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Lawsuit Against Russia Reveals New Details About 2016 Hack: In suing Russia, the Trump campaign, and others over the hack of its systems in 2016, the Democratic National Committee has also filled in important timeline details. https://t.co/z6T73AOKlK https://t.co/T7DQZI3Tms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'Do Not Disturb' App Protects Your Mac From 'Evil Maid' Attacks: Detecting an insidious physical attack on your MacBook may often be as simple as alerting you when its lid opens. https://t.co/0hYug3Hjay https://t.co/bKFrcO5j8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Dedham): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/jsBcoUfX0s https://t.co/czHEfKgV0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Engineer: The Company Were a tech company thats changing how people bank and think about their finances. We value empathy, curiosity, craft and efficacy. Our mission is to help people feel confident with their money. We do that by bringing… https://t.co/rDVY7KVJls https://t.co/4uuib72C5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Software Database Architect: 101502BR Sr Principal Software Database Architect MA – Cambridge 101502BR Sr Principal Software Database Architect  The work for this Pathfinder Project phase will be performed primarily at the Pivotal Labs site… https://t.co/UwjnEnbKku https://t.co/jHOAL47p8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Commissioning PM: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Construction Commissioning Project Manager with 8+ years of experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing •Lead and manage commissioning projects.… https://t.co/S5C2RqOKVW https://t.co/MZFAtMqI9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator/Project Manager – Concrete/Asphalt: Fremont, CA Full-time $0k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Estimator/Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive base salary up to $130K DOE – Full Benefits! –… https://t.co/3bmWTzbWF9 https://t.co/jXyDqrznPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Architect/NPI Program Manager: Woburn, MA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Chief Architect/NPI Program Manager with power and micro controller electronics experience, please read on! Based in Woburn, we are the leading developer… https://t.co/Ls0Ck5LcPH https://t.co/inC6d6PV1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Contingent Workforce Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications, hosting, cloud and IT services company enabling millions of customers to transform their businesses and their lives through innovative technology solutions.… https://t.co/HTkyyCzLGh https://t.co/QHXcR1uXS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Pipeline: THE COMPANY Fannie Mae provides reliable, large-scale access to affordable mortgage credit in communities across our nation. We are the leading source of funding for housing in America, which means more people can buy or rent a home. We… https://t.co/o8eUzY42YU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s 4/20, and an FDA Panel Just OK’d a Drug Made From Marijuana: The treatment was fast-tracked for approval, and the first person to use the drug in the US was our writer's son. https://t.co/S33zBYUWg4 https://t.co/bTQJu3rB5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer – API Engineering: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/9YQi36FYIY https://t.co/3RzGHiKqEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Solutions Architect/Developer: Support the design and development of Jacob’s Program Performance Portal application and other custom applications for our clients in delivering some of the world’s most complex programs. As a business solutions expert,… https://t.co/U2Qv2qULA7 https://t.co/7xDSjJAPtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Solutions Architect – GETS: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/2vTmnbOFv3 https://t.co/rQkGVzzDPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Reality Takes a Political Turn in the Trump Era: From climate change to reforming white supremacists: At this year's Tribeca Film Festival, it's about the medium and the message. https://t.co/2rvw9ZKbcX https://t.co/h0hBDCAGHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Specialist, Principal: Job Description POSITION SUMMARY: As a company authority, ensures that quality software is consistently planned, produced and delivered by establishing project- and/or organization-level processes, metrics, tools and… https://t.co/kFfJSDIprk https://t.co/Qj9kaholQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-Sales Engineer – Los Angeles: Why Silver Peak?: Silver Peak is currently at the forefront one of the most exciting and disruptive trends in the history of the networking industry – the software-defined wide area network, or SD-WAN. Enterprises and… https://t.co/vfFTCK3Wxu https://t.co/tz18n77N4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic Marketing Manager: Strategic Marketing Manager (Timing &amp; Frequency Division) Sunnyvale, CA The Timing Marketing Manager is responsible for identifying, evaluating and contributing to the development of new technologies and products for both new… https://t.co/m9aKQ6BVlv https://t.co/iOlk5lFUAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management &amp; Planning Operations Representative Senior: Req ID : 425551BR Job Code/Title : E1753:Prj Mgt &amp; Plng Opns Rep Sr Job Description : This position will serve as the Mission Systems Control Account Manager (CAM) for the LRIP 9 and on… https://t.co/NytZYMiwWE https://t.co/11OBKSyePp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physics Explains Why Braves Fans Can’t Beat the Freeze: A spandex-clad superhero keeps beating Atlanta Braves fans...even when they have a huge head start. https://t.co/MYxUEjkSn6 https://t.co/hJ5ZDdy5Bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 95507BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/oBzMp52U40 https://t.co/gX6FNkJlyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/kmZo20GJaZ https://t.co/OlmdmxnYXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our South San Francisco, CA location to support the total design and implementation effort and participates in multiple projects, consistently solve complex problems. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg, Math,… https://t.co/SStCzGvtly https://t.co/NAOZmwxHD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and how… https://t.co/RNmlUudIhO https://t.co/ntiCYCAWpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/xee5fdnNou https://t.co/Ix7t41oLT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber Eats: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose when and how… https://t.co/pV5FGm1aRd https://t.co/UMf1ql9Vra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/ER9Bg08YqS https://t.co/UYWegyoZ9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Meaty,' 'Broad Band' and 10 More Books You Must Read This Summer: Fiction. Nonfiction. Science! Looking for some beach reads? This list is a good place to start. https://t.co/xW9lOwnFIx https://t.co/9T47yqEmVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/QchKzvZyvV https://t.co/kwKcDlHI3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JSE – Application Development Specialist: Job Description: About Our Company Building on 30 years of experience as a pricing intelligence pioneer, RetailData equips retailers to win consumers and drive growth. We fuel retailer strategy and systems with… https://t.co/mnYXhBOpjE https://t.co/TyWwflmSFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Trump Campaign Aide: My Russia Ties Are Not Nefarious!: Michael Caputo is helping launch a video startup that involves a bunch of Russians. He’s also sending a Russian ballerina on tour. But that doesn’t make him a Putin stooge, he insists. https://t.co/MWIoSEurXG https://t.co/3eDOuyoBrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer 3 – Mid-level: The Boeing Co. is looking for a mid-level systems engineer with proven experience in sub-system, system level integration, verification and validation of hardware and software platforms. This position will assume both a… https://t.co/YU8SQILD3F https://t.co/buAuJGi7dP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director (First Customer Network) (IT Infrastructure): Description Palo Alto Networks is the fastest-growing security company in history. We offer the chance to be part of an important mission: ending breaches and protecting our way of digital life. If… https://t.co/KbskuOSyl0 https://t.co/M7wIaVlUTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Job Description IT Business Analyst (19834) We are searching for an experienced IT Business Analyst who can gather important company data, prepare reports, and interpret business analyses for different operating divisions of Utility… https://t.co/JZonbU3GCZ https://t.co/8py5P6jXhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP BW/ HANA Consultant: Job TitleSAP BW/ HANA Consultant – ID:31726 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsHANA, BW LocationPiscataway, NJ Date Posted05/15/2018 Works on problems of moderate and varied complexity where analysis of data may require… https://t.co/hoPYaU8XQM https://t.co/PPmE450YEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead https://t.co/6M53uGz8a7 Developer: Job Title: Lead ************** Developer Job ID: ******* Location: FL-BocaRaton-6600NMilitary Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Responsibilities Technology is the office product of the future.… https://t.co/BJk190oYE1 https://t.co/YJID3ga8rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's Self-Driving Crash, Elon's Twitter Rage, and More Car News This Week: Plus: updates on Tesla Model 3 production, Porsche's new Cayenne hybrid, and college kids make the Camaro into a tree-hugging muscle car. https://t.co/nXHBreWcVp https://t.co/Rfvd95BKlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer – Aerospace: ***This is a remote position based in the US.*** Carpenter Technology Corporation is a leader in the development, manufacture and distribution of cast/wrought and powder metal stainless steels and specialty alloys… https://t.co/5z1loua46O https://t.co/ZACHxK6QTb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>