<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/zrFnGydEd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/Hikbqb53VF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/eG4SojTU2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/0eMZIN1RKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/PBdfjc8X3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/M7dmHwJOGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/pAhX1pbnoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/7gHHvLEoLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/l32TuuZGRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/odnvMqRwdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/3M3aTbABo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/sXAvvqMjph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/BAvuSZmyZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/8Gi2Zl1dxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/nYp6UFGlTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/IlkB29QxnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/fgtc3NpBa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/KuKXPYK5Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/zz3gKoBrZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/pQ59rMTrrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/4DIkkwEdQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/jYVrWl1s9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that when things seem to go wrong, stay calm and wait till you see the bigger picture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/MgO7bzgYeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/OeVMITqrMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/YsRqP1UpDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/KaF8m9jPVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/ZvZX99K1UD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/yOKAHO5glg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/wPExKDGwMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/zvG2VXOofe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/wARlkvWKvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/VFf0uF1bnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/v4EmV6OoJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/JP7tgndrMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/vattKKYjcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol and gas do mix but they taste terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/VqnLzmhgB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/Xivdvw15Vu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/Ql6qosbEQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/oMzEc024Lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/inigQLYTOp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>