<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#RomanticFriday

IntimacyCode

Love leaks. The same way a glass of water kept by your window frame evaporates... https://t.co/gMzmUXzMqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking Beyond The Usual

Sometimes parents drive their children to succeed on the wrong thing. 

As parents, we... https://t.co/bRF8zC5guS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jv7SMjcgb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/D82ERz6Ypk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUE LOVE

1. True love is practical. Don't tell me you love me, demonstrate it through your behaviour.
2. True... https://t.co/ZryLFiRvK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeleAgbogun: Good Management of Conflict Leads to Growth And Maturity. Be Deliberate About Resolving Issues With Your Spouse.
Marital B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimateCommunication 
When couples master the art of intimate communication, they take D lid off the level of intimacy they can experience https://t.co/zvARlmhkZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Value what you have. Appreciate the life you lead, the people you love, the privileges you enjoy etc. Celeberate your accomplishments! https://t.co/jKmsAKTmW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good spouse is also looking 4 someone good.Hence, D more quality U build into yourself, D more U position yourself to attract great spouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submission: The perspective of the 21st century wife – By Uju Okorie

When I was contacted to do an article on... https://t.co/0l4DTiZ9Xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submission: The perspective of the 21st century wife – By Uju Okorie: When I was contacted… https://t.co/Pz4RKIBuCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Submission: The perspective of the 21st century #wife – By Uju Okorie: When I was… https://t.co/CtySsNQCgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submission: The perspective of the 21st century wife: When I was contacted to do an article… https://t.co/NEeuJeYPsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Submission: The perspective of the 21st century #wife: When I was contacted to do an… https://t.co/f8kZxrcrSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/pu0NuoNMh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FamilyThursday

9 WAYS TO AVOID IN-LAWS' RIVALRY

1. Do not allow your parents to pressure you into becoming... https://t.co/GxGP5FQ62U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FamilyThursday 

The rechargeable lamp

Love is like a rechargeable lamp, if we want it to glow at maximum... https://t.co/DAwn2bOFpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PromotionWednesday

"Marriage will test your character and show you who you truly are, while challenging you to... https://t.co/LN7evmiJwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Broken Trust by Chidi and Victor Akunna: Sometime ago, we wrote that… https://t.co/CtMAOM99Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Broken Trust

Sometime ago, we wrote that "marriage never leaves you the same". The more we invest... https://t.co/3EyFbexd5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Broken Trust by Chidi and Victor Akunna: Sometime ago, we wrote that… https://t.co/6Tv1Bbt8Jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34.Use every opportunity to connect and bond with your spouse by speaking words that build intimacy. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33. Communication is vital, we can work on getting better and better. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32. Do not allow what you know about people (their secrets) reduce their worth before you. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31. Be that person who people are confident to share information with, trusting that they are safe. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30. Don't use information your friend, fiancé/fiancee or spouse shared with you in a demeaning way. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[29.Establish ground rules eg.no name-calling.Some people make sinister comments when they communicate.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28b. ...thinking the person is getting at you.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28. Not often the case, but the tendency is to misunderstand "aggressive" dispositions...#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27. Understanding people would help us excuse certain actions. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26. Extroverts may seem aggressive in their approach and introverts may seem weak.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. See people for who they are. This will help us understand them better.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. Understand before seeking to be understood, so you don't annoyingly interrupt. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. Study your spouse to know when best to bring up sensitive discussions. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. For football lovers, the time a match is on is not the right time for certain discussions. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. Capture key points and be sensitive. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20. Do not just take the headlines and keep complaining. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18b. ...while men use words to communicate facts. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. To a woman, the art of communication is part of building intimacy,... #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. Women are into details and men are into headlines. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. Some men think women don't make 'sense'. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15. Remove prejudice and bias. For instance, bias against the opposite sex. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14.Confrontation must not be disrespectful.Be careful not to be brash&amp;condescending,even in your tone.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13b. ... if you do not express yourself. Talk! #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13. No one can understand how you feel about something he/she has done or not done... #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12b. ...so would rather not speak? #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Do you feel that expressing your feelings may be misunderstood as being confrontational, ...? #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. Express your feelings, do not just leave the other to make out what you have in mind. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. The quiet one must also be willing to express him/herself to avoid assumptions.#IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. It is important that the 'talker' learns to 'hush' and let the other speak. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. Interestingly, such persons are often attracted to introverts. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. Some people are extroverts and love to talk. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. There is need for balance. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. It is challenging when one person does all the talking, while the other listens. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. It is 'co' - an exchange, not a teaching/instruction. You don't just talk &amp; talk, or give orders. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Communication is not a one-way street. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. It builds a sense of self-worth and leaves people feeling more valuable and listened to. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IntimateCommunication

Communication builds and sustains romance and intimacy between couples. Hence, it must... https://t.co/mMXKkm3hR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Intimate communication is the kind of communication that leaves people feeling better. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Bishop T D Jakes, "You cannot enjoy a lifetime of love in your marriage without forgiveness". Most... https://t.co/ETwa1r6J9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ntimacyCode https://t.co/Yx4qXroWzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Women must learn to use questions to extract the right information. #IntimateCommunication #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: https://t.co/SoTGwZ9zR8 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Understanding Your Spouse By Chidi Akunna

A key virtue in life is understanding. We need to... https://t.co/aJxpgRdq2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Understanding Your Spouse By Chidi Akunna

A key virtue in life is understanding. We need to... https://t.co/8kZFxmI72K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: Understanding Your Spouse By Chidi Akunna: A key virtue in life is… https://t.co/fOwJLP2gws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimacy Code: #Understanding Your Spouse: A key virtue in life is understanding. We need… https://t.co/lnDfk3PTD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Approach to Money

Money is a touchy issue in a lot of homes. Statistics have shown that this is one of the... https://t.co/kkuoWoME33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The greatest weakness of most humans is their hesitancy to tell others how much they love them while they’re still alive.”
-Olando Battista]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Approach to Money: Money is a touchy issue in a lot of homes. Statistics have shown… https://t.co/z8F4NVAmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Approach to #Money: Money is a touchy issue in a lot of homes. Statistics have shown… https://t.co/idZfXGW09h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FamilyThursday

MORNING REFLECTIONS

Sometimes, we take on the role of the Superhero, trying to fix everyone at... https://t.co/qJmGtqNtbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gmABysG1Zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How we make decisions 

James: "I always looked forward to getting married; I dreamt, prayed and fantasised about... https://t.co/RUG7AASZdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How we make decisions: James: “I always looked forward to getting married; I dreamt, prayed… https://t.co/U9BaH9QURd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How we make decisions: James: “I always looked forward to getting married; I dreamt, prayed… https://t.co/XmYi9I0eRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If every time you have a misunderstanding with your spouse, you discuss it with your weight watchers group, your... https://t.co/Vp467Dzic1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romantic Jesus: He loved his wife (church) so much that he died for her. What sacrifices have you made for your spouse? We must take action!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MORNING REFLECTIONS
The challenges of modern urban lifestyle such as rising up early to beat the traffic,... https://t.co/Htulw3vpqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @excelength: Surely...resolutions are weak. That's why people come back to them every year. Determination and commitment better! https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond New Year Resolutions!: Life is a God-given opportunity to be a blessing and make an… https://t.co/KZ2nTNZiJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond New Year Resolutions!: Life is a God-given opportunity to be a blessing and make an… https://t.co/CVrUhkRCZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEYOND NEW YEAR RESOLUTIONS!

Life is a God-given opportunity to be a blessing and make an impact in someone... https://t.co/9EJcOrDhPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastorpoju: When God is about to open you up to something big, somebody strategic in your life will walk out. Don't grieve, he is your…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastorpoju: If you have done everything in faith you know &amp; yet no results, do this, pray in the spirit for a lengthy period until you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pastorpoju: Reflecting over somethings i realized i let some measure of my core issues slip. When you get distracted, power leaks. Look…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you praised your spouse today? https://t.co/fFt38neQ3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/rhge3WXo1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/GcjExXyRJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chykeohuegbe thank you so much your Excellency!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chykeohuegbe: @FamilyAffairs05 You guys look lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HVngZe0ZxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/Dg0CQ4MvxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our group is up and running: https://t.co/oMKNRTmaAI https://t.co/6bz5IYwJv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying In Control Of Your Costs This Christmas Season - By Sola Adesakin 

Needless to say that Christmas is... https://t.co/ALUF0qm9va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying In Control Of Your Costs This Christmas Season – By Sola Adesakin: Needless to say… https://t.co/cDe27V9EF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying In #Control Of Your Costs This #Christmas Season – By Sola Adesakin: Needless to… https://t.co/wtoOzVZpzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improve Your Marital Experience – By Victor Akunna: At the start of my school days, my… https://t.co/tbx9muVl1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the start of my school days, my parents suffered a huge financial setback that made them change my school. In... https://t.co/etxJyajA0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improve Your Marital #Experience – By Victor Akunna: At the start of my school days, my… https://t.co/uGjgbLrSh1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>