<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news: They take advantage of a loophole in insurance companies' rules to make money for individual investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have dogs at work, you need a 
Dog Tribunal
.

This company sounds fun, but also the opposite of fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know exactly what "manipulate" means in that quote, but anyway ISDA declined the request.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Morgan Stanley's key point is that we'll have a utopian society by 2026.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PwC let its client edit its report, and accepted some edits that made its client look better, because that was the assignment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More from Cryan: “I sit on trading floors and wonder what drives people,” he said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh by the way it's worth noticing (?) that this argument doesn't run in reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, the hacking is presumably illegal, but is it insider trading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stranger-originated life insurance is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not for any particular regulatory reason, just so we can all kibbitz about short campaigns the way we do on long activist campaigns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest is Mylan's big offer to buy Perrigo for $28.9 billion, which I guess you would characterize as a hostile offer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We talked the other day about how Nasdaq's Linq blockchain can replace Microsoft Excel as a way to keep corporate cap tables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Harvard Business School news. The weird thing is that this guy teaches in the "Negotiation, Organizations &amp; Markets unit" at HBS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though Goldman is doing its best to 
turn them off
. I guess I can't criticize; I used to file my nails at my desk at Goldman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank earnings. Bank of America announced earnings this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook topped out at the quinquagintacorn level, so this "would make Uber the world’s most valuable private start-up by far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently investors prefer the Morgan Stanley approach to the Goldman one, but why should that matter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sends a bit of the wrong message, especially when "Republicans and Democrats Agree: We Hate Wall Street."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To do so, he had her download a bitcoin wallet app to her smartphone, then used his own phone to scan the wallet’s QR code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The substance is: You manipulated some whatever, and now you write the government a big check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. This one, on the other hand, is on the way out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too big to jail. Too big to jail too big to jail too big to jaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you run a sufficiently small bank, you can probably do a lot of your risk management by intuition, or by crude models.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For regulatory and economic reasons, I guess now is a good time to get out of the business of trading physical commodities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose giving customers a demand account that costs $4.95 a month and doesn't let them write checks qualifies as an act of charity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now he has all that money. What to do with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's claiming prosecutorial misconduct because Bharara authorized the raid, and also invited the news media to the raid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L’Abeille Vie called this an arbitrage, but really it was a gift. Is the stock market up this week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElieNYC Too big to jail too big to jail too big to jaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or something? The message here is perhaps that no one has any idea what's going on in Qingdao.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about stock buybacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it takes on an added regulatory importance when the job that overwhelms you is rating mortgage-backed securities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not as much of a thing in many other areas of finance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider trading in out-of-the-money call options.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile here is some crazy stuff about New York politician Sheldon Silver and his nemesis Sheldon E. Silver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it keeps happening. Is this one of those cases where the media simply doesn't appreciate the realities of the industry that it covers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not a ton of constructive places to go after that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd want to deliver the cheapest possible bonds into the auction, to maximize your CDS recovery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if he'd addressed those problems in the public sector! What would he do now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unicorns are descending on Washington, though not in an enchanting whimsical way, more in a lobbying-against-labor-regulation sort of way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Investors are fleeing from a business they see as confidence-based, and therefore prone to unravel at speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's another "Can Bitcoin Clean Up Its Act?" story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Somebody’s going to get a big haircut, and I didn’t want it to be me,” he said. It's him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its spelling is also unimpressive. There's gonna be a whole lot more of this, are you excited?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a new pattern to the trader’s use of his security pass?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presumably some of those will also turn out to be ridiculously profitable. No one is particularly agitating for share buybacks at Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every Moment should inspire viewers to want to share it," say Twitter's Moments guidelines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Twitter gets more terrible in an effort to become Facebook, Facebook is outflanking it by becoming even more terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should governments hedge oil price risk? Unsurprisingly, the oil price slide is bad for oil company stocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the real benefit of the "hedge fund" title is in framing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so great: Regulators think banks might have bad "cultures," and they want every bank to emphasize having a good "culture."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or, sure the list price of the drug is high, but you have assistance programs to make sure that anyone who needs it can get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. Disappearing primary dealers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe more interesting, though, is the question of, if you've decided to break up the banks, what do you break them into?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But maybe the right conclusion to draw here is that universal banking is a bad idea, for Citigroup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hardcode fudge factors into an Excel spreadsheet, come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elliott plans to sue to stop this, and I have to say that if it was suing in Delaware I'd like its chances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similarly, only Nasdaq can do the Nasdaq closing auction for Nasdaq stocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It averages around 13 percent of U.S. stock trading. That makes it one of the biggest of the 11 exchanges, but still just one of 11.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though, in the event, the market is not particularly in chaos today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a big new report from the American Bankruptcy Institute recommending changes in the U.S. Bankruptcy Code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is because interest rate swaps, foreign exchange and cleared credit derivatives can remain within the bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't even have an intraday price, really, just that weird premium to NAV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, the Treasury announced that "There is Only One Solution to the Debt Limit," which is for Congress to raise the debt limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The prosecutors and the SEC rely on unspoken customs and market expectations to make out the case for fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If current trends continue, by next week this linkwrap is going to consist solely of that sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allison Nathan: What about asset managers? Given their growth, are they in a better position to step in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“They all seemed to have this contained sitting posture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stefan Krause is a Deutsche Bank management board member, and this was in a discussion about too-big-to-fail subsidies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People make very comfortable livings doing this stuff, it is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except Citadel, Citadel is great, they're expanding into lots of market-making businesses that banks are leaving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Stuff kicked off as an e-mail newsletter one year ago today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I assume the "legal protections" that Shkreli negotiated are supposed to prevent that, but maybe they could release a close substitute?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not laughable to find that coincidence odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never specified that gold would hit 5000 in two years," Schiff wrote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring non-Twitter users to make Twitter less appealing to Twitter users seems to be Twitter's core strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hang on, Charikov said: Actually banks in 2006-2007 didn't care at all about anyone's income, or their intent to live in any houses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, the top two are Boca Raton and Long Island, with the rest of the top five all in Florida.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The consensus seems to be that "challenging" is an understatement: “This makes a capital call even more likely,” said Mr Barua.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one dies if a merger is delayed or a stock goes down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doubling down. He observes that "when investment fund managers 'double down' on positions that have run against them, they outperform."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poorer people eat cheaper food than richer people, and first-class airline passengers cross-subsidize the people in coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently though it has enough American investors to care about tax efficiency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean: "Home run" has a similar long and clichéd history of being used metaphorically for business success. "Megahits" is, just, come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human relationships don’t usually change nature very quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about stock buybacks.
SpringOwl is, at least, though its solution is more stock buybacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, here is a front-page New York Times story about how much presidential candidates lie (a lot).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems to have been one of Sason's strategies, e.g.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 has to be U.S. Attorney Robert L. Capers, who was happy to sign his name to Shkreli's indictment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually it's just documented for Bank of Scotland, not Lloyds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(BlackRock, for instance, often pushes this idea.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies plan to arrange their affairs to avoid taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think reviewing criteria with investors would be good, or at least indicate that you're not defrauding them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of Bloomberg View's editorial board or Bloomberg LP, its owners and investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being right 99% of the time and missing the shockingly unexpected calls along with everyone else provides no value to clients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will hear it from hedge fund managers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton is on the list, but at this point Shkreli enemy No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fraud isn't just about saying false words; it's about your counterparty relying on those words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think literally no person disputes this fact.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>