<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/M20G3Kecgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/QXu8ccT52D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not really interested in making money. Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/HJy4RCNneu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/UH3CGWJvmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/6qQhaom9he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/dS9Nh6iHk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/Emr0nOsgRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/TfBFL0VMhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dIz5tNp1pG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/pgd2qe9t7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/jm9vRIoWbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/An3gKDuA83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/cPxYcxak0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/X5BrQnhVSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/gNHKgdGw9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/K4acMKK7xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/PrsX98yXDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9mPKuNIaVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/fXbpQEeLwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/YiBqjUpcOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/3uTnMNrJDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/abivlImf4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/UZj3HYopyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/xEtegTMZU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/N34PZPYWwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest schoolboy is now familiar with truths for which Archimedes would have sacrificed his life. - Ernest Renan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/gYBpRpx2Xb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/Xkfwoaztqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/PwPemqhBQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/tjggjOmNFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/jzUnverqVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/iB6NujjTfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/DJBfDQYRPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/V9Tc7zJjX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/7VTuNxz461]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/ZfkF1LaGm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/Vnr3FLjqfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/H9t0XlibAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/lmixnKPHwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/qaKBPw8VXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got rock 'n' roll in my blood. - William Shatner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/s4JuyXXrOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/tvrRkWDVO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/Ro1qtXFbn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Introduction to Ray Bradbury  http://t.co/ig6OoXDL9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/zw7anyRL7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/lUpf3d2yoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/i8TnCuclKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/EpbO6lJQ7Y]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>