<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buster_ESPN Mlb network reporting he vetoed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexfan590 in a standard league.. do you draft with a targeted flex in mind or fill later with best option based on roster depth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EASPORTS_MUT: #Top3Giveaway #Madden18 https://t.co/CUDkhXUe1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Harper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParamedicCook @crunchypicks @JaysFromCouch Situational stat, but with his increased playing time most of his numbers are down...even defensive metrics..but love is blind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crunchypicks @JaysFromCouch I just muted him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crunchypicks @JaysFromCouch Can someone explain the love affair with Goins?  I don't understand it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crunchypicks @JaysFromCouch Truth be told,  I hear Goins in the DH spot a lot.  Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaysFromCouch @crunchypicks Hahah you win the internet today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg in a standard league.. do you draft with a targeted flex in mind or fill later with best option based on roster depth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heathcummingssr standard league.. do you draft with a targeted flex in mind or fill later with best option based on roster depth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealElMacho @buffalobills Lmao well played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rob_husovic @ari_shapiro Lmao.  Ok Rob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Better asset? A "career" year in a situational stat that has come out of nowhere in a well below average career at the plate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Be "clutch" all he wants down the stretch..still don't want him as an everyday player if everyone is healthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @JimTrotter_NFL Can you blame him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin You mean the fans who showed up late 2015?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ To bad heart can't make someone hit better then .200]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawrenceKS_PD: I'm sorry Blake, this is awkward, but that's not a police car. You vaped in front of a water service vehicle. 
¯\_(ツ)_/¯…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cgrand3: Each game, I wear my socks high in honor of #JackieRobinson. Today I did it in a @dodgers uniform -and it felt really special…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHowsam Absolutely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHowsam Goins isn't the issue, just his fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Quality tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BleacherReport: Chris Long takes a stand. https://t.co/vhr47MZeGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaseballAmerica 2 balls, no strikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Avocados are toxic to almost every other animal except humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair 4 years, 90m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexfan590 Thought this was #Madden18 for a moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fact "I don't want to buy your death sticks" https://t.co/ttWvjFhVqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaysFromCouch: Did you know: the avg cost of care for ALS patients is $150k-$250k per @ALSCanada

Join our cause to help families: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair @BringerOfRain20 His new contract starts at age 33.  They'll trade him before he hits FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports He'd be terrible in the CFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexDEAFootball was gonna take this year off but damn the game looks great!  Guess I'll see you on the field in 3 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PriscoCBS @JameyEisenberg So a 6 game suspension followed by an appeal down to 4? Heh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ofctimallen If an idiot asks this question daily, why are there still idiots?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro If they move Stanton, it will be in the offseason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ People don't hate Goins,  just his fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dres1011 @Nutt007 @CobraElDiablo @ChrisWilson101 @TakeThatDarwin @drunken_neo @djboptics 98 million light years?  Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueJaysVillage Thinking the Nationals consider Bautista at this point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KOAS1963 Gord is our Northern Lights now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougGilmour93: Heartbroken today. Few Canadians touched this country like Gord Downie. Thank you for everything you gave us. My deepest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKincade checking in from Toronto, Ontario]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks Outside of those two all star teams, Cito didn’t manage very well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports Thanks.  Wanted your opinion before I dropped coin on Hero Talib and Newman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports based on your MaddenTampa 2 series on YT.  Which 3 CBs fit that scheme? Sherman, Newman, Talib, Woodson, Ramsey, Harris Jr?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexDEAFootball AH filters reset after buying an item.  Please fix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexDEAFootball post patch AH filters rest after a purchase.  Is this planned or glitched?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mark_azak @seanblaze305 @buffalobills It’s about standing up (or kneeling in this case) for your principals.   Even military people said kneeling was a respectual way to protest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timandsid I expect them to muddle in mediocrity known as the second wild card race.  Fail to trade him at the deadline and lose him for NOTHING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports Beyond pay to play this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JameyEisenberg standard format.  Strong at RB but need a WR.  Trade McCaffery for Baldwin a good move?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShiDavidi Ahhh it’s like the wildcard race we were supposedly in all season.. but for JD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlaje @ShiDavidi Exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xmasape Crazy thing is he almost threw a pick six on that play too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EASPORTS_MUT: In honor of hitting 400k followers on Twitter we're giving away 400k coins to a few lucky winners! RT for a chance to chi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro What is supposed to say?  He doesn’t like playing here, the city sucks?  We’ll see how he truly feels when negotiations starts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thefantasyshow Ertz or Graham?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: Scientists detect ripples from black hole collision https://t.co/CDOSVCdBZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PRESlDENTBANNON: Day 251

Wall length: 0
Tax reforms: 0
Clintons jailed: 0
Golf club visits: 60
Hands: tiny
Swamp: vast
Healthcare: Oba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeAnnMcAdoo Nobody cares..they’re to distracted whether or not some kneels during the anthem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senssensei @CoachsCornerDC There isn’t?  Then who is responsible for all those home runs, touch downs and awards etc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swashbucklerrr @MikeAndMike Am I missing replies?  I’ve only seen your posts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnpodesta @RogerJStoneJr I heard your “pizzas” come under done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills So are you boycotting the NFL until Sunday when you'll eventually cave or is this legit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhop3132 @AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buffalobills For all you triggered fake ass chickenhawk patriots https://t.co/nCxeFyGDm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateLoz @buffalobills Lmao triggered much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshua__frank  https://t.co/FT9aHXhfnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The fact you were so easy with the Natzi March yet so livid about the NFL protest speaks volumes and what is truly wrong about America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeAndMike Or completely silent when the NBA player continued his warmup routine during the Canadian national anthem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeAndMike Same people freaking out over kneeling were completely SILENT when Nazis roamed the streets a few weeks back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2liveunStews @effyousparky @MikeAndMike however you look at it..God forbid anyone mentioned the outrageous military budget or you don't support the troops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @getnickwright: The protests have been hijacked by folks with an agenda. I tried to set the record straight this morning. I think this i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@effyousparky @MikeAndMike Hard to, especially when the Pentagon spends millions every year to be so heavily involved with the political ceremony at sporting events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeAndMike  https://t.co/rbMrOfTwd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeAndMike when did the anthem become to sole possession of the military?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  https://t.co/ekoJ51kFxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a 5 time draft dodger talking about disrespect? Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This 5 time draft dodger talking about disrespect... asshole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 So while everyone is triggered over Anthem protests, they changed the top 1% to pay less taxes.  Trumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jake_Vig: If I wanted to hear two fat guys call each other names and threaten each other with nuclear weapons, I would do more online g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 I'm Canadian and find the almost religious over the top patriotism creepy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia So then what if you felt some of your fellow Americans weren't being afforded those ideals the flag is supposed to represent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 No doubt.  Gasoline on the fire to get some work done behind the scenes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 To protect special interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia Tell me what the ideals and what they represent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 Well said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 It just feels like the military has bought this way of thinking over the last decade.  Probably why nobody questions the outrageous budget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia It's about the ideals, not the country or a fallen military member]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 However over the last decade, the military has paid to be heavily involved in the anthem ceremony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 I see it two way.  Before the anthem and flag was to represent the ideals the country was founded on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia They are kneeling because they feel a percentage of Americans are being afforded those ideals the flag and anthem are supposed to represent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia Kneeling isn't disrespecting the flag.  Being forced to stand disrespects the ideals it was founded upon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abel1408 What does the flag respesent to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia All Americans who aren't afforded the same freedoms and equalities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia It still doesn't change the fact there is inequality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia I wish Twitter allowed larger responses.   I tweeted more of my thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia ..being afforded those same ideals.  And I find that more disrespectful to the men and women who serve..not the protest itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlwaysTrumpXYZ @buffalobills @BauerleBellavia ..everything American was supposedly built on.  It's that very reason they kneel because a demographic of the population isn't ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>