<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. BI Developer: Sr BI Developer: Design, develop, deploy &amp; modify BI dashboards &amp; reporting products &amp; solutions for search marketing agency, w/emphasis on UI &amp; UX design &amp; data visualizations. Chicago, IL location. Req’s MS in Info Sys Mgmt &amp; 2 yrs… https://t.co/z3LCl59Mm8 https://t.co/ugztFtUwwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Manager: TECHNOLOGYDeloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Manager, Technology, AMS in Kansas City, MO and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to provide technology-enabled business… https://t.co/5nF1fZt37c https://t.co/VIgLsLRuPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Engineer #CA17-0727: Quality Engineer [CA17-0727] AMA Plastics, Inc.-Riverside, CA. General quality engineering activities in industrial manufacturing setting. Bachelor of Science in Industrial Education or related or equivalent plus 5 years… https://t.co/c7vBdeQWha https://t.co/wJ1MpaiNLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Engineer Stf: Req ID : 428642BR_3 Job Code/Title : E2544:Info Assurance Engineer Stf Job Description : This position is for an Information Security professional working for Lockheed Martin (LM) Enterprise Business Services (EBS) in the… https://t.co/G2KW4Oq7c4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Scrum Master III: Description The Scrum Master III is primarily responsible for leading a dedicated self-organizing team to deliver functionality through development and quality assurance execution provided by subject matter experts. In addition, acts… https://t.co/D3NMcnwKD0 https://t.co/sfeu2HXHlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager (Software Engineering): Job Description Technical Project Manager (Software Engineering) 2018-05-30 Professionals ( &gt; 2 years of work experience) Tasks: Technical Project Manager (Software Engineering) positions offered by ABB… https://t.co/LkTsmmnCkr https://t.co/PNfefBs7Jc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer: Redwood City, CA Full-time $80k – $150k Posted Today We're a start-up level tech company that's sitting snugly between The Bay and Silicon Valley. We specialize in using AI to aid in the discovery of chemical and materials data and… https://t.co/mkcomWyzWy https://t.co/rBRZzZ0ND1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payroll Administrator: Job Description PAYROLL ADMINISTRATOR This position is based in Los Angeles, California and reports to the VP of Finance, Americas. The Payroll Administrator manages payroll and associated financial reporting for the Americas… https://t.co/WQWeBqi2uS https://t.co/xrdap9gf4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager – Sales Enablement: Program Manager – Sales Enablement Req #  39307 Location(s)  US-TX-San Antonio Category  Project Managment, Sales Job Overview Overview &amp; Responsibilities JOB TITLE: Sales Enablement Program Manager IV  PRIMARY… https://t.co/CxMssd9AH1 https://t.co/msALTnT49s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Engineering Job: Senior Network Engineer at Altice in Hicksville, NY | Altice Careers SHARE THIS Welcome to Altice USA Careers Search Opportunities SEARCH 5 Miles10 Miles25 Miles50 Miles100 Miles GO JOB DIVISION Search Jobs by… https://t.co/ZkXJXy5Y0e https://t.co/8u5D2AvMgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Network Engineer/Trainer: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Cyber Network Engineer/Trainer Key Role: Oversee the integration of a proprietary Cyber training network environment. Manage new installations of Cyber systems, ensuring… https://t.co/WOndUwej4L https://t.co/j2iQ1T5Ywa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector IT Controls Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/65y5PCwy69 https://t.co/67LLRSxbJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Windham): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/Madbtf1ntb https://t.co/Nk7f5J0yNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Wenham): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/WYsZYRK7Dn https://t.co/her63TAkjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technology Manager: Job Description The Wholesale Financial Crimes Compliance Technology team is looking for a highly experienced technology manager to drive our Customer Due Diligence platform transformation to meet the heightened regulatory… https://t.co/rRAPcNeuFL https://t.co/6tEw2MjKoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle HCM Systems Implementation Lead: Oracle HCM Systems Implementation Lead ====================================== Req #: ******Location: Chesapeake, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current… https://t.co/uSRS9u8cix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: iCentris, a dynamic company changing the way people are empowered to run and market their own businesses, is looking for a world-class DevOps engineer. Why join us? Youll get to work with some truly amazing people, and our work matters… https://t.co/vosainmpaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Analytics Engineering: Data Scientist – Analytics Engineering – Swisslog designs, develops and delivers best-in-class automation solutions for forward-thinking hospitals, warehouses and distribution centers. We offer integrated systems… https://t.co/DPqMoBpFcg https://t.co/MYhoKkXJcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car Install (MECP Basic, Geek Squad): Our technicians are passionate electronics experts and are especially impassioned when talking about the connected car. As a Geek Squad Autotech, youll go through the typical onboarding, job shadowing and new hire… https://t.co/kIW37KUld3 https://t.co/UW1mWhFVBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst And Computer Programmer: COMPUTER: ZedVentures Inc. has multiple openings at its office in San Jose, CA. Computer Systems Analyst: Will analyze systems, business process, map process flow &amp; coordinate migration. Require min.… https://t.co/PAlFebrv6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technician IV – IP: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed… https://t.co/ZE4BQN6W5p https://t.co/W1f90mlkON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Analyst 3: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/B9D5KUzKql https://t.co/e1DHP1J3mD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Senior DevOps Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing 1) Architect, implement and manage our infrastructure in the AWS cloud,… https://t.co/TCEVTntkuN https://t.co/9oKujHZ1fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scientist: Palo Alto, CA Full-time $90k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Senior Scientist with experience in Computational Fluid Dynamics modeling, fermentation and kinetics simulation, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – We are a… https://t.co/qAy7EmhDbh https://t.co/TEKJgfsozc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial Programmer: OVERVIEW OF THE INDUSTRIAL PROGRAMMER POSITION: As a growing global manufacturing organization, our client strongly believes that their success and innovation starts with their employees. Fostering a work environment that promotes… https://t.co/p5x9YcTp6p https://t.co/MPhJYCRE8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Consultation Agent: Geek Squad Consultation Agent Our Agents are the first point of contact for clients and command the check-in and check-out experience of client devices. They ask the right questions, listen to client needs, take detailed… https://t.co/zNNga7duf0 https://t.co/cSKVFXthYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Pepperell): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/zW4dn2I1aY https://t.co/YafL8CQuqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Building Engineer (Building Automations &amp; HVAC): JOB SUMMARY Performs complex preventive and corrective maintenance, repairs and installations of electrical, mechanical, plumbing and/or HVAC equipment, machinery and controls located in the interior… https://t.co/FuTBJcaXO7 https://t.co/ZcV47HhPQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Applications: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and… https://t.co/T1xQUOXJEF https://t.co/lHrhdYbzRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer (Java, AngularJS, AWS): Job Description Job ID: R44767 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman… https://t.co/VZWmvbtrLZ https://t.co/NRo6Qo4xJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Job ID: PK-******* Description: As the healthcare industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable healthcare for our members.… https://t.co/4HiRTMagoV https://t.co/d9gQPAQ42Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Facility: SAP NS2 Facility Intern-Herndon-20171 Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword Search by… https://t.co/aLEqWLpVRh https://t.co/Bjkp0nkSSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Applications are being accepted for the following vacancy on the Non-Teaching Professional staff of Hudson Valley Community College, 80 Vandenburgh Avenue, Troy, New York. Senior Network Engineer  HV-NTP-903 In order to be… https://t.co/2gpIliy7pN https://t.co/Uk9w24nYGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Warehouse Engineer: Progressive Leasing, LLC located in Draper, UT seeks a Senior Data Warehouse Engineer. Duties include design, deploy, &amp; troubleshoot SQL Server Reporting Services &amp; Power BI reports, Integration Services packages,&amp;Analysis… https://t.co/LxFE2jYPFS https://t.co/3FTAlOQ3Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers #SA: Americloud Solutions, Inc. seeks Software Developers for various &amp; unanticipated worksites throughout the US (HQ: Schaumburg, IL) to design, develop, debug &amp; test real time embedded software apps. Master’s in Computer Science or… https://t.co/Rs0Ks0XYe3 https://t.co/lFYDe0DxuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Space Systems Engineer: Why choose between doing meaningful work and having a fulfilling life? At MITRE, you can have both. That’s because MITRE people are committed to tackling our nation’s toughest challenges—and we’re committed to the… https://t.co/8FUAwMZUBa https://t.co/FJAYG7wix7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: TCG is an award-winning, government IT solutions provider. We are seeking a JavaScript Developer to join our project team at a major Federal agency. Although this is primarily a telecommuting position, candidates must reside in the… https://t.co/3q7S8ydlzI https://t.co/TnuPBrt51j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integrator Job: Systems Integrator (Job Number:432474) Description: System Integrator Job Description: The successful candidate will be a proactive, forward-leaning self-starter able to work in an environment with minimal oversight. The candidate… https://t.co/GVb0awKQXH https://t.co/EQToqgVyJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dir IT Internal Audit:   Job Description – Dir IT Internal Audit (18000829) Job Description  Dir IT Internal Audit – (18000829) Description   Join us as we “DRIVE PAYMENTS AT THE SPEED OF CHANGE”. At ACI Worldwide, we are ACHIEVERS, COLLABORATORS,… https://t.co/1dnhvLEp1C https://t.co/7NGT44s7sg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Location: McLean, VA Description Altamira brings a commercial mindset to solving the most complex national security problems by delivering mission application development, multi-intelligence analysis, and data science… https://t.co/lMtGqxKjqd https://t.co/VUwz5D1UkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator III: Linux System Admistrator III with TS/SCI Clearance and Active/Current Polygraph! Provide Tier III system administration support for CentOS operating systems. Install, upgrade and configure Linux workstations. Maintains… https://t.co/zCNu7x9rYM https://t.co/ws78uuBDwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst II: Only candidates who submit a resume and complete the full application will be considered – anyone without a resume will be declined automatically. For assistance with your job application please use our External Candidate Job… https://t.co/BadRnQwSV9 https://t.co/H0M72vQRZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst Design, develop&amp;maintain interactive Chat Bots with Microsoft BotFramework, UCMA&amp;Microsoft Azure; Design, develop&amp;integrate solutions with Azure Cognitive implement AI solutions; Securing Applications with Azure… https://t.co/TE9JT1AHkR https://t.co/gkQWvFA8FN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Quality Engineer: Development Quality Engineer St. Jude Medical CRMD in Sylmar, CA seeks qualified Development Quality Engineer Responsible for ensuring new/modified products conform to quality standards &amp; establishing compliance with quality… https://t.co/Lukrck9k8R https://t.co/hGWAsoWouL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Wareham): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/YZJIlCsP96 https://t.co/llFLxw2yIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Specialist: Implementation Specialist We’re WELL and were the modern communication platform for the $3 trillion healthcare industry. Using WELL, patients engage with their healthcare teams on their schedule and based on their preferences.… https://t.co/KIXfQa04rQ https://t.co/xnyGCnufi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator Location: Quantico, VA Job Code: 2982 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the… https://t.co/0wz6y5xGss https://t.co/hE6GgofxIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer x 6: We’ll be in touch shortly X Not seeing it here? Send us your resume and join our network First Name First Name is Required Last Name Last Name is Required Email Address Email address is Required Phone Number Phone Number is Required… https://t.co/5iieNTiUCc https://t.co/Lqkpd5kCF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Analyst: Software Support Analyst 10-4 Systems, a Trimble company, is disrupting the transportation industry with real-time technology solutions that bring much-needed visibility and efficiency to the $800B market. Our solutions create… https://t.co/fx4MHAHpcI https://t.co/GmtedMTT3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer: Test Automation Engineer (56557 ) Ref No.:18-06778 Location: FORTWORTH, Texas Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/12/2018 Following job posting is open and you can submit profiles against same. Job posting details are as… https://t.co/Xcg1VsF3TT https://t.co/MsmAd6ONFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineer: Operation Technology, Inc., DBA ETAP located in Irvine, CA is seeking an Electrical Engineer with a Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering. Email resume to: careers@etap.comrecblid ao587ydwho9y13yl4mgr6fodalkft5 https://t.co/QMdLRrDXN9 https://t.co/ecAOdEPeHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT (Research Triangle Park, NC): Analyze &amp; implement solutions to ensure the production stability of trade settlement (margin &amp; clearance) systems utilizing PowerBuilder, CICS, COBOL, JCL, DB2 Stored… https://t.co/kVVLnxoQCJ https://t.co/rzus4EAacH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Pepperell): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/E1vbmQUuQM https://t.co/g8z2Nx2Me4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Modeler III: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/zLW6xN7TiE https://t.co/LIBsadKkcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead: Project Lead Location: Fort Knox, KY Job Code: 1831 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/wGtIig3Fk3 https://t.co/BX8Rrhz32H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Architect: Computer Systems Architect Job Locations US-CO-Littleton Job ID 9779 Minimum Clearance Required TS/SCI Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities: Procures, installs, configures, integrates, and maintains Linux and IBM AIX… https://t.co/gGnunJabfV https://t.co/3b0BM1pbe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Hybris Manager $170k: New York City, NY Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a SAP Hybris Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily… https://t.co/YoEM5NoItd https://t.co/HYQjvf1HsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Officer (IA Security Specialist [Journeyman]) – 16588: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering… https://t.co/gOOCRb8obj https://t.co/VFgMcpMZiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Corporate – St. Louis, MO: Role Overview: We are seeking an Angular developer with a C# .NET background to join our team in St. Louis, MO. You will have the opportunity to utilize a wide range of new development technologies while… https://t.co/dNXfA2OPui https://t.co/PI44DLuKn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: : Company Summary Crown Castle is the nations largest provider of wireless infrastructure, with revenues in excess of $3 billion. We are a publicly traded REIT (Real Estate Investment Trust) and are listed on the NYSE (NYSE:… https://t.co/svP1ZHGtLz https://t.co/unKfZuZ8Sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: ONLINE VA17Programmer AnalystVDH87558597*Richmond, VA*JAVA developer with 7 to 10 years of experience, development of large scale applications using JAVA, struts, spring, ORM tool and Oracle CLIENT MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS: (ONLY APPLY IF… https://t.co/k4uSTNCVTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/7YenGsISOo https://t.co/dfsbxfjFZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Architect, Krakow – Poland: As a Senior Architect, you’ll have the chance to work on state of the art facilities for microelectronics, data centers, heavy industrial, research &amp; development, and general manufacturing. Working with other members of… https://t.co/8yqG4XyaP1 https://t.co/HfuSczOZ20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Management Analyst &amp; OPS Research Job: Date: Apr 5, 2018 Location:Springfield, VA, US Company: SAIC Senior Project Management Analyst &amp; OPS Research (Job Number:427447) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: – Participate in NGA and NSG studies and… https://t.co/imoilurA1U https://t.co/gUixOTcgbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lustre/Infiniband Engineer: 30011BR Lustre/Infiniband Engineer Annapolis junction Maryland United States BAE Systems is looking for candidates who have worked extensively with Lustre and Infiniband Networks and who have the ability to create and… https://t.co/limzVSfpxE https://t.co/KEbo2gbsUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Capture Management 3:   Job Description – Mgr Capture Management 3 (18003883) Mgr Capture Management 3 Requisition ID : 18003883 Location : United States-Virginia-Herndon US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/ifCqs08zcK https://t.co/IEH92woVnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Design Engineering 2:   Job Description – Mgr Design Engineering 2 (18007212) Mgr Design Engineering 2 Requisition ID : 18007212 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/1X3E2mdUYT https://t.co/DjZ6640HSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Competitive Intelligence Analyst II: Overview The Competitive Intelligence (CI) Analyst II role focuses on market research, win/loss and pricing analysis and will be responsible for serving as an expert on iCIMS competitive landscape, key customer buying… https://t.co/RWrcxLvcbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Writer: Technical WriterIWD37558326*De Moines, IA*Research, analyze, and understand related legislation for Workforce Innovation and Opportunity Act (WIOA), regulatory related information, and the ability to deliver policy and standard… https://t.co/7mt7OZESCs https://t.co/MMzMWxGdeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Commerce Product Manager: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/zhLPNKVUux https://t.co/tcXKChkZtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – AWD: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems. This applicant must have prior experience in… https://t.co/uAVe1lBLwJ https://t.co/RlGcIrlYwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 4 – Static Analysis Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/Wq6w8VtA0h https://t.co/EJEbgOWw2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window Installer: Must have your own transportation (you must have your own vehicle to get you to and from work, no car = no job) Experience in installing premanufactured windows and SGD prefered but not required. Windows such as ( MI , PGT , MGM,… https://t.co/IElbWbYNUP https://t.co/BSs9xT8KFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procurement Administrator: Procurement Administrator ID 2016-7520 Category Operations Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities TransPerfect’s Operations Team is responsible for the company’s global operations and facilities management. This highly adept… https://t.co/IbyomKrnsF https://t.co/gXdoGmIAd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integration/Test Engineer: Req ID : 422161BR Job Code/Title : E1782:Sys Integratn/Test Eng Job Description : The selected candidate will be supporting the Signals Reconnaissance Program in designing and developing complex solutions for customer… https://t.co/1OQ7crmlml https://t.co/zehpJYnxjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Field Superintendent – MOD: Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Start apply with Xing Apply Now Please wait… Location: Chicago, IL (ADAMS), Illinois, US Requisition ID: 13331 Location: Chicago, IL (ADAMS), Illinois, United States … https://t.co/aykjyranSD https://t.co/Z1D8I9aJpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COMPUTER SYSTEMS ANALYST: COMPUTER SYSTEMS ANALYSTS Southlake, TX area. Analyze science, eng., bus., &amp; other data processing problems for app. to electronic data processing sys. Analyze user reqs., procedures, &amp; problems to automate or improve existing… https://t.co/5hO5MO4F4W https://t.co/KWe1YPauq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per Diem IT Assistant: $15 – $25 per hour based on education and experience. Position is with a mid-size labor union in Albany NY. Duties include: desktop publishing, web editing, user support, troubleshooting, Windows desktop support, network support,… https://t.co/dSGbs1NEcP https://t.co/mrcqUPFXS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst Expedent Corp Irving, TX. Required Knowledge &amp; skills SQL, PLSQL, design &amp; development of applications using J2EE technicians, JDBC, Java Servlets, JMS, EJB. VB, C, C++, .NET, ETL Informtica, AGILE method’y (SCRUM)… https://t.co/pfdx7TU9qV https://t.co/MPrGJXnSu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst And Computer Programmer: COMPUTER: ZedVentures Inc. has multiple openings at its office in San Jose, CA. Computer Systems Analyst: Will analyze systems, business process, map process flow &amp; coordinate migration. Require min.… https://t.co/jQYtJYhvqZ https://t.co/oi0MMHjnhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Director – Cloud Services: IT/SOFTWARE Associate Director- Cloud Services (Santa Clara, CA): Responsible for sales and delivery of consulting &amp; IT services and/or software products in a targeted customer base specifically focusing on the… https://t.co/a1fpu0hAPu https://t.co/QjITEoaAue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Contract Compliance Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/15GNTxMNfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Structural Engineer:     Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment opportunities… https://t.co/juh52XNmA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MARKETING PROJECT MANAGER: University of Washington Location Seattle, Washington, United States Salary Not specified Job type Employee Category Administrative / Office,Health Care,Management / Executive,Marketing / Advertising / PR,Non-Profit /… https://t.co/41Nmph3Nvo https://t.co/7ebfsrm2xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPSI Technical Solution Lead: Req ID : 422285BR Job Code/Title : E1755:Prj Mgt &amp; Plng Opns Rep Sr Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the… https://t.co/CFLLjDqQ7Z https://t.co/oacLXNGmGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Designer: Our client is an established mid-sized agency with a top-tier portfolio of clients, ranging from the worlds largest non-profits to Fortune 500 brands. They pride themselves on their people-first culture and a low-ego workplace that… https://t.co/nWQkTueVDd https://t.co/uzpKiyzeEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Operations Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/VR24ANKVrU https://t.co/CirXYT8FWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Application Developer: Cherry Companies Junior Application Developer Houston, TX 77048 Cherry Companies is looking for a Microsoft c# .net software developer to Join our small Development Team. The right candidate Works well with a small team and… https://t.co/3ELiV2zSDD https://t.co/atxoJLGDf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist PhD (R&amp;D | IOT | Deep Learning): Our client leverages advanced machine learning methods to solve challenging Research and Development problems. These challenges range from developing smart products, personalizing consumer experiences and… https://t.co/N0vLMhtk53 https://t.co/jIw8mbXPBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology, Federal Civilian, and National Security, Aerospace &amp; Defense and International government… https://t.co/7xcCX7xne2 https://t.co/Jv0dMBhyV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Developer Ariba, Inc. seeks a Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of specific product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Eng, Math,… https://t.co/MQ3oEkfIho https://t.co/7ANTQHz4Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL / SSRS Developer: We are looking for a new member for our team. Do you have the talent and experience to step in and work with us and deliver for one of our top strategic accounts? Youll need to be an experienced developer with a solid background in… https://t.co/A9x9iw2ouT https://t.co/7b6LW7vVUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TS/SCI Full Stack Developer: OVERVIEW This requirement is in support of a member of the U.S. Intelligence Community focused on the geospatial mission domain. The work environment is very positive and collegial and co-located with the government at the… https://t.co/yPKXzdIAKs https://t.co/fnyo9w6Oqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water Resources Engineer: WHO WE ARE Michael Baker International is a global leader in Engineering, Architecture and Consulting professionals dedicated to developing and implementing innovative solutions to the world’s infrastructure and environmental… https://t.co/VhrxUaHZGf https://t.co/lSRRa77y7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING Broadcom Corporation has an opening in Irvine, CA for R&amp;D Engineer IC Design 4 (IRDNA) to work on definition, design, verification, &amp;documentation for ASIC development. Ref job code &amp;mail resume to: Broadcom Corporation, Attn: HR… https://t.co/eii4VjS0RU https://t.co/P2gAsEvCVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineer IV: https://t.co/0mmkQbDNlH Services, Inc. – Austin, TX. Support Engineer IV – Provide technical support, including fielding &amp; handling customer issues via phone, chat, &amp; email. Equal Opportunity Employer. recblid… https://t.co/7tcuENdt6Q https://t.co/3l3Q6BiM4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: Customer Solution Adoption Specialist for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg, Math,… https://t.co/31kfhMKn1I https://t.co/d5enfPtOhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Analyst, Marketing Analyst: PayPal, Inc. has the following job opportunities in San Jose, CA: Director, Data Science 1 (Req.#09-581): Design, dvlp &amp; maintain predictive statistical models used for risk mgmt. Innovate &amp; improve PayPal’s fraud… https://t.co/3xzI7nQlQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Application Specialist: Careers Center | Data Application Specialist Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/soHTMI9dXp https://t.co/gsus7Wwtcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Analyst – Manhattan: Job Description Job Title: Sr. Systems Analyst – Manhattan Requisition Number: 23509 Position Type: Full Time City: Plainfield Campus: Indy State/Province: Indiana Job Description: The Sr. Systems Analyst – Manhattan is… https://t.co/lxOv5wvFK0 https://t.co/FSe8oDaFWG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>