<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerbuilder-Programmer-with-C VB-and-ASP Lansing MI: We are hiring a Powerbuilder Programmer with strong PowerBuilder coding expertise along with a subset of .NET (MVC/C#/VB/ASP), and web languages (HTML/CSS/JS) experience. Location: Lansing, MI… https://t.co/erdCmuxubA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure-Solution-Architect AMANDA Lansing MI-: We are looking to hire Infrastructure Solution Architect who is proficient at the formulation of architectures, including requirements discovery and analysis, formulation of solution context, solution… https://t.co/b061kL5soi https://t.co/zw43hjwTrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio Hardware/Software Engineer: VP2 Radio Hardware/Software Engineer, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – English – Italiano – Franais – Espaol – Portugus – – English English en – Italiano Italiano it – Franais Franais fr-ca –… https://t.co/QQebtmJhdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom is the only survivor after family of five's kayak flips: A family's vacation on Lake Superior took a tragic turn when a kayak capsized, killing the father and three young children and leaving the mother as the sole survivor. https://t.co/MIC6GoN7wO https://t.co/31sJiEGedg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Senior Project Manager Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including… https://t.co/dsoVOjSByj https://t.co/lFA9NJpgWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ADAS Performance Engineer Virtual Artist: ADAS Performance Engineer – Virtual Artist – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/qitZtVR0Me https://t.co/QPnspajSwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Representative – Information Technology: IT Service Desk Representative – Information Technology Req ID #: 38793 Location: Mattawan, MI, US, 49071 For 70 years, Charles River employees have worked together to assist in the discovery,… https://t.co/HHYsg6RZGZ https://t.co/OSs8JdWTq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sfdc developer: sfdc developer Ref No.: 18-35115 Location: Farmington hills, Michigan Production Support – Bug Fixes – New Enhancements to the site – Monthly Releases – Checking Logs – Batch Jobs on CA Scheduler – Data loads using Data Loader – Creating… https://t.co/FAt5ebybQF https://t.co/yFyQFhJe1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U2's Bono suffers 'complete loss of voice': Legendary Irish rock band U2 canceled a performance in Berlin on Saturday night, saying that lead singer Bono had "suffered a complete loss of voice." https://t.co/GEzYh9jr2k https://t.co/4qPw18OMZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childish Gambino's 'Feels Like Summer' features all-star cast https://t.co/7V6L5mrifJ https://t.co/7rLax0bPSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dole pays tribute to fellow veteran McCain: Former Sen. Bob Dole reflected on the late Sen. John McCain's service to the nation after he and other leaders paid tribute to the Arizona Republican in Washington on Saturday. https://t.co/NEgboCURAP https://t.co/pp1pXCExyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Support Specialist Building Automation Plymouth, MI: **Service Support Specialist – Building Automation – Plymouth, MI** Locations:Plymouth, Michigan Job Family: Customer Services New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building… https://t.co/vGW3UH3fNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Highly Automated Driving: Company Description Do you want beneficial technologies being shaped by your ideas? Whether in the areas of mobility solutions, consumer goods, industrial technology or energy and building technology – with… https://t.co/zxe4YskKOw https://t.co/ZAd6Zch5zP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Chassis Controls: Company Description Do you want beneficial technologies being shaped by your ideas? Whether in the areas of mobility solutions, consumer goods, industrial technology or energy and building technology with us, you will… https://t.co/YIFlGZkLDs https://t.co/HXJHspnvnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Requirements Engineer: Job opening: System Architect &amp; Requirements Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective… https://t.co/Pf3HmjIrvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/75T5k69Fp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java developer: Full Stack Java developer – SageOne Inc – Dearborn, MI – 08-20-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/K2RQqX3EwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama finds its QB for next title run https://t.co/tx3QUT4YeP https://t.co/ByK9ZHQs3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Devops with CI/CD: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right… https://t.co/0D8JGOW0LA https://t.co/RvTQkkPYCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows bomber blow himself up as officers near: New video from the Texas Department of Public Safety shows the Austin bomber blowing himself up as authorities close in. https://t.co/S8Y1qGAsWt https://t.co/JwbIWzOdmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer II-Emerging Technologies: Software Developer II-Emerging Technologies Software Developer II-Emerging Technologies Job ID 2018-19048 Primary Location Michigan, Ann Arbor Regular/Temp Regular Full-Time/Part-Time Full-Time To all… https://t.co/2hIVsPArJk https://t.co/qh7ficaOad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/U5U2SAnNv9 https://t.co/HJzgkAH24z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/xOr6BZgYy4 https://t.co/mjDpDZcZrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer: Job opening: Senior Staff Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective links: – 0 Navigation –… https://t.co/EryfMWzbJR https://t.co/nzywbAm181]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer I: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/AIDgq8PKXW https://t.co/2216tmVnVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer: Gestamp Chattanooga, LLC. Job Description TITLE: CNC Programmer Reports To: Tool &amp; Die Supervisor Department: Tool &amp; Die Exemption Status: Non-exempt Location: Chattanooga TN Date: 08/12/15 Approved By: HR JOB SUMMARY Responsible for… https://t.co/eUAxdRD9uy https://t.co/dVXVOEhkwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Coordinator:   Job Description – Project Coordinator (1803196) Job Description  Project Coordinator – (1803196) Primary Location : US-MI-Troy-TROY Job : Administration Organization : Health Plans Job Posting : Jun 1, 2018, 6:56:53 PM Additional… https://t.co/9dsDkZzbJ2 https://t.co/1m46t56WLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French actor accused of rape by friends' daughter: French actor Gérard Depardieu has been accused of rape and sexual assault by a 22-year-old woman, a spokesman for the Paris prosecutor told CNN. https://t.co/eV18x6Sxa1 https://t.co/PheW3zS74y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/14/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/exWiPT3ksb https://t.co/65kewKs33f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced East Lansing, MI: For Siemens CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/44ZSRfF7hM https://t.co/NdGwotwGVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile App Developer – Innovation Lab: As an App Developer you will be part of a small R &amp; D Innovation team developing products and services utilizing future technology. We are looking for a candidate to work with us on innovative products and services… https://t.co/rlq15nfLhR https://t.co/0s1PE4eHZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interaction Designer 3: Interaction Designer 3 – Warren, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip… https://t.co/BYE8dnEFAx https://t.co/xBKGuiQjne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Seats: Project Manager Seats Brose USA | Online since: 30.07.2018 As a successful family-owned company on a path to global growth, the Brose Group offers challenging responsibilities and exciting career opportunities to… https://t.co/fs3ha0IiLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banner ERP Manager: Banner ERP Manager Posting Number: ******* Reports to: Chief Financial Officer Department: Information Technology Classification: Administrator Full or Part-time: Full Time Job Summary: The Banner ERP Manager (ERPM ) manages the… https://t.co/c9QyrvNlad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Applications Analyst Senior – Auburn, MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Senior Business Application Analyst The Senior Business Application Analyst is responsible for the development and enhancement of Credit… https://t.co/j8Xt2g1RQK https://t.co/1q0OIIV6QY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad's amazing catch of falling toddler: Watch dad Nicholas Lynch race to catch his 2-year-old son when he falls headfirst trying to climb out of his crib. https://t.co/ymYFWjDc78 https://t.co/6jBT9ds3jA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Project Manager: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Peoplesoft Project Manager for location Livonia, MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Strong ERP and Peoplesoft PM experience. Strong project… https://t.co/QzJJD3yxR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer I: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/8rRfPXbNJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows Austin bomber blow himself up as officers closed in: Newly released video from a Texas law enforcement helicopter shows the explosion that ended the life of Austin serial bomber Mark Conditt as pursuing officers tried to arrest him earlier… https://t.co/yh8H9vaPsL https://t.co/ijhO2wRTPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS Traffic Engineer: Careers Center | ITS &amp; Traffic Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/SkmajAdLSX https://t.co/zhryF974Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Analyst (SAP Implementation): Business Process Analyst (SAP Implementation) Ref No.: 18-37162 Location: Auburn, Michigan Job title: Business Process Analyst (SAP implementation) Location: Auburn, MI Tax Terms: Contract (C2C / W2) Job… https://t.co/WwTaBLxgIj https://t.co/uAObvELVfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst: Job Description Business System AnalystBridgman, MI Posted: 8/27/2018 Category: Nuclear Job Type: – Minimum Experience: 2 Required Education: Bachelor (BA, BS…) Branch: Staffing Solutions Group Job Description Job Summary:… https://t.co/RqzKXqaaYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Manager: Technical Manager Primary Responsibilities: Participate in internal and external stakeholder meetings to assess business needs. Collaborate with Product Management, Operations, Production and other cross-functional groups to define,… https://t.co/7sBVfBF7wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['ER' actress killed in California police shooting: Vanessa Marquez, an actress best known for her recurring role as a nurse on the NBC drama "ER," was shot and killed by police in South Pasadena, California on Thursday, according to the Los Angeles… https://t.co/zDeKBUYOZ1 https://t.co/riVqPomrPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer PLM Software East Lansing, MI: For Siemens Application Support Engineer – Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/ybvRqSf5gK https://t.co/JwwExrLdLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Developer, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching experienced Embedded Software Developer for fast growing team in Detroit area. Team develops innovating testing development environment for one of the Luxoft… https://t.co/UXSaltHxiw https://t.co/U9GnEN1Hz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College football's winningest coach dies https://t.co/ag7einb6b5 https://t.co/0Fmkgd9FOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows Server System Administrator: Arconic Engines is a world-class producer of aero engine and industrial gas turbine components, including airfoils, rings, disks and forgings. We excel in vacuum melted superalloys, machining, performance… https://t.co/hAm0ZlmFOW https://t.co/DiKxsV8VqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Northville, MI: **Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Northville, MI** Locations:Northville, Michigan Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital… https://t.co/2liIXs46LB https://t.co/AdcLDPUgXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['SNL' creates GOP locker room party celebrating Kavanaugh: They were cheering, wearing goggles and drinking beer. It was a "Saturday Night Live" locker room party for Brett Kavanaugh's confirmation. https://t.co/BrJhGDm63D https://t.co/Mir9PaHVi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/aTWbrdpZ4d https://t.co/AMwjDns5Rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verification Validation Engineer – Data Analyst: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Ref No.: 18-40093 Location: Troy, Michigan Position: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Location: Troy, MI Duration: 12+ months contract to… https://t.co/Q93X3UvPho https://t.co/VQF4nWR4OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bounce pad goes flying, kills 2-year-old: A 2-year-old boy died after a strong wind gust blew away a bounce pad the toddler was playing on at a Nebraska pumpkin patch. https://t.co/mOpBLlJf33 https://t.co/SVyatZTACj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer: Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBilingual Customer CareBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck… https://t.co/QvBK2cz4jz https://t.co/10ZNl77XwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Solutions Architects: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You’ll lead team of Solutions Architects to drive excellence in solutions development, solutions selling, and opportunity closure through strategic engagement with assigned… https://t.co/yuboLnCPBq https://t.co/36otHEDHel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Resources Analyst – Benefits: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as well… https://t.co/Pn6CZB5MGB https://t.co/trYstqr0lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Developer Sr.: Training Developer Sr. – Warren, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip… https://t.co/vKVVUJhqj5 https://t.co/YPwTEKIn2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York has a new Playboy Club. Is it nostalgic -- or tone-deaf?: New York has a new Playboy Club — again. https://t.co/IKM23Wrbx4 https://t.co/EYOlTEdzj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Solutions Architects: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You’ll lead team of Solutions Architects to drive excellence in solutions development, solutions selling, and opportunity closure through strategic engagement with assigned… https://t.co/POLfeIo6n8 https://t.co/0099MA3xzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Junior Consultant: Job Position – SAP Junior Consultant Company Information abat US. LLC is a leading SAP consultancy specialized in solutions for the automotive and logistics industries. The abat Group is headquartered in Bremen Germany with… https://t.co/nCE0wnyhWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL informatica developer: ETL informatica developer Ref No.: 18-40512 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Role:-ETL developer Location:-Aurbun Hilss,MIJob Description(As per hiring manager) Minimum of 6+ years overall IT experience: including 4+ years of… https://t.co/8BRN5D6D8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 35579BR Domain Financial services Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Country USA State / Region / Province Michigan Work Location Grand… https://t.co/O3G7cNzqvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer – Infotainment: Senior Embedded Software Engineer – Infotainment – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our… https://t.co/sJAAxhCezc https://t.co/rtlbqGsN3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New owner wants Time magazine unshackled: Salesforce's Marc Benioff says he bought Time magazine because he "values storytellers" and wants to protect an iconic brand -- but says he'll stay out of editorial decisions. https://t.co/jzg9bf7IZz https://t.co/rABW85q7zO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Overview Flex-N-Gate is a leading manufacturer and supplier of components for the automotive industry, recently ranked 10 th of the 150 Top North American Suppliers in Automotive News. A growing and vital company, Flex-N-Gate… https://t.co/zCNiOgI0u8 https://t.co/gvoOfGOMya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shopper in viral video hailed as hero: A woman is being hailed a hero after confronting another woman who was criticizing two friends for speaking Spanish to each other at a store in Colorado. https://t.co/mmiaXUgIdW https://t.co/l7AcdFOiPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Developer Sr.: Training Developer Sr. – Warren, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip… https://t.co/beQELjwtcX https://t.co/l9KVIMT6X6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Software Engineer – Powertrain Controls: Description: Software Engineer – Engine / transmission controls Designs and integrates engine control software. The selected individual will work within DENSO’s Engine / Transmission Controls team.… https://t.co/rJisUFxlaL https://t.co/eAekPJqccA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Application Developer: Mobile Application Developer – Auburn Hills, MI – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company… https://t.co/vpyHVoahKm https://t.co/dAzqhI3mKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Functional Support: SAP Functional Support (PP / MM) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering Jobs – Accounting and Finance Jobs –… https://t.co/qRHwyguXaq https://t.co/TgGEbp7vBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Nobel choice captures moment in history: The announcement of who will receive the Nobel Peace Prize is always most powerful when it taps into the global conversation of the moment. https://t.co/BZqjjuhq6R https://t.co/4BNagJ2EFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LARA Programmer 6: LARA – Programmer 6 PROGV1 Ref No.:18-06095 Location: Lansing, Michigan Start Date / End Date: 09/10/2018 to 08/23/2019 Requisition Description Engagement Type:Contract Short Description: Converts data from project specifications and… https://t.co/eTKbK7OL2F https://t.co/DwWIvPt2EF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/gQkYYBtBIh https://t.co/gmSqWUJhsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Mobile Developer (Connected Experiences): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the… https://t.co/yV37N76Z6h https://t.co/ZQgED452Jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters hold kegger at Sen. McConnell's house: Protesters gathered outside the home of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell and staged a "confirmation kegger," in the final hours before the Senate prepares for a confirmation vote for Brett… https://t.co/L8pOW3X7ki https://t.co/J2pz7q53S3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verification Validation Engineer – Data Analyst: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Ref No.: 18-40093 Location: Troy, Michigan Position: Verification &amp; Validation Engineer – Data Analyst Location: Troy, MI Duration: 12+ months contract to… https://t.co/9y3u4PX9Oa https://t.co/wMZ97CKxsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/yDZDACbwW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Auburn, MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Senior Software Developer The Senior Software Developer is responsible for the configuration development of the credit application system used to leverage… https://t.co/xLkmOPGkMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 35589BR Domain Enterprise Package Skillset SAP , ABAP Country USA State / Region / Province Michigan Texas Washington Work Location Dearborn, MI Houston, TX Redmond, WA Company ITL USA Job… https://t.co/uRSe5sJPWA https://t.co/MUdx3R4IDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: Role Technical Test Lead – US Auto req ID 35579BR Domain Financial services Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Country USA State / Region / Province Michigan Work Location Grand… https://t.co/OFxp78xrHC https://t.co/euM1qw3tXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/CcYRDDTPyC https://t.co/cGQSVoksXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/GA170hhdKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Security-Analyst—Incident-Response–Lansing–MI: We are hiring an IT Security Analyst to monitor and advise on information security issues related to the systems and workflow at an agency to ensure the internal IT security controls for an agency are… https://t.co/eqoWGvg1x7 https://t.co/mtSm0lz1px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-39478 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Salesforce Developer job description Job brief The Salesforce Developer will perform hands-on technical implementation, with a focus on delivering functional… https://t.co/7Q5VdigQrv https://t.co/8ol4arlnJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Systems Analyst: Software Quality Assurance Systems Analyst Job Title: Software Quality Assurance Systems Analyst Location: Southfield, MI Position Type: Full-time, Salaried If you are seeking an environment that encourages… https://t.co/jIdEyXRike https://t.co/Kwihuu1xyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: This opening is with Arconic Engines – a world leader in the investment casting of super alloys, aluminum and titanium primarily for jet aircraft and industrial gas turbine markets. For more information on Arconic, visit us online at… https://t.co/3Os1p5zohQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Project Development Engineer – Embedded Systems Quality Engineering (ESQE) Governance and Assessments: Lead Project Development Engineer – Embedded Systems Quality Engineering (ESQE) Governance and Assessments, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI… https://t.co/65C4XlTV6M https://t.co/BMsqdpRBWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Resource Analyst: Job Description This position functions as a Human Resources Analyst for the Office of Human Resources serving the Department of Licensing and Regulatory Affairs. This position is responsible for a variety of classification… https://t.co/gTttegk4PT https://t.co/l5E2yGAGha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The week in 25 photos: Take a look at 25 photos of the week from September 27 through October 4. https://t.co/Seiiw0EHG7 https://t.co/tjOJ1Xer3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: Job Code/Req #:****** Discipline:Quality Business Unit:Moulded Foam Location:Romulus, MI, United States Position Status:Regular Wage Type:Salaried Work Shift:Rotating The Woodbridge Group a global manufacturer of foam products and just in… https://t.co/TwkTB4GmXF https://t.co/k5jsC65Zxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution: Lead Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ============================================== Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Lead Software Engineer to join our Public Safety Product s… https://t.co/0ZFXqnKxHW https://t.co/my44uHnbgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gnGxkTr5Iz Developer: ******* Developer Ref No.: 18-34998 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 06/25/2018 to 12/31/2018 Job Summary: Company: Artech Information Systems LLC Position Title: *******… https://t.co/omUx1mfkFa https://t.co/ezKsKdDRw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Validation Technical Integration Engineer (TIE) – Software Programming: Global Validation Technical Integration Engineer (TIE) – Software Programming, Warren, MI, General Motors. Plan &amp; dvlp validation strategies to ensure fully robust vehicle ECU… https://t.co/2BZTXadxmC https://t.co/1wZr9vXBGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration unveils new counterterrorism strategy: President Donald Trump has signed off on a new national counterterrorism strategy, articulating his administration's vision for how the US should confront terrorist threats at home and abroad. https://t.co/hktKqiivYw https://t.co/s92NKeWPup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution =============================== The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with… https://t.co/PZEuTsB5UP https://t.co/Vz4TOuXMFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Trainer: Global Information Technology is Professional IT training and consulting services corporation that has been in business since 1999. Global Information Technology committed to providingstudents with the necessary skills and attitudes to… https://t.co/W3Ptx3UAIC https://t.co/9dn6w2SApS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-51901 Location: Novi, Michigan Start Date: 09/17/2018 Job title Scrum Master Location Novi, MI Duration: Long The Senior Scrum Master has the responsibility of leading a mid-size team of Developers, Testers, BA and… https://t.co/cMq1Y6dDPh https://t.co/llYyB5PpiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Supreme Court nominees who faced controversy: A single new justice on the tightly divided nine-member Supreme Court can change the law in America, and as past ordeals demonstrate even a failed nomination can change the course of history. https://t.co/NgNj1EGRtA https://t.co/UuMOBsAn7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst: Job Description Business System AnalystBridgman, MI Posted: 8/27/2018 Category: Nuclear Job Type: – Minimum Experience: 2 Required Education: Bachelor (BA, BS.) Branch: Staffing Solutions Group Job Description Job Summary:… https://t.co/0pc7Agvv5r https://t.co/estNIT2gu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Northville, MI: Recruiter Siemens Location Northville Salary Competitive Posted 26 Sep 2018 Closes 26 Oct 2018 Sector Power and Nuclear Category Skilled Trades Contract Type Permanent Hours Full Time You need to… https://t.co/HHyeA2lIUn https://t.co/59ePwkenXw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>