<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/53aKlOkVjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/N3UoOW7dn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/qeMoGtz9Dv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/JOz398hFwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/n17E5mYK5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/ISmcCJtYoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/5Sx8zK2wnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/VVYT620LQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/wlHNsDOt8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/HKn3bL0K1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/AXBe2BrBcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/umYvNVNgoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/AmoOvKGG4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/Dc0BLU2Khv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/iIcHaRHi4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/JxWYYJrrMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/EEYPMKdLEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/77VLT23p0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/pKcQdf4wEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/1c3cGZKT4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/TusKboLiCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/D0sIqHbtcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/uBmDuO09UQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/eMYNk1CZ5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/Ylk7AvyB60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/GuTvXNIuGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/5jLs6c341b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/8ID1EpetJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/iGDSTrZaLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/lp5sOUzWX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/X7TQ7yHTdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/wRCOzlWSnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/fwx9pRIJpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/4Ee8KnRHHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/Jw8EciK98k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/ZBKzGiePmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/m0wRfxpQ0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/WanvoX7Mgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/HlPFhbeAiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/kJvHvw6YR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/OxhVKiqfvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/vs9jqcvoRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/TccMD22M9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/EDxbX4jvmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/1PTcv1x9On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/ppZ1hPWXlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/oNVVBeMMJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/oh1ePo0yMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/d8QP20jwMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>