<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/Z9BLz1F3lY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/EFMoSMxJe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/xma11BPJhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/tgwiXuv0us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/p6ooqPoJOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/btaYBsLvZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/PLtuZvWtSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/tgha1aFTon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/RlCbN4N62H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/zqovbdP0dP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/Q1c0YoBlkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/1l8NpY95nY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/VMvI1vBtIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/MxUmv4TIcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/T6zH1AmmDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/TMoSxQDRZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/MuSDBPVt6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/TxICuES22H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/9UqvdC7cX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/sHsOsu61g5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/SqJz7H4uwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/Ov8pfR2ENn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/oHwGKQNdUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/w9TTtGs5yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/s25NO0iM8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/2oxn5Tir6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/SrsM06vt2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/edSLbb8KoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/lXH2b2leT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/ZV2oOKnTno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/sdAx50joji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/c1lDxcRvon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/sHzpdRURke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/tgha1aFTon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/4M0ncyL8Mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/GoIsKn09jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/DKesuOH0VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/yLQ8sX1oZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/Tjn82hvxOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/i22eI7uNxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/T6zH1AmmDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/kEsSY65YE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/Ov8pfR2ENn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/yYLpm0gjhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/KDBK6U9L4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/6u0ASp1m7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/0bQmB8nrjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>