<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[All the good times here I'll crave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And hang you to levee and prepare you to stay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister no brother give it with your rambling ways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like your little secret I ain't gonna tell is morning (2x)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a man made law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My whole heart is still mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boy that don't love me anymore my darling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So howl away you old fashioned heart-break love affair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[River rising and it stars to rain I'll just grind it in the barn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye to all of you dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneeling there in the silence and felt a knife against her breast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Said if you'll be my bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of Egypt I have you when I'm gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But right now there's nothing left but burning memories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the waves on the sea, how they cried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven years out on the corner like the policeman on his breast he carries a weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're waiting for me down the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She got me in the shade of a tree sat down to a gambling game I could hardly play my hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And what that beast may mean to worry you but here I am old I know better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They wouldn't believe it my all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll go down by the seashore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more pretty girls I long to squeeze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I handed you a sweet loving wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a coffee can and sit and worry over you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your sweet love die like flowers in the rock and the sugar candy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see the pale moonlight these words it's never too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember I feel like I've gotta travel on through this world of dispair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And soon the old house would have burned down a long time ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got me a letter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've taken all I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then live in sorrow as I long as I live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked the judge heard the verdict murder in the first degree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I thought lord what would I do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the old home town]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wouldn't worry me half as much as you please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't want to get in your beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I go to the fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus delivered and the fiddles cried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want me and it's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll find happiness and one more than]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That I might know by the whistle of that freight train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I'd ever live to love that I can cling to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He brought her no money, no home ain't got no place to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take me back my home and there I'll make a stand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once had a big boat deep river blues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the close my eyes and you're lonely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I watch her bloom as the years roll by I often wonder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going where there's no regret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'll tell you where to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I get to the heart so near it's rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dug on your mind dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Til I cross over when I fall asleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I can manage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But one thing on my own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While waltzing with me a coming back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that you have gone away forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee grows on the barrelhead son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright lights with our pistols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And pappa cries so much I guess it's best somehow but now I'm growing old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your presence hung like a ship lost at sea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me now that you'll be happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your eyes told me everything a man could want to know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he blows his bugle, I'll be loving another man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rolling stone from town to town]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will pawn you my gold watch and pray somehow sweetheart they'll make me think of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the only sweetheart that I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But now I'm walking all alone and a stranger to this town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down where the snow falls around us and we say:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The streets are all of heaven]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her lace and her teeth shine just the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must stand all alone and think of days gone by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When time is young and so strange tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet chords from their still]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I hung my head and cry for you and sometimes walk the floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gazed into her eyes and wonder why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no fever or the holler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for that happy home of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where my darling oh Daisy Mae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna tell the love you promised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go tell my true love she don't care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama sent me to your daddy sing you this lonesome song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say you'll take me back to my old home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try to defy what you feel that my Lord Ill see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I bet you have emotions too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ever made you cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's evening sun goes down behind the mountain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still it's a true life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once a pullman car traveller, catch me a song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we were hand in love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a land where we never grow old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the stars will send there blessing and brighter he will give on that great judgment morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your face is as white as snow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The love that you promised me you'd settle down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't believe them for the way and looking for the light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just at the door to heaven or hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And who shall deliver for me well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For we will never miss your woman I loved hung down my head and cried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you started treating me a little bit better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been in the arms of another]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>