<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to fix a friendship is to try. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to build a snowman? It doesn’t have to be a snowman. –Anna  in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to get what you want in this world is through hard work. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A conscience is that still small voice that people won't listen to. That's just the trouble with the world today. –Jiminy Cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right things may seem wrong sometimes, or sometimes the wrong things may be right at the wrong time. –Jiminy Cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. –Charles (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will protect you from everything around you. I will be here, so don’t you cry. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things don't always go the way we planned, but you'll see every day that we'll never turn away. –Simba "Lion King II"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one decides my fate but me. –Belle (Once Upon A Time)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're curious and curiosity keeps leading us down new paths. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a river when you fall. It's the greatest power of all. –Cinderella (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we work together, things are always better. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth sounds insane sometimes, but that doesn't mean it's not the truth. –Linguini (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned an important lesson. You can’t count on anyone. –Syndrome (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real treasures are your friends and family. –Woody (Toy Story 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there someday. I can go the distance. I will find my way if I can be strong. – Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they’d look closer, they’d find out there’s so much more to me. – Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes failures lead to better things. –Monsters University]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you haven’t found your talent yet, doesn’t mean you don’t have one. –Kermit in "The Muppets"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[\"If you are what you eat, then I only want to eat the good stuff. –Remy in "Ratatouille"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell everybody I'm on my way, and I'm loving every step I take. –Koda in "Brother Bear|"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play it safe. Better to not know which moment may be your last, alive to the mystery of it all. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “When you wake up in the morning, what's the first thing you say to yourself?" | Pooh: "What's for breakfast?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “When you wake up in the morning, what's the first thing you say to yourself?" : Pooh: "What's for breakfast?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake with the morning sunlight to find fortune that is smiling on you. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and me together, that's how it always should be. One without the other don't mean nothing to me. – Monsters, Inc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not lost for I know where I am. But however, where I am may be lost. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People often ask me if I could tell others how to make their dreams come true. My answer is, you do it by working. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember music and I remember love. –Ariel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what happens to me, I'll always be with you forever. –John Smith - "Pocahontas"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/08uBCfpoOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream. All you have to do is think about it, work on it every day, and you'll get it. –Sebastian "Little Mermaid Series"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remember to smile. –Elinor (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody wants to live happily ever after. Everybody wants to know their true love is true. –Giselle in "Enchanted"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t take action without having a plan first. It doesn’t have to be a good plan, but some plan is better than no plan. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets rough, I like to hold on to my dream. –Olaf "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody seems happy. Why does the world have to be down on me? – Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don’t go away. Please? No one’s ever stuck with me for so long before. –Dory in "Finding Nemo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we do fantasy, we must not lose sight of reality. –  Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I love you, I insist you run. –Olaf in Frozen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your heart be filled with sorrow for all you know tomorrow the dream that you wish will come true. –   Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real treasures are your friends and family. –  Woody in "Toy Story 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think, believe, dream, and dare. –   Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let it go. You'll never see me cry. Here I stand and here I'll stay. –  Elsa in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not exactly sure what I should do. –   Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t get Minnie off my mind. I just can’t go on without her. –  Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can. That doesn't mean that anyone should. –Remy in "Ratatouille"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I never knew you, I'd be safe but half as real, never knowing I could feel a love so strong and true. –  Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you wish for something, doesn't make it true. –Tiana in "Princess and the Frog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunny is sweet, but friendship is sweeter. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/xwHq836oka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/fwp43ip28z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams connect us even when we're far apart because dreams come from inside your heart. –Ariel in The Little Mermaid Series]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever stop to think, and forget to start again? – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Np4PW4WI2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/xqrM6QYNCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams connect us even when we're far apart because dreams come from inside your heart. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/EX2blIygvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you laugh is just the best. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forever is a long, long time, and time has a way of changing things. –Big Mama in "Fox and The Hound"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/IXB9tPLyP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your talent makes you who you are. You should be proud of it. –Tinker Bell in "Disney Fairies"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunny is sweet, but friendship is sweeter. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute http://t.co/fOVAPNE6Fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's impossible. –The Doorknob in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends will stick with you until you’re unstuck. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you do the things that you CAN do, you will find a way. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your strategy isn’t working, try it from another angle. – Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words describe a mother's tears. No words can heal a broken heart. – Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t worry. Everybody has problems. Everybody has bad times. –Phoebe in "Enchanted"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though life was hard sometimes, I tried to keep my hopes and spirits up. – Cinderella in "Princess Stories"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Cinderella !! She's my favorite. This is my favorite disney princess story! http://t.co/d109kw9XiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart has wings and I can fly. I'll touch every star in the sky. So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming of. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a state of mind. You can be happy or you can be unhappy. – Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only I could promise forever, then we could just be we forever you and me, forever and ever. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be with you forever. I want you right here beside me forever. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard "Frozen" will be released on DVD and blue ray on March 18 ! Get ready! :-) http://t.co/5cWfHhq0Zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing is family. – Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t you ever stop dreaming. You can be anyone you want to be. –Travers Goff "Saving Mr. Banks"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like a road that you travel on when there's one day here and the next day gone. –Cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am at war with myself. –P.L. Travers in "Saving Mr. Banks"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely. http://t.co/e0UPDb6fQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise me you won't forget about me, ever, not even when I am a hundred. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A laugh can be a very powerful thing. Sometimes in life, it’s the only weapon we've got. – Roger "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When somebody loved me, everything was beautiful. Every hour we spent together lives within my heart. – "Toy Story 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/kh6Yn4JJJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without Minnie, my dreams have become nightmares. – Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on! Live your life to the fullest! http://t.co/uOoZ9xHz6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/KC2nCDVEWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/sgNaKjpX0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/q5LploAsHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/wM6UazJ8LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jOsq7zA4fI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/aEohs68txY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Nl54a3cNBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/pFVT89IZWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen, and you can't do anything about it. –Timon in "The Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you believe you are ready to shine, the princess inside you will show. –Sleeping Beauty in Princess Stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just one of those days. Again. – Eeyore]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>