<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mail-Order Food Sellers Bank on Procrastinators: To handle the holiday crush from last-minute shoppers, America’... http://t.co/Rre97TUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven Rules for Coping with Sales Rejection: From setting goals to developing routines and relationships, small ... http://t.co/65OiMeAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verizon To Buy Netflix Rumors Hit The Web | Share Prices Rise As Market Reacts To News: Could Verizon be about t... http://t.co/DMNBiDOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @designersays: Just found a typo in my alphabet soup. That's it. I'm never coming back to this restaurant again. &lt;--Hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanSafkow: [video chat replay] Your questions about membership sItes answered by @AlexMandossian, @AndrewLock & @chrisfarrellcom htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Moms Are Influenced by Blogger Reviews: A couple of days ago, we were discussing book bloggers, revi... http://t.co/zW4w3XyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree Do You Secretly Fear Creativity? http://t.co/r0fjDgzW // Interesting article from @IncMagazine! #creativity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid Search Strategies for the Holidays: Retailers have rediscovered paid search this holiday season.  Compared ... http://t.co/eXBwwemL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Holiday Spending Up Thus Far in 2011: We still have around 10 days left in the online holiday shopping se... http://t.co/GcNQo2tn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Strategies for a Winning Sales Presentation: How to put your best pitch forward, win over prospects and mak... http://t.co/WoKzxIev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Snowe Asks Amazon to Halt Price-Checking Promotion: She says the promotion gives individuals an incentiv... http://t.co/knVgnOBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Gift For Tangle-Free Listening: The last item to make our Indie Merchant Holiday Gift Guide is a pair of Zipbu... http://t.co/oadaYQN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Snowe Asks Amazon to Halt Price-Checking Promotion: She says the promotion gives individuals an incentiv... http://t.co/fXEqW2Tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs December Ten: Weekend Favs December TenThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend blog post ... http://t.co/DYYn7fbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: Lessons From An Ex-Real Estate Lurker: Before I owned my own business, I worked in-house for a large... http://t.co/yT9sphsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Snowe Asks Amazon to Halt Price-Checking Promotion: She says the promotion gives individuals an incentiv... http://t.co/MYTUmO3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About that Twitter Self-Serve Ad Product: Twitter grabbed headlines with the announcement of its new look and fe... http://t.co/aimKqjVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Facebook subscribe button | Adware apps | Most expensive keywords: Online Ad Market:

New 'Adware' app... http://t.co/4qBhwA3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Simple Rules for Building a Blockbuster Brand: The entrepreneurs behind Fresh cosmetics share the roadmap t... http://t.co/rjD6XzCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Android 4.0 tablet under $100 | Apple loses trademark in China | AT&T throttles: Mobile Computing:... http://t.co/paXtDmDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Ads Get More Media Buyer Cred with Tremor-Nielsen Agreement: VideoHub, a division of Tremor Video, and Nie... http://t.co/PSh1Ppf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Goggles Improvements Add to Your Search Options: Search sure has come a long way from its blue text link ... http://t.co/HJWfVl1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women CEOs: Debt and Regulation Hurt Job Growth: Women business leaders meeting with Republican lawmakers said t... http://t.co/VqKcFucI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global iPlayer App Comes To iPhone, iPod Touch As BBC Sees Future In Mobile Service: The BBC has announced plans... http://t.co/MieM3AsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Plan to Invest More in Social Media and Email: With the end of 2011 nearly upon us, it’s time to take ... http://t.co/QgWyJ7kr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree What do you think about this @Harvardbiz article? // To Grow, Leave What You Know Behind: http://t.co/hguxxQGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Text Marketing Can Still Appeal, But Better Add Some Pizazz: Mobile texting, that utilitarian form of mob... http://t.co/z2rX8N2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still the Question is Debated: Are Social Media Campaigns Worthwhile?: Yahoo has published a blog post touting t... http://t.co/inh9BuEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Social Media for Research and Development: Consider this advice for getting customer feedback over Fa... http://t.co/7i1of6Ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney, Gingrich Join Obama on Payroll Tax: Republican presidential front-runners Mitt Romney and Newt Gingrich ... http://t.co/I1w8UATn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[StumbleUpon Redesign Invites You to Explore More: StumbleUpon put on a new face this week and not only is it mig... http://t.co/cI04xY2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMandossian These entrepreneur's took their business idea &made it a reality (via @EntMagazine): http://t.co/1ymiYA6N #entrepreneurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York's Commuters Can Shop Toys R Us Via QR Code: New York commuters that wish to buy select toys from retail... http://t.co/fBiHrm4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If This, Then That: If This, Then ThatThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
QUOI Media via Flickr CC
Reaching y... http://t.co/HV5VQWlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Mobile to Reach Holiday Bargain Hunters: Small businesses can fight the promotion clutter by using te... http://t.co/qk08Ew5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Recover Quickly When Disaster Strikes: Small businesses can't predict when Mother Nature may strike, but ... http://t.co/AAUG4Ppf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Smartphone Shoppers Do it at Home: It’s kind of ironic, but more people use their mobile phone to sh... http://t.co/TLA8afpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Xbox Live Upgrade Brings TV and Movies Galore To Xbox 360 As Microsoft Eyes Future: If you have your Xbox 36... http://t.co/JEJNvnEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Study Shows Young Adults Just Want to Have Fun: For marketers, going online often means business, but for 53... http://t.co/Ge9mcR88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my new video where I interview Isabelle Mercier – Branding, Marketing, and Productivity Tips  http://t.co/PvUP4VRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree VIDEO: How to Focus on Your Business and Managing Your Time - http://t.co/LsPOw5fG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Makes Life Easier for Global Brands: Domino’s Pizza is the latest example of a brand using Facebook for... http://t.co/qatzjhuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is Killing Google+ In the Referrals Category: Google+'s referral numbers are viewed as one gauge of the... http://t.co/jG1KWAI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What If Facebook Bought Gowalla?: The rate of rumors being truth in this industry is increasing at an alarmin... http://t.co/SUPfI2H9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Animals Were Harmed to Make This Lip Balm: Today's featured item from our Holiday Gift Guide is a vegan lip b... http://t.co/0gGz1QM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I Love The New YouTube Design | YouTube Grows Up, Becomes Organized Media Center: I don’t know about you but... http://t.co/iVouQpsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Jewelry Out of Broken Plates: The next item selected for our Indie Merchant Holiday Gift Guide is a neckl... http://t.co/qdjDOUPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: Pep! Pep! Pep! Pep Talk?: 
Pep talks are awesome aren’t they? Heck, I watched the one above 6 times ... http://t.co/tlcXKsAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a QR Code Campaign for the Right Demographic: eShave, line of shaving gear, has launched a campaign cal... http://t.co/MlIH5Bc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New YouTube Design Stresses Channels: YouTube has done a major redesign and it wants you to think “channels”. Th... http://t.co/X4J4XE1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree 10 Ways For Female Entrepreneurs To Get Funded: http://t.co/5KRFScjC #entrepreneurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT  @AlexMandossian 5 Tips for Integrating Social Media into Your Business (from @successmagazine): http://t.co/VDJ7tmNb #socialmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe All Those Mobile Sales This Weekend Weren't Such a Good Thing: One of the sub-themes of the banner Thanksg... http://t.co/dcxBhuUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sacrificing Clarity For The Wrong Reasons: Since we’ve been discussing clarity the past couple posts, here are a... http://t.co/xHvWndl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony Experimenting With Early Digital Sales To Tempt People To Buy Rather Than Rent Movies: What do you do when ... http://t.co/HjpVtvPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patagonia Tests Sustainability Legal Status:  http://t.co/guk1Grhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DQ Drives Social Media Membership With… Email Marketer Silverpop: Dairy Queen recently used content and social m... http://t.co/9hWJ8bkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major Marketing Mission: Figuring Out Generation Y: If there was ever a group of people that are coming up throu... http://t.co/U15vRpY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: CES | Ultrabooks | New AT&T devices: CES:

Why CES still matters.

Mobile Computing:

Intel shows ... http://t.co/8Y3JxGnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond Yoda and Pepsi: NFC-enabled Mobile Gaming: Pepsi announced a coup last week with plans to use Lucasfilm's... http://t.co/beR4HTDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: CES | Google & Bing & SEO losses | Out My Window: CES:

Consumer Electronics show has 2012's hot tech ... http://t.co/2309XohI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Robots: Rise of the Machines (Again):  http://t.co/BAkcdCR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate America Pledges $1.2 Billion in Services to Boost Startups: Nearly a year after launching Startup Amer... http://t.co/PkD8jk4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: CES gadget track record poor | Facebook, Moo partner on Timeline business cards | Ramnit worm: CES... http://t.co/ChOWrKVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers Still Don’t Know What to Do with QR Codes: QR codes are popping up everywhere. Not long ago, these mys... http://t.co/nrATiQCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Sell Anything Using Social Media: How to Sell Anything Using Social MediaThis content from: Duct Tape Mar... http://t.co/WpXzBfH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roku Streaming Stick Brings Web Video Content To Both Dumb and Smart TVs With MHL Ports: Roku sees a future when... http://t.co/sK4C1nxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail Sites Held Their Own for the Holidays: With no major mishaps or e-commerce fails reported for the last we... http://t.co/3EAjuUuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Shows Global Social Media Differences: Forrester has released its report “Global Social Media Adoption in... http://t.co/fDLszOHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Market Passes 400,000 Apps. Should We Care?: I am torn on passing along information like this. It seems ... http://t.co/TrUlOXPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Universities Fail Women Inventors: An experiment shows that, given the same invention, tech transfer officer... http://t.co/cJUwYnts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overcome Five Obstacles to Growth in 2012: Business strategists pinpoint impending challenges and offer advice t... http://t.co/SAWRvhIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Readies for 2012 Campaign Season With New Webpage: The holiday season is over—unless one includes the Sup... http://t.co/4jehSH2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet Marketers: Meet the New Year, It’s the Same As the Old Year: I know it’s the in thing to put together a... http://t.co/5pY8rl7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY NEW YEAR!: Looking forward to a real good 2012!

 http://t.co/TTlpm5ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Sources Suggest Multiple Apple Television Sets (iTV) Will Arrive In 2012: Another day, another set ... http://t.co/cmAfluXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: How To Be A Better Marketer In 2012: Oh yes I can already hear the champagne bottles popping! Happy ... http://t.co/YejTE87H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Sell to China Now: Small businesses that persist despite piracy, malleable contracts, and a spotty legal ... http://t.co/KbQVaSiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank You to Our Marketing Pilgrim Sponsors: We couldn’t do what we do here at Marketing Pilgrim without the con... http://t.co/FQqKOgVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Method Vision: Green Consumers Want to Have Fun, Too: This guiding principle helped the founders of an eco-f... http://t.co/PZlrapMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Top 10 Most-Pirated Movies Of 2011 Revealed As U.S. Box Office Numbers Disappoint: 2011 has been a poor year... http://t.co/rLfE7BIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Facebook Attacks [Infographic]: I spent much of my Christmas holiday trying to clear a virus off my son’s c... http://t.co/n5Iheg52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree 7 Simple Techniques To Build Customer Loyalty: http://t.co/QyzmuOZd #customers #sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myspace Returns, but Will the Fans?: About a week ago, Myspace took a big leap forward but hardly anyone noticed... http://t.co/wB48bGj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Look At Yahoo Search's Rich Ads Performance: Last month Rich ads under Yahoo became available to all adCenter ... http://t.co/qA2Vh6tM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Call Genie acquires VoodooVox | Facebook stats | Holiday web sales hit $35B: Online Ad Market:

Call G... http://t.co/Y9MI55RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Company's Valuable Devices: A look at six tools to help keep your offices, and the equipment ... http://t.co/0vS9kQKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix, Gap and Overstock Show Biggest Declines in Customer Satisfaction: We just looked at the dollars, now le... http://t.co/GNmQ3RCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google+ Growth Points to Serious Facebook Competition ; SocNet Demand Is Big Enough for Both: Google+ now has 62... http://t.co/8qRM7GOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McAfee: Spammers Continue to Mimic Legitimate Advertisers: One disconcerting trend identified by McAfee in its 2... http://t.co/0ho4CRCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinkers As Online Shopping Demographic: Before we get started I will tell you that I honestly had not given thi... http://t.co/P1ku78rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Tips to Kick-start Your Sales Skills: Learning to sell yourself, and your product or service, is one of the b... http://t.co/iAmap257]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What We Watched On YouTube In 2011 – Rebecca Black, Nyan Cat, Music Videos Galore: YouTube remains the premier d... http://t.co/GWDSvj6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoDaddy Fights to Hold on to Customers as Rivals Scoop Them Up: GoDaddy CEO Warren Adelman got a Christmas card ... http://t.co/fhZq4kDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Campaigns Increasingly Include QR Code Element: At one time, an integrated ad campaign was some combi... http://t.co/Kd7yRAA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Sales Get Another Gold Star for Christmas Sales, But Can It Survive the Return Process?: Mobile sales has... http://t.co/EuCcocBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: 2012 predictions | Kindle Fire gets upgrade | Apple fined in Italy: 2012 Projections:

Google: Five th... http://t.co/U8JAVawQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home Businesses Flourish on LiveJournal Singapore: In 2011, small business owners in Singapore set up shop on Li... http://t.co/wScTEnbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mail Delivery May Stop in 2012:  http://t.co/1j9PvTn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postal Service Cuts Worry Kitchen-Table Entrepreneurs: Planned cost-cutting measures could challenge millions of... http://t.co/JqPbOdPg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>