<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[On the way to my heart I wrote "Entering forbidden", but Love came in laughing and said "I enter wherever I want".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you an interior decorator Cuz when I saw you the room became beautiful. s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is something you always think you have plenty of, until there is none left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the caterpillar calls the end the rest of the world calls a butterfly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes out your phone, look at the time. Keeps phone in pocket, forget the time. Takes out phone, look at time again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing yourself sing in the shower and wondering why the heck you havent made an album yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fix it if it hasn't broken yet. Don't regret it if is hasn't happened yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to music is sometimes a distraction from work when your favourite song starts playing. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time it's over. I"m keeping my heart. I'm going to be strong and not fall apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls find out EVERYTHING. I advise you to not lie to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you say "I love you." You are making a promise to someone else s heart..... try to honor it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher: From all this noise I assume you're done working Student: From all this b**ching I assume you're still single.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We just have to accept the fact that some people are going to stay in our hearts, even if they don't stay in our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been so trapped for so long, I've forgotten what its like to be free...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't realize the distance you've walked until you take a look around and realize how far you've been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you truly believe in yourself, you will certainly find yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People change and are constantly evolving. Sometimes they change for the better and other times it's for the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be the prettiest, smartest or strongest, but at least I m me, and don t pretend to be someone that I m not meant to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the type of girl who can be in the middle of saying something and then stop and say,"...wait... um... what was I just saying"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regret is for the people who can't see that life is beautiful, and will always get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ILoveYou is better then I Love You because there's no space for lies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a crush on someone you've exchanged less than  words in your entire life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not afraid to tell you what's on my mind, I'm just afraid of how you'll react.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a lover not a fighter, but I'll fight for what I love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so skilled that I never trip down the stairs...just up them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find someone who can change your life, and not just your relationship status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got no where to run, because the only place I've ever wanted to run was into your arms...&amp;now you're not here anymore...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear girls, every calorie is not a war. You are beautiful no matter what you eat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want that one that I can look at and say "The day that I met you was the happiest day of my life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I come off kinda shy, but it's hard to say what's on my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when someone who always starts drama complains that they hate drama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best things in life are worth waiting for, fighting for, believing in &amp; just never letting go of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life does not promise us anything, we have to go out and get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it again. I've said it before I'll love you forever and then a lil bit more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lost because I trusted. I trusted because I believed; in all those Lies you told me... I loved and you deceived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want you to know that you're beautiful in everything you say &amp; everything you do. And no matter how you turn out, I'll always love you .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haters don't really hate you, they hate themselves; because you're a reflection of what they wish to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting your alarm  hour ahead of the time you intend to wake. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were just in it for the action. I'm not your personal theme park attraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't give my heart to anyone. But if you are brave enough, you can try to steal it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem is, you never made me feel like I was special enough. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not falling in love, I'm falling into pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to be absolutely ridiculous than to be absolutely boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're lonely always remember that theres someone out there loving you more than words can explain&amp;smile just knowing that person is me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I'm single. And you have to be amazing to change that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People do need to realize, there are times where I actually want to be alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a strange thing. It can make the weakest person strong &amp; the strongest person weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scars you can't see are the hardest to heal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I chose construction over demolition because I wanted to build people up rather than tear them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the caterpillar calls the end the rest of the world calls a butterfly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want tell you that I've gotten over you and I don't think about you everyday but I was told not to lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a crush on someone whom I know will never love me back. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You re sorry? Yeah like I haven t heard that one before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking your phone to see what time it is and checking it again because you weren't paying attention the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be lying if I told you that losing you would be something I could handle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tough thing about following you heart is that people forget to mention that sometimes the heart takes you to places you shouldn t be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I actually did "live like there's no tomorrow". I'd be in jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He broke my heart. He's touched my soul. Left me in pieces then made me whole. He's made me laugh then cry a river. He is my past&amp; my future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is not blind. It sees all; it just doesn't mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you tell someone you love them and they say "I know"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing apart from the people you once were closest with is hard. Even harder when you aren t sure how to fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will always be a song in our playlist which we always skip, but never delete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swore I needed you. Well consider them lies, because baby here I am without you and I survived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication + Trust = A relationship that will last a lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm good at faking a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish everyone would just forget my mistakes so I could as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if I told you I didn t care a million times, you d know I was just telling a million lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake friends are like shadows: always near you at your "brightest moments", but nowhere to be seen at your "darkest hour".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He stole my heart and I'm planning to take a revenge... I'm going to steal his last name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That one girl at school that's just psycho ... yeah you know who I'm talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will forget you, I will find someone who is better than you, and he will love me the way I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate it when some people are so sure that they are right, and they don't give you a chance to explain yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My excuse for staring at you is: Incase I go blind tomorrow, I want to remember everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was a keeper but you didn t care for her. She loved you but you didn t respect her. She s gone and won t come back to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hate, live simply, expect a little, give a lot, always smile, live with love, and be with God.; the recipe to happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't mean to be rude but does it look like I give a fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's just a boy who doesn't know what's in front of him and she's just a girl who never learned how to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With this pain in my heart sometimes I wake up thinking "You still matter to me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not depressed, I'm just tired of being happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful who you open up to. Only a few people actually care, the rest are just nosy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you fall in love you feel like you're in heaven...when your heart is broken, all hell is unleashed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It s easier for people to hate than to love because love is seen as a weakness when it actually makes you stronger. Hate leaves you bitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are afraid to care too much, for fear that the other person does not care at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're amazing and I love you, but I'm not waiting forever. Let me know where you want to take this, don't leave me hanging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texting someone and falling asleep while waiting for the reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful...the ones that make you smile are the same ones that have the power to shatter your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the problem with getting attached to someone. When they leave you, you just feel lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check this funny and amazing app==&gt; http://t.co/o7q8WvIXQl - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New version 3.1 now available for this funny and one of a kind app!!! http://t.co/hMglxM3hO0 - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG The FREE software THEY don't want YOU to know about. see this ==&gt; http://t.co/YVNA8a7l04 - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality dating shows have never been this funny, Burning Love,  Watch this==&gt; http://t.co/J5er0crRgM - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SharkWeek will always be my favorite week of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never find another girl that will put up with you and love you the way I do. Just so you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God knows if we're meant to be together, He'll find a way to bring us closer no matter how far apart we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LADIES: you wanna know what your most beautiful curve is? your SMILE :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is one of the essential ingredients. Each day brings , seconds. Whatever isn't used is gone forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was just a chapter in my book. I am going to turn the page but not close the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept your defeats with your head up and your eyes open, with the grace of an adult...not the grief of a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love sleep. My life has a tendency to fall apart when I'm awake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know the truth that you're to scared to admit, you're with her, but when you look at me, you can't even remember her name...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>