<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/WMUwv5qPAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/fOKqAME40s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/qEo3h6rWg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/UYkdYaF9kN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/WfdKIFIbyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/z88g3ViSNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/6qSDui6RoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/EdWaA5EHcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/e2E1o8ytip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/sm69AXFhZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/oUv7bItZbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/TOmJv8YnmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Tv1c8FYbwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/16NgXPrprI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/4IFBqhq1FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/gg5FuN2nZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/oFgl0mNWly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A business has to be involving, it has to be fun, and it has to exercise your creative instincts. - Richard Branson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/9JAnZQhJyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/g4A4M6JnwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/Je6XP86HYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/7lXnozYxhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/svm4I3GZi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/g1kkFJl02z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/8edkvDrqrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/Erkc1oQW5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/57QgKyNUvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/67sfeEFiIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/iA042sE0cu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/cZoSxFYZSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/UYkdYaF9kN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/yHNBo1J3We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/11x33ykA3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/9hO5tpqleB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/BtBDIljUVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/BuB4IjdYgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/8T72ZSCwy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/E07eSGs5JD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winner ain't the one with the fastest car, it's the one who refuses to lose. - Dale Earnhardt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/n8zwM4uRSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/DEb2lPpDvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/NSx4Oj1WdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/Qg7h37FxW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/lyTPkrtQ3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Everyday Impact of Math  http://t.co/CDVeiiNZrp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>