<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Specialist: Recruiter UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN Location Ann Arbor, United States Ann Arbor Michigan Posted 25 Jul 2018 End of advertisement period 07 Aug 2018 Ref ****** Job Type Professional Services, IT Services Contract Type Permanent… https://t.co/Gwc3p6Z8bF https://t.co/o83DU4Ch0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stelter: This reveals how the pro-Trump media works: Brian Stelter shows how the President works hand-in-hand with the pro-Trump media to discredit the Robert Mueller probe. He compares it to a "hall of mirrors" and says the political jockeying… https://t.co/z58RcQZUZ1 https://t.co/jB2K9CxbzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Dearborn, Michigan. Relocation may be necessary. Job Title: SYSTEMS ANALYST Job Description: Duties for this position will generally include the… https://t.co/32SrWfx3KX https://t.co/TJfzkfFLqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Dearborn, Michigan. Relocation may be necessary. Job Title: SYSTEMS ANALYST Job Description: Duties for this position will generally include the… https://t.co/eWvuZy0oO4 https://t.co/AmOn4DYU83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Deployment Specialist: Job Description Position Description Deque is seeking a full-time Software Deployment Specialist to join our Support Team. This position will perform the installation and upgrade of new customer implementations of Deque… https://t.co/5XoTs2VBke https://t.co/j7XS87Rwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ADAS Performance Engineer – Program Support: ADAS Performance Engineer – Program Support – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We… https://t.co/qejadeeCUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android/Linux Engineer: Logic Solutions is a full-service development firm headquartered in Ann Arbor, MI with 4 additional offices around the world. Founded in 1995, Logic offers website design and programming, eCommerce solutions, customized web and… https://t.co/EiXsTfp8Rg https://t.co/lSnYgfr7CQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active Safety Data Analyst: Active Safety Data Analyst – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion –… https://t.co/PPurQJ89bR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP WM Consultant: Trustek, Inc is a highly recognized provider of professional IT Consulting services in the US. We are actively seeking SAP WM Consultant for a client in Southfield, MI. This is a long term contract position. If you may not be looking… https://t.co/bsus3cEYnW https://t.co/E7AsMTIOwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shot! 33 amazing sports photos https://t.co/ZYZ0Q3azCl https://t.co/4o4ISLyNWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: Job Description – Zeeland, MI, USA – Full Time If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career opportunity for you!… https://t.co/8sI4dr3oSO https://t.co/eoHxLohzIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loan Officer – Hastings, MI: Job Title: Loan Officer – Hastings, MI Location: Hastings, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: GreenStone Farm Credit Services Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Finance, Banking, Insurance and Real Estate… https://t.co/f1isSSaXud https://t.co/JNY3dHvqyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former UFC fighter dies of cancer https://t.co/5ZX0tPkmHG https://t.co/EbwUBiNVpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SOA Consulant: Oracle SOA Consulant Responsibilities: – Participate in technical planning &amp; requirements gathering phases including Design, code, test, troubleshoot, and document engineering software applications. – Ensuring that technical… https://t.co/XjU6ipF32D https://t.co/ymJfyRrpN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Technical Support – Incident Response (Sucuri): About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under… https://t.co/ZrLNZvuY6P https://t.co/F64Vtb9IyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LARA – Programmer 6: LARA – Programmer 6 PROGV1 Ref No.:18-06095 Location: Lansing, Michigan Start Date / End Date: 09/10/2018 to 08/23/2019 Requisition Description Engagement Type:Contract Short Description: Converts data from project specifications and… https://t.co/wiHy4GiIvt https://t.co/zigSJ7zbpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software-Developer: Software Developer Populus Group seeks a Software Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to design, develop, modify, and test large-scale, Object-Oriented, multi-tier software applications utilizing the… https://t.co/8WSTGCKrCP https://t.co/w5YXAtx7RK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/BjLIIncfX5 https://t.co/GJspAd7h2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Technician: Your opportunity As a GIS Technician n the Traffic and Travel Information Product Unit you will be responsible for validating customer feedback involving traffic incidents, road closures and other relevant traffic information. You will… https://t.co/IMqdJ0OhdA https://t.co/sWIPQ1y1ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Advanced: **Application Support Engineer Advanced** Locations:East Lansing, Michigan Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/egeTXE9YEp https://t.co/NqAm5zn0dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Developer: Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Java Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to design, develop, and modify web-based enterprise software applications throughout the software development life cycle (SDLC)… https://t.co/CptPY6Ao87 https://t.co/eH9ie1L25W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Applications Analyst Senior – Auburn, MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Senior Business Application Analyst The Senior Business Application Analyst is responsible for the development and enhancement of Credit… https://t.co/vZZbZBJNMw https://t.co/SHXZdPwXs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An unbelievable card has 0% interest until 2020 https://t.co/j9pqitUTjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GM Basic Software: Software Engineer – GM Basic Software – GPS******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire –… https://t.co/QPWfQ61Sw8 https://t.co/QUldVR6avv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Business Intelligence: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/D6J4O6WfE4 https://t.co/QLFDJluEbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Dawn Technologies – Home – Organization – Partners – Privacy Policy – Terms Of Use – Services – IT Strategy – Application Development – Mobile Application Development – Business Intelligence – Cloud Computing – QA Service Offerings –… https://t.co/1ymcGYwKdt https://t.co/j4ZQPNF8I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Job Details Technical Support Specialist Exciting IT opportunity within our Technical Services group offering exsposure to and responsibility for level 2 &amp; level 3 problem resolution for our global organization. About the… https://t.co/exmQSjiNNn https://t.co/CJxoCZqYaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business One Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/HuwI44VOTG https://t.co/CDZouCRhPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager – Solutions Architects: Job Description What you’ll be doing… You’ll lead team of Solutions Architects to drive excellence in solutions development, solutions selling, and opportunity closure through strategic engagement with assigned… https://t.co/hfgscWxu5h https://t.co/DAMDKHpDIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: A financial services organization is looking for a Data Architect to join their team in Detroit. Responsibilities: Maintaining the logical design and implementation of databases and data systems Resolving complex data related issues,… https://t.co/f8fJMPv505 https://t.co/4wImHVGwGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Human Resources Analyst: Associate Human Resources Analyst HARMAN International Date: Aug 21, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Job Description A Career at HARMAN We are ONE HARMAN.… https://t.co/NlBl8T3GfU https://t.co/Gw57UPOoUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – Engine / Transmission Controls Designs and integrates engine control software. The selected individual will work within DENSO’s Engine / Transmission Controls team. This individual will help integrate DENSO software… https://t.co/7kP3ziVOmE https://t.co/hNJTbe0eWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer: Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer – ENG******* in Detroit, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our… https://t.co/WJIm563OSg https://t.co/lU2ETfk2LB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's most famous actress vanishes without a trace: Imagine if one day Jennifer Lawrence was walking the red carpet in Los Angeles and the next she vanished completely with no word about where she was. https://t.co/EzZyyaIDJB https://t.co/QfpsiISLmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer: Job opening: CES Interior Electronics – Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the… https://t.co/NqvVUnC1th https://t.co/pdQ4Ua18JK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: Connected vehicles and connected navigation is a domain in which many innovations take place at a rapid pace. The System Architect needs to stay current with these innovations and the asset developments in the various TomTom… https://t.co/2RBMw9PFaw https://t.co/xRcfU0WaWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developers///only Green Card And Citizens Can Apply: Android developers///Only Green Card and Citizens can apply Michigan Center, Michigan TechnogenInc Jobs Toggle navigation Failure Message Sign In Sign Up Career Portal How to Sign up to career… https://t.co/eqZUETUopM https://t.co/il0m8sG3yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MDOT Departmental Analyst Real Estate Data Analyst: Job Description This position is a recognized resource for MDOT’s statewide Real Estate technical program. MDOT’s real estate technical program consists of MDOT right-of-way plans and right-of-way maps.… https://t.co/Zr6eIVdxhy https://t.co/YlNWTXzdIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer: Crystal Reports and PUSQL Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBilingual Customer CareBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck… https://t.co/blbQhA1KA3 https://t.co/RlZ69ElG4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile App Developer – Innovation Lab: As an App Developer you will be part of a small R &amp; D Innovation team developing products and services utilizing future technology. We are looking for a candidate to work with us on innovative products and services… https://t.co/D7ySnedB1I https://t.co/ctCDbBI1yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow, Theresa May is still standing: Next week marks six months until Brexit day -- the moment when the UK actually leaves the European Union. https://t.co/cDVRqzbn4d https://t.co/gTHYa9pMoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated Driving Software Engineer – Entry Level: Automated Driving Software Engineer – Entry Level, FCA Job #*******, Auburn Hills, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – English – Italiano – Franais – Espaol – Portugus – – Japanese – Korean – English English en –… https://t.co/K4b2l6jK1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No.… https://t.co/iMjhD0myTM https://t.co/Lu60d6XTzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Hardware Engineer, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program –… https://t.co/2POtWgwgaK https://t.co/i2OklCAjPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst 3: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking System Analyst 3 for location Lansing , MI for one of our Top client. Responsible for creating intuitive user interface designs for mobile applications, web… https://t.co/apGJeQwwSU https://t.co/c0bjRqsxzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer – ENG******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Benefits –… https://t.co/UjBGKau42e https://t.co/zt9F0or87X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Banking Training Program (Credit Analyst) Detroit MI: Job Description Internal Ref: ************* Job Description Commercial Banking Training Program (Credit Analyst) Anticipated Start Dates: January 2019 and June 2019 Credit Analysts are… https://t.co/jZshOfmOKk https://t.co/zy0vuHv50o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 9/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/InbXjEnOLx https://t.co/XTwIGHPTvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Senior- PLM Software job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/VOUmpShvZx https://t.co/aDNh7QhFji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria to investigate rare monkeypox cases in UK: The Nigeria Center for Disease Control (NCDC) is working with Public Health England to investigate two cases of monkeypox diagnosed in the UK this week, in patients who had recently traveled to the west… https://t.co/jNTIMGxPOy https://t.co/hc6RvELqAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier III ICQA Data Analyst: Job Description Tier III ICQA Data Analyst Location: US-MI-Romulus Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Fulfillment &amp; Operations Management Job Description Job Description: The Data Analyst… https://t.co/JzlneuhkY1 https://t.co/MaFdrtiSm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Technical Support – Incident Response (Sucuri): About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under… https://t.co/RN323ISLIC https://t.co/wOgl6RMyiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/tWJVQLxu61 https://t.co/NrXElS6Vwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions in China flee Typhoon Mangkhut: More than three million people have been moved to safety in southern China as Typhoon Mangkhut moved northwards and continued to wreak havoc across the region. https://t.co/wPoFwzzg84 https://t.co/hNvflFAos3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florence has filled rivers, roads and houses. And it's still raining.: Small streams look more like rivers. Rivers like raging torrents. And city streets and stretches of interstate highways -- dotted with rescue boats -- like free-flowing waterways. https://t.co/5KaNqCeEQI https://t.co/ey6zuMsd7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Applications Analyst – HR / HCM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as… https://t.co/QSVMV0b6qU https://t.co/oUwnHSoicG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/sn7HoGX7bv https://t.co/hjrKDHOolP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon investigates claims that employees sold confidential data https://t.co/LBYbmmJUHs https://t.co/TvNVIeDJuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Date: Sep 14, 2018 Location: Ann Arbor, MI, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 28328 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/3hpTeKGU3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/00zjXm2f9Z https://t.co/GlzgVq3dP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr–Java-Developer: Sr. Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Sr. Java Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software application design, development, testing and deployment utilizing the following: Java, J2EE, API,… https://t.co/rBixT4JfX9 https://t.co/lifSUdNmq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBIEE Developer Lead: OBIEE Developer Lead Ref No.: 18-41011 Location: Midland, Michigan Title: OBIEE Developer Lead Location: Midland, MI Job Description: Working on OBIEE ad-hoc reports + dashboard developer. OBIEE 11 reports development experience of… https://t.co/NAPL5dModA https://t.co/erFHk4flTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/sk0qY0PBMW https://t.co/t7NOFeQBFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/S8FRRn3It7 https://t.co/2ei5s26dq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who really paid to protect us from Florence: As we write, Florence is slamming into the Carolinas. State, local and federal emergency planners have been working around the clock for the past week to prepare their communities and citizens to deal with… https://t.co/AOeA9GZPf9 https://t.co/CByQx6ptAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/IGy93cXEMY https://t.co/nVKPdH7jDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Advanced: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Advanced job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS –… https://t.co/CI9luRDGmE https://t.co/nIjjs75DdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOPer: Six ways media can regain credibility: In the past few weeks, we've seen the editorial pages lock arms in organized opposition to President Donald Trump, the host of "Meet the Press," Chuck Todd, call for a more aggressive approach to reporting,… https://t.co/3iAymWwUS6 https://t.co/yhWpGtIwN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Analyst I- Production Systems: This position is a primary support for the Manufacturing plant floor, supporting the local IT department. Support in the area of network communication IT Analyst I- Production Systems Responsibilities: IT Analyst I-… https://t.co/cvDWtXazCg https://t.co/6DxSRXocgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motorsport Software Engineer: Company Description Bosch Motorsport North America is looking to expand their high performance team with a Software Engineer to continue to foster its North American Motorsports product development growth in supporting… https://t.co/n1JRY86jtC https://t.co/SsvNOU3R65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico City killers wore mariachi disguises: Dozens of mariachi bands were serenading couples and families in Mexico City when five men disguised as musicians unleashed a hail of gunfire. https://t.co/IABxgRqjQh https://t.co/3cLBk5N7LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/UriMx6m8Di https://t.co/Ur86fjmNR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maintenance PLC Technician: now Maintenance PLC Technician (Hourly) =================================== Company Name: Michigan Dairy Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Non-Exempt Position Summary: Support programming, troubleshooting, calibration,… https://t.co/03JZjmCtyJ https://t.co/q3djTv0qw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Lead: Career Opportunity: Test Lead- Farmington Hills, MI Are you thrilled to work on the latest in in-dash navigation and services for cars? TomTom s Custom Systems teams are challenging, fast-paced environments where people are empowered to make… https://t.co/j4YZQFW96v https://t.co/6Y5Rb5dmHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Design Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-52200 Category Engineering Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 20-30% Position Code 8927 Position Description The Solutions Design Senior Engineer is a key team member within a… https://t.co/cbwrwYXkpn https://t.co/N181UPgXpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Representative – Information Technology: IT Service Desk Representative – Information Technology Req ID #: 38793 Location: Mattawan, MI, US, 49071 For 70 years, Charles River employees have worked together to assist in the discovery,… https://t.co/lVIR1h3O1E https://t.co/fWiNQ2tHoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Validation Technical Integration Engineer (TIE) – Software Programming: Global Validation Technical Integration Engineer (TIE) – Software Programming, Warren, MI, General Motors. Plan &amp; dvlp validation strategies to ensure fully robust vehicle ECU… https://t.co/KXPoGnag9Y https://t.co/V5iyrCbOP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmy predictions: Who will win the night's major awards?: With the Emmy Awards just days away, here's a look at how things could shake out in 18 different categories. https://t.co/vz4pVXSO7i https://t.co/EL7JcUL5Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IVR Developer: IVR Developer job | Cognizant job in Southfield, Michigan, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values –… https://t.co/K6P3L3hZRw https://t.co/on9hjoSnnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Mill Set-Up Programmer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/ZtcsHTDzgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typhoon sends debris flying as it nears Hong Kong: Hong Kong's storm alert was lifted to its highest level Sunday as Typhoon Mangkhut swirled off the coast, bringing the city to a standstill as residents prepared for the threat of heavy rain, storm… https://t.co/IDJZCp5S8R https://t.co/L4Pgt5l869]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Michigan Address: Post Date: 09/08/2018 00:12 Req ID: 27780 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/xtp6IGJdPC https://t.co/W6C7H6SN7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Hardware Engineer, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program –… https://t.co/bq9tEgtyaV https://t.co/bkJwGtS3uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Hardware Engineer, Automotive Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program –… https://t.co/modri8WhKN https://t.co/gtIOB4TDCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Don Jr. became the President's most vocal defender: The week after a parade of Cabinet-level officials released statements denying their involvement in an anonymous New York Times op-ed attributed to a Trump administration official, a high-profile… https://t.co/9Ranslkvbi https://t.co/SYJkGl2twc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: SunIRef:Sales:title Sales Implementation Specialist – Detroit, MI 48202 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/f1gJ68lTKg https://t.co/hXJ26QX3rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer Intern: About Us… GreenStone Farm Credit Services is over an $8 billion financial services institution with over 500 employees in 36 locations throughout Michigan and northeast Wisconsin. GreenStone provides short term and long… https://t.co/hzYZM7oza7 https://t.co/9XdVidMB9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/94eKHIQPB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with PCF Experience: Java Developer with PCF Experience Ref No.:18-15685 Location: Dearborn, Michigan Position Type:Contract Start Date: 08/31/2018 Java Developer with PCF Experience Dearborn, MI Contract Detailed JD: Must Have Strong… https://t.co/UhkDl7RpOl https://t.co/c7rpIJOhDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-38054 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Key skills required for the job are: .NET-L3 (Mandatory) – Minimum of 7+ years overall IT experience: including 5+ years .NET application development – Responsible for… https://t.co/TwA5XciIbB https://t.co/S3Q7HNJ1hP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: This opening is with Arconic Engines – a world leader in the investment casting of super alloys, aluminum and titanium primarily for jet aircraft and industrial gas turbine markets. For more information on Arconic, visit us online at… https://t.co/1eqanviOzd https://t.co/JuVin0VoDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business/Data Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/20/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/cmSBQJLIAH https://t.co/E3hvsFq3Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAE Geometry Development Support Applications Engineer Advanced: For Siemens CAE Geometry Development Support Applications Engineer Advanced job – Engineering – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation… https://t.co/SyFDataDyp https://t.co/DYYZuod30b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer: Gestamp Chattanooga, LLC. Job Description TITLE: CNC Programmer Reports To: Tool &amp; Die Supervisor Department: Tool &amp; Die Exemption Status: Non-exempt Location: Chattanooga TN Date: 08/12/15 Approved By: HR JOB SUMMARY Responsible for… https://t.co/hgsUFAVy50 https://t.co/78Hn2IkV3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr–Java-Developer: Sr. Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Sr. Java Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software application design, development, testing and deployment utilizing the following: Java, J2EE, API,… https://t.co/6CIVlF7TZi https://t.co/4ZkEfQ5xx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front end JavaScript Developer, HMI, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching experienced Embedded Software Developer for fast growing team in Detroit area. Team develops innovating testing development environment for one of the Luxoft… https://t.co/HrSWL5EFc6 https://t.co/xVHQ2G2hhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29782BR Domain Utilities Skillset Sharepoint Application Migration , Country USA State / Region / Province Michigan Work Location Battle Creek, MI Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys –… https://t.co/D2AAZZ4vHu https://t.co/RZ0HT9Dbn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: Connected vehicles and connected navigation is a domain in which many innovations take place at a rapid pace. The System Architect needs to stay current with these innovations and the asset developments in the various TomTom… https://t.co/UUbx4oTTCZ https://t.co/EHG63K6WNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer PLM Software East Lansing, MI: For Siemens Application Support Engineer – Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/zd93nbXQxl https://t.co/dNhdWQaUjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL-Developer: ETL Developer Populus Group seeks an ETL Developer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide database development in the healthcare industry; develop, design, debug, test, and document ETL process for Date… https://t.co/gh89uJoNJg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>