<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Tulsa, Oklahoma – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsPython,DjangoTax TermsC2COverview Python Developer 6+ Months Tulsa, OK Required Skills : * Python, Django and angular or… https://t.co/aNkGh6tpUC https://t.co/qQN22T8mOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/YfCkSYZY2v https://t.co/FyfDCPBBqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphics Software Engineer: Description: Leidos currently has an opening for a Graphics Software Engineer.  We are looking for an energetic, motivated, independent, self starter for a challenging position supporting a dynamic team that develops and… https://t.co/d49PGQYuPW https://t.co/DxuJ5yS3w5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoC Performance Modeling Engineer: Description:Leidos has an excellent opportunity for a System-on-a-Chip (SoC) Performance Modeling Engineer located in our San Diego, CA office.   The successful candidate will participate in an SoC computer processor… https://t.co/9ZW0JBY89F https://t.co/UFVn5wrRQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Video Engineer: Client Reference Code: 216833Job Scope The Video Operations group is responsible for operating the video ecosystem at Spectrum and is comprised of the following groups: Video Core, Video Systems, Planning &amp; Implementation and… https://t.co/dOj0IL3TDV https://t.co/dFrwMuETbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Lead, PICTE: Description:Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   We are seeking a promising… https://t.co/WMIANaDFuC https://t.co/OwOXH8Uh8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/yXmpsC5VDC https://t.co/ONjONmRHW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/ddXtkJjK81 https://t.co/vJVdGeFwsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Since 2006, WMC Global has worked with digital services providers around the world to deliver insight into digital threats targeting consumers. By monitoring channels for threat delivery, analyzing relevant data, and… https://t.co/OkmKhzDTsz https://t.co/xo3qrtKijm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place people come… https://t.co/L4jm7yCtsj https://t.co/rV3FikjaAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Server Engineer: Shopkick is the leading shopping rewards app, bringing moments of joy to everyday shopping. Consumers can be rewarded for everyday actions like visiting stores, checking out products, and making purchases across hundreds of brands… https://t.co/dkOhuHr1rh https://t.co/04v50PwZkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: Understanding of PC Platform and mother board architecture Good understanding of different power states of system and devices (ACPI S-states,… https://t.co/Ht3dOK4mWp https://t.co/4k8jknuvN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/S7byXe4Xqp https://t.co/80sq9I2keq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[devops engineer: We are looking for a highly motivated Senior Cloud / DevOps Engineer to join our innovative startup. The candidate we are looking for is an experienced cloud software engineer who is ready to design, automate and support our cloud… https://t.co/KoMQEZ1r6i https://t.co/4qPI28L6y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer – Integrations: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered… https://t.co/fzmzcNS44x https://t.co/hiSu8idBaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer (GeC): Position Description Develops Innovation strategies, processes, and best practices Drives the execution of multiple business plans and projects Ensures business needs are being met Leads and participates in medium- to… https://t.co/LjjTnHEz31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Strong… https://t.co/PRDvUrtWUz https://t.co/jENLqn3uDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Test Automation Engineer, Connected Care Applications: Mobile Test Automation Engineer, Connected Care Applications Careers That Change Lives Medtronic leads the health care industry to provide solutions that benefit the daily lives of people… https://t.co/BbtwvqnJvQ https://t.co/TlvNvSAKPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/fZ0ROR0NIB https://t.co/YDQD41VUK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Software Design Lab Developer: Intern – Software Design Lab Developer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate… https://t.co/yC9yNwCeFK https://t.co/sJy8swy2M3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/6xbyMqdc8a https://t.co/cGcimqcBGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Backend Developer/Engineer Professional: Looking for a Financial Developer/Engineer Professional that has Python Backend Developement Salary: $100-120k Location: McLean, VA 1-2 years plus hard core Back End Server Side development in… https://t.co/QOFfxSHJCZ https://t.co/JKGrqoOE6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Product Developer – Java/JavaScript/React: Join our elite IT team as a Full Stack Developer – Java/JavaScript As a Full Stack Developer, you will be a part of the Product Services team.  At CARFAX, we create products for our consumers and… https://t.co/DfjMhKwJxw https://t.co/jbXxY6cUXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deals Analytics Experienced Associate – Chicago: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/GbXnawrdWS https://t.co/sZvPi8qrYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/nfi65BWDeP https://t.co/HpEGshpZVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineering: Description: Job Description This position is a Systems Engineer on the Exploitation Services (program), working hand-in-hand with the ACE, Chief Architect (CA), Chief Engineer (CE) and the Program Management Leadership team… https://t.co/ePYrBAA2rd https://t.co/gqhh8D7DkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead IT Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed… https://t.co/c9bqqKrlNF https://t.co/vedFgYzfHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/BDhjDTdniz https://t.co/4oAXfXniTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Application Developer: Senior Linux Application Developer Menlo Park, California – United States Job Start Date – 03/20/18, Posted Date – 03/20/18 Primary SkillsSenior Linux ApplicationTax TermsC2COverview Client: Mercedes-Benz Title: Senior… https://t.co/e3OZaw7Q7V https://t.co/SWuCtEJw1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Database Middleware Eng: Sr Database &amp; Middleware Eng Role/Responsibilities This is a challenging position within the Database and Middleware Engineering team of the Infrastructure Services. Reporting up to Moodys Chief Information Officer,… https://t.co/nGgow9Cxbt https://t.co/DNvqa15M0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect Technical Lead: Application Architect Technical Lead McLean, VA Enterprise Business Technology Office organization provides support to the business areas for delivery of programs and applications. This includes partnering with the… https://t.co/broCns3HhD https://t.co/WrEzAaFUsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/ykRcvQ3PsZ https://t.co/RSZjZYSkEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/SxxIJTF395 https://t.co/GFpW8jTOvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer -PHP – Python: Venice, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – PHP/Zend –… https://t.co/cxN8r7qhzb https://t.co/8azQax7b6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/s4L05buFHh https://t.co/mBgTS2nmEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II- CORE OPTICAL: Client Reference Code: 214889 JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Operations team is responsible for the implementation of approved… https://t.co/lyrrzlwQV2 https://t.co/I1HKEVqOAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/SYe7aWqIaK https://t.co/S5SjSGitas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Administrator (Tues.- Sat./ 2PM-11PM): Interested in artificial intelligence and cognitive technology? IPsoft is looking to expand their Cognitive Operations team with the Linux Support Engineer role. Your role would be as our first… https://t.co/miZ5O1ix2y https://t.co/PcyNRm3MEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/Zj1Cr5Nc0S https://t.co/STLsvgJJOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer 16392: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology,… https://t.co/cJlFar5Sax https://t.co/wiCFtLRX2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist ($150-180k) – Python and MATLAB: San Francisco, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today Job Title: Financial Controller Job Location: San Francisco, CA Salary: ($150-180k) Based in San Francisco, CA, we are an exciting medical… https://t.co/GPTA7sxVA3 https://t.co/kTw4jET72e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Senior Technology Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/pN0YfU6zVA https://t.co/otWQJICBCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/r4oavWmfUC https://t.co/iYUrQ3ty9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/SJjC52Vu5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer Angular with python: Full Stack Developer Angular with python Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 04/03/18, Posted Date – 04/03/18 Primary SkillsAngular,Python,Full StackTax TermsC2COverview Full Stack Developer Angular… https://t.co/5HcAUja9Aw https://t.co/buwuv50aUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 16227: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology, Federal… https://t.co/62mXcY1fG2 https://t.co/NNP9RQN6h8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/XAb7ntPKjl https://t.co/44dZxao6gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/6/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/jzkjDFsb4Y https://t.co/Dv0tbgH8lX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer: Los Gatos, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Sales Engineer with experience, please read on! We deliver a SaaS product that enables users to convert the mass of data on websites into structured, machine… https://t.co/6KnUcmoIAO https://t.co/9g0nfmeumL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/Vl0JDF8pkg https://t.co/iGr8A5y6e0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucidworks Fusion/Apache Solr Software Engineer: Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking an Application Developer with strong search engine tools engineering. Candidate will be involved in software design, development, customization and… https://t.co/PmUBAivznP https://t.co/MN5pL4ScC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Engineer Unix/Linux: Job Description Radiance Technologies is an employee-owned company with benefits unmatched by most companies in the Gulf Coast area. Employee ownership, generous 401K and profit sharing, health/dental/ life/vision… https://t.co/DKhXXmSj6v https://t.co/65PGNb9qCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Primary Overview: Boeing Satellite Division in El Segundo is seeking senior software engineers, passionate about space and excited to work in a multi-disciplined, collaborative engineering environment to design, develop and… https://t.co/E6Ci9qK59T https://t.co/Hcx2tSCMXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Flask Developer (Contract, Part-Time): Croscon, a digital product studio, is seeking an experienced senior python developer to join our dedicated backend team focusing on distributed computing solutions &amp; bespoke business systems. You will… https://t.co/KNfMtAhIv7 https://t.co/UBzoA4lEpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer downtown Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsPython DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD from IT Serve Phone – Skype 5 month project in downtown Chicago. Please… https://t.co/agaPbD1PEE https://t.co/2lNBpoBKnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Hey, we’re Article. We’re a digital-first furniture brand that’s re-engineering the furniture experience one sofa at a time. We don’t have brick and mortar stores, so we’re able to deliver remarkable value on beautiful,… https://t.co/dMmrPI9QXi https://t.co/uREHn50qE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python/Django): THE COMPANY Our unique online greeting card and gift system allows everyone to act quickly when prompted to reach out to othersthere has never been an easier way to send a genuine card or heartfelt gift. With just a few… https://t.co/pmHbsGvstI https://t.co/st4aLizHCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: LawnStarter [*************************** is looking for a Senior Backend Engineer to join our growing product development team. LawnStarter is a fast growing startup with an engineering team that prides itself on high energy,… https://t.co/QhfCF7T9ht https://t.co/aMTHDgNswD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/9MTWKfPtFM https://t.co/ykfGTJeY38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/w7F25vk3u9 https://t.co/f8AKOo6E0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred.… https://t.co/lwp4oRUp1D https://t.co/50GMQTq6xV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Relish Works: Relish Works is seeking a Full Stack Software Engineer to support a new innovation hub. Who We Are We are Relish Works, an innovation hub focused on challenging the status quo and pioneering the next evolution… https://t.co/dWdKISbizd https://t.co/TzGZ9PAhKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Healthcare Economics – Minnetonka, MN: We invite you to bring your performance, ideas and innovations to an elite team within a culture built for collaboration. At UnitedHealth Group, we seek individuals who have the ability to drive change,… https://t.co/nH2RahOaxn https://t.co/d5WDM1QP7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with adaptable skills in Object Oriented Programming (Remote): Do you enjoy reading and applying new concepts to constantly improve the quality of your code? Do you value collaborative teams, honest communication, and a teaching culture?… https://t.co/HiHwRn1JwJ https://t.co/o7nhL9La0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit – Technology Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us… https://t.co/zj7c6veSue https://t.co/F10MMqOO3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/raIQbiZAcZ https://t.co/lxPq4wu2gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/5gF9zTaWO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/faeYjwjQGc https://t.co/s9cFTNrMrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Developer – Award Winning Market Leader in the Greater Providence, RI Area: We are looking for passionate individuals who want to be part of a very dynamic and successful team. We offer an entrepreneurial and casual work environment where each… https://t.co/3rocDxo8vJ https://t.co/SgexXuQvnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/4gUrLbSwSd https://t.co/aPjUreeAd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Solutions Engineer/ Architect: Infrastructure Solutions Engineer/ Architect Ref No.: 18-11738 Location: Newark, New Jersey Title: Infrastructure Solutions Engineer/ Architect Location: Newark, NJ Duration: Full Time Job Description: 10+… https://t.co/NyfU4rVL53 https://t.co/BDsHobcqzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/aYx9tSGTUm https://t.co/IyMqIBCpfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/Infrastructure Engineer: About LendKey LendKey is solving a complex challengeto improve lives with lending made simpleby helping financial institutions compete in the digital age and provide a delightful customer experience, while providing… https://t.co/gBFK5Xatqi https://t.co/PRz3dFTeKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting: Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting jobs in 08057 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/FxkI6HYfcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 3: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/CwlXBH4LN8 https://t.co/pt2C39wMfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/b6tX5dzUdV https://t.co/xyl32dLeND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer II – LDAP: Client Reference Code: 214817 Job Scope The Systems Engineer II – LDAP is responsible for assisting design, development, and implementation of enterprise-wide Operations Support Systems (OSS) applications and their associated… https://t.co/sROskILhgJ https://t.co/h0FmYJ1H1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai's Alibabacoin says Alibaba has no monopoly on 'magic' name: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The Dubai-based cryptocurrency firm Alibabacoin Foundation on Tuesday said Alibaba Group Holding Ltd cannot monopolize the "magical" Alibaba name, and asked a U.S.… https://t.co/thsVAVdwfo https://t.co/9fFQtpkCON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Data Engineer: Junior Data Engineer Stonecrop Technologies, a telecom innovator focusing on improving the speed and motions of developing and improving communication networks seeks a savvy Data Engineering Manager to lead our Supply Chain Data &amp;… https://t.co/DiSWrE8lR5 https://t.co/sIQY6mBkv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Linux System Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/FnwUWTclNB https://t.co/L8AIIDDk6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer -PHP – Python: Venice, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – PHP/Zend –… https://t.co/TqWGc41lGG https://t.co/8PIAwyH42s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Ariba, Inc. seeks a Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of specific product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd &amp;… https://t.co/wQthfNFEsf https://t.co/CFB2QCZG2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC – Senior Backend Engineer: Located In Kimball Junction, Park City – 20 minutes from Salt Lake! Banjo, a leader in Artificial Intelligence, is looking for a senior platform engineer in our Park City office. Banjo is changing the way the world… https://t.co/57ODY1EdEm https://t.co/UMZP3OCoS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/HDeUXY2uuA https://t.co/5SyOCFcIgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/AWA0kcEqTn https://t.co/PpMAjMfnj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Unity AR/VR Developer: Banjo is looking for a full-time Senior Unity Augmented Reality and Virtual Reality Developer to join the team immediately. This is a great role for an experienced developer who wants to build useful tools and engaging… https://t.co/jK3dFfrwr4 https://t.co/hxsdHSq33e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/BHWPrY7Tts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Senior Technology Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/DgoPIOLRe9 https://t.co/TfLMkB42GC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/VXF2Gmb8yq https://t.co/RUpfOmb5uN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Python, R, SaaS): Redwood City, CA Full-time $140k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Due to massive growth and demand for our services, we are currently… https://t.co/eGvQ8oF9Tr https://t.co/eDPnm5vWg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/tStHG5a3TF https://t.co/wqhP9qYrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal – Analytics Delivery: Role Principal – Analytics Delivery Auto req ID 29889BR Domain Analytics Skillset PYTHON , Country USA State / Region / Province Washington Work Location Redmond, WA Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys– DNA– Principal… https://t.co/Zc2XlHwciM https://t.co/3nJR78fwJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Redwood City, CA Full-time $90k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Data Analyst with experience working with Python and SQL, please read on! Located in beautiful Redwood City, we are seeking a Data Analyst to join our team! We offer online… https://t.co/ETBNI9ovVF https://t.co/wyksoN80cI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/2zLNp6Ukfa https://t.co/Qui8YX1csm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Engineer 3: ENGINEERING Applications Engineer 3 sought by ASML in San Jose, CA, to support leading customer with defect inspection &amp; control challenges, driving technical team to integrate solutions to meet customer reqmts by identifying… https://t.co/iBJTLC3l1N https://t.co/gT8UNaESSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Support: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/CfGzoFmUFb https://t.co/JFkM2YlpXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/j8oiSGfChZ https://t.co/vxr7pj6TPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Tulsa, Oklahoma – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsPython,DjangoTax TermsC2COverview Python Developer 6+ Months Tulsa, OK Required Skills : * Python, Django and angular or… https://t.co/VTl3eWAft4 https://t.co/m2SUmaFg3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/ulAQ7KwPJK https://t.co/dUhIMsk2gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/AGc1tcthXv https://t.co/Jk8XrIY7t9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>