<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Interpreting Institutional Fit: Urbanization, Development, and China’s “Land-Lost” http://t.co/H6M8Y0Afki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Impact of Philippines’ Conditional Cash Transfer Program on Consumption http://t.co/iSsvvYDLWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An approximation to the Informal-formal wage gap in Colombia 2008-2012 http://t.co/leDuWVEANb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Land constraints and agricultural intensification in Ethiopia: A village-level analysis of high-potenti... http://t.co/ztaXYk9Z81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does internal migration improve overall well-being in Ethiopia?: http://t.co/V8Tzbp28ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Links between tenure security and food security: Evidence from Ethiopia: http://t.co/h9Vy887kr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income Shocks and HIV in Africa http://t.co/MrzgMWhfQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Social Assistance and Informality: Examining the link in Colombia http://t.co/Kp8fXG7pbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Reversal of Gender Gaps in Child Development: Evidence from Young Children in India http://t.co/nVhi3RWyEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: What do people actually learn from public health education campaigns? Incorrect inferences about male c... http://t.co/8irFBcUvL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Regime Change, Democracy, and Growth http://t.co/xDZtGaQ5MG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Having a Son Promotes Clean Cooking Fuel Use in Urban India: Women’s Status and Son Preference http://t.co/K5xuUmXck1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Why Is Polygyny More Prevalent in Western Africa? An African Slave Trade Perspective http://t.co/TY86vA2WBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Who you train matters: Identifying combined effects of financial education on migrant households Error]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Electoral Rules and the Quality of Politicians: Theory and Evidence from a Field Experiment in Afghanist... http://t.co/bA6hQ0xMtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: A Refinement of the Relationship between Economic Growth and Income Inequality in Developing Countries http://t.co/Z78RgxkjQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The economic spillovers from resource extraction: a partial resource blessing at the subnational level? http://t.co/eMxQngP5YW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income Inequality and Health: Evidence from Developed and Developing Countries http://t.co/Dz0tKTaktg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income Inequality, Trade and Financial Openness http://t.co/3GmWOHNr4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittances and Household Expenditure Behaviour in Senegal http://t.co/TI5F1N4sUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Conditional Cash Transfers, Civil Conflict and Insurgent Influence: Experimental Evidence from the Philippines http://t.co/1giwzlivU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Disease and Development: A Reply to Bloom, Canning, and Fink -- by Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson http://t.co/kHRQBw8NST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Job Displacement and the Duration of Joblessness: The Role of Spatial Mismatch -- by Fredrik Andersson, ... http://t.co/bIt4Nw54si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Editorial Advisory Board Error]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Editorial Advisory Board http://t.co/e3i5tUb4Jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Public Health Insurance, Labor Supply, and Employment Lock http://t.co/6TtFaijVgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Effects of Remittances on Poverty at the Household Level in Bolivia: A Propensity Score Matching Approach http://t.co/4FRlGRX8EU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Microcredit and women's empowerment in Bangladesh: a structural equation model for categorical observed... http://t.co/UlMn9nTJUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Welfare Impact of Land Redistribution: Evidence from a Quasi-Experimental Initiative in Malawi http://t.co/XN76kPw1Ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Globalization and Child Health in Developing Countries: The Role of Democracy http://t.co/UAI5ykzKfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The informal labour market in India : transitory or permanent employment for migrants? http://t.co/upYXiuCyTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Community-Based Development and Aggregate Shocks in Developing Countries: The Experience of an NGO in Pakistan http://t.co/MqpMuLy2qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income Distributions, Inequality, and Poverty in Asia, 1992–2010 http://t.co/J2zx2MclIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of seasonality-adjusted flexible microcredit on repayment and food consumption : experimental ev... http://t.co/dGTr429dDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: National Institutions and Subnational Development in Africa http://t.co/NWIqXzIchT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: International Labor Mobility and Child Work in Developing Countries http://t.co/JRYKGVVMER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Ethnic Inequality http://t.co/OYOqYmARiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Long-Term Barriers to Economic Development http://t.co/SBvWbw9xdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Medieval Universities, Legal Institutions, and the Commercial Revolution http://t.co/GvT3WU14t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPubE: U.S. war costs: Two parts temporary, one part permanent http://t.co/xa1rUY7FfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: How Do Providers Respond to Public Health Insurance Expansions?  Evidence from Adult Medicaid Dental Ben... http://t.co/t7XIKkO8vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Assessing individuals' deprivation in a multidimensional framework http://t.co/Bt20RmBstd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: From tradition to modernity: Economic growth in a small world http://t.co/IpUteEZRTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Endogenous coresidence and program inciden South Africa's Old Age Pension http://t.co/B0FHrswucb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Who you train matters: Identifying combined effects of financial education on migrant households http://t.co/mTT4j3wXbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Mass media and public education: The effects of access to community radio in Benin http://t.co/1vV4vYNS6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPubE: U.S. war costs: Two parts temporary, one part permanent http://t.co/jj80O4FDjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPubE: Taxation and the Long Run Allocation of Labor: Theory and Danish Evidence http://t.co/UpVATHpzos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Mass media and public education: The effects of access to community radio in Benin http://t.co/Fd4lWXlrRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Weather and Child Health in Rural Nigeria http://t.co/BPMSCsHV11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Agricultural Decisions after Relaxing Credit and Risk Constraints http://t.co/wrQoXd0KJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: From tradition to modernity: Economic growth in a small world http://t.co/SHl4Hf5ui2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Endogenous coresidence and program inciden South Africa's Old Age Pension http://t.co/qp4rgawSBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Who you train matters: Identifying combined effects of financial education on migrant households http://t.co/RLOqNEi4oQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Corrigendum to “Land tenure and investment incentives: Evidence from West Africa” [J. Dev. Econ. 95(2), (... http://t.co/i2YJEZlJYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Assessing individuals' deprivation in a multidimensional framework http://t.co/SFBzF0Blxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Regional Favoritism http://t.co/xXuNDgSfcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: The Agricultural Productivity Gap http://t.co/Jx3VMFcThL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Colonial Institutions, Commodity Booms, and the Diffusion of Elementary Education in Brazil, 1889-1930 -... http://t.co/UlGgIbWZQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of an adolescent girls employment program : the EPAG project in Liberia http://t.co/iUdEle8Oeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Informal Sector Wage Gap: New Evidence using Quantile Estimations on Panel Data http://t.co/RAtnqCCuy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Foreign aid and mobilization of growth factors in sub-Saharan Africa http://t.co/f35clGxW4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Life-Satisfaction in Urban Ethiopia: The Role of Relative Poverty and Unobserved Heterogeneity http://t.co/6rTWyrmFEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of sectoral allocation of foreign aid on gender equity and human development http://t.co/blO9BDbaIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Post-harvest loss in Sub-Saharan Africa -- what do farmers say ? http://t.co/9JfoKGHOnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: International Labor Mobility and Child Work in Developing Countries http://t.co/sweeHAGaKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Poverty Persistence and Intra-Household Heterogeneity in Occupations: Some Evidence from Ethiopia http://t.co/qOCzQhxsVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Buffer Stock Savings by Portfolio Adjustment: Evidence from Rural India http://t.co/kCRARwFC7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Differential Impacts of Foreign Capital and Remittance Inflows on Domestic Savings in the Developing Co... http://t.co/1BAe5w7wJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: School Resources, Behavioral Responses and School Quality: Short-Term Experimental Evidence from Niger http://t.co/WDQukFFf0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Assessing Foreign Aid.s Long-Run Contribution to Growth in Development http://t.co/FqSskgeDpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Learning the hard way? Adapting to climate risk in Tanzania http://t.co/VosJGNiaV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Poverty and Crime: Evidence from Rainfall and Trade Shocks in India http://t.co/Wp47zfvqgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do poverty traps exist ? http://t.co/mNmNs0BxIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Cash transfers and child labor http://t.co/6fosT3JjQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Savings in Transnational Households: A Field Experiment among Migrants from El Salvador http://t.co/mcFsnlKndd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Women’s Empowerment and Prevalence of Stunted and Underweight Children in Rural India http://t.co/gHeTNfQLoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Human Capital Effects of Anti-Poverty Programs: Evidence from a Randomized Housing Voucher Lottery http://t.co/xQXuHGlAK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Selective Schooling Systems Increase Inequality http://t.co/I9w2g3jD9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Effects of Access to Health Insurance for Informally Employed Individuals in Peru http://t.co/YW3ZudPoTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Informality and Development http://t.co/h7z68egnpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Under-investment in a Profitable Technology: The Case of Seasonal Migration in Bangladesh http://t.co/GJzA5bdUqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Estimating the Impact of Microcredit on Those Who Take It Up: Evidence from a Randomized Experiment in M... http://t.co/nwyg6s4bes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: An African Growth Miracle? -- by Dani Rodrik http://t.co/QccpyMuwYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPubE: The impact of a carbon tax on manufacturing: Evidence from microdata http://t.co/Nvv1eImlts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Informal economy and the World Bank http://t.co/SHbWDgtnNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: What a difference a state makes : health reform in Andhra Pradesh http://t.co/VzDzDHESCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Migration, Education and the Gender Gap in Labour Force Participation http://t.co/j14Op0TlWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Economic Growth Reduce Corruption? Theory and Evidence from Vietnam http://t.co/Thsp0h6OoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: "To Have and Have Not": Migration, Remittances, Poverty and Inequality in Algeria http://t.co/sXdZiv3UTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Community mobilization around social dilemmas: evidence from lab experiments in rural Mali http://t.co/gEfzDEKrcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Return Migration, Self-Selection and Entrepreneurship in Mozambique http://t.co/vN7627K6Xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: China's Impact on Africa - the Role of Trade, FDI and Aid http://t.co/o8Kr4rbg5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Cash transfers and temptation goods : a review of global evidence http://t.co/0KuxNA50QG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Microcredit Impacts: Evidence from a Randomized Microcredit Program Placement Experiment by Compartamos Banco http://t.co/nnE3LdPLkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Long-Term Barriers to Economic Development http://t.co/XaNYrSLKo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Winners and Losers among a Refugee-Hosting Population http://t.co/UtDENVWbli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Evaluating Aid for Trade: A Survey of Recent Studies http://t.co/c35ViwjIqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Husbands and Wives. The powers and perils of participation in a microfinance cooperative for female ent... http://t.co/pD7ipljfBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Housing and urbanization in Africa : unleashing a formal market process http://t.co/iKsdigXs6L]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>