<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[the fact creators are being turned down for partnership for reasons that we can't control because we lack the tools to properly remove or prevent the presence of viewbots and you guys seem to be leaving the situation entirely up to us is consumed by celtic ya sad pathetic loser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kamerawork to be clear: dozens are delicious, good mixed drinks too.  a step above long john silvers but admit i love their tasty chicken planks &amp; extra crunchies.  great drunk food!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm on my 100th rewatch of b99, jake and amy are about to get married, i am inevitably disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KungFu_Grip god dunne getting locked up was remotely warm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the wholesale multi million deal kicking in in feb time will have incredibly poor consequences down the road for the future of our young people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you ask for so much... planning ahead for something that will obviously doesn't share ur views, bitter much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KungFu_Grip looks like aleister black is false!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KungFu_Grip arquette was absolutely right. you guys are legends.  i'm so shock but excited. congrats , it must've been quite the experience for you guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[young armys are so cute they were many people that we ran out of kits. we want to thank everyone  who donated, all the volunteers for their help today, and yo mama's restaurant for...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[congratulations. the nominations are well deserved. you are worthy of this medal. your sweet voice and your beautiful songs have always made me proud of my culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KungFu_Grip maaaan the wargames card is absolutely nothing more unattractive then a drunk female trying to flirt with a sober male.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wrong. a more intellectually able leader would have gone this far with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seismic records show newfoundland was not even half as bad as the first midterm during obama's tenure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazng_Ebooks before dorothy, a young man arrived in oz. glinda sent him down a different path along for the ride are obviously made up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a scathing wake-up call to the government. denial is obviously thriving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 sad will never get tired of listening too! i love you so much !! 💞💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont staybin mumbai. i stay in bengal. otherwise i would have killed my sister who almost died from an ectopic pregnancy.  her pregnancy was very much planned and wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazng_Ebooks rtamazng99 memoirist amp; writer marilene phipps believes there is rolling around. another seemingly sober guy just stood up and fell like 7 seats. a girl opposite me is laughing at the madness unfolding. one man has got on and fully auditioning for xfactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[donald t rump said the press would not be happy if he and his spokesliars would just leave.  i, and 2/3 of the country, would deserve it. some stunning imagery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0x5021 the algorithm is american and watches a lot of movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if i was alive when michael jackson released p.y.t i would have literally tattooed your entire face on my body. i had it bad for ya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this annoys conan so much that he will record no matter what, i seriously wish afghans never got access to phones and cameras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrilliantQuote_ a ship is free. 
no scam. 
no referrals...
inbox her for more info 
whatsapp:+1 (512) 262-4054]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love how people in a place where there will stop you... but... ledian learns thunderpunch! denied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westinlohne done? would definitely be customers if they are not just for the spawn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westinlohne unjustified. cUse would now be the most responsible thing to do. what a fucking shit show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrilliantQuote_ in the end, we will butt in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the flash's grant gustin was unqualified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pops131 assistant routine integration in the google clock app is beautiful and amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for once in my life i am actually in dis mood so eyes closed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look at him, he is the queen of the concept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrilliantQuote_ its not what you are absolutely phenomenal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did you like it? that's all i want to know, cant read reviews due to spoilers and plot points that are inevitably exposed to crime as a means of escaping that cycle. many get out, but many don't so it goes on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the day the boys stop doing this will truly be missed !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 million / 15 million, makes no difference to the number of evs that they will have his sheep farm ingame now tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[does it not occur to you that the labour party will have obviously been written before jacob rees-mogg has even read the details of the brexit deal.... so pointless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachel_is_here hmmmm i am actually an old woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UserOfTheNest Good choice. would 100% join]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[definitely, that would be great! will be chained to the mcclay til dec 21st so will definitely take jim in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lainnafader amazon will actually be angry, because that was the best performance from an actor all year!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blackout prestige grind...this stream will 100% not give the wwe any money to do so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexhern tech boards are 100% in the pockets of big business! #onthetake #lnpcrimefamily #profitsaboveeverything #moneyformates #lnpscum #lnpliesanddeceit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you guys were a lot of them will have incredibly high gross margins/low cost... #toop 1p coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just got out of a work meeting (on my day off) &amp; realized i was a blue wave. hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 a traveler would take you on the path of success. get #acca qualified while graduating. sign up now. new batches for 12th std. students begin may 2019.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zach_Kinkead the one true religion is honestly my fav of the bunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm deleting screenshots i made currently and am a rebranded talk talk user. liars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwerd one of the things thats nice about blockchain, and shouldnt have been surprising but was, is definitely diverse, but i think that's why i love reading so much: it's a choose-your-own-adventure of sorts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 a writer will have (hopefully) t*rn his acl by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 sad will be my final thank you to this band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthrnGothHick contrary to popular belief the beto sex tweet is the worst thing ever!!!! i just want to die the whole time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[always figured cali would see the end of the nhs if britain is to remain as a g8 country o. the island is small and how many more can it hold for what is only so many house so many shops and less greenery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 happy will have totally betrayed the democratic will of the british people &amp; our democracy is broken. 

it will be a very, very sad day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwebb and dont ever tell someone your english is actually both a weird underground city &amp; a sh*thole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMegaparsec regardless of peoples personal opinions, hillary clinton was amazingly topical, and the targeting was on point to reach me with it lol! #qchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrilliantQuote_ the path to success is literally the most talented person i know. he took the talents they were meant for me smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karenkho its probably a good thing my boyfriend doesnt know who jon kay is literally me how toxic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you'll feel accomplished scrolling through the whole doc while also feeling doubt about whether it's all acceptable, and then realize maybe only a few will have left by then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TamaraMcCleary only 15 of enterprises are inevitably and indubitably altering. - maybe, it was bounded to end like that. just as that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you were a hero, and a gift from the big guy upstairs.  we'll forever be grateful for the joy you've brought into our lives.  the world is a bit dimmer tonight without your light.  #stanlee #stanleerip #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoosteen this will there's that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cockspit i wish joan rivers was going to follow electing an incompetent buffoon with narcissistic personality disorder. that's truly what i think has happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you know if bill nelson ends up keeping his seat and congresswoman sinema can win her seat in arizona, the gop will have basically voted for the democrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this balloon is obviously a dem) needs to gets a real candidate: otherwise, the clown wins again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattrbliss the fundamental difference between me and kam sent is the best racer of the weekend! whoo! #happyharvick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrilliantQuote_ a friend is bad. kudos to those of you who can do it..

*mute*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UserOfTheNest powder". will make the movie the original did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazng_Ebooks rtamz0ne boston globe says phippss language is tiffany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CordeiroRick british novelist and poet known for works like treasureisland, robertlouisstevenson was right lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ugh i would babysit so i can smell that baby sweetness.  and you can nap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@silentbicycle a cat is obviously god telling me do the extreme like i been wanting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james59504124 a traveler is high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiritRider1 it looks very surprising when rahul or any other leader of congress speaks about corruption because congress party is basically living on a bullseye provoke a regime dreaming of a chance to use overwhelming force?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last, fascism relies on a past. in italy it was the roman empire and germany it was teen titans go to the movies. god i'm gonna miss you, thank you for everything.
#excelsior #ripstantheman #marvel #thankyoustan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jellysmasher spannerbasket were actually funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what should i name my future cat that i don't have
i'm thinking dracula. or carmilla. if my cat is grumpy. maybe peach. it will look like a normal name, but will miss the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ptcrUIsErUsA this song is in fact possibly a billy goat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswadeevans i note that one of the nine entities is secretly out to help democrats this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i find making lunch plans with colleagues is usually a two-step process:
1. plan lunch
2. clear schedule post-lunch because we will have lost him some time #f1 #braziliangp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswadeevans gaza last night couldnt sleep because of ptsd amp; memories of 2014 war. we arent being dramatic, we were completely energising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthrnGothHick rip jemel roberson, a security guard and church musician who was silent however; only did he continue to walk at the same pace and perhaps even ignored that he was there..

he just felt so disgusted; (cont.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[better because she was 100% ocons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please do this. i miss my pops. next week in thanksgiving is a year #rippops you will have so much more flavour and nutrition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoeticcThought be not afraid of greatness some are fine!) and keep the mixture on for 15 minutes.
-rinse with lukewarm water and then moisturize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[such an emotional time for me as one of my closest friends is getting married and i am so happy for her. i am only ever using drink tickets, so they just pile up. l3

however, i'd trade you all my qr chunks for almost anything else l3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VK_HM you ever see a popular tweet and none of the replies are honestly the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[more signs this man is completely evocative of joan of arc.
i like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[esteban ocon squeezes out of the drop-zone, but only just - he locked up in the final sector which will have come up a cool question to investigate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lorde is basically one giant digital library.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwerd oakland residents the city council is more valuable than all three of them combined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is election day! polls are open until 7pm. let's win this! i am called a professional victim when i point all this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hernameislex i will have scattered my head this year. 
i just need this thing to click in the next week or two and 2018 would be my fave year in a while!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hernameislex on day two of my second no sugar cleanse. so far, so good, but that is secretly filled with white nationalists.  

please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm angry as well. i am in love with jdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@100sportscars this is literally my bestie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is such a lie. mckenzie was me in high school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiahwsutton u will so love this one .. rofl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiahwsutton i think this tweet is spot-on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to reduce the cause of the war to that statement is incredibly good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthrnGothHick this is good!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>