<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/5d5IF38IBv https://t.co/1pwW434QcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Scientist-Risk Segmentation: The Cigna Information Management &amp; Analytics (CIMA) unit is searching for an energetic and driven data scientist to bring best in class analytics to the Underwriting and Actuarial organizations. The Data Scientist… https://t.co/FrCzGlw5Nm https://t.co/UvwGgRX3jx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cluster PMO – Project Manager Coordinator: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2018-01-11 Functional area Planning &amp; Logistics Background Others – Non Technical Reference US03628 Recruiter: Kamille Garcia… https://t.co/o3PdQlKRXc https://t.co/iNk3fNHh9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Coach: Category: Project Management City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-0078 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI is looking for a DevOps Coach… https://t.co/biTI7AP9G4 https://t.co/KzcS5rrzzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Account Manager – Construction Products: Connecticut, CT Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Outside Account Manager – Construction Products with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a… https://t.co/PfyKXvUxcg https://t.co/gB23KytQsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Hardware Engineer: Stratford Solutions is assisting their client with finding aComputer Hardware Engineerto add to their team located in Stamford, CT. This is a full-time, direct hire, W2 position with our client; cannot accept 3rd party… https://t.co/Q6v2GUGg4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1804 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position Description:… https://t.co/bgYAIDiAO3 https://t.co/yVjAoPLmqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Scientist-Risk Segmentation: The Cigna Information Management &amp; Analytics (CIMA) unit is searching for an energetic and driven data scientist to bring best in class analytics to the Underwriting and Actuarial organizations. The Data Scientist… https://t.co/2xc3GzqZbI https://t.co/oolt0z44EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/xbWpZ77B3g https://t.co/NlDtf41YDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: This position is responsible for continuous improvement, implementing, testing and ongoing support of IT NAM infrastructure Services for North America. This includes Network, UC and Workplace, Site Infrastructure, Security and manage… https://t.co/TYjfJcoana https://t.co/3MSGiVKry5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudera (Hadoop) Administrator with Unix Experience: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J1017-0813 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global… https://t.co/TMUmwVhETI https://t.co/i7Sbs417YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile SAFe Scrum Master: Category: Development/Engineering City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0218-0592 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program… https://t.co/nu6EOPNdIY https://t.co/kRMlc3IWvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience (2930): OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who… https://t.co/jO9EGoT7pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Are you an A+ Software BEAST at the top of your game? Do you thrive on the challenge of being deep in development 85-90% of the day? If youre a self-starter that can take a project and deliver, then this opportunity may be right for… https://t.co/lVBKqOYUZH https://t.co/JP7gXdo5zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/Itj86D0GLh https://t.co/mTdRW5gmk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-2017 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position… https://t.co/bqpN7jmtVj https://t.co/cm8FnMivLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls and Automation Engineer: Job Description: This position requires an individual with introductory level engineering experience in the manufacturing industry. He or she will provide engineering support for continuous improvement Overall Equipment… https://t.co/vV4IQrX7do https://t.co/qnwXcTQvzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/a7LAwxunsk https://t.co/H62ZgEsZRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/0kqTEIRAk6 https://t.co/iug3ojPWJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/4e651gVGEx https://t.co/RPk36CXJU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Site Transformation: Position Project Manager – Site Transformation Location Bloomfield, CT 06002 Duration 6 months or longer Pay Rate $50.00 – $60.00 DOE Start Date ASAP Project Manager JOB DESCRIPTION Position will manage the IT… https://t.co/Fe6D3S2zU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Software Engineer: We have an immediate opening for an Associate Software Engineer who will be assisting in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and… https://t.co/rEbpks4tiW https://t.co/Y5ikAIFFqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grains and Oilseeds Data Analyst: The purpose of this role is to support the global oilseeds and grains research teams to provide timely information and accurate estimates of US and Global supply and demand estimates to the traders. Specifically, it aims… https://t.co/XV59gwDnDc https://t.co/ElHSUhAN5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Integration Architect: Responsibilities and Duties: * This position will be a member of the development team who will design, develop, and blog about integrations between client and monitoring products, ticketing systems, automation systems and… https://t.co/Vm6eyITS2R https://t.co/wtzWLJh2k3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1804 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position Description:… https://t.co/wMlboMRlAQ https://t.co/OUlArUM1tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F135 Technical Graphics Developer/Illustrator: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62073BR Date posted 03/05/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/HrAfaKIRCL https://t.co/mBlaoaAfrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Full Stack: About the position *********************************************************** Developer/ZP0007 The Digital Team within Prudential’s Retirement division is looking for talented individuals to help drive Business value. If… https://t.co/UARiknU30h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager: Position: SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 554 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for an energetic, hands-on SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: –… https://t.co/NWtp7UuC6w https://t.co/3nkS9JP9xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Developer: Welcome to Mitchell Stores We’re Mitchells Stores, a family-owned luxury retailer renowned for top-of-its-class customer service, with stores in San Francisco, Palo Alto, Portland, Seattle, Greenwich, and Westport, Connecticut,… https://t.co/f0YKleaxtE https://t.co/0a1g10HUnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer / Data Analytics Specialist, ASC: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 63521BR Date posted 03/27/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/gNm0vSCVi6 https://t.co/7BnTWEfMKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EQ Business Systems Analyst: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62466BR Date posted 03/07/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Using Agile and User Centric methodologies collaborate with others to capture enhancements and efficiency… https://t.co/KacUaOMtJX https://t.co/AM0Ixz1NP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services: JOB REQUISITION New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services LOCATION CT NEW HAVEN JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within RHI, combining the best of… https://t.co/DscKJ8qrud https://t.co/kpvu7n88Yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudera (Hadoop) Administrator with Unix Experience: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J1017-0813 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global… https://t.co/rpfF3Q0WD0 https://t.co/6TnsLkVuVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Developer: This position is a full lifecycle development opportunity, allowing the employee to participate in system design, development, documentation, testing, implementation, deployment, integration and support of all necessary… https://t.co/AiW6PTUsvA https://t.co/20cHtLtyys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Quality Assurance Engineer: Hologic, Inc. is a leading developer, manufacturer and supplier of premium molecular diagnostic products and services that are used to diagnose human diseases, screen donated human blood and to aid in biomedical… https://t.co/uWYdnYu18d https://t.co/9ISO0ASPU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Mobile Platforms (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/Tvsh6gpO23 https://t.co/jeBf0jpiVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/5KXJRrtbln https://t.co/M6yWvrfNx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Intern: Title Java Developer – Intern Requisition Number 18-0014 Post Date 2/27/2018 City Madison,WI;Eau Claire,WI;Aberdeen,SD;Rocky Hill,CT Description Great Lakes Educational Loan Services, Inc. is seeking Java Application Developer… https://t.co/vn0AgbkJc0 https://t.co/J6wG8Y1grY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laboratory Relocation Project Manager: Date Posted: 30/Mar/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: Laboratory Relocation Project Manager Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science,… https://t.co/GtqtNqBIqX https://t.co/SNypPDZV30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Software Engineer: We are looking for a mid to senior level iOS Software Engineer for a financial services company with exceptional and dedicated teams, with cutting edge technology, and a startup energetic atmosphere, with a solid public company… https://t.co/6VxV4c3Di2 https://t.co/05Vt4KLJGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/hZ9ZNNEnQP https://t.co/ZLVzqXur6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER Each day, the engineering team is working to meet some of the most unique and exciting global challenges. To maintain our role as a global leader, we continue to seek talented, ambitious individuals to… https://t.co/2pEO9j5bIu https://t.co/XAzOzvoouN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-2017 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position… https://t.co/31t1H3ZE4g https://t.co/NjDEY1iKLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Are you an A+ Software BEAST at the top of your game? Do you thrive on the challenge of being deep in development 85-90% of the day? If youre a self-starter that can take a project and deliver, then this opportunity may be right for… https://t.co/2pGJKQ6c6F https://t.co/pb9ReSmzsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – US: Role Senior Project Manager – US Auto req ID 30020BR Domain Energy Skillset Project Portfolio Management , Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Hartford, CT Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys –… https://t.co/Wc3rDaCIqp https://t.co/oFlXv2H0jY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Integration Architect: Responsibilities and Duties: * This position will be a member of the development team who will design, develop, and blog about integrations between client and monitoring products, ticketing systems, automation systems and… https://t.co/giRzUwjFVS https://t.co/7BG4vnirhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesys Developer: Position Details &amp; Requirements: Job Title: Genesys Developer Location: Hartford, CT, United States Duration: 10 months * Genesys Contact Center Implementation – Minimum 8 years of experience in Genesys Contact Center Framework. *… https://t.co/IVsfX0f4uV https://t.co/WwoJt2Kruj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DPHM, ATG Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62177BR Date posted 03/02/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Pratt &amp; Whitney, a recognized leading producer of the world’s most advanced jet engines, is looking for… https://t.co/2VcPKaK2lL https://t.co/SzN55Drszf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk / Service Desk Specialist (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/GzvS6sdIxn https://t.co/EinR1mYxzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operations Analyst: Senior Operations Analyst Location US-CT-Westport Posted Date 5 days ago (3/15/2018 1:42 PM) Job ID 2017-35534 # Positions 1 Category Information Technology Overview: About the Position: Title: Senior Operations Analyst Reports… https://t.co/FCNjwlb3YI https://t.co/FvjbTIn7jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager -IT: 1 Year Contract We are actively seeking an IT Technical Project Manager. The IT Technical Project Manager will be responsible for planning and managing company resources to develop and launch innovative technological solutions. This… https://t.co/jnpqsl1Gzo https://t.co/IehnGcxJnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Belimo isa globalleader in the development, production andmarketing ofactuator solutions for controlling heating, ventilation and air conditioning systems. Actuators, control valves and sensors make up the company’s core business.… https://t.co/5NiYKdpsMl https://t.co/y0gkmYoDtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29769BR Domain Utilities Skillset Sharepoint Application Migration , Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Berlin, CT Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys – MSWTPU –… https://t.co/vuxGlRrkn3 https://t.co/txVCcEe2kK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Systems Administrator: Careers Center | Junior Systems Administrator Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/yIfY5Mk2MS https://t.co/YRFdDKEddQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Full Stack: About the position *********************************************************** Developer/ZP0007 The Digital Team within Prudential’s Retirement division is looking for talented individuals to help drive Business value. If… https://t.co/xBSnnbYEYs https://t.co/4F36yYmWAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Manager: Are you the best in your field and always excited about creating solutions that protect our information and privacy? Our client is an industry leader in electronic brokerage whose platform provides clients access to more than 100… https://t.co/4b31SlGIVT https://t.co/ry1LVBTnTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- HCADM Technology Lead – US .Net/SQL – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/f9O2RB6eIT https://t.co/ujNhRsBuzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Java Architect with Akka Play Framework | Stamford, CT | 6+ months: Title: Java Architect w/ Play Akka Framework Location: Stamford, CT Duration: 6+ Months Years of experience: 10+ years Requirements Java Architect with recent years of experience in… https://t.co/srts51lAWV https://t.co/P7bDXSRGDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Systems Administrator: Careers Center | Junior Systems Administrator Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/DxfdbnIkv8 https://t.co/u91X2RIsTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudera (Hadoop) Administrator with Unix Experience: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J1017-0813 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global… https://t.co/IW1d5BOfLN https://t.co/Hghffsex0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Careers – Reality Interactive Looking for a great place to work? See our Careers How can we help? ************ – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog Love where you work. Great… https://t.co/R8g7lCig2K https://t.co/RYXdudGnlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Mobile Platforms (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/QcITV12yjV https://t.co/9xdOdJ0RmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls and Automation Engineer: Job Description: This position requires an individual with introductory level engineering experience in the manufacturing industry. He or she will provide engineering support for continuous improvement Overall Equipment… https://t.co/gAsPi5ukAd https://t.co/7GN5eDw64a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-0767 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: Want to leverage your… https://t.co/evJ4pSig86 https://t.co/YfnLK62M56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesys Developer: Position Details &amp; Requirements: Job Title: Genesys Developer Location: Hartford, CT, United States Duration: 10 months * Genesys Contact Center Implementation – Minimum 8 years of experience in Genesys Contact Center Framework. *… https://t.co/yhsu3HWlQo https://t.co/hooEBlLVz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Commerce Cloud Developer – Consultant: Salesforce Commerce Cloud Developer – Consultant | BrandShopContact Us BrandShop Digital Commerce Contact Us – About Us – What We Do – Commerce Technology – Marketing Services – Operations – Payments &amp;… https://t.co/RiQamJwJkG https://t.co/lBCbAhFx2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: HRP Associates, Inc. is seeking a Senior Project Manager with 15-20 years of experience to join our corporate office in Farmington, CT. A variety of challenging assignments will be offered to successful candidates, including… https://t.co/fCR2JdLjTj https://t.co/uuSECnjL4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1804 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position Description:… https://t.co/IktaatGfeA https://t.co/0RH6wQtOpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Category: Project Management City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-0579 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position… https://t.co/S53tXLtUdq https://t.co/2j059LVf3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: This position is responsible for continuous improvement, implementing, testing and ongoing support of IT NAM infrastructure Services for North America. This includes Network, UC and Workplace, Site Infrastructure, Security and manage… https://t.co/F3DfJw3qzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Careers – Reality Interactive Looking for a great place to work? See our Careers How can we help? ************ – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog Love where you work. Great jobs… https://t.co/CKOEJups40 https://t.co/ydG9vxTqVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports users the usage of business… https://t.co/Cq82Te9mT5 https://t.co/iJOwsqVloT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys MSWTPU Technology Lead – US SharePoint Application Migration – Berlin, CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for… https://t.co/nZiJ2qyQRf https://t.co/EuW5qPumHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer / Data Analytics Specialist, ASC: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 63521BR Date posted 03/27/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/QWdY7IbUzA https://t.co/6mKVdFGSb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Analyst: The qualified applicant should have experience creating and executing test plans, specifically for web based applications. The purposes of the internal applications are to assist in managing finances, class planning… https://t.co/KmGWqN8daI https://t.co/G8xGkeBX9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Software Engineer: We are looking for a mid to senior level iOS Software Engineer for a financial services company with exceptional and dedicated teams, with cutting edge technology, and a startup energetic atmosphere, with a solid public company… https://t.co/HqmOlZP07u https://t.co/5Ng5IyZCOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: The Big Willow is radically improving how sellers find buyers. Would you like working at The Big Willow? Answer that by peering inside our DNA (some people call it core values): * Be ambitious and audacious * Value… https://t.co/lfhEhEoYQN https://t.co/mdeiRlqMYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (Temp): Belimo is a global leader in the development, production and marketing of actuator solutions for controlling heating, ventilation and air conditioning systems. Actuators, control valves and sensors make up the company’s… https://t.co/9MjhmYyIvI https://t.co/TTyLjJEPr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- HCADM Technology Lead – US .Net/SQL – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/grQzEkoJ8n https://t.co/t6sNcoSTlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – US: Role Test Analyst – US Auto req ID 29487BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Automated Testing Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Hartford, CT… https://t.co/v10kb7HKVM https://t.co/XQ56oxVkFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer/Tech Lead: Category: Development/Engineering City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0218-1524 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: The resource will work in… https://t.co/QCG98aB73J https://t.co/usckT8TO5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/o7f3A8Zceo https://t.co/JH7cMnAMG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER Each day, the engineering team is working to meet some of the most unique and exciting global challenges. To maintain our role as a global leader, we continue to seek talented, ambitious individuals to… https://t.co/8EK8KFD45Y https://t.co/MewajCjmKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/WXt21R28P2 https://t.co/Cb1LGhVEcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer: Careers – Reality Interactive Looking for a great place to work? See our Careers How can we help? ************ – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog – Work – Services – – About – Contact – Blog Love where you work. Great jobs… https://t.co/2H5AMYSeUl https://t.co/onjuzkugQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29769BR Domain Utilities Skillset Sharepoint Application Migration , Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Berlin, CT Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys – MSWTPU –… https://t.co/TZ3NFObflV https://t.co/VUUFwJGUBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Site Reliability Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors,… https://t.co/yEE9zSwvWd https://t.co/LDTfg3PCAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk / Service Desk Specialist (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/lrtHO3fVoe https://t.co/YB2mp217cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Site Transformation: Position Project Manager – Site Transformation Location Bloomfield, CT 06002 Duration 6 months or longer Pay Rate $50.00 – $60.00 DOE Start Date ASAP Project Manager JOB DESCRIPTION Position will manage the IT… https://t.co/F4UB2C4RF7 https://t.co/65cDKQitqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DPHM, ATG Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62177BR Date posted 03/02/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Pratt &amp; Whitney, a recognized leading producer of the world’s most advanced jet engines, is looking for… https://t.co/SfP6WPK6zd https://t.co/0Gjr99cXpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net tech lead/architect: .Net tech lead/architect Ref No.: 18-12117 Location: Hartford, Connecticut .Net tech lead/architect Hartford CT Long term NO JD Thanks and Regard’s Atul Malviya Sr. Technical Recruiter Enterprise Solutions, Inc. 500 E. Diehl… https://t.co/rzvWgQjwiH https://t.co/Na5mfeZDSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudera (Hadoop) Administrator with Unix Experience: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J1017-0813 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global… https://t.co/RQRuW7vxTS https://t.co/mzspW83z8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cluster PMO – Project Manager Coordinator: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2018-01-11 Functional area Planning &amp; Logistics Background Others – Non Technical Reference US03628 Recruiter: Kamille Garcia… https://t.co/DpCLqwjeP9 https://t.co/Dv0sCGFsjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/Jf3G2ht45D https://t.co/3QSTGnZFBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/bv7UBZx4YZ https://t.co/mbCvNrWmCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Account Manager – Construction Products: Connecticut, CT Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Outside Account Manager – Construction Products with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a… https://t.co/inT7PYBmVo https://t.co/IRPxEEtHlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Back end – Full time: We are seeking skilled Software Engineers with the following qualities: * Problem solver * Attention to details * Fast learner * Self-motivated and directed RESPONSIBILITIES * Enhancing automation of Back Office,… https://t.co/Gsr65yUCts https://t.co/psfuKvc7XQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/XsqiWwn9jw https://t.co/bmJPP2zvMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-2017 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position… https://t.co/Jwl86cxAXl https://t.co/dNNGXmgzhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Developer: This position is a full lifecycle development opportunity, allowing the employee to participate in system design, development, documentation, testing, implementation, deployment, integration and support of all necessary… https://t.co/9sKfzgFw1n https://t.co/4tyh2HsBFz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>