<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer: At Two Bulls we look at the landscape of emerging technology and create innovative products which become tomorrow’s solutions. We are a band of roughly 80 people with offices in Melbourne, New York and Berlin. We ship early and… https://t.co/xtE5sWm8v3 https://t.co/7kEoU43QCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular and React Developers: Passionate about technology? Do you like shipping software and seeing real results? If that describes you, you’ll feel right at home at Chariot. We are a tight knit group of software professionals, putting our expertise to… https://t.co/VEJ5nZBz08 https://t.co/OWxzpsmh9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Analyst/Programmer – C++, Python, Visual Studio: Belay Tech is seeking CNO Analyst/Programmer with windows development experience (Visual Studio), C+ development, python, and subversion experience. All candidates must have an active and full DoD… https://t.co/wCx2Tef94u https://t.co/aUzmccJ2XX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .Net Developer: Full Stack .Net Developer Philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 02/27/18, Posted Date – 02/27/18 Primary SkillsHTML,JQuery,*******,AJAX and JSONTax TermsC2COverview Years of Experience: 5+ years working… https://t.co/tjVq59mmZo https://t.co/lDSYKFyOy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/YvvP3ah6nd https://t.co/7UBOyoGmFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/qUTaLAUBWX https://t.co/0OBrZVIfW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Software Engineer – Python Developer: Job descriptionPosition Purpose: Design, build, test and maintain scalable and stable off the shelf application or custom built technology solutions to meet business needs. Act as a subject matter… https://t.co/YhQrnzKEpF https://t.co/Bs0wLqm8w0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Weapons &amp; Lethality Solutions Analysis Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Advanced Weapons &amp; Lethality Solutions focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the… https://t.co/JFb5Bg9vay https://t.co/FuIxcJXhmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/s8EHJwcvrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer, FireEye: Support the FireEye ecosystem including patching, and administering configs with a FireEye AX, CM, EX, FX, HX, NX environment Test FireEye HX Agent configs prior to upgrades and testing FireEye Appliances and validate… https://t.co/vhPTQHALD6 https://t.co/2S3KwIzDMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – .NET/Python: Position Purpose: Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs… https://t.co/8848qKRAY7 https://t.co/yXx0lHskya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Hey, we’re Article. We’re a digital-first furniture brand that’s re-engineering the furniture experience one sofa at a time. We don’t have brick and mortar stores, so we’re able to deliver remarkable value on beautiful,… https://t.co/SjJEQfSyna https://t.co/n5Y0CZEYod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify sees revenue growth easing as gears up for listing: STOCKHOLM/LONDON (Reuters) - Spotify, the world's top selling music streaming service, expects revenue to grow 20-30 percent this year as currency swings slow the pace from 2017, it said on… https://t.co/HtYV3Mjo6S https://t.co/kXVV7U5nvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Security Engineer: Position Summary: The Secure Coding Team, of the world renowned CERT division of the Software Engineering Institute, is a pioneer of the identification and development of secure coding and secure software development… https://t.co/kDFCJE0A01 https://t.co/SBFLL57Pb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/ztnZbe1cdo https://t.co/rPxlc5r7Al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/M2qSCICWan https://t.co/zBNNcr7Rlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Surveillance &amp; Strike (Contested) Analysis Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Surveillance and Strike focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy… https://t.co/C1vT0W4H4K https://t.co/qRY4Vd0Nwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reverse Engineer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/xHTPQh1Szs https://t.co/iGqcItTTLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/JMqqU7Lj5k https://t.co/BefQSZ2vUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer with Tableau: Python developer with Tableau – iTechwin Systems – Milpitas, CA – 02-26-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths… https://t.co/ENtcISAn8p https://t.co/wQhLhQ9oH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Product Development Architect: Treeline Interactive is searching for a Senior Software Engineer to join our growing Development Team. You will be responsible for architecting software solutions on a number different platforms and code bases,… https://t.co/GiE5AaHMfs https://t.co/JyoSYkv3g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Web Application Developer: SunnyvaleSunnyvaleCalifornia [CA]United States [US] Fortinet strives to be the global leader in network security with both of our special hardware appliances and sophisticated cloud infrastructure to satisfy the most… https://t.co/XVw6wNOvtL https://t.co/Hpqiy2HL6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer: At Two Bulls we look at the landscape of emerging technology and create innovative products which become tomorrow’s solutions. We are a band of roughly 80 people with offices in Melbourne, New York and Berlin. We ship early and… https://t.co/kw4xkhTG83 https://t.co/qNckrCcVs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/GwjVcZmogy https://t.co/uof7j3eYPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Flask Developer (Contract, Part-Time): Croscon, a digital product studio, is seeking an experienced senior python developer to join our dedicated backend team focusing on distributed computing solutions &amp; bespoke business systems. You will… https://t.co/RLAoakJpMO https://t.co/UFLyfW7ek7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Engineer II or ABOVE (Java, Python, SQL) – Digital Innovation Team: Product Engineer (Java, Python, SQL), Digital Innovation TeamAt Company, were building the future of payments. As a member of the Digital Innovation team, youll be part of a team… https://t.co/zX8dVkNotd https://t.co/7dpVw0zOp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Automation Engineer – Intralot Inc: INTRALOT is engaged in the supply of integrated gaming and transaction processing systems, innovative game content and value added services to state licensed gaming organizations. Based on… https://t.co/xW1u0dkvOz https://t.co/ukBkDFDf7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Ariba iXp Intern – HANA Software Developer Job: Date: Mar 1, 2018 Location: San Ramon, CA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Software-Development Operations Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Student Employment Type: Intern… https://t.co/JaB8XlWja8 https://t.co/hE2bRQDiW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator: Category: Development/Engineering City: Sacramento, California, United States Position ID: J0917-0399 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: CGI Federal is seeking a System Administrator in Sacramento, CA. Your… https://t.co/VBmORoJgzp https://t.co/x0Um3QbKEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Ref No.: 18-10432 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Role: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Location: Washington DC Duration: FTE – Responsibilities The… https://t.co/VT8yA61peO https://t.co/vYZEW9r3dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reverse Engineer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/0tYu8P48Pe https://t.co/EV1cLF67Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/wnDINnok7T https://t.co/6gp1IXouF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/H6xE75y7rP https://t.co/ACxDx8WTJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer: Position Summary: As a member of CERT’s Workforce Development program, the candidate will work with other team members in developing cyber-security training exercises and simulations, primarily for US military/government… https://t.co/zPEtFgFIL4 https://t.co/StwGvMQsbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Systems Integration MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Mission Systems Integration Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation… https://t.co/taCpcBkGn4 https://t.co/kvPg2klo9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber to sell Southeast Asia business to rival Grab: sources: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Ride-hailing firm Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] has agreed to sell its Southeast Asian business to bigger regional rival Grab, sources with knowledge of the matter said… https://t.co/XYwGc2K4kX https://t.co/iEdcdGPXmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist ($150-180k) – Python and MATLAB: San Francisco, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today Job Title: Financial Controller Job Location: San Francisco, CA Salary: ($150-180k) Based in San Francisco, CA, we are an exciting medical… https://t.co/Ua1kuqMpoH https://t.co/Shd9O4Noen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer 2018: Simple Energy is a fast-paced, Boulder-based startup. We graduated TechStars in 2011 and have continued growing and improving since. We are changing the world by helping people understand and reduce their energy consumption. We are… https://t.co/GDktJklAXj https://t.co/iQDcZZr0g3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/3dfhniWEoF https://t.co/GwplvvXDfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software/Infrastructure Engineer – Continuous Lifecycle Solutions Team: What We Do: The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement.… https://t.co/hVvAJ7BI5B https://t.co/o2ibC6gECG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Threat Research &amp; Modeling Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will develop/lead a strong 10 person team to assess threat-modeling gaps and develop/enhance NG threat models for assets… https://t.co/3yl3iSwnqv https://t.co/Pweq5kVNNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Position: DevOps Engineer Type: Full Time Location: Scottsdale, AZ or Denver, CO Already have an account? Member ID: Password: Forgot your Password? tr, td, a { padding: 5px; } fieldset { width: 250px; } legend {… https://t.co/8gQmbWZnxh https://t.co/kn5CfjTgZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/FzcgRTj1Lh https://t.co/TeMQVeiK1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/2RsfuKZ4fC https://t.co/1HbdLwcKMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivability MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Survivability Technology Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the… https://t.co/ohOz9WcMwL https://t.co/exilJBvnBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Web Engineer: Home About Employment Lead Web Engineer Lead Web Engineer Lead Web Engineer InsureMyTrip is looking for software engineers to join our team to help build our next gen web technology. We’re looking for natural leaders who can understand… https://t.co/GDkFjjxPpb https://t.co/fXBoYnMJOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/yDKy8T1Afs https://t.co/Fn2bm54vwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python and… https://t.co/es1aueeECq https://t.co/6ySLGi2GQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radar Systems Modeling Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Radar Systems Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions… https://t.co/Cjo3BiA9T1 https://t.co/ImnX09okX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/FsAzbPMNjJ https://t.co/XNYUYydUOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python: A well-known prominent automobile manufacturing company is looking to add a Software QA Engineer to their R&amp;D team. In this role, youll be responsible for extending and customizing their existing Python automation framework. You… https://t.co/fY29ZLn5P5 https://t.co/tfBG88UDXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counter-Air Threat Modeling Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Counter-Air Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions… https://t.co/NmodJr1Z2S https://t.co/at4iOTy4uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer: Home About Employment Web Applications Developer Web Applications Developer InsureMyTrip is looking for several developers to join our Development team. We are currently in the process of renovating our core architecture,… https://t.co/x7KNXR1c7t https://t.co/89o1dFO0Hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/jwy8SqjT2X https://t.co/aneEuEEvYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/i6NfUqSqb8 https://t.co/vCSGMkwnom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3 / MATLAB Developer (Cambridge, MA): At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our… https://t.co/UPS66ZfMZD https://t.co/Yjzh2Tchwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/nfKqGmdtNl https://t.co/tmQLT8Smia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk deletes Facebook pages of Tesla, SpaceX after challenged on Twitter: (Reuters) - Verified Facebook pages of Elon Musk's rocket company SpaceX and electric carmaker Tesla Inc disappeared on Friday, minutes after the Silicon Valley billionaire… https://t.co/S60GVuuMZ4 https://t.co/HrjAsHnzSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/gLWjnwRvEA https://t.co/q2dEgbioLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer: At Two Bulls we look at the landscape of emerging technology and create innovative products which become tomorrow’s solutions. We are a band of roughly 80 people with offices in Melbourne, New York and Berlin. We ship early and… https://t.co/4CU7YIaRDK https://t.co/oxdlmCBDEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/iW0poiGIX4 https://t.co/i9Ek6AJdJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Position: DevOps Engineer Type: Full Time Location: Scottsdale, AZ or Denver, CO Already have an account? Member ID: Password: Forgot your Password? tr, td, a { padding: 5px; } fieldset { width: 250px; } legend {… https://t.co/INFjIQUCgj https://t.co/FbsVUGjULZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/Python) Job: Software Engineer (C++/Python) (Job Number:434869) Description: SAIC has an exciting opportunity in the growing field of robotics. In this position you will be using and modifying a web based multi robot control unit… https://t.co/vtsNH1EMqK https://t.co/0YIRFVTAnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/4cIeSKQrMn https://t.co/7g7INWXsjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Engineer II or ABOVE (Java, Python, SQL) – Digital Innovation Team: Product Engineer (Java, Python, SQL), Digital Innovation TeamAt Company, were building the future of payments. As a member of the Digital Innovation team, youll be part of a team… https://t.co/G5g3yGgWKY https://t.co/bhkgLRfBdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Engineer: Cloud Engineer Location: Boston, MA Position Summary: Act as part of cross-functional team to ensure QuickPivot’s cloud platform is highly available, scalable and secure on the AWS platform. Assist Engineering and Operations teams in… https://t.co/KCjt34rzHX https://t.co/wme2DfqFm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/Evva1x8rS1 https://t.co/ofIVqmZZHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/wNnzwgk5Y1 https://t.co/xpl5FYhxW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: If you are passionate about building the best possible data platform to underpin a mobile app that’s used by millions of users a month to navigate the complex maze of travel planning, we’d love to talk to you. Hopper is a mobile-only… https://t.co/FZHzLzpJhk https://t.co/34QnIgZsKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Software Developer: Prestigious Financials Firm is currently seeking a Web Software Engineer with Python development skills. Candidate will design, develop, deploy, and support batch systems. Candidate will help architect systems, optimize… https://t.co/d5aCxEcmFs https://t.co/xO0jERTyWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer-WA: Software Developer Bellevue, WA Fulltime position Exp: 3-8yrs Job Description: Minimum Requirements: Must have a minimum of a Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. 1 year of experience with… https://t.co/TT2swJU3vj https://t.co/UheoHNwvv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – PHP/Javascript: Whats Curvo? Glad you asked! Curvo is clinical spend management for the modern hospital supply chain. We engineer cost out of provider organizations. So, what? Theres no better time to be in healthcare supply chain.… https://t.co/UmIsa4cHL1 https://t.co/RAYhZH902Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Located in Salt Lake City, we are a growing security company. We provide innovative solutions for global organizations. We are currently hiring for passionate developers with a solid DevOps background. We work in team environments… https://t.co/rMUJKzI2GV https://t.co/OOxUUrVe6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer: Full Stack Java Developer | Aegon Vacancies Working at Aegon Roles Career development Inside Aegon You are viewing the Global section in English Global | English Other location/language Full Stack Java Developer – Home –… https://t.co/n3UofLXzHa https://t.co/9zfnuWfpYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/KhFha8PCQX https://t.co/t0vURQnNGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer, Senior: Jobs at Booz Allen Hamilton Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation Home What We Do Who We Serve About Us Featured Careers Cleared Professionals Commercial Careers Consulting Careers Corporate Professionals Cyber Careers Data… https://t.co/DqFEaeLd63 https://t.co/zYyPEwnuTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/hDc07AnsPE https://t.co/sMQiBdp2pF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/BDir3DJFRJ https://t.co/vPnpuw08KB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer, AREA Method (Part-time): Overview Cheryl Einhorn is the founder of AREA Method, a decision-making system designed for individuals and companies to solve complex problems. The AREA Method builds strategic touchpoints throughout a… https://t.co/9W5oGTWvML https://t.co/sByNr6wnBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Docker, Python (Cleared Position!): You should have experience with Java 8, python, and Docker to develop, maintain, and enhance complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development,… https://t.co/bBehtjCPR1 https://t.co/VKfOCRAYPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/91dgiN3Fhb https://t.co/bJhlM18uDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm re-elects board of directors with tepid support: SAN DIEGO (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc re-elected its board of directors on Friday with weak support from shareholders, who grilled the U.S. chipmaker over its strategy following its successful… https://t.co/fnknlLdZl2 https://t.co/LroQMxQY8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/aT8hsVp8cs https://t.co/SAzBvCsk28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Ref No.: 18-10432 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Role: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Location: Washington DC Duration: FTE – Responsibilities The… https://t.co/niO4bToWGb https://t.co/lJp2bFQ7GW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/sbXTzsP4zZ https://t.co/S2oHfFiIwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Growth: About thredUP thredUP, based in San Francisco, is the leading online marketplace for buying and selling like-new womens and kids clothing. thredUP was founded in 2009 and currently employs nearly 1,000 people across its… https://t.co/mhKtheCQpE https://t.co/IAxyt5IiPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/ri6IHAFl2d https://t.co/Kf8kFL4Dot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Python, R, SaaS): Redwood City, CA Full-time $140k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Due to massive growth and demand for our services, we are currently… https://t.co/BFUqUE1BTs https://t.co/LcJcUJJuRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/hID7l6nGTn https://t.co/ppKpKiUSXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/dlYlPgSHiH https://t.co/izEJZpB3DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/QUOx6Z3Bck https://t.co/dV1hbyqZyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer (C /C++ /Python): Req ID : 403146BR Job Code/Title : E2551:Cyber Intel Analyst Asc Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are impossible? If you… https://t.co/rwS0TlTaCm https://t.co/sl88SD3xGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Software Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/rQELu0WMKo https://t.co/ySaYBI2Mp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/yV4lOnZJv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/osVtPHAXN2 https://t.co/PXCpyEhgt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – .NET/Python: Position Purpose: Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs… https://t.co/OEGbDMR0Bh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer – Why Vyze – Products – Point of Sale – eCommerce – Financing Center – Request a Demo – Why Vyze – Products – About Us – Customers – Lender Network – Blog – Press – Contact Request a Demo Latest… https://t.co/DiRg0TpbGQ https://t.co/8bHWfCtIRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Developer: APPLICATION DEADLINE: March 19th, 2018 Portland General Electric values the energy of teamwork, diversity, and innovation to provide our customers with safe and reliable power. As Oregon’s largest provider of electric service, PGE is… https://t.co/2wXAct4avM https://t.co/7GVNNM4sPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/aci8J5qYAB https://t.co/0vpf9eSZel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Machine Learning and AI: Etsy is looking for a Data Scientist to join our Data Science team in SF. Etsy is committed to advancing the fields related to E-commerce related fields by building technologies that help Etsy buyers and sellers… https://t.co/F2M76GboTa https://t.co/GxfkNuz5Rn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>