<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer – Machine Learning: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a… https://t.co/wz4HI5GpVJ #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/zP1W575R7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to… https://t.co/m57VoBQgic #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/vyCz6GDXQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Threat Research &amp; Modeling Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will develop/lead a strong 10 person team to assess threat-modeling gaps and develop/enhance… https://t.co/Q61098qnO8 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to… https://t.co/yoVWJni6po #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/k3bI6UiE8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3 / MATLAB Developer (Cambridge, MA): At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world… https://t.co/UV6Po5m2O2 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile… https://t.co/4zlfOBS01B #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/eJEL8dc7gX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 3: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to… https://t.co/AnmFocr6ei #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Ycc9JUuy5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Full-Stack Developer (Python): Company Introduction OneinaMil is a talent matchmaking firm, we specialize in culture driven recruiting. Our mission is to change the way traditional recruiting is done. We put… https://t.co/vQVpDxcpmj #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/EmHZPMNQCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 3: Job Description The individual in this role will support the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions (GSMS) group in the development of advanced concepts and… https://t.co/oFOhjjfjyE #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Software Developer: Careers Center | Python Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/E4WtAZuyiT #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/jwEFVKkkCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Technology Architect – US: Role Senior Principal Technology Architect – US Auto req ID 28698BR Domain Analytics Skillset Grid Computing Platforms , HADOOP Country USA State / Region / Province… https://t.co/M6jl8hGVbO #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/RSSwWwc5px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Python Developer: LEAD PYTHON DEVELOPER (CLOUD) Exciting opportunity to work with an Atlanta household name and global technology leader as a Lead Python Developer. This position is a hands-on lead development… https://t.co/UPnPvAje9F #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/JRX2m3RCxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Consultant: Job Location: North America, USA Location: Willing to let right candidate work out of a home office anywhere in the US with practical access to air travel. Position Summary: PostgresSQL is a rapidly… https://t.co/3iysldbztu #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/PGyqk2DtJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Linux Development (C / C++ / Python): Req ID : 355681BR Job Code/Title : E2564:Cyber Architect Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on… https://t.co/edT6ESYKua #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/uPc5BeTIpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Manager 3 – Platform Security Monitoring Manager: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/2aoUzjHuyy #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/exJq90gu16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack developer: Client Reference Code: 213239Job Scope Leads in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service… https://t.co/0N2oZNiX8C #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/5LgtkxF516]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming… https://t.co/JaPthWpMgE #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/SYno29Lu5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Algorithms Systems Engineer: Overview Seeking a highly technical candidate with 10+ years of relevant experience working on the design, integration, and verification of Command, Control, Communications,… https://t.co/qhoNGHkjYq #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/zNnIssBhSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Since 2006, WMC Global has worked with digital services providers around the world to deliver insight into digital threats targeting consumers. By monitoring channels for threat delivery,… https://t.co/HVsXSQtHnA #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/FlV3GNfChE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Position: DevOps Engineer Type: Full Time Location: Scottsdale, AZ or Denver, CO Already have an account? Member ID: Password: Forgot your Password? tr, td, a { padding: 5px; } fieldset… https://t.co/NrjqVLrONd #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/s0ZJtLCD2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coca-Cola, U.S. State Dept to use blockchain to combat forced labor: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Coca-Cola Co and the U.S. State Department along with two other companies said on Friday they are launching a project using blockchain's… https://t.co/9wKLqlYSHN #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/4sxpIwnNxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search the best IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/AfjvzjP2o3 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/ecnM7QsIPL #jobboard #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ho0n1olPL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Consultant: Technical Solutions Consultant (San Bruno, CA) Identify, drive and optimize various operational work-flows and tools for Google projects.. #1615.26660 Exp Incl: Python; SQL; Rvsion &amp; Srce… https://t.co/o0EiCHuinZ #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/PQQgypsV51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python)… https://t.co/7d310oPOWd #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/9hlMnWDh1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr Python Developer: Following established written procedures, guidelines and techniques, develops, enhances, modifies and/or maintains applications that support business units or support functions in the Global Markets… https://t.co/fKXi6vFsGP #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/QedNLK9W7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Manager 3 – Platform Security Monitoring Manager: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/CmBME4YfyU #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation… https://t.co/zaYktQffqj #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/uj2L9ereyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: SENIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER (CLOUD) Exciting opportunity to work with an Atlanta household name and global technology leader as a Senior Python Developer. This position is a hands-on development… https://t.co/MqApeDNw1s #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/B1TIiVnvjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer (C /C++ /Python): Req ID : 403146BR Job Code/Title : E2551:Cyber Intel Analyst Asc Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that… https://t.co/WUgOJKT5xn #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/zp0urbwVpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Threat Research &amp; Modeling Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will develop/lead a strong 10 person team to assess threat-modeling gaps and develop/enhance… https://t.co/OfFMSXWdJ8 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/UIbQRJKos4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted 01/11/2018 Located in a beautiful office in the Mission District in San Francisco, we are an early staged funded B2C Fin-Tech start up that is combining… https://t.co/iCAIvXmcl6 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/f3oo7a24Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead IT Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management,… https://t.co/NCAimmALvO #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application… https://t.co/jQVsmkM1O2 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks… https://t.co/lf2ZEWQLdj #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr DevOps Engineer: Qualifications: Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science or related field is required, advanced degree preferred. At least 7-10 years of relevant work experience in a senior technical position… https://t.co/DdVKtcPrUy #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/5JLylsh02q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development… https://t.co/sC6RW2Y6fh #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming… https://t.co/KP6GJ0sTsl #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/KJBax3j91W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy… https://t.co/ogKDxzEI5W #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/OV0BN07jea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tools Programmer: Youre into games you love playing them and you love making them. You enjoy working with creative types. You spend your time thinking about how outstanding content can improve games. You use your… https://t.co/thkfXtXEMY #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/G3N3zrsc0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Test Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS… https://t.co/GiGyRMtKsm #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/LquChPnJ1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China may adopt some of Germany's law on self-driving cars: expert: BERLIN (Reuters) - The Chinese government is evaluating a German law that lays the groundwork for use of self-driving cars, and will likely adopt some of the… https://t.co/VBk19krR7n #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/MgcuddXizR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/AfjvzjP2o3 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/fLmcPkCnxb #jobboard #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/YVC6RoTSmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: The QA Automation Engineer will be a member of the Software Engineering team and will report to the Manager, Quality Assurance. The primary duties of the QA Automation Engineer require the… https://t.co/mrilGiixpB #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/UjzbCfoOQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Would you rather join a cause, not just a company? Become a part of one of the fastest growing FinTech companies on the east coast! StreetShares is a military focused financial services company… https://t.co/kFNCNNaQoc #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/yzFAbuEKzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Cryptocurrency: DV Trading is seeking a Software Engineer to join its cryptocurrency trading division, DV Chain. This role provides an opportunity for a skilled developer to work on the firms next… https://t.co/znDzIIhlt7 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Web Developer (Node/Python): We are seeking candidates for a Full-stack Web Developer, here in the Charleston, SC area. Are you interested in working for a culture-focused organization, that is a leader in… https://t.co/zONlZdKOTF #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/evqfYrTGUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the… https://t.co/IeIWky7ftk #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/yITvIraRXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Marketing: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell,… https://t.co/9ZXJGEjnLU #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/dWEFAE0JKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: Full Stack Web Developers Job Description Know Me is a small start-up in Chapel Hill that is focused on creating web and mobile applications. Our mission is to help people who have difficulties… https://t.co/caKfRUCAhR #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/20gYbx64Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Automation Engineer: Software Automation Engineer at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program – Students… https://t.co/UlSd9TB7YE #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/4BvMUi6d3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases… https://t.co/35Md3X0gdq #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Network Operations Analyst Programmer: Company Description ThreatConnect arms organizations with a powerful defense against cyber threats and the confidence to make strategic business decisions. Founded in… https://t.co/IrEIbuP7bP #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Django Developer: Zipari is a technology start-up company based in DUMBO, Brooklyn, NY. Our mission is to disrupt the insurance industry by introducing consumer-centric solutions powered by data analytics. We are… https://t.co/p7WBbdosLh #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer [Django and Python Superstar]: JOB DESCRIPTION Your Responsibilities * Collect, analyse &amp; refine requirements together with our product team. * Define big picture architectures and break them down into… https://t.co/3CjDxbBQYD #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Developer Engineer: We are looking for a brilliant mind to join our team, working on solving very real and important problems. You will take a leadership role in our algorithm team to develop… https://t.co/UYUcASC5QA #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Bellevue, WA: Software Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: In this position, the candidate will be integrating and validating different machine learning frameworks also… https://t.co/DMBtyRFn2D #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom ends bid for Qualcomm after President Trump nixes deal: (Reuters) - Singapore-based Broadcom Ltd withdrew its $117 billion bid to acquire Qualcomm Inc on Wednesday, two days after U.S. President Donald Trump blocked… https://t.co/9m9sJjZqrE #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/whPojz2hOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/AfjvzjP2o3 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/lDg6IC2smI #jobboard #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/LdZcYO6mZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile… https://t.co/UYOZ3L9Ael #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/Python) Job: Date: Feb 28, 2018 Location: San Diego, CA, US Company: SAIC Software Engineer (C++/Python) (Job Number:434588) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: SAIC has an exciting opportuning in the… https://t.co/ygiVshONAJ #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Data Scientist: CME Group: Where Futures Are Made CME Group (****************) is the worlds leading and most diverse derivatives marketplace. But who we are goes deeper than that. Here, you can impact markets… https://t.co/CiZCQe3yWv #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/oIX3a1vftt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming… https://t.co/poIJ8yZIOn #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist / Engineer: Dialexa is expanding its Data Science practice and is looking for great talent to join us building intelligent, next generation platforms. Are you tired of just pushing out ones and zeros and… https://t.co/EM6mMrDjCH #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator: US Government Security Clearance Required Love Linux and Security… This job was written for you! Before you read the whole requirement ask yourself these questions: * Do you love Linux and… https://t.co/shXOwRmzSB #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Linux Development (C / C++ / Python): Req ID : 355681BR Job Code/Title : E2564:Cyber Architect Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on… https://t.co/31TXssuNbL #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist (Boston): QuantumBlack helps companies use data to drive decisions. We combine business experience, expertise in large-scale data analysis and visualization, and advanced software engineering… https://t.co/NJARCpH7ZF #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and… https://t.co/ezyo4MEsY4 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – St. Louise, MO: Software Engineer St. Louise, MO Full Time Position Job Description: Looking for Strong technical expertise in designing and developing C# (must have) and C++ (desirable) Looking for… https://t.co/20xzGcLOrm #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Designer/Full Stack Developer (•Python•JS•React) 200k: San Francisco, CA Full-time $130k – $200k Posted Today Calling All Unicorns! If you are a Full Stack Developer with Product Design experience, please… https://t.co/DvUUjj6m1z #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Web Services: This job advertisement is for a software developer supporting a national agency Research directorate. The ideal candidate possesses a broad range of experience embracing… https://t.co/fbcrQ5blGW #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Staff: Req ID : 416864BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Mission Processing is seeking strong software engineers with experience in java, C++, python and cloud based… https://t.co/SENSMtJy82 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Programmer Analyst: NOTE: LOCAL CANDIDATES TO THE LITTLE ROCK AREA ONLY. US CITIZENS AND GREEN CARD HOLDERS ARE ENCOURAGED TO APPLY. WE ARE UNABLE TO SPONSOR H1B, F1 OR EAD CANDIDATES AT THIS TIME. DIRECT-HIRE… https://t.co/7cP5hfBlbG #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – US: Role Project Manager – US Auto req ID 28996BR Domain Communications Skillset SQL Server , SSIS Country USA State / Region / Province Texas Work Location Plano, TX Company ITL USA Job Description… https://t.co/ePqOdcjgJa #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development… https://t.co/pLHPnRmAzf #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Leonardo DRS Leonardo DRS is a leading supplier of integrated products, services and support to military forces, intelligence agencies and prime contractors worldwide. Focused on defense… https://t.co/vEa4ceLSPN #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting… https://t.co/Pa2GK5OHws #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using… https://t.co/7hCNxZqyZl #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A… https://t.co/QiGKUGtFDF #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain to consider taxing digital giants' revenue: LONDON (Reuters) - Britain said it was considering taxing the revenues of internet companies like Facebook and Google until international tax rules are changed to cope with… https://t.co/rC66R7G9ID #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/V0ueWhBDW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Best IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/AfjvzjP2o3 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/3CsKK77azI #jobboard #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/q4y9VnIhvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and… https://t.co/opXi3BWMlq #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Since 2006, WMC Global has worked with digital services providers around the world to deliver insight into digital threats targeting consumers. By monitoring channels for threat delivery,… https://t.co/dhWzXKFuDZ #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer (C /C++ /Python): Req ID : 403146BR Job Code/Title : E2551:Cyber Intel Analyst Asc Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that… https://t.co/erZVgMErPY #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump halts Broadcom takeover of Qualcomm: (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump issued an order on Monday prohibiting semiconductor maker Broadcom Ltd's proposed takeover of Qualcomm Inc on grounds of national… https://t.co/ru38Y19nMM #news #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ayCo4m1UQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search and apply to thousands of tech jobs on 🔵 https://t.co/AfjvzjP2o3 🔵: Entrepreneur Magazine Feature ITJobPro as Most Popular Tech Job Site #IT #jobs #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/VmnluuBdLo #jobboard #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/s5kiWbHbNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-14621 Location: san jose, California Hi, This isShipra fromEnterprise Solution Inc.I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below. Job Title: Python Developer Location: San Jose, CA Duration:… https://t.co/phL82PwN1r https://t.co/zG751UgpcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/JQfmiImjLf https://t.co/pRBEfybM8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Requirements Full stack developer with demonstrable modern framework experience, to participate in the creation and maintenance of discrete applications written in Javascript frameworks and Java, Python and .Net languages. Must like… https://t.co/N2bOnK31wh https://t.co/veUbXlqIes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Numerical Algorithm Software Engineer: SciTec, Inc. is a dynamic small business with the mission to deliver Advanced Sensor Data Exploitation technologies and Science Instrumentation Capabilities in support of National Security and Defense. SciTec has… https://t.co/q1aattg3aj https://t.co/W1VGT0iU8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Programmer: Associate Programmer – Hertfordshire Hertfordshire N/A Skip Navigation Toggle navigation Account – Refine search – View my account – Sign in Job details Associate Programmer – Requisition ID: ****** – Position: Full-Time Regular –… https://t.co/qGP1qUGzIm https://t.co/bLLCpSweJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/5krrMZqYsW https://t.co/BLiv8ZHNnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Support Engineer: Client Reference Code: 216834Job Scope The Video Operations group is responsible for operating the video ecosystem at Spectrum and is comprised of the following groups: Video Core, Video Systems, Planning &amp; Implementation and… https://t.co/qsHJ6zynR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Software Engineer – Python Jobs in Philadelphia Area | SIG Careers You are using an unsupported browser. Some features may not work correctly.Close Menu Meet Our Team Beyond Work + Benefits News + Events About Trading Quant… https://t.co/9e50cVE0xZ https://t.co/8dyierwQgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Backend Developer w/API: Looking for a mid-level (2-5 years experience) Python developer that ha experience doing Back End development and API. Some relational database experience is a plus. Must be comfortable with database paradigms, data… https://t.co/GRFkEfeLFj https://t.co/B0fVma0yDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Cloud, Containers and Machine Learning are changing standards in todays IT environments. Movere is a SaaS product that enables organizations to achieve cloud adoption and containerization swiftly and efficiently, and all that data… https://t.co/I983sG5j2R https://t.co/6GaYqbNrla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description Software Engineer (WD***********) What you will do: As a software engineer you will participate in the design and development for an SOA-based, multi-tenant, cloud platform. We’re looking for hands-on technical… https://t.co/r9teihIzda https://t.co/oCFAlSYrcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer: Description:The Civil Health Operation is currently seeking a Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful candidate will work within an ITIL… https://t.co/tAbpAR0oyg https://t.co/09lJ8DTsxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/hNOMpFmiqL https://t.co/W4yFJAw2gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-15855 Location: Mountain View, California Position : Python Automation Engineer Location : Mountain View, CA Job Role : Full Time Job Description : Strong Python automation with 4 to 6… https://t.co/A7lSnwSuC1 https://t.co/jfueN9Kl4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook must face class action over facial recognition: U.S. judge: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - A U.S. federal judge ruled on Monday that Facebook Inc must face a class action lawsuit alleging that the social network unlawfully used a facial recognition… https://t.co/JY2Taf6f3y https://t.co/NIgKVn6OkH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>