<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @janariess: Utah people: GO SEE THIS MOVIE on Friday or Saturday. It’s a vicarious ordinance you’re performing for all the rest of us wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheExponent: The Exponent blog supports the new film Jane and Emma!  https://t.co/kf2megVz5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @notstevenwhite: We take it for granted, but it really is astonishing (and incredibly consequential for human existence) that Republican…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellreports: Troubling report from the front lines at tonight's MAGA rally https://t.co/td0ZFuSHYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Ted Cruz turns down CNN invite to participate in town hall, O'Rourke to appear solo https://t.co/44VmM9bwnm https://t.co/ID68w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @atrupar: REPORTER: Have you read the alarming UN report about imminent, drastic climate change?

TRUMP: "It was given to me, &amp; I want t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s hoping that @Acosta asks Yrump what percentage of Americans are evil? https://t.co/sQ3tFHcWs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrFilmkritik: Taylor Swift endorsed Democrat Phil Bredesen in the Senate race in Tennessee, and voter registration boomed.

Beyoncé sho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @patrickqmason: Friends in Utah: I'd encourage you to go see #JaneandEmma this weekend.  It's the rare religious movie that focuses on w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @viaSimonRomero: https://t.co/1OFYW5KGVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CitizenCohn: This is an epic and thorough dismantling of @senatemajldr talking point about SCOTUS nominations. Read and save for the ne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This—&gt;

(And hire more religion reporters!!!) https://t.co/fdGFTGHSxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bryndiswoods: Are you #RegisteredtoVote?? https://t.co/RMlUHEHluS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ccjones13: “Mormon women’s participation in the political sphere has been fraught with ambiguity for more than a century.”

Smart analy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JoyCastro Happy Birthday! Where are you, may I ask? So beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinMKruse: Good Lord, this is depressing. https://t.co/p8gA4LirJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haley's resignation means it's a good time to read @tifflstanley's profile of her in @ReligPolitics. https://t.co/hzpCmWJnDN https://t.co/S4gKPb5UUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Or primary Trump. https://t.co/XudxbOumMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amyfiscus: Nikki Haley has resigned as UN ambassador, per @maggieNYT https://t.co/dqNSKgUdni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umm... why just LDS women? https://t.co/8xWub78cTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamdavidson: Forget all the noise. Trump's true story is simple and clear and not disputed by Trump, himself. 

- His father created a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeerJeet: Is it normal for a Supreme Court Justice to celebrate his confirmation at a party thrown by the lobbyist of a giant corporati…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReligPolitics: What the Brett Kavanaugh Protests Revealed about Mormonism and Women https://t.co/syYtF1GPIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @questlove: Y’all keep supporting climate deniers who just wanna keep generational wealth &amp; care about none of you in power &amp; this will…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, "job killing EPA" the week we learn that we are heading towards a global environmental apocalypse? https://t.co/H6iJACzl3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a father of a new baby, this makes me nauseous. And it should make us all change our behavior, politics, and priorities TODAY. We are the Planet Killer. https://t.co/unfwUTVpgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: "A betrayal beyond words": The far right melts down over Taylor Swift’s endorsement of Democrats https://t.co/SDrRd4Q6VJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racheldrayer Seriously curious what they called his “merits.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fahrenthold: NEW: In 2004, @realDonaldTrump lost his financial lifeline -- his father's businesses. But after that, Trump didn't cut ba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: .@lisamurkowski you ran and won as an Independent.  Am hoping you will consider becoming an Independent and caucusing with…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KristenClarkeJD: Today, 4 states (MN, VT, AK &amp; SD), 60 cities (LA, Seattle, Denver, Phoenix, Austin, Nashville), and a growing number o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Planet Killer is coming. And it's us. https://t.co/UcQXcSwpSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fellow men, what is wrong with you (us)? https://t.co/SnJGK5CXRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLWeisenfeld There's a book in this family history, to be written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheTattooedProf: Happy Genocidal Slaver--Shitty Geographer Day from the president* https://t.co/j4dY3KyltV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Public_Citizen: We should eliminate #ColumbusDay as a holiday and make Election Day a national holiday in its place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hokie_prof No consensus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoyAnnReid: Journalist @Greg_Palast has created a database where Georgia voters can find out if they have been purged from the rolls, a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hokie_prof We debated in my Jesus class for a good period whether "Jews for Jesus" are Christian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats and exciting! https://t.co/GjpOqHWweV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @talulavirtch: https://t.co/3KtSKT40Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NPRinskeep: Dickerson keeps giving facts; McConnell keeps not addressing them, and concludes, “You’re not listening to me, John.” https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dearnonnatives: Everything is free for me today. 

Reparations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An amazing map. Thanks for this, @nativelandnet (and H/T @SikhProf). https://t.co/O8NqYkkp4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeromesoco: A story I did for @MorningEdition today on faith-motivated voters:  https://t.co/0mMCCjRfFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: From The Post Editorial Board:  We need answers on Jamal Khashoggi’s disappearance. 

Saudi Arabia must immediately ans…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: Saudi Arabia is believed to have murdered and dismembered the brave Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi. Here are the columns…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Preventing one extra degree of heat could make a life-or-death difference in next few decades for multitudes of people and ecosyste…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very true. https://t.co/mgfsm60UOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FemiLinzi: I'm not interested in revelation that does not help and lift the least of these. Full stop. If your revelation harms the vul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: A reminder we are in an unusual year for midterms, and have an unique opportunity to take out some of the particularly hor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, @RepDonBacon, we know you’d gut protections anytime your party called on you to. You serve the GOP not NE. https://t.co/RSFQ9n5wpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BYUStudies: Looking for something to read? Check out "Race and the Making of the Mormon People" by Max Perry Mueller! Read what Matthew…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going on a twitter hiatus. Time to get some writing done and focus more on what's here, not there. See you on the other side. https://t.co/nJMfufFQBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nprpolitics: House Democrats say their first bill after taking power would establish automatic voter registration and reinvigorate the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamSerwer: The president calls for the disenfranchisement of American servicemembers overseas right after Veterans Day https://t.co/yf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BenSasse hasn’t tweeted about #ThousandOaksShooting, #TreeOfLifeSynagogue, #krogershooting, #campfireparadise,  but ballooning deficit, of which his tax scam is largely at fault, gets his attention. #Priorities https://t.co/HzZuZwkDT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse And you are responsible for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmmanuelMacron: Patriotism is the exact opposite of nationalism. Nationalism is a betrayal of patriotism. By putting our own interests…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @esglaude: WTH?! https://t.co/zRyM8xUbYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: This is a sitting United States Senator asking the public to reelect her. https://t.co/RrXrYd4QEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriBerman: This is a coup against democracy https://t.co/FAjgmz2NIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrIbram: Seemingly every year another new word or phrase of denial becomes popular. Thank you @AdamSerwer for exposing the latest post-…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: Churchill’s grandson weighs in on canceled Trump and FLOTUS American cemetery visit in France https://t.co/M6W6GyBRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeschlossDC: In the Paris rain, May 1961, JFK and de Gaulle honor soldiers who gave their lives: https://t.co/4Dh61zgVBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SRuhle: And in Passchendaele, it rained for weeks. Soliders never left the trenches...up to their wastes in mud...trapped...horses died…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaraJeffery: Hillary had fucking pneumonia and attended a 9/11 memorial anyway and fainted and Trump and his supporters went bonkers a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardDivinity: On the 100th anniversary of the end of #WWI, the Dean of @Harvard's divinity school discusses the psychic shock of the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @staceyabrams: Thousands of ballots still remain uncounted, which means thousands of voices around the state have not yet been heard. We…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAtlantic: Montana voters decided it was still worth taxing themselves to fund public colleges. And that vote holds a lesson for the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BGwinslow Best feeling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzy53mccoy Cause they all did it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PABresnan: Hello friends. I produced an episode of @heavyweight. 

https://t.co/IYSkILxo1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non, sans le président des États Unis. Nous les autres Américains y sommes toujours et, bientôt, de nouveau. https://t.co/vfthWb1hTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BettyRbl: Now available on Project Muse: Pt 1 of the joint forum on “Materials and Methods in Native American and Indigenous Studies” i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was my favorite @heavyweight yet, and that’s saying something. Adding this to my grad seminar in the American West syllabus. Can’t wait to read @BettyRbl’s book. https://t.co/gnhKteSMJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HelpMeRhonda74: Make this viral @LaDemos @DNC  @Indivisible337 @IndivisibleTeam @Indivisible_DR @Indivisible_LP @IndivisibleATL @indivi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilmoreGlenda: Trump is fiddling while California burns. https://t.co/0nkSRIMarK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GretchenAAdams: America's descent into total oligarchy has been stopped. For now | Heather Cox Richardson https://t.co/dGAedd5khO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jerryiannelli: NEW: I obtained photos that appear to show tons of uncounted ballots sitting inside a Miami-area mailroom in Opa-locka.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @varin: Lawyers and the courts (and now the FBI) are figuring out what happened in Porter County on #2018ElectionDay. They've reassured…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marceelias: MEDIA ALERT: The GOP is trying to throw out 205 valid ballots in Broward County due to alleged signature mismatch on 22 of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: This new ad from Republicans for the Rule of Law on Matthew Whitaker and the Mueller investigation will air on several of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @anneapplebaum: another unexpected interest of Trump's new acting attorney-general https://t.co/EokzagZT7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikiebarb: BIG: Acting attorney general has said, in this audio, that Russia did NOT interfere in the US election. That's a false state…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was writing today about allotment—manifest destiny on the scale of acres not continents. There is so much power in what Elder Darren is undertaking. https://t.co/2oGyDZiHve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The palpable disdain he shows to women of color in particular (@AprilDRyan especially) speaks volumes about his character. Tell me again, fellow citizens who support Trump, how can he be a role model for our children? https://t.co/94K9BP40aP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisDunkerLJS Whiteness is the national religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: Blackface helped build Memorial Stadium. https://t.co/ydwhXwCg5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Racism is the father of race.” --Ta-Nehisi Coates https://t.co/NIoJjZE3N5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a Blue Wave AND a Blue Tide Rising. https://t.co/cNvGpetn00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janekleeb Count me in. In fact, it's a return to Nebraska's rural progressive and populist roots (see William Jennings Bryan). MN's DFL is a good model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maxperrymueller: My 4-year-old heard about #RBG’s “ribs” and wanted to tell her to get well soon. “She needs to disagree with all those…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 4-year-old heard about #RBG’s “ribs” and wanted to tell her to get well soon. “She needs to disagree with all those mistaken men!” https://t.co/CEvZ5y8yYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: “I hope to God no one sends me anymore prayers. I want gun control. No more guns!” 

The mother of shooting victim Telem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VpNrLFsTbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StandUpAmerica: “When people talk about what the public would do if this turns into a way to kneecap Mueller, if this turns into a cons…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lincoln’s #ProtectMueller, #NoOneIsAboveTheLaw.@MoveOn, @IndivisibleTeam, @indivisibleLNK. https://t.co/rYzF5QZn4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccjones13 It's yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's truly beautiful. https://t.co/Vs4LvfpDi1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>