<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Chamber Meetings Still Beat LinkedIn for Networking?: A recent survey finds that online networking and women'... http://t.co/GwlAidMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Reaching consumers via analytics | Facebook events feature, gaming feed | Apple online shoppers rule: ... http://t.co/ftp3k2IU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers Seek FTC Scrutiny of Google's Search Results: Even wonder why Google's own products and services appea... http://t.co/yTBHeds0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Analytics Primer to Target Last Minute Shoppers: Most retailers, if they use analytics at all, do so with the... http://t.co/AlA0YHUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's On Your Car's Online Dashboard?: BMW is adding Yelp to BMW Online. The application will give drivers acce... http://t.co/9OzGa6dQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Health Coverage Policy Passes ‘Hot Potato’ to States: Under the new guidelines, state lawmakers must eithe... http://t.co/CWzf0fXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Report Shows 50 Percent Hike in Google+ Fan Presence: Google+ Pages for brands arrived with a decent amount ... http://t.co/75lRk2GF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hallmark Jumps on the Second Screen Bandwagon: Ever since we discovered that people watch TV with their smartpho... http://t.co/bxNJxxPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMandossian Good article from @SuccessMagazine // Baby Steps to Better Business: http://t.co/9n8p9o0r #business #goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Secret Lives of Healthcare Information Seekers: People seeking healthcare information online are leery about... http://t.co/hE9L01x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2012 Will Bring Sponsored Ads to Your Web Facebook Feed: Get ready for another flood of cries from the wilds of ... http://t.co/KLbimwbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Health Coverage Policy Passes ‘Hot Potato’ to States: Under the new guidelines, state lawmakers must eithe... http://t.co/LlNo3tFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FedEx Driver Trashes Computer Monitor & Reputation: How Should FedEx Respond?: If you’ve not yet seen this YouTu... http://t.co/ZYPMO4nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Health Coverage Policy Passes ‘Hot Potato’ to States: Under the new guidelines, state lawmakers must eithe... http://t.co/3GaiClSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the Fastest Growing Online Ad Format? Video!: Video may have killed the radio star, but it’s working wond... http://t.co/8JnloVTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Approachs to F-Commerce: Multi-channel electronics specialist Maplin is launching a fully transactional stor... http://t.co/dU5ShHaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: HuffPo to launch streaming network | Facebook ads | EU targets Google privacy policy: Facebook IPO:

A... http://t.co/OXmFSdzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Urges Extension of Small Biz Tax Breaks: President Barack Obama sent Congress a package of small business ... http://t.co/3tTXxyzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Hedge Funds, a Career Rejuvenation: A TSA inspection helped Julie Macklowe switch careers from hedge fund ... http://t.co/yT3AX1sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[84% of Millennials Rely on the Opinions of Others: “By 2017, Millennials – those consumers now in their mid-teen... http://t.co/A0lGVZpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A One-Trick Pony Can Work on Twitter. Honda Proves It: Visibli analyzed the top 5 auto brands to see which one o... http://t.co/JnN3CRkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Watching the Super Bowl May Inspire You to Start a Business: An entrepreneurship organization is running an ... http://t.co/0nIyktOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Facebook files its IPO | Google buys ads to defend privacy | Kinect for Windows apps: Finance:

Fa... http://t.co/heE5aM5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Future of Cereal Packaging Includes a Digital Surprise: What did you read as you ate breakfast this morning?... http://t.co/6cyphMxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google is Combining My Data! ….. Oh: Thanks to Avinash Kaushik

Created by Kashmir Hill, Forbes.

 http://t.co/mTUKJQgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win Copies of Brian Carter’s “The Like Economy: How Businesses Make Money With Facebook”: Can you believe it’s b... http://t.co/wtLHZkBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Seeks 'On-Ramp' for More Startups to Go Public: For certain small companies going public, the change would... http://t.co/GapamHvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Facebook to file $5B IPO | Neil Young's digital music endeavor | Ethical iPhone: Finance:

Faceboo... http://t.co/EnbjngeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2012 Presidential Campaign: the Email Marketing Version: Much has been made of the various presidential candidat... http://t.co/B1Uf5hhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellooooo! Super Bowl Ads Before the Super Bowl: I am a Seinfeld fan. A fan of the show that is. His standup? No... http://t.co/Ae0u9LlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Lessons a Serial Tech Entrepreneur Learned from Bill Gates: Naveen Jain shares the insights he gleaned fro... http://t.co/8wzjHTMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will 2012 Become the Year of Mobile SEO?: This post comes from our SEO channel sponsor Link Assistant.
The mobil... http://t.co/giFVQxkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Now for the Good News: Communities Ban Together to Save Local Shops: Ready for another Groupon horror story?... http://t.co/UAFHuzvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HubSpot Deal Highlights ROI of Voice-based Marketing Automation: Ifbyphone will be supporting the HubSpot App Ma... http://t.co/VQiWcpda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider Shifting Emphasis and Dollars to SMO and Reputation: This post was created by our Reputation Channel sp... http://t.co/XyZm2tpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wealth Debate:  http://t.co/KV48XtUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One-Percenters Want to Buy the Corner Bakery: Smarting from poor returns in the markets, ultrawealthy individual... http://t.co/KmpemIMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Mobile Ad Spend Grows Faster Than Predicted: In what seems like a rare moment these days, analysts are saying... http://t.co/loljpFIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Buying online reviews | Twitter's censorship | Apple No.1 smartphone: Mobile Marketing:

Advertisers w... http://t.co/TccV2LPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snooki, 'Housewives' and the Reality of Celebrity Businesses: How 15 minutes of fame can lead to as many problem... http://t.co/hgA6aCxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Zynga Bingo | AT&T forecast falls short | Wii U: Social Media:

Zynga Bingo launches in beta on Fa... http://t.co/9Imv3Ixg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local Paper Uses QR Codes for, Well, Everything: Let's Eat Out Menus is a new magazine format launched in Spotsy... http://t.co/6GRUPexJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernanke to Give Lecture Series at George Washington University: Federal Reserve Chairman Ben S. Bernanke will d... http://t.co/CbtQXeT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admitting We Have a Problem Is the First Step: Admitting We Have a Problem Is the First StepThis content from: D... http://t.co/XXr61dVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Privacy | iPhone to be delivered this summer | Public alerts on Google maps: Privacy:

Should Goog... http://t.co/1yPKFJZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Social Media Super Bowl: I’m going to go out on a limb here and say that the Super Bowl will be the biggest,... http://t.co/QL6pjR6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art and Science of Using Images in Email Marketing: If you want your email to be memorable, possibly even to... http://t.co/qO4RkSZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Plans to Fund Recovery Through Data Protection Fines: Ok, it may be that I took a liberty or two with the hea... http://t.co/WaITyr6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Social Media – Part Two: This post was written by our Social Media channel sponsor Full Sail U... http://t.co/EuvEx0Lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Privacy Policy- All For One, One For All!: Google must have had a meeting at the end of 2011 that possibl... http://t.co/dAmd4yPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Combines 70 Privacy Policies into One. User Data Sharing Is Part of the Mix: Google is integrating some 7... http://t.co/XrcspBBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Women Are Decisive, Ambitious and Stressed: I am woman and if you hear me roar, it’s probably because I’... http://t.co/Dhbo2YpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global E-Commerce's Language is Not English: Copy Blogger plucked an eye-opening stat from a J.P. Morgan-prepare... http://t.co/2lzZWHNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Google updates name policy | Twitter acqires Dasient | Android favored by developers: Social Media:

G... http://t.co/6I8J29tU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks Is Into Them. But What Exactly Are CDFIs?: A quick guide to Community Development Fund Institutions: H... http://t.co/QGFf1tvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Hits New Video Milestones – 4 Billion Views Per Day, 60 Hours Uploaded Per Minute: YouTube is growing st... http://t.co/qYJydbU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Time to Evolve: Introducing Evol8tion and Startups for Brands: OK, so it only took me a year to finally ann... http://t.co/KL8vigo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Don't Be Evil search tool | Digital music grows worldwide | R: Search:

Facebook, Twitter devs rel... http://t.co/FNAP1h03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Users Upload 60 Hours of Video Per Minute: Reuters is reporting that users now upload around 60 hours of... http://t.co/BkDRnA2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gibson Takes on the Government:  http://t.co/a87xAdIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slideshow: Rock ’n’ Roll Royalty:  http://t.co/HRHRcEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DAA Launches ‘Your AdChoices’ Campagin for Consumers: What do jackalopes, killer veggie burritos and taxider... http://t.co/lUMxoL2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loyalty the Latest Function to Join Email Marketing: For the past few years email marketers have been beefing up... http://t.co/XxXKkGFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Bing Is For Doing: Bing is not the decision engine anymore. In new ads there is a new attempt to position th... http://t.co/PNCCSM0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s “Search Plus Your World” to Kill Facebook and Twitter?: This post comes from our SEO channel sponsor Li... http://t.co/AbS1Vdyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MegaUpload Knocked Offline As Feds Arrest Admins | Then Why The Need For SOPA & PIPA?: MegaUpload is no more, at... http://t.co/lOFNXyFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted: More Black Entrepreneurs: Startups are seen as key to halting erosion of the middle class http://t.co/qScYfrFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Megaupload takedown | Apple's textbook foray | Anonymous strikes back: Social Media:

Facebook Tim... http://t.co/f9h9ymjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shark Tank vs. Undercover Boss: Which Are You Tivo-ing?: See what's coming up on both shows this season, which k... http://t.co/QjDiEfZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft, Google Incorporate Gamification in Unusual Places: Microsoft and Google are incorporating gamificatio... http://t.co/ldqj53xK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Nears the 500 Million Mark, But How Many Have Flown the Coop?: Hear that? That’s the sound of 9.3 people... http://t.co/OugAdHWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Branson on Strategies for Success: A look at the most helpful advice for entrepreneurs from the celebrat... http://t.co/MglYuPOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google+ Adds Auto Hashtag and Photo Text LOL!: Google+ is nothing if not well balanced, they’ve recently release... http://t.co/bGaMnDJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hosting a mastermind meeting in Los Angeles, great group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70 Percent of Consumers Won’t Buy from a Company They Don’t Like: 70% of consumers said they wouldn’t buy a prod... http://t.co/QC2GCM4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luxury brand Ralph Lauren Scores with Online Sales: Ralph Lauren Corp. reported a telling figure in its latest f... http://t.co/3CUKel5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple 4S Release Seriously Dinged Android Purchases in Q4: I am not completely convinced of many things surround... http://t.co/PxrbHAhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Business Marketing Workshops, Seminars and Keynotes: Small Business Marketing Workshops, Seminars and Keyn... http://t.co/t7IqKjBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Videos and the Conversion Factor: With videos appearing in the 70% of the top 100 search results, compan... http://t.co/h8ohDois]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Techshot Hopes to Monetize Value in http://t.co/nM1pfW6S URL: Techshot has hired lead generation company, LeadJen... http://t.co/xVfpmalz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Open Graph App-slide Scheduled for Wednesday: As if most don’t already feel as if they have handed thei... http://t.co/RnHhF8Km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six Mistakes Entrepreneurs Make When Seeking Venture Capital: Learning how to pitch investors is an invaluable s... http://t.co/vixIaqdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers Give Facebook Shopping a C+: This past holiday season, consumers had more ways to shop than ever befor... http://t.co/C2vqFSp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Get Down to Business with Google Search, Plus Your World: After analyzing the obvious (yes Google+ con... http://t.co/3UB0RQXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven Ways to Whip Your Website into Shape: Here is a guide for giving your business website a makeover that wil... http://t.co/npkZNa6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning Marketing Strategy Into Action: Turning Marketing Strategy Into ActionThis content from: Duct Tape Marke... http://t.co/r3PzkUvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Hanks’ Animated Series ‘Electric City’ Finds Home At Yahoo As Web Video Matures: Web video is maturing, with... http://t.co/H7H4Shzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo! Site Explorer Is Dead – What Are the Alternatives?: This post comes from our SEO channel sponsor Link Ass... http://t.co/d3lfrxHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greatest Running Shoe Never Sold: How hard is it for an independent inventor to sell an idea to a multinatio... http://t.co/HWDkRMk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bing Tops Yahoo for Search Share in December: Microsoft’s Bing search engine grabbed 15.1% of the total search p... http://t.co/6u2nSfF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employees, Maybe You Do Own Those Social Media Contacts After All: The question of whether a company or its empl... http://t.co/4l2whizM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Comments Goes Mobile: Facebook is bringing its Facebook Comments option to mobile sites. Facebook annou... http://t.co/ttz2A6Xj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Improves Image Search: Google has tweaked its image search functionality to make it, well, more visually ... http://t.co/ekT2htfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Plans (Reluctantly) for a 7-inch Tablet: When Google’s acquisition of Motorola Mobility is complete it wi... http://t.co/jzRQyIbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Improves Related Image Search: Sometimes it’s fun to just see Google make a search change like the good o... http://t.co/9HxWTgnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast Unveils Streampix – A New Streaming Video Subscription Service For Cable Customers: The U.S. cable compa... http://t.co/g9qCtTZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ads on Your TV, Your Phone and Now Your Glasses?: Imagine you’re walking down the street and as you pass a Starb... http://t.co/klilKVCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gamestop, Others Gives Up on F-Commerce. Are They Right?: Amid growing signs that Facebook commerce, or F-Commer... http://t.co/caTND39p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn's Rapportive Deal Bodes Well For Email-Social Integration: LinkedIn has acquired Rapportive–a transacti... http://t.co/9Cldu97X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Should Take a Home-Office Tax Deduction?: Fearing audits, relatively few taxpayers claim a home office. Here... http://t.co/xVjDF9E4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>