<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Catholic Ireland man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust this to happen in the year I move abroad https://t.co/M8w9xiNQpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@under_thecosh @clncrwfd Count me innn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenWills Wenger has some sort of voodoo hex on Conte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bjarm_ @TheFinal_Third @under_thecosh Thx m8 x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexLukasNathan Yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNoveltyAct 💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies @TheFinal_Third Cheers man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rise911 @TheFinal_Third @FUCKEDUP @TheNoveltyAct I love Fucked Up! And thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Oh yeah? Nice. Tell him to hit me up if he is haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin @JackRathborn Don't think that's the case this time around. Just genuinely think a few of those players aren't up to the standard of a top team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies I don't think they are in this case. Just think quite a few of them aren't good enough for a top team. Conte's negativity hasn't helped either, but I think he's just been worn out by the incompetence of a directionless board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@No1isChelsea This is exactly it. The club can't continue with this short-termism. It's sucking the life out of the team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea are a leadership club who willingly sack managers, sign bang average players, ignore the best youth academy in the country and have no long-term plan. Why on Earth would Hazard and Courtois extend contracts for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely Chelsea have an academy midfielder or two who would do a better job than Danny Drinkwater?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenWills Not if Luis Enrique is in charge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tehTrunk Probably wouldn't start ahead of Son tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he hasn't contemplated it already, this 90 minutes could push Hazard over the edge and fully convince him to leave Chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBlairNewman It's sickening really. If this Napoli can't win it from Juve, then who can? Worrying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell by the devastation amongst the Napoli fans in the stadium that they know it too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that's Juve's 7th title in a row anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@under_thecosh It's why they never win anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust Roma to show up for the first time in months in the one game I want them to lose ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Proper order. That is despicable behaviour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilbronikowski The worst part is you know it's coming, you can see it unfolding and there's nothing you can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConJClancy If Napoli manage to win the Scudetto from here it'll be one of the greatest achievements in the history of football. Juve would crush your heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juventus are evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mo Salah is going to be incredible in that Real Madrid frontline next year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tehTrunk BIG OPINIONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darren__holland Atlanta bookies favourites. Not sure why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new video for @TifoFootball_ on Ed Woodward's rise through the ranks at Manchester United that I worked on with @JM_Devine if you're interested there https://t.co/AERyGaQBqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Fucking wish I was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_Flynn4 Apologies. Forgot you were Instagram's beer expert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to discover Canada has these bad boys. Quality https://t.co/0mkcHw3wUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rise911 Hard to tell. Mbappe has already delivered in the knockout stages of the champions league, so he's pretty exceptional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is about as good as it gets from City. Total football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteTudor123 This a thousand times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephenmaaaaac big ups on the film blog. Felt like a broken record telling you that you should've done it haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Keating91 The main reason I'm envious of the snow back home is the excuse for everyone to go on the piss midweek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyTheNic Likeable, funny, engaging and never afraid to probe pundits with facts on typically PFM nonsense. Best football anchor around alongside Jimbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BetBright: New - @ConorPacKelly  Believes that Alvaro Morata is Looking Increasingly Lost At The Top Level

https://t.co/XrLkUed1Ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corrzauber You'd miss the pure madness of it haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main take away from the snow storm back home is that pretty much everyone's back garden looks the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Hess Anyone who makes the Ballon d'Or their primary aim in football deserves all of the above]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alvaro Morata is just not good enough for a top four team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBrewin_ Feel your pain here. Seems like a tragic thing to witness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching this in a New Zealand bar full of Welsh and English fans in Toronto and it's fucking magic #IREvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Very much so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Sexton strangely wasteful from the tee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Against Ireland in Dublin it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic Wales this. Utterly dominated yet somehow find themselves in front]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl Wash your mouth out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's some properly brilliant and inspiring music coming out of Dublin at the moment. This Kojaque EP being latest. Ace https://t.co/SNDLOOSjqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDiss Not sure if it's fun, but still one of my favourites https://t.co/qAD09kIDtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregianjohnson This is proper good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read that it's the final Bruce Willis at home tonight. I'll always have the fondest memories of those nights in Lost Society back in the day. A special time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kvn_clmn One of the great delights of living abroad now is avoiding that spoofer's analysis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steviegrieve Forgot what an absolutely ludicrous performance that was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning It's as important as the League Cup imo. In fact, I enjoy the league cup more because it doesn't have the nonsense narrative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomMc_Sports: Will Grigg has more goals against the Top 8 PL teams than Lukaku this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Magic of the cup'.... nah, it's still shite and doesn't matter by comparison to the league or the Champions League]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Hess Tevez sprinting along the touch line and cupping his ears in front of Ferguson when he scored his first goal against United]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@COILIROILI I believe in u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning @BetBright @TifoFootball_ So you're telling me you see a path back into the first team for Rashford? Where in Mourinho's history as a coach has he given a young player the time required to develop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteTudor123 Sevilla is a much tougher draw in fairness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New for @betbright on the futures of Anthony Martial and Marcus Rashford in the wake of Alexis Sanchez's move to Manchester United. Both should look at Kevin De Bruyne &amp; Mo Salah for the answer https://t.co/bWo9BhIQp4 https://t.co/wdJTpx4i0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteTudor123 You could add in Liverpool there as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TCite92 Pathetic really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year is 2026 and Real Madrid have won the champions league for the tenth year in a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Convinced of the same tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never any doubt that refs will give even the most marginal penalty decision in favour of Barca and Madrid at home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commiserations to all back home who have to sit through LFCTV because @RTEsoccer wouldn't show the belting Madrid-PSG tie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul Why does any media outlet still pay him to talk about football? He's been out of touch for at least a decade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastcarbuzzy @Mark_Flynn4 Get fucked troll scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tehTrunk Sitting in a bar and I'm getting weird looks as I chuckle to myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gigi should just play forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never back against Juve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millar_Colin The point they were making was more that the Sanchez signing pushes him further down the pecking order. And given Mourinho's track record with young players, entirely valid debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobPalmer_OTI I'd happily ship Netflix before Spotify. Probs the best subscription fee I pay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobPalmer_OTI Bad decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Milk in coffee in Italy. Tut tut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul Probably more in touch with golf than he is with football tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvertonianJamie @SachinNakrani @F365 Would possibly take Scholes though tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvertonianJamie @SachinNakrani @F365 Depends on your definition of world class imo. For me, world class is a player who would definitely start in a world XI. Cole the only certainty for me during that era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SachinNakrani @F365 The only true world class English player of his generation. Great piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iightworks This. Totally agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iightworks It's to the point where I'm not even excited by Drake projects because there's such an over-saturation. Literally no intrigue about him. Not even in the same ballpark as Kendrick these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iightworks Never gonna happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotRothwell @kenearlys @SecondCaptains Sweet debut man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@under_thecosh Read that he's considering playing on beyond this season anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@under_thecosh Wait, has Gigi not retired?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz God, he has the most punchable face in ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Already in tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Mackenzie Haha you sound like my Leeds supporting uncle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul The Denmark game felt like a natural conclusion. Just don't see any way back tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Mackenzie We'd end up rescinding Spain's World Cup medals at that rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Mackenzie When I'm FIFA president, the first thing I will do is outlaw the Ballon d'Or and all other individual awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul It's going to end very badly this time around, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holllyyyyy fuckkkk, this is incredible. Great job @RichieSadlier https://t.co/9FOFowLcum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garebear__11 @waynefarry No one deserves to discover him in their mentions]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>