<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JVandepolder awesome - whats your booth number at harmony? im 36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JVandepolder hey thanks for following! caledon...where is that? im from st catharines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3JsPhotography thx for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diggin this owl piece. http://t.co/ynooanLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New sushi paintings!! #HAF2012 http://t.co/pNTYAjE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an updated shot of my giraffe painting which will be on exhibition @harmonyartswv starting this Friday! #HAF2012 http://t.co/2gWI9fPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday's I make art outside http://t.co/15dXlMco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece in the works for @harmonyartswv #HAF2012 http://t.co/5HOjDtmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New progress on this owl painting. It's starting to come together nicely... http://t.co/JVQZDlhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missyleegeiger my bad - 'background,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm uber stoked for the Harmony Art Market which opens Friday, Aug 3. I've been wrapping up a lot of new pieces... #HAF2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv yup, you got that right! very west-coast inspired subjects :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv i love makin em cuz theyre a cool variation to my larger canvas works :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv check these sushi paintings out! Some of these-and new ones-will be at the Harmony Art Market! #HAF2012 http://t.co/4ZGcJJNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm working on a new sub series of sushi panel paintings, to be available at @harmonyartswv starting next Friday :) #HAF2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitalann thanks! ill be looking at doing some urban decay inspired pieces in the coming months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitalann thanks for the follow! i dig the background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First layer of colour on these parrots http://t.co/zkoBPmcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flipflipmeheidi thx for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deEscalate hey mate thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoonApe thx for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaisyBits thanks for following me! i like to paint :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm teaching @OpusArtSupplies today in downtown Vancouver. From 2-4pm I'll be going through the steps of my artmaking process :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonyartswv hey guys here's some work i'll be exhibiting at the art market! stoked!

http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harmony Arts Festival is in Two Weeks! I'm stoked to exhibit these pieces and more by the water in West Van:... http://t.co/fP7mUimz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new piece in progress of an OWL. The colours are funny in this photo, but the ink work and lines make sense :) http://t.co/OrEMEYUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missyleegeiger nice bg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited to paint these fellows http://t.co/qFmDYAvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part about documenting this painting is that the best light for the photo was in a beach bathroom http://t.co/tNLOMPkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends! This Saturday I'm demo-ing my artmaking methods and techniques at Opus, downtown Vancouver from 2-4pm!! weeeeeeeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW SUSHI PAINTINGS STARTED WEEEEEEE
http://t.co/dEIDhzCk via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new flamingo painting I'm working on. Love outdoor summer painting :) http://t.co/NYxwKEIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New sushi paintings! Here's the start of a fresh order of ten http://t.co/J1g69st7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest animal study!

Aquila Chrysaetos  20" x 20"  Ink, acrylic and newsprint on canvas  2012 http://t.co/VadXVYFY via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShudderGallery thx for following guys! i walk by shudder all the time on teh way back from my studio (165 e hastings)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pharr2 thanks for following me!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHayesArt thanks for following mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check it - doing a demo if u wanna see some artmakin techniques, on the 21st:

http://t.co/B0gtFqaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CultureCrawl: How many is too many? 326 artists registered as of today. The highest ever for the 10-weeks-to-go mark. 
http://t.co/c ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indi_gone ya second that! i was at a friends apartment recently and someone was throwing out an old poster print of that sign! i swiped it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7wonderlicious thanks for following :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new work I started. I built up more textures than usual, which really grabs the paint in interesting ways. http://t.co/3rSW3IBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet just got registered for this year's East Side Culture Crawl :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This abstract piece is very yellow so far!! http://t.co/29NGNSdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's more progress on this abstract piece. I wish this photo showed the textures you see in real life :) http://t.co/T8qVZcxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lorenzshan hey there! love that line "addicted to the mountains and ocean".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is super awesome: http://t.co/vz3PceyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HUSHVancouver thanks for the follow - where are u guys based in van?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreLeMasurier thanks mate! its been one year exactly now since i started back at it - lots of stuff happening in one year already! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreLeMasurier super good mate! art in vancity my friend :) (and the ol mac of course during the days :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreLeMasurier been a while mate hope your are well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelissaMercier thank you for following me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished first layers of ink drawing. Next up-more paint and collage http://t.co/3xOWym3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check my new giraffe painting here: https://t.co/XUHtJBJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinylVancouver thanks for the follow guys :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanessaVlinder hey there! nice colours in that background :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a recent commission piece I did for a friend - it was a sneaky surprise birthday gift :) http://t.co/zd9Ogi7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a few days off after the recent shows - recharging the art sparkplugs :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Lum doesnt reside in Vancouver anymore, but he has a new article for Canadian Art Mag: http://t.co/MxveWXPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warndt cant remember if i replied to this but no the show was the last two weekends only.. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraylingsinVan haha thats fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraylingsinVan hallo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moeinika thanks for following meeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warndt no it was the past two weekends only. I'll b making lots of art on the weekend tho! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BIGTRAVdotCOM works for me mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsoltis ya man send it along, I'd be curious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsoltis hmm I'd considered the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha. Sure do! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling i did a run of shirts and had them hand screened too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling i had a lot of requests this past show for reproductions, since a high price point excludes most people from getting one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would reproductions devalue my work? what do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warndt thanks mate! it was a blast to make it - lots of new pieces on the go now too..!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warndt how goes mate. i like your splash page :) you were at the harmony show while i was there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like my new abstract methods/approaches here? http://t.co/cLEt1XC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PetleyJones thanks for the follow - really dig the space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated progress-abstract #3! bwauuu http://t.co/16yBwnFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract progress - lines are lookin cooooool http://t.co/FAkQJnvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding some line work! Digging these abstracts! http://t.co/jnrjHaxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract #3, part two! Bwwawww http://t.co/f6z8bZKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harmony show day 5-starting this new yellow abstract piece, zany! http://t.co/MBtud7Rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second weekend at harmony arts festival starts tomorrow -  I'm stoked to keep demoing my new abstract piece.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraylingsinVan thanks for following!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GatherPopup hey there!! whats the venue to be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QiyiTam heeeeeeeey!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByNatureDesign thanks for following! those are neat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might've just not mentioned it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liangzhed hey thanks for the follow. your personal blurb there sounds a lot like me haha (to-van, painter, GD, beaches and bikes..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I worked on this abstract piece tonight. I'm building up more layers on it and starting to increase the contrast. http://t.co/tPpXseCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting thicker - neat effects http://t.co/Uv7k9YH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reversing my halftone stenciling effect here - i pressed the stencils into primer to create raised dots instead! http://t.co/PGinzS8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curranjosh i have the lens hood at work, can keep it safe an sound here until we can meet up :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to get prepped for the culture crawl at octopus studios...it's gonna be great!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checkin out a cool show tonight at SMASH gallery - never been there but the space looks and sounds rad :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya guys I'm stoked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thursday evening mixing of neon yellows and pinks http://t.co/jhS0iTeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I brought it with me. Can meet u anytime to return tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed man! Thanks so much! Ps I have part of your camera :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DusanPos oh for sure! id crumble inside if i wasnt outputting as much art as possible (after work hours, that is..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting stuff up on my profile page for the @CultureCrawl - http://t.co/WVpATWWe]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>