<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to Share a File with a Friend? Pipe It Over Facebook!: I spend a lot of time on Skype. One of the things ... http://t.co/4yiwwV5Rzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Overcoming Early HR Hurdles: Of all the struggles you'll face as an entrepreneur, hiring, training an... http://t.co/rr3FMtdJqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google CEO Larry Page's Vocal Condition and Breaking the Silence About Illness: How business owners can keep a... http://t.co/S6t3mzVYAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs May Eighteen: My weekend blog post routine includes posting links to a handful of tools or great ... http://t.co/LKn4N3B0a9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes: What It's Really Like to Pitch for a Spot on 'Shark Tank': Meet the entrepreneurs who lined... http://t.co/2N7b75srIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Secrets for Lifelong Success  From Martha Stewart: The celebrity entrepreneur discusses her philosophy on wh... http://t.co/VbJ5QGARE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Banner Ads Does It Take To… | Google's 'Enhanced' Campaigns Strain Definition: Signs of Doom:

Hubsp... http://t.co/O74VH5qPGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make Strategy More Than a Nice Idea: Few things are more confusing to business owners and marketers tha... http://t.co/y6s0OLK04v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Young Entrepreneur's Best Friend is His. . . Mom?: A helping hand from mom -- or dad -- can be vital for newbi... http://t.co/BBj25iH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ValueClick Adds Digital Video Ads To Its Offerings: ValueClick Media has announced the launch of its new digital... http://t.co/mBGrfPvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mapping the Mobile Future, Apple To Drop Google Maps for In-House Creation: Apple is rumored to be drawing one o... http://t.co/mibWk0XV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gearing Up for Its Public Offering, Facebook Opens Terms and Policies Hub: Facebook is about to go public with w... http://t.co/Zn9Ml4yC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lookout Safeguards Smartphones, but Do Consumers Care?: The startup's security app detects threats, yet many use... http://t.co/I8o1k8qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail eCommerce Spending Continues Double-Digit Growth: Do you sell things online? Yes? Great, cause I have som... http://t.co/90Eh7cd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rating the Best -- and Worst -- States to Do Business: Find out how your state and county compare to the rest of U.S. http://t.co/Y8jUKo2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook App Center: 900 Million Potential Critics: More work for marketers and app developers. Facebook yesterd... http://t.co/xydhlJmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Facebook’s App Center Answer Their Mobile Prayers?: Facebook has announced their new app center.
From the F... http://t.co/YNnZqSLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Businesses Burdened By Slow-Paying Customers: About one in seven small business owners cite payment irregul... http://t.co/xbPTTrsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Maps For Android Now With Offers and More: Google does one thing better than anyone else (in my opinion, ... http://t.co/23KU1XCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Marketers, Advertisers Trust And Conduct Media Audits: At the Association of National Advertisers’ annual A... http://t.co/IKrmpoB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Places Unveils New Tool To Manage Bulk Listings: If you have ever dealt with Google Places in any way you... http://t.co/xADrj9bH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Inside Look at Arizona State University's SkySong Incubator: Before you start up, you might want to consider ... http://t.co/7h4EX5A7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Online Companies Using the Wrong Data to Measure Success?: Everyone knows you need analytics on your website... http://t.co/tvxldNDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 75% of Tablet Use Occurs in the Home: A recent study by Viacom states that tablet users are most comforta... http://t.co/HZizdvd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Infosys Launches Marketing Platform | Salesforce Magic Quadrant | Experts Decipher Oracle/Google| RTB ... http://t.co/BPlpDY2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect Your Company's Website From Malware: While most business owners are aware of computer viruses, they're l... http://t.co/69EeFvvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand Building and the Impact of Social Media: When asked about brand building strategies, marketers in a recent... http://t.co/P5hjpkxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Beyond the ‘Like’: Facebook Action Links and Google’s Faux Pas: When social sharing was fresh and new “lik... http://t.co/e23GoGSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Forums May Be the Most Powerful Social Media Channel for Brands: Forums and message boards can help you conn... http://t.co/7N1zW6zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demographics: Men (Particularly Affluent Ones) Love Online Shopping: Never mind the perception that men dislike ... http://t.co/DmpIw0j4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impact Investing for the Rest of Us: You don't have to be Bill Gates to make a difference as a social entreprene... http://t.co/hmXGKh57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Things You Don't Know About Tony Hawk (Video): In this Trep Talk Extra, the skateboard icon and entrepreneur s... http://t.co/TRHYw3R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs May Five: My weekend blog post routine includes posting links to a handful of tools or great conten... http://t.co/89ga17w9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Out Tonight? Zoom In, Point And Click: New nightlife apps from three young treps give scenesters the insid... http://t.co/7FSRcySb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: You Might Be A Scumbag:  A few weeks ago I heard some SEO friends talking about how an SEO they know... http://t.co/NW9c3Bs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key west from the air, not what i expected to see, but v. interesting http://t.co/SIpPn0Vp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Rolls Out ‘Offers’ To All-ish: Facebook is famous for dangling the carrot then pulling it away when you... http://t.co/h5wSrQvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New App Pushes Newspaper Display Ads, Daily Deals to Facebook: “Newspapers today have these really big audiences... http://t.co/Y4ZJwU4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh Founders on How to Partner with a Big Company (Video): In this Trep Talk Extra, the creators of a global b... http://t.co/h2mQTqFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SMB’s Who Embrace Mobile See Success: Did you know that May was Small Business Month? Neither did I. In honor of... http://t.co/HMlquIcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girish Navani: Examining a City's Health: With a trove of electronic health data, his company EClinicalWorks aim... http://t.co/EPZcFebo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Retailers Saving Big on Debit Card Processing Fees: Federal Reserve report shows financial reforms are maki... http://t.co/5moSTNRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Launches Sponsored Discussion Board for Women: LinkedIn is one of those sites that I should use more th... http://t.co/UxduyZbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Spirit Airlines No Refund Policy Worth the Reputation Damage?: Spirit Airlines is in the midst of what could ... http://t.co/mDnOv84A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Buzz: 2012: Year of the Online Political Ad: Business Buzz:

2012: Year of the Online Political Ad [INF... http://t.co/HKfUfsUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey Says Social Customer Service is Popular but Messy:  There’s nothing like the spirit of competition to mak... http://t.co/OWautOmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Breastaurant' Battle Ends With Pair of Press Releases: Hooters and La Cima, a franchisee for Twin Peaks, reach ... http://t.co/xT0MQ3lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Are More Social -- When It Comes to Social Media, That Is: A new report shows women are the major players ... http://t.co/MRI31W6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Hawk on Selling Out Without Being a Sellout (Video): The skateboard mogul shares why he doesn't stress abou... http://t.co/jzeBSBwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email Marketing: Mobile Will Overtake Web-Based Email This Summer: It will be a quiet shift, but a huge one. In ... http://t.co/pxy3L87S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Prioritize As an Entrepreneur (Video): The first step in setting priorities as an entrepreneur is to view... http://t.co/4pooLd9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New President, More Overseas Investment on Yum's Menu: The parent of KFC, Pizza Hut and Taco Bell plans new grow... http://t.co/UvR6HAg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Theater Policy: Please Do Not Silence Your Cell Phone: Second-screen usage while watching TV is a growing tr... http://t.co/ADpqdGRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank You To Our Marketing Pilgrim Sponsors: While the Internet marketing news front is a little slow this is th... http://t.co/mxENWZ6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Gets Hit With Fine for Obstructing FCC Investigation: Google’s Street View is a very helpful tool when yo... http://t.co/e3yrjhlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Looks to Make Search Ads Move Mobile Apps for Advertisers: Today Google announced several improvements to... http://t.co/JiALoVIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Your Staff Sabotaging Your Pricing Strategy?: Making sure your sales-team members understand the way profit w... http://t.co/gpcq3P9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study Shows Social Media Marketing Management is Haphazard at Best: A surprising number of people are still conf... http://t.co/7AACOWYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs April Twenty Eight: My weekend blog post routine includes posting links to a handful of tools or gr... http://t.co/h6KmBrh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: Don’t Waste Your Time Learning To “Code”:  Every now and then I hear a friend of mine that works in ... http://t.co/r8Iztshh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair Trade's Growing Pains: Pivoting a Successful Model: The founder the Fair Trade certification program in the... http://t.co/PwVOfegH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nielsen: Spring Training, March Madness Took Over the Web: The bad news is that March is gone, and with it, Majo... http://t.co/85BZAaYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just What Is A "NewFront?" And Should Brands Be Interested?: It would have been fun to see cranky interviewer Pi... http://t.co/5pWVWdcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Don’t Need No Stinkin Process: I’ve spent the last decade or so preaching the gospel of systems thinking for ... http://t.co/GPbExBuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Acceptance of Cause-Related Shopping is on the Rise: Nearly half of all consumers surveyed said they’ve... http://t.co/Ak3xzmQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Positive Customer Experience Leads to Customer Loyalty: A happy customer is a loyal customer. You probably alr... http://t.co/oTduHK0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When It Comes to Networking, Farmers Will Always Beat Hunters: Asking for the business too soon is a common netw... http://t.co/FjQJPSKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Math: What's a New Customer Really Worth?: You want to market to gain new customers. But what is a new... http://t.co/xSbH9FpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groupon Looks to Grow Up (Burp!): I know the whole daily deals thing isn’t very newsworthy to our readers. I get... http://t.co/ThQo7BEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Fans Rejoice: Your iPad App Has Arrived: The popular business networking site has created an app for Ap... http://t.co/P0KBLkDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Runaway Tow Truck and the Unpredictability of Social Media: The televised high speed pursuit has become an o... http://t.co/4IwnMGTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Age of Pinterest, Google Wants You To Know How To Index Images: First, social media took the art of the c... http://t.co/dNCT7qqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons from the Founder of Stumptown Coffee Roasters on Becoming Powerful and Influential: How did Stumptown Co... http://t.co/s6VeoFGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Spending on the Rise: There are 32 Billion Apps for That: How much do you spend on mobile in a year? Figu... http://t.co/J4PVXLZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: DG Buys Peer39 | Porsche's QR Strategy | Google, FB Lobby | FB Revenue Falls | Netflix Vs. Comcast: Bu... http://t.co/XaixXDJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Consumer Market: Huge, Largely Untapped, Won Through Fair Representation: Only 26% of Black consumers feel... http://t.co/YuD28DHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daymond John on Engaging Young Entrepreneurs and Building a Better Business: The 'Shark Tank' investor shares hi... http://t.co/m3A0jaR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Takes a Bigger Bite Out of Mobile Impressions – Maybe: InMobi just released their Mobile Insights Report f... http://t.co/J9TDZQTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZenithOptimedia Group Rolls Out "Live ROI" Tools, Brand Image: Media agency network ZenithOptimedia Group has la... http://t.co/SvmWhocC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Hawk on Building a Brand Around Doing Your Own Thing (Video): Skateboard icon Tony Hawk talks about the cha... http://t.co/UYo1VhM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Dads Buck the Stereotype When it Comes to Shopping for the Family: When you think about advertising aimed ... http://t.co/M0b2EYPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube to Give Away $50 Million in Free Advertising for New Video Program: Google's video publishing powerhouse... http://t.co/3pHCxGFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulu Ramps Up Original Programming, Adding Four New Shows To Already Impressive Line-Up: Although online televis... http://t.co/n2RodlY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterest is On Trend But Does it Convert?: Unless you’ve been without an internet connection for the last few m... http://t.co/D6VCxQu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco: Video Will Drive Internet Growth Four Times By 2016: Cisco has released its annual Visual Networking Inde... http://t.co/C03HF3Dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Facebook's IPO Debacle Means for Startup Funding: The disastrous Facebook initial public offering isn't lik... http://t.co/2EE3pRKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Reasons to Develop for Android First: As part of our desire to help our readers see more of the Internet and ... http://t.co/vxXgiyOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What We Talk About When We Talk About Recession: A new survey shows that 71 percent of small business owners thi... http://t.co/vbZccKwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google: Some Display Formats Dying While Others Thrive: “It might be time to hold a wake,” said Google of some o... http://t.co/h4HdWkKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving Awareness with Vehicle Advertising: You can get a lot of free exposure in your everyday trips around tow... http://t.co/Agjfpcud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New VIDEO explains opportunity to make money from local businesses: http://t.co/j8r1TZKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killer Tips to Making Web Videos and Marketing Them Like a Pro: Whether we watch them on our smartphones, YouTub... http://t.co/t9HZYaFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Takes Steps to Build a 21st Century Digital Government: Franklin Delano Roosevelt brought the country clos... http://t.co/1zrK3xtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Eating Entrepreneurs Today: Small-business owners have a lot on their minds these days. http://t.co/JJdo1tXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would You Buy A Facebook Phone?: The New York Times has reported that Facebook is once again trying to build its... http://t.co/bzIMkda0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Branson on Office Ties and the Company Dress Code: The British billionaire calls for banishing the tie a... http://t.co/fBJe0k4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Begin With a Referral In Mind: A referral is the result a job well done, exceeded expectations and delivering an... http://t.co/2Wc0NfLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gtrot and a Vision for Local Discovery (Video): Zach Smith of Gtrot talks about the company's changing vision an... http://t.co/C9iAGkG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank You: 
Pilgrim’s Partners: http://t.co/Bmghq1Lo – Bloggers earn cash, Advertisers build buzz!

 http://t.co/mEPzRtJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Episode of 'Help! My Business...' Web TV Show is Live http://t.co/tY0kxqOJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>