<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @FredRAlexander are all matt damon films in the same continuity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @FredRAlexander So they're set in the same universe at roughly the same time and he survived interstellar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredRAlexander @strongmisgiving the subtext of both films is let's fire matt damon into space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @heytherejeffro: ♪It's like BAAAAAAAAAAAAAAANE
On your wedding day♪
#RoyalWedding https://t.co/4FshWqYlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[turns out everything is sadder with French horns. https://t.co/r750BeZMIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[performers/showing off types: what do you wish you had known before you did your first open mic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisHewitt: This is incredible. A man has set a reminder so that he can have an argument with another man in 20 years. Now if that isn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Silent_Tongue: I suspect this sort of request will cause a meltdown in a journalist's inbox as this awful behaviour is rife... Anyway,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thermoso this must be what billy corgan felt like when he wrote bullet with butterfly wings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this morning: ABOLISH THE ROYAL FAMILY
this afternoon: COME ON MOTHERWELL FUCKING DESTROY THEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will concede that, by the standards of opulent events in the age of austerity, it had better representation than usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had 'our day', but we, y'know, paid for it ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone has tweeted 'just let them have their day' about the wedding, as if we had any fucking say in the matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@actualprincecas I feel like you could cut "trying to discuss centrist dad memes and the word gammon" from that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving i look forward to you meeting an assassin disguised as a postman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drewmagary: (Reads about Jordan Peterson) 

oh, so he’s a dipshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josherick3 I hope it's not ironic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering increasing my woke credentials by claiming the narrator in my early poems is gay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scriblit: So...

meBODY ONCE TOLD ME THE WORLD IS GONNA ROLL ME https://t.co/aGqvZxLE4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InterrobangEdin: The folks @hiddendoorarts found @DougGarryPoet lurking @LeithTheatre &amp; asked him about #theambassador and his infamous…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @ricky_ballboy Surely he is my avatar this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lituainianach: eh i know this is controversial in scotland but i dislike neither edinburgh nor glasgow and you all need to chill and ta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gross_its_me: Faceswapped a cat and a husky and made a cursed image https://t.co/tsFqS2lewY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Skoogeth: In Shrek, Shrek grabs a frog, blows it up like a balloon and IT FLOATS.

Does this mean Shrek has the ability to exhale pure…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cocteautriplets: Hey guys I found this beautiful old high school, 1 careful owner, surplus to council requirements that's right near th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re last RT - this is part of the reason I thought Infinity War made GOTG2 into a worse film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jenniferbrozek: Avengers spoiler in the article. THIS. This thing that @therisingtithes writes about. I was furious when it happened. I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords I will look in tesco for a "30 years of trend bucking" card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords Both were awful. I dare you to buck the trend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving IT is your greatest mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Good good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving you seen this? https://t.co/JcB76W8mBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheHitch: It's official guys. No turning back. No sirrreee. Actual full hour on my own with nothing but me, several cameras, and a bag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords 31 is just like 29 though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alissamarie: Genuinely worry that fandom is a disease https://t.co/CCw9LEGnCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Mac13 I think the audience will be radio 4 listeners who think the news quiz has got a bit edgy recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate I respectfully agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MHarrison90: When the phrase "English nachos" appears in my timeline... https://t.co/LfpkG4khss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To encourage new writers the BBC have given play-writing opportunities to Frank Skinner, demonstrating what anyone who is one of the most famous comedians in the country can achieve https://t.co/P3U8QClrLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords Please do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords Can you add More Robbie in there somewhere?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel like Catty Subtweets would be a great name for a news anchor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roy_gill Don't listen to him you're doing fabulous sweetie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did a little sick in my mouth, my eyes, my soul https://t.co/7iH3XbRLa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_dcalg: Jamie Oliver ends everyday by driving to an empty car park and eating a 4 pack of uncooked, freezing scotch pies. He uses his t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prawn_meat: me: what a lovely day! even the flowers are singing! 
flowers (singing): the sins of our forefathers bind us to the dirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yiddouche @strongmisgiving @ringo_starrrr @nataceae Listen to More Robbie by Daft Punk if you get the chance. Sound of the summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo @strongmisgiving @essikert @stefmowords @ringo_starrrr Such is the power of more Robbie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmyDentata: By 35 you should have taken out at least ten replicants and panicked over the possibility that you yourself are a replicant…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @etherwaves: Roddy in today’s @heraldscotland josherick3  #scottishpoet… https://t.co/CPzPldvbHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Papapishu: gonna be haunted until my dying breath by the image of a camera turning into George Lucas https://t.co/ntRmQlZsqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @essikert @stefmowords @Dashmundo @ringo_starrrr No no
No no no no
No no no no
No no there's MORE ROBBIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Start with refilling the nor loch, keep it simple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pappystweet I think it's best if Tom doesn't come here https://t.co/64cd6IxyCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a wall fell on him, poor sod https://t.co/m6jnahcDHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @essikert @stefmowords @Dashmundo @ringo_starrrr So give me pressing more Robbie
Eaaasily
I've seen so much I'm going blind and I'm brain dead virtually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @stefmowords @essikert @Dashmundo @ringo_starrrr Why do I always press more Robbie? 
Is it cos I lied when I was seventeen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo @ringo_starrrr @strongmisgiving @essikert @stefmowords Mooooooooove closer
Hold more Robbie next to mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords @strongmisgiving @ringo_starrrr @essikert Let's get physical, physical
Let me hear more Robbie talk
More Robbie talk
Let me hear more Robbie talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords @strongmisgiving @ringo_starrrr @essikert More Robbie, no cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringo_starrrr @essikert @strongmisgiving put your hands all over more robbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@essikert @strongmisgiving I have unleashed this upon my timeline and found it good content]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathos doesn't get me, but really good scripting on the other hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cried at the sheer brilliance of compressed storytelling in the first two pages of all star superman https://t.co/36BVXaKwae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal Arts https://t.co/hy9olP3bD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving I dunno her well enough to speculate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving - the umpire is Lorde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/FG4e1r56Ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving - have three hoops behind the bowler guarded by a wizard
- appeals to the umpire can be aided by meme usage
- The wicket is replaced by a ceremonial gammon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my cat does not like the Sea Devils soundtrack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SimpsonsSPFL: Liam Lindsay: "You? Got called up to the Scotland squad? You?"

Lewis Stevenson: "Sure, you never have?" https://t.co/uDG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving anything with 'your body' in the lyrics can and should have it replaced with 'more robbie']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringo_starrrr this exact phrase was in my school report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bresaola is air-dried, salted beef that has been aged two or three months until it becomes hard and turns a dark red, almost purple colour. It is made from top round, and is lean and tender, with a sweet, musty smell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historically Helen Lewis hasn't been great on slur chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GoldenHareBooks: Despite James Daunt and @waterstones open promise that their copycat indies would only open in areas with no independe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcQueer you seen this? https://t.co/W4B16Oljgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoisAnnounces Kudos for trying one where the drums are kinda important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josherick3 Excellent. Might start playing Mogwai bass lines in Joppa around 6 ish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuckyIsotope: B52’S GUY: I got me a car that’s as big as a whale
NEIL DEGRASSE TYSON: I’m going to murder you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[has anyone ever seen a busker doing shoegaze?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unamccormack that scene where he's processing everything that's happened and doesn't know whether to laugh or cry was my favourite bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can't wait to see Danny Swanson and Michael O'Halloran come on to change this game

*laughs bitterly forever*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a nugget of purest Hibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dohoodle: For anybody hurting, for whatever reason: shuffle will betray you and play a song you're not ready to hear. Albums &amp; playlist…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulavarjack @strongmisgiving @brightonfringe Cool, my plan of not leaving Scotland is paying off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gavinworby: I haven't seen this story in ages. https://t.co/QM9ILQ93Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing but respect for my Eurovision winner https://t.co/VJJiWvIj8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah let's have Eurovision in Jerusalem, what could possibly go wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other people eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next year we probably shouldn't try too hard #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmphysics: When you look in your toaster and find a wee borrower #eurovision https://t.co/qZXvc2S1YW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's never a wicker man around when you need one #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SpacewhaleHana: Best gif ive ever seen #Eurovision https://t.co/zFG1dv5qRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kieran_hurley: Eurovision, but for weird esoteric sound-based performance art. Same production values, same overall high camp aesthetic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: "More of a comment than a question" https://t.co/sl1chQ72oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy have already forgotten their own song #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've gone full Shakira]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumjodwyer We do not have to tolerate YOUR BULLSHIT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>