<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[MDS Coordinator: Crystal Heights Care and Rehabilitation Center in Oskaloosa is looking for a qualified MDS Coordinator to join our team. This is a great opportunity for an RN with long-term care/ skilled nursing experience. This position is full time… https://t.co/Bvr6sOTsxa https://t.co/22x7EajJ8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer/Analyst: Job Description At Wells Fargo you’ll find a team with proven track records of success who are smart and possess strong values. You can enjoy a diverse career as you learn and grow your capabilities across our… https://t.co/i2ScX0d75u https://t.co/6uyaWygQZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer: iOS App Developer needed for minor updates to major feature builds. Part time/Full time. Looking for someone who can work "outside the box" as we We currently have an office in Phoenix AZ with our main office currently being… https://t.co/yP6VB2C9Zv https://t.co/BIfN7HeV9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Position Description Position Requirements SG is an Equal Opportunity Employer and does not discriminate against applicants due to race, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, veteran status, or on the basis of disability or… https://t.co/pqICurS25u https://t.co/dd88ykVhQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer, Sr.: Systems Engineer, Sr. Location Simi Valley, CA Employment type Regular – Full Time ID 86 Apply Now Who We Are Based in California, AeroVironment (AVAV) is a global leader in unmanned aircraft systems, tactical missile systems and… https://t.co/VXGBvnRZAY https://t.co/EA897ObEsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer 4:   Job Description – Systems Engineer 4 (17015079) Systems Engineer 4 Requisition ID : 17015079 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/9SEeJBCH3p https://t.co/NT5OWAmry3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer: Sr. Web Developer at eBay Skip Navigation Press tab to begin typing your search or press escape to close. Search Site close MenuHeader Logo – Our Company – Overview – Who We Are – Connected Commerce – Our History – Our Leaders – Our… https://t.co/GpFOs4IKLY https://t.co/GncPZaWWtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support: Technical Support Our client, the eighth largest commercial bank in the U.S, is actively looking for a Technical Support to join their team! Duration: This is a 8 month long contract to start Responsibilities: * Providing management… https://t.co/slJpJQW6XV https://t.co/0ctAvZxYHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer: Informatica Developer ===================== Apply now Date: Apr 10, 2018 Location: Blue Ash, OH, US, 45242 Company: Kroger Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business: Corporate… https://t.co/19JeGVrW9y https://t.co/sXjUc8svXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Data Analytics Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/APoVqdlaDK https://t.co/VhuorPtrd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Health IT Interoperability Lead – Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/PHuccMY2z5 https://t.co/VVOEoaiqsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytic Apps – Insights Platform Distribution Lead: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/UrnLFsWVCU https://t.co/egw5Z8CN0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Supply Chain – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/5j7HGwLIXA https://t.co/45CUNLTJLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data &amp; Analytics Technologies – Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/6Hntyf0lz3 https://t.co/LmuakdwE4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory TMT Tech Strategy&amp; Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/DYz6ZgQFcm https://t.co/Y7IYtWtmu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotics Process Automation IT Process Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/lIc4K7v35s https://t.co/hMSqxCPCoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Systems Engineer: At JJ Sonik, we bring individuals and companies together with a specialization in relocation. Top three reasons to consider relocation: · You can always come back home. Today, companies don’t expect you to retire from… https://t.co/YROsKeZCiq https://t.co/d6J3SROsuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator 4:   Job Description – Systems Administrator 4 (18002403) Systems Administrator 4 Requisition ID : 18002403 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/BEbw2CoSrl https://t.co/NOFmGKRggz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Intern: Job Seeker FAQs and Support – Jobvite Contact Blog Job Seeker Support Customer Support Customer Support Job Seeker Support Support Plans Login Customer Login Job Seeker LoginHello Bar 2018 Recruiting Benchmark Report: Learn How… https://t.co/WTUYu35q2A https://t.co/qAvQNNyCmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: COMPUTER/IT Ariba, Inc. seeks a Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of specific product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Eng,… https://t.co/SICN4CJdta https://t.co/ynTzSckGS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asset Protection: Position Description Communicates with (or to) individuals or groups verbally and/or in writing (for example, customers, suppliers, associates) and conducts directed shrink related audits and report findings to appropriate leader or… https://t.co/IO8ojHfef1 https://t.co/mNRhlhqHUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager- Commercial Interiors: Costa Mesa, CA Full-time $90k – $110k Posted Today We are an up and coming firm who specializes in commercial TI. We have made the OC Business Journals fastest growing company list for the last 3 years.… https://t.co/yWV5lQiKeh https://t.co/D7448su5o5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Unix/Linux System Maintainer: 106241BR Senior Unix/Linux System Maintainer CO – Aurora Raytheon IIS/GIS provides Operations and Maintenance support for the Intelligence CommunityRaytheon is currently seeking a Sr Information Systems Technologist… https://t.co/GydoNONMQO https://t.co/XQvvvAAC06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows System Administrator/Analyst 2:   Job Description – Windows System Administrator/Analyst 2 (18003835) Windows System Administrator/Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18003835 Location : United States-Ohio-Cincinnati US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/YXK631ADkV https://t.co/LAC6NwqlNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Attorney – Original Content – Legal and Studio Affairs: Production Attorney – Original Content – Legal and Studio Affairs Job Number: 113660182 Culver City, California, United States Posted: Apr. 9, 2018 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job Summary Apple’s… https://t.co/9l2AUMVgxt https://t.co/JDEgxYmzby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/WhpExoytRd https://t.co/WlEkoEESVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Linux / Platform Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/UtoUhZF6cU https://t.co/BmCRmdxKbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Support Analyst 4: Job Description Wells Fargo WWT Platform services division is seeking an Systems Support Analyst 4 to provide Level 2 Application Prod Support for lending applications. Level 2 support comprises of senior application support… https://t.co/0RYWV7TGQH https://t.co/CAWe34Xeo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: San Jose, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today San Jose, CA, US- RELOCATION INCLUDED! **Your application will be considered incomplete unless the screening questions are answered, and incomplete applications cannot be… https://t.co/zTHmhb9gI3 https://t.co/wbLwQAOb5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Researcher (Engineer Systems) 4:   Job Description – UX Researcher (Engineer Systems) 4 (18005051) UX Researcher (Engineer Systems) 4 Requisition ID : 18005051 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes… https://t.co/GTwnjkOhD7 https://t.co/x2tmtNh8RE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Team Engineer: Red Team Engineer Job ID  2018-15702 Primary Location  New Jersey, Jersey City Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  Omaha,Nebraska,United States;St. Louis,Missouri,United States;Ann Arbor,Michigan,United… https://t.co/VcESJk8z2z https://t.co/QlnsrqYDgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NC Programmer: Country: United States Work Location: St Louis State: Missouri Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do JobPurpose To define, plan, design and refinefixtures, data and processes necessary… https://t.co/338MJCjSa3 https://t.co/igTPIVK92H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. ETL Developer: Calance Job Opening – Sr. ETL DeveloperJob Openings | Calance IT StaffingJob Openings – Calance Calance Creating Customer Alliances – Job Openings – By Job Title – By Date Created – By State – For Employeers – Contact Us – Corporate –… https://t.co/eKEj2OOLZj https://t.co/pTMs0s1GfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Computer Forensic Specialist: Senior Computer Forensic Specialist =================================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: NACIClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job… https://t.co/L114ppzmwH https://t.co/ENhCdgIUCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer The Office of the Revisor of Statutes, a nonpartisan office in the Minnesota Legislature, is seeking applicants for a Systems Analyst/Programmer I position. The office has implemented an XML-based, bill drafting,… https://t.co/nsZg8dXnQP https://t.co/7ROnPBvU5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member Technical Staff #DC1-N: Looking for Senior Member Technical Staff at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Design, architect and create solutions using Java, Micro services and Cassandra NoSQL database.  recblid g3ukvkv7nkb0u6wdafg35aqw5eeugv https://t.co/rFD3JvxjaS https://t.co/D67gIQVrLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Architect: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/KeOhyMDajW https://t.co/1DU6v2PY6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Payspot, Inc. dba epay North America (Leawood, KS) – Software Engineer to dvlp secure transaction process sys, enterprise apps, sys admin apps, sys integration &amp; distributed WAN sys incl embedded terminal apps. Req’s Bach in IT or Soc… https://t.co/9HltQchQFk https://t.co/HRNCapf8MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer #18-MG0218: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV industry.… https://t.co/nOXksYqzOe https://t.co/iW5F3ftxDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Analyst: Hibu Inc. is seeking a Senior Database Analyst position for its King of Prussia, Pennsylvania office. The Senior Database Analyst is responsible for performing database systems development, contributes to the data management… https://t.co/atHK4yKZqb https://t.co/hgfz06UFHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Arlington, TX for Software Engineer Advanced to design, develop, modify &amp; implement software programming for Teamcenter Application products.  EOE recblid nl1lpqz01tbz6dloqaldji8tz9i5hf https://t.co/PwPbqtXliH https://t.co/U94iHS3o8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAVPower Power Bank Exclusive Deal: A WIRED deal on an outstanding battery pack, Air Force-grade smartwatch, and other gadgets galore. https://t.co/wnzgW5aWLa https://t.co/5dMAzeuJ3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead: Proj Lead, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Define &amp; dvlp UNIX S-TAP release test plan &amp; execution process. Design &amp; implement quality processes &amp; metrics. Anlyze changes &amp; new features based on functional &amp; design reqs. Recommend test strategies.… https://t.co/649DuDGnwJ https://t.co/SAXKo5FXq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Community Enhancement: Director of Community Enhancement  Chesterfield County, Virginia (Richmond-Metro Area) is seeking an energetic, collaborative, strategic thinker who can articulate a clear vision for community enhancement and… https://t.co/j6aiAAdCi9 https://t.co/tve6jRHMs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer #7788: Data Engineer Job #7788 $64,000 – $80,000 Annual (Salary DOQ) Basic Responsibilities: Provide analytic support and services across the organization. Support the development of new analytical models and business intelligence solutions… https://t.co/tW2QHW7M0w https://t.co/hsDEH195nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window Server System Administrator: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Window Server Systems Administrator at Scott AFB, IL. JOB SUMMARY: Leidos… https://t.co/Fh6PkHzXS1 https://t.co/so2RDC5iWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – US: Infosys IVS-FS- Test Analyst Automation Testing Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/EwHsNrVnBM https://t.co/qgaqon3HSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Transactions Platform: Sr. Software Engineer – Transactions Platform at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA About the job: Twilio's customers send millions of communications every day. These communications become a firehose… https://t.co/iVKdhEVxwX https://t.co/uyFM0P6S9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP (168): Strong hands-on implementation and support experience working with latest releases for SAP ECC, CRM, PI, HANA, BW, Solution Manager with SQL server on Windows clustered environment. SAP NetWeaver administration and core technical tasks in… https://t.co/OinsYxwDJN https://t.co/IOShIXGp20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPA Firm Audit Manager: Location Woodland Hills, CA Salary $90,000 – $160,000 Job Type Direct Hire Degree Bachelor of Science Date Feb 09, 2018 Job ID 2568327 CPA Firm Audit Managers &amp; Seniors Well established, highly profitable CPA firm offers several… https://t.co/HLovdhEQsL https://t.co/af1dAf87xT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT PROJECT MANAGER: IT PROJECT MANAGER CONTRACT-FOR-HIRE Duarte, CA Contract for Hire – $125 – 150K (DOE) We seek a contract for hire IT Project Manager to work on IT PROCESS IMPROVEMENT PROJECTS In a hospital / medical environment. WORK INCLUDES: *… https://t.co/KYxhHJatP1 https://t.co/EUY3QuSWk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java/AWS Developer: Java, Devops, Linux, AWS, Jenkins Duration: Contract W2, Long Term Compensation: Depends On Experience Location: Rosslyn, VA Telecommuting not available Travel not required Mandatory Skills: * 2+ years experience with Linux/Unix *… https://t.co/oYasolHBgl https://t.co/zH15qC9XbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Application Developer: You will work in a team with the back-end developers and communicate with the API using standard methods. Responsibilities Delivering a complete application Ensuring high performance on mobile and desktop Writing tested and… https://t.co/k68zVMMX9V https://t.co/kZ7Jm5lo9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: Software QA Engineer, AT SLEEP NUMBER CORPORATION, 111 W Saint John St Suite 1200 San Jose, California 95113, 8+ yrs exp software tester;Tech fld BS rqd;Exp design verification, reviewing specs/ test planning;Exp creating software… https://t.co/XUlpA1Qd9I https://t.co/V9DkZoQHTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Grand Lake Mental Health Center, Inc. Claremore, OK Desktop Support Tech We are currently seeking a Desktop Support Technician with at least three (3) years of experience in computer repair and maintenance. Some basic… https://t.co/PYXE9UaMDc https://t.co/wmqmYiIw2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer # 180031119: Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer Columbus, OH. Design, Develop &amp; maintain various MFTS platforms (Secure Transport, AXWAY API gateway, File Mover, IBM Sterling secure proxy etc.).… https://t.co/IW2qA362ug https://t.co/gmtCcHqKZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Lyft, Inc. has the following openings in Seattle, WA. Software Engineer (SWE) (multiple). recblid 39ypo69ybe7dhq7o3w6ctpa635ui1b https://t.co/GcifPjuyRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE ENGINEER: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Arlington, TX for Software Engineer Advanced to design, develop, modify &amp; implement software programming for Teamcenter Application products. Mail resumes to Attn: Tiara Robinson /Req#223896,… https://t.co/LSujGR27ZH https://t.co/pA3EfBU7hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/6m97Px9coc https://t.co/S4y6au96GC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering – Multiple Positions: ENGINEERING: Quantum Secure Inc (San Jose, CA) F/T positions: Solution Engineer III: Resp for analyze &amp; cust security suite; req Master’s or equiv + 2 yr exp + skills (telcom. ok). Big Data Engineer: Resp for large data… https://t.co/oCZ94G2tJv https://t.co/fhxSwaZ5ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer: Quality Assurance Engineer sought by RGB Systems dba Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Complete manual &amp; automated testing of Extron’s products. recblid afhwn73zkcos9qqbbw3srlk8v5v6tm https://t.co/anR6KyaQ8F https://t.co/segBgzQOx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Specialist #XGGS18FC0318RIC4: Technology Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application Management Services (AMS) in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites… https://t.co/l4F86l1CV7 https://t.co/WiRSZAdPvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administrative Clerk: Administrative Clerk  Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of Administrative Clerk located at our Milton R. Young Station near Center, ND. Position requires a one-year certificate in… https://t.co/5o2UopKdN4 https://t.co/ekOgIam3pu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Ariba, Inc. seeks a Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of specific product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd &amp;… https://t.co/8cpmPp3XA7 https://t.co/fCggPlRaOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst): Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst) Puget Sound Workers’ Compensation Trust and Unemployment Pool has an exciting opportunity for a Senior… https://t.co/POJT5qmCQs https://t.co/pRJrNFRYJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gently Breathing Somnox Robot Cuddles You to Sleep: The Somnox is a fuzzy, bean-shaped robot that mimics human breathing to help the human holding it fall asleep. https://t.co/vbck20yJrK https://t.co/IxlHCtqaDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecom Analyst #80159P: Telecom Analyst The Telecommunications Analyst position is a technical role to support the telemanagement system responsible for inside and outside cable plant records. This position will create and maintain accurate… https://t.co/ThLVNfTGAF https://t.co/jeXkLQbGMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Data Integration Developer: Senior Healthcare Analytics Data Integration Developer (Memorial Health Services, 17360 Brookhurst Street, Fountain Valley, CA 92708) POSITION DUTIES: Develop data integration solutions to end user and application… https://t.co/ai5u0q83Du https://t.co/vqBSoERour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Manomet): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/dl1MsyFv8u https://t.co/Cu4RDY5XLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer I – DOCSIS: Client Reference Code: 210845JOB SCOPE: Charter is proud to have a network that provides service to millions of users across the country. The Network Engineering team is responsible for the implementation of approved network… https://t.co/ZWLcYB9nWS https://t.co/oS7WSbEbbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted 12/01/2016 If you are a Senior iOS Developer with experience, please read on! We are a series B start-up based out of a beautiful office in downtown San Francisco, our company is… https://t.co/MeyTpSnnk0 https://t.co/QBn8Rg9GW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Document Specialist: Clinical Document Specialist ID 2014-4602 Category Quality Assurance/Compliance Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities The Clinical Document Specialist is responsible for maintaining the quality of client Trial Master File… https://t.co/h4Kz4v699o https://t.co/FRYmlxYGli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Lead – Factory Operations: 110711BR Cyber Security Lead – Factory Operations MA – Andover The Modernization and Innovation team has an exciting opportunity for an Operations Factory Cyber Security lead. Take on the role of protecting… https://t.co/2kD60YEGDW https://t.co/OYTmv0ZQnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect/ Tech lead: Trimble  is recruiting for a  Software Engineer/ Tech lead to fill an opportunity in Westminster, CO. Virtual Site Solutions (VSS) is a joint venture between Trimble and Caterpillar Inc. responsible for the development of… https://t.co/ESpEG2wHlu https://t.co/h3aCiXPPmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Global Enterprise infrastructure: IT/Software DIRECTOR, GLOBAL ENTERPRISE INFRASTRUCTURE sought by Burleigh Point, Ltd. dba Billabong USA in Irvine, CA. Responsible for IT infrastructure operational results and KPI’s. Provide strategic… https://t.co/hoaueT8fwv https://t.co/6VsjcaY5ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Engineering – IT Opening for degreed and/or exp’d applicants for Business Systems Analyst in Arlington Heights, IL and other multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S.; send resume by mail &amp; include salary req’ts to:… https://t.co/dqRYLkBHJy https://t.co/RaX1ZIojf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Manager / Data Analytics – Franklin, TN or Eden Prairie, MN: Be a driver of change and run part of the marketing machine at Optum. Optum is part of UnitedHealth Group and a key leader across most major segments of the U.S. health care… https://t.co/et4oYqANZb https://t.co/PdPUIyMgKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Check If Cambridge Analytica Could Access Your Facebook Data: Facebook has released a tool that lets you see if you were caught up in the Cambridge Analytica fiasco—and what other apps know about you know. https://t.co/kisXvXLy6m https://t.co/UzYQnKW4aU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Engineer 3: ENGINEERING Applications Engineer 3 sought by ASML in San Jose, CA, to support leading customer with defect inspection &amp; control challenges, driving technical team to integrate solutions to meet customer reqmts by identifying… https://t.co/P6pphYCD6G https://t.co/WlVplm841V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software QA Analyst: Sr. Software QA Analyst (job code CGS03062018SSQA): Review &amp; Understand clients biz proc &amp; data rqmt specs. Create test automation strategies &amp; framework. Bach deg in CS, CIS, MIS, Biz Admin, or rltd + 2 yrs exp w/ SQL, QTP,… https://t.co/MSxLxIVc74 https://t.co/hlFXUDGVLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer (Payspot, Inc. dba epay North America, Leawood, KS): Maintain &amp; devlp BackOffice system for US/ AU/NZ businesses. Reqs BS in Elect Eng or Comp Sci or frgn equiv. recblid jfjxqcjef56r9lpy8dk231rc8y3sq3 https://t.co/zwkPU9iCMN https://t.co/mPm6z0pjPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Backend Engineer: Livongo Health, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks a Senior Software Backend Engineer to assist a team of software engineers to create software features for the company’s new data cloud. Must have Bachelor’s degree or… https://t.co/GsUJjcTQDv https://t.co/PdOqKyT2CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer Manager # 180032916: Applications Developer Manager Columbus, OH. Estimate project requirements; forecast resources &amp; project delivery commitments. Equal Opportunity Employer/Affirmative ActionMinority/Female/Disability/Veteran… https://t.co/vmgskariXs https://t.co/yPVlVJK7DX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Sigma Infosolutions Inc. S/W dev. &amp; Services CO. in Irvine, CA has openings for S/W Dev. Resp. Understand &amp; translate user req. into well engineered &amp; integrated tech. solutions &amp; reusable components. Design &amp; program… https://t.co/9JsYDRr627 https://t.co/8KSrZZITSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer – Software Quality #2018-43102: Senior Engineer – Software Quality Software Quality sought by DISH Network, LLC in Englewood, Colorado. Design, develop, and maintain DISH digital TV and movie delivery software; participate in release… https://t.co/TbArVDFE77 https://t.co/yxymQeEGSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk/Technical Support Specialist: FHLBank Topeka’s products, services and programs help our member financial institutions provide affordable credit and support housing and community development efforts. We are accepting resumes for the position… https://t.co/mjEOiAlZP6 https://t.co/4EOj67tpZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting Analyst: Senior Reporting Analyst Freedom Mortgage Corporation seeks a Senior Reporting Analyst to perform research and information gathering necessary to define, design, create, and document business requirements and specifications as… https://t.co/tY4SfsvkZ9 https://t.co/N2UYMNfhwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Engineer: Careers At Raytheon One Global Team Creating Trusted, Innovative Solutions to make the world a safer place. Use your engineering skills to make the world a safer place with a career at Raytheon. We partner with our global… https://t.co/rVnvKTmREK https://t.co/xSeKhEhXXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/NFGbQfrsqA https://t.co/JS4uAcyJL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Title:                      DevOps Engineer Category:             Exempt Department:       User &amp; Systems Support Benefits:               22 Days Annual Leave, 15 Days of Sick Leave, 3 Days Personal Leave, 15 Paid Holidays Tuition… https://t.co/5kyrXyEmHy https://t.co/4x4hLHqeRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Best Smartphones of 2018: Guide to Android, Samsung Galaxy, iPhone: If you're on the prowl for a new Android, Galaxy, or iPhone, read our full guide to the best smartphones of 2018. https://t.co/cWVItZpQou https://t.co/YVm2l5B9PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Architect: Arrow Electronics, Inc (Englewood, Colorado) is looking for Enterprise Architect. Work across Information Technology domains as well as business applications to identify opportunities for improving efficiency, enhancing quality of… https://t.co/CVY6m9cdmF https://t.co/U7Dh430zsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer #18-MG0218: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV industry.… https://t.co/NaGQ9K2oYy https://t.co/aKmcf43rzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part Time Thrift Sales Associate &amp; Part Time Keyholder: Part Time Thrift Sales Associate &amp; Part Time Keyholder Needed for Atlanta Mission! We offer a great work environment as well as benefits including Dental, Vision &amp; 403b with discretionary match… https://t.co/7VJUAkloSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRS Operational Risk Consultant 4 (Testing Strategy &amp; Execution): Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers… https://t.co/pbctE2cF8R https://t.co/Ih3L0bnUDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Test Automation: QA Test Automation Alpharetta, GA. Full Time position Job Description: 6+ years’ experience in software testing of web based application and web services Review of functional requirements, writing test scripts/scenarios to verify… https://t.co/RewHQFVi4d https://t.co/XsFTtl4RIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Analyst: About Us Gympass is a disruptive health and wellness platform that connects gyms, studios and health clubs to companies and their employees. We are currently in 4,000 cities and 13 countries and quickly scaling up in the United… https://t.co/E961s5l8u3 https://t.co/EJJWPR2kKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Software Analyst – Intralot Inc: INTRALOT is engaged in the supply of integrated gaming and transaction processing systems, innovative game content and value added services to state licensed gaming organizations. Based on its extensive… https://t.co/7rEUUwiZV0 https://t.co/Ve8dsDPkb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Specialist Module: Engineering Project Specialist Module Job Number: 113505203 Santa Clara Valley, California, United States Posted: Mar. 9, 2018 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job Summary Apple's Engineering Program Management Team is looking… https://t.co/hErI1vm8nc https://t.co/7rX5TFBDM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Analyst: Posting Details Position Information Job TitleSenior Business Intelligence Analyst Position Number ****** Vacancy Open to All Candidates Department AAH Inst PlanningAssessmentResearch Department Homepage… https://t.co/PBwWg7ig5F https://t.co/8ogwkM1vVT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>