<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you found the hidden Disney characters&gt;&gt; http://t.co/5rUn0zoV - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walt Disney once said... http://t.co/kNWnhWfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're only in trouble if you get caught. - Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children have got to be free to lead their own lives. - Sebastian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here together, friends forever. Some things were just meant to be, and that's you and me. - Winnie The Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm with you, I feel at home. –Pooh’s Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be right beside you, because we're friends. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughter is timeless, imagination has no age, and dreams are forever. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't always sit in your corner of the forest and wait for people to come to you. You have to go to them sometimes. –Owl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 of Disney's best princess fashion moments, I love #2! http://t.co/SR9vKv6P - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every laugh, there should be a tear. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, you don't talk very much. I like you. –Ellie (Up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your heart believe, dreams can take you anywhere if you just set them free. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s okay to be afraid. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you believe Disney is giving this away to the 500th visitor tomorrow---&gt;  http://t.co/8TrEPKyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Be Patient" is very good advice, but the waiting makes me curious. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafiki: “It doesn't matter. It's in the past.” | Simba: “Yeah, but it still hurts.” –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/cXWRwAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tell me you love me, like I love you. You know you do. –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m still learning myself. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know how men are. They think that "No" means "Yes" and "Get lost" means "Take me, I'm yours". –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking up via text is the worst. You have to see these breakup texts. #1 is so bad! http://t.co/JRezZtVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heal what has been hurt. Change the fates' design. Save what has been lost. Bring back what once was mine. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're true to who you are, you will always find your star. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because I cannot see it, doesn’t mean I can’t believe it. –Jack Skellington (Nightmare Before Christmas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna miss me while I'm gone, huh? Who's gonna miss me? Who's gonna miss me? –Woody (Toy Story 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/6Ayn6FTr - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a world of laughter, a world of tears. It's a world of hopes, and a world of fears. –It’s A Small World]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people care too much. I think it’s called love. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if it’s not everything I dreamed it would be? And what if it is? What do I do then? –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant believe they would put Disney on this list--&gt;  http://t.co/8TrEPKyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People always do crazy things when they're in love. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So hold on, never let go of your dreams. You’ll see the magic. Believing is where it begins. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you go through life you'll see, there is so much that we don't understand. –Simba (The Lion King II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/cXWRwAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be free to write our own story. Follow our hearts and find love in our time. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even miracles take a little time. –Fairy Godmother (Cinderella)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to put the past behind us. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this great Job! Best part, no experience needed &gt;&gt; http://t.co/jaRBca86 - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends will stick with you until you’re unstuck. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll always be part of my favorite story. –Belle (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll do anything to make things right again. I just have to be brave. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Pott (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking up in a text is the worst. You have to see these breakup texts. #1 is so bad! http://t.co/JRezZtVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye? Oh, no, please. Can’t we go back to page one and do it all over again? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s important to make a good first impression. –Ken (Toy Story Campaign)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/cXWRwAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in the dark, just keep on trying. Suddenly the world is bright. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t stress over anything that you can’t change. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let anyone tell you that you're not strong enough. Don't give up. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't just run away from who we are. –Elinor (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In learning you will teach, and in teaching you will learn. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you believe that Disney is on this list of bad vactions i mean look at #2---&gt; http://t.co/8TrEPKyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary things happen to extraordinary people. –Reepicheep (The Chronicles of Narnia)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “We'll be friends forever, won't we, Pooh?” | Pooh: “Even longer.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Check out # 3! http://t.co/ipUhi04Z - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. –Charles (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is perfectly blue. The clouds are perfect too. And here I am with you, what could be more right? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it’s hard to keep the faith sometimes. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)
Collapse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things never happen the same way twice, dear one. –Aslan (The Chronicles of Narnia)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admire a person who's willing to do whatever's necessary. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pumbaa: “I ate like a pig.” | Simba: “Pumbaa, you are a pig.” –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could be worse. Not sure how, but it could be. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed these hidden #Disney characters in other Disney movies? Retweet if you can find them--&gt; http://t.co/cXWRwAEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to know, but right now all I can do is guess. –Candace (Phineas and Ferb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss you, Daddy. I wish you could be here with us. –Ariel (Little Mermaid II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere there must be someone who’ll love me and show me a world that I never knew. –Anastasia (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not lose faith. –Mushu (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you focus, you can accomplish anything. –Stacy (Phineas and Ferb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In dreams, you will lose your heartaches. Whatever you wish for, you keep. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you haven’t found your talent yet, doesn’t mean you don’t have one. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies don't start fights, but they can finish them. –Marie (The Aristocats)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t you worry, okay? Things will work out. We started this thing together, and that’s how we’ll finish it. –Mushu (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To laugh yourself is to love yourself. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew when I met you, an adventure was going to happen. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many wishes a star can give. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughter is timeless, imagination has no age, and dreams are forever. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love? Just a boy, meeting a girl under the right conditions. –The King (Cinderella)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world. Too many people grow up. They forget. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can stay in here and hope for a miracle, or you can get out there and make a miracle of your own. –Laverne (Hunchback of Notre Dame II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and I are a team. Nothing is more important than our friendship. –Mike (Monster, Inc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes everything seems out of my reach, no matter how hard I try. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you follow your heart, there's no heart you can't win. –Cinderella II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you truly love someone, they never leave. They remain in your heart forever. –Master Gracey (Haunted Mansion)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want and what we need are entirely different things. –Pleakey (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too old for Disney movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change is good. Yeah, but it's not easy." -The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never say goodbye, because saying goodbye means going away. And going away means forgetting." – Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone says, “You can't do that”, our reply is, “Oh yeah? Just watch!” –Disney Imagineer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know at the moment we meet, my heart will start skipping the beats. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mother. She's in charge of every single day of my life. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn’t a dream at all. It was a memory. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the rain, the sun will reappear. There is life. After the pain, the joy will still be here. –Bambi 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not too late to set things right. –Jaq &amp; Gus (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just need to believe in yourself. –Rex (Toy Story 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I go back? I'm not who I used to be. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little "When you ever need me, I'll be there". It isn't much, but it means a lot. –Belle (Belle’s Magical World)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need someone to be my friend, someone who won't run away. Maybe send me an angel, the nicest angel you have. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “Pooh, you have a lot of friends, don’t you?” | Pooh: “Yes, but only one Piglet.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is not the problem. The problem is your attitude about the problem. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>