<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[On the balcony, Roger Stone informs Kellyanne Conway that small business owners are ready to negotiate. Michelle Malkin cancels an appointment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Darrell Issa boldly informs President Trump that European immigrants are becoming too powerful. A lovable old man fails the bar again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, H.R. McMaster patiently explains to President Trump that Lutherans are very affordable. Trump Junior unloads a pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Louie Gohmert decides not to tell President Trump that abortion doctors are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. Don King works the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Rex Tillerson informs Betsy DeVos that retirees are capable of great things. Dana Perino tries on new outfits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Darrell Issa overhears someone tell President Trump that ABC reporters are standing in the kitchen. Carl Higbie sniffs glue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Sean Spicer persuades Kellyanne Conway that rappers are Schwarzenegger fans. Jeffrey Lord falls down a well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Jared Kushner reveals to Katrina Pierson that New Yorkers are hiding in Trump Tower. The sommelier works the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grim-faced Pete Sessions reluctantly explains to Jeff Sessions that movie stars are American patriots. An obsequious reporter quotes Hegel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Darrell Issa overhears someone tell Melania that CIA agents are enemies of the people. Mike Tyson tries to make memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Rex Tillerson overhears someone tell Rick Perry that prisoners are big fans. The maid insults Ronald Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Butch Otter rudely informs Ben Carson that Amway executives are actually gay. A corporate lobbyist plugs a leak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Carly Fiorina boldly informs President Trump that Nazis are not very smart. Ted Nugent wins the lottery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Air Force One, Wilbur Ross politely tells Rick Perry that unicorns are patriotic Americans. Mike Tyson wears a fake mustache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Butch Otter mistakenly tells Jeff Sessions that Jews are at Mar-a-Lago. Lou Dobbs tries hot sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Stephen Miller persuades Katrina Pierson that Alaskans are drilling for oil. Hulk Hogan bogarts the joint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Paul LePage insists to President Trump that Republicans are digging holes in the yard. Chris Christie drunkenly accosts strangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get revenge, Steve Bannon announces to President Trump that unicorns are building a pipeline. Tila Tequila puts on very tight pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Marco Rubio insists to President Trump that the hired help are extremely wealthy. James Woods prank calls talk shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While cleaning up, Rick Snyder proclaims to Melania that conspiracy theorists are drug addicts. Jon Voight comes back to haunt Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Facebook, Carly Fiorina tries to convince Omarosa Manigault that the backup dancers are lurking everywhere. An obnoxious neighbor quotes Marcuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Kevin McCarthy confesses to President Trump that the New Black Panthers are really good at dancing. Sean Hannity finds change in the couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Ryan Zinke overhears someone tell President Trump that Iraqi refugees are buying up Trump properties. An obnoxious neighbor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Rand Paul confesses to Kellyanne Conway that Catholics are airing their grievances. Charles Krauthammer gets lost at the zoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Mike Huckabee patiently explains to Jeff Sessions that rural youth are about as dangerous as kittens. Adam Sandler walks into a spider web.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Marine One, Stephen Miller admits to Omarosa Manigault that red state governors are big supporters. James Caan insults Ronald Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While skinny-dipping, Darrell Issa patiently explains to President Trump that Lutherans are unusually angry this week. Larry the Cable Guy gets voted out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Lindsey Graham patiently explains to Kellyanne Conway that millennials are part of the deep state. Benjamin Netanyahu gets way too drunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Lindsey Graham boldly informs Katrina Pierson that neoliberals are excessively fastidious. Bobby Jindal checks out Grindr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Rand Paul fails to convince President Trump that FBI agents are pro-Trump. Michelle Malkin pretends to be deaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, John Kasich explains to Jeff Sessions that Amway executives are not really worth the time. An adorable orphan quotes Chomsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Steve Bannon patiently explains to Rick Perry that skeptics are coming over for Christmas. A mysterious man naps in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, VP Pence fails to convince Betsy DeVos that European immigrants are infiltrators. Vladimir Putin violates the NAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Ryan Zinke persuades Omarosa Manigault that NAACP members are probably contagious. A local TV anchor creates an international incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a quinceañera, Steve Bannon carefully explains to Rick Perry that environmental activists are dropping big hints. Hulk Hogan tries nihilism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Lindsey Graham confesses to President Trump that Russian businessmen are building the wall. James Caan tries tai chi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While cleaning up, Jeb Bush calmly tells President Trump that college professors are not watching Fox News. A corporate lobbyist kills a baby seal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over coffee, Rex Tillerson fails to convince President Trump that Syrian refugees are drains on public coffers. Peter Thiel gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thanksgiving, Rick Scott politely tells President Trump that Chinese officials are not good with computers. Erick Erickson learns to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a long hike, Jeb Bush tells Melania that Catholics are coming over for Christmas. An adorable orphan oozes pus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Reince Preibus explains to Kellyanne Conway that Nation of Islam members are excessively fastidious. George Will talks awkwardly about sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Rick Snyder decides not to tell Betsy DeVos that neo-Nazis are real. James Woods screams incoherently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Marco Rubio tells President Trump that paleoconservatives are unusually angry this week. Arnold Schwarzenegger talks awkwardly about sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Paul Ryan insists to President Trump that the in-laws are not really worth the time. Kayleigh McEnany testifies in court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Rick Santorum informs Katrina Pierson that red state governors are not returning phone calls. Larry the Cable Guy bores everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the hot tub, Wilbur Ross reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that the Obamas are special guests. Michael Savage finally takes a shower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the hot tub, Hope Hicks announces to President Trump that Black Lives Matter activists are cannibals. The butler plugs a leak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Pete Sessions proclaims to Ben Carson that ex-cons are phishing .gov email accounts. Chris Christie makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Ted Cruz carefully explains to President Trump that Muslims are extremely wealthy. Peter Thiel discovers 4chan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jealous Rand Paul confesses to Katrina Pierson that KGB spies are waiting at Trump Tower. Charles Krauthammer checks out Grindr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Elaine Chao tells Kellyanne Conway that the voters are hiring lobbyists. Glenn Beck gets a swastika tattoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedraggled Roger Stone fails to convince President Trump that socialists are untrustworthy. The butler quotes Judith Butler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Steve Bannon tries to persuade President Trump that felons are patriotic Americans. Vladimir Putin ignores reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Jason Chaffetz convinces President Trump that the caterers are vandalizing statues. Stacey Dash wins the lottery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed John Kasich insists to Rick Perry that black politicians are ripe for the plucking. The White House chef plays Street Fighter II.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, John Kasich reluctantly admits to Melania that Apple and Microsoft are refusing to cooperate. Adam Sandler abandons ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Lamar Smith reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that Presbyterians are in the Oval Office. Tila Tequila bids farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Twitter, John Kasich confesses to President Trump that rural youth are planning something ominous. Trump's body double tries nihilism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Mike Huckabee fails to persuade President Trump that Russian oil executives are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Vladimir Putin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Rand Paul tries to convince President Trump that rural youth are part of the shadow government. Melania's bodyguard greets visitors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Ivanka informs Omarosa Manigault that international bankers are sitting on vast reserves of oil. A lovable old man endorses Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Lamar Alexander fails to persuade Betsy DeVos that rural youth are ripe for the plucking. Trump Junior orders takeout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Ted Cruz divulges to Ben Carson that LA Times reporters are sitting on vast reserves of oil. Mike Tyson snorts a few lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Mitch McConnell divulges to Katrina Pierson that paleoconservatives are conservative Christians. Willie Robertson ignores reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Paul Ryan accidentally convinces Omarosa Manigault that Nazis are patriotic Americans. Karl Rove tries to slip in through a window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Ted Cruz announces to President Trump that evangelicals are terrorists. Kayleigh McEnany drinks all the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Louie Gohmert carefully explains to Rick Perry that Tea Party Patriots are hilarious. Tila Tequila struggles to speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Rick Snyder insists to Melania that Fox reporters are crushed by excessive regulations. The sommelier admits to pranking Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a confusing mixup, Lamar Smith persuades President Trump that the New Black Panthers are potential voters. Ted Nugent runs for office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Stephen Miller rudely informs Omarosa Manigault that Communists are drilling for oil. Ted Nugent has a training montage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Jared Kushner fails to convince Melania that convicts are potential allies. Ted Nugent wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thanksgiving, David Shulkin admits to Omarosa Manigault that the servants are probably contagious. Pat Buchanan gets an ulcer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Mitch McConnell divulges to Jeff Sessions that Trump's sons are withdrawing support. Bill Kristol posts comments on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Nikki Haley proclaims to President Trump that Scientologists are using TOR to evade detection. Bill Kristol wins an arm-wrestling contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Lamar Smith persuades Rick Perry that Chinese officials are faithful conservatives. Don King has plastic surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, General Mattis rudely informs President Trump that the in-laws are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. A corporate lobbyist has an intervention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Jeb Bush boldly informs President Trump that NAACP members are tying up the phone lines. Arnold Schwarzenegger puts on very tight pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Rex Tillerson announces to Katrina Pierson that NRA members are requesting donations. Michael Savage opens all the windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, VP Pence decides not to tell President Trump that the McCains are digging holes in the yard. Hulk Hogan quotes Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Reince Preibus tries to persuade Ben Carson that iPhone users are ignorant hayseeds. The White House chef has to wrestle a bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Jared Kushner rudely informs President Trump that the New Black Panthers are hiding in Trump Tower. Scott Walker forgets to flush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Pete Sessions announces to President Trump that evangelicals are actually gay. An obnoxious neighbor posts comments on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Paul LePage convinces Melania that AARP members are fans of TrumpCare. Cthulhu publishes a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Louie Gohmert proclaims to Katrina Pierson that Tea Party Patriots are alcoholics. Melania's bodyguard solicits donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, Liz Cheney divulges to Ben Carson that Pussy Riot are not to be trusted. Dennis Miller makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, Sean Spicer explains to President Trump that Mormons are not really worth the time. A corporate lobbyist cooks breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Jared Kushner boldly informs Katrina Pierson that evangelicals are struggling to raise money. A lovable old man stonewalls reporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Ryan Zinke tries to persuade President Trump that Somalian immigrants are releasing Trump's tax returns. An obnoxious neighbor unleashes a virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Sean Spicer informs Rick Perry that NRA members are strapped for cash. A lovable old man guest stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Sam Brownback rudely informs Betsy DeVos that journalists are in on the joke. A White House tourist celebrates diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, Wilbur Ross fails to convince President Trump that the backup dancers are dangerous. Arnold Schwarzenegger wears pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Louie Gohmert decides not to tell President Trump that Black Lives Matter activists are planning something ominous. Milo Yiannopoulos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Liz Cheney overhears someone tell President Trump that Chinese officials are ripe for a prank. Dana Perino reads a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Jeb Bush admits to Rick Perry that most voters are extremely wealthy. Michelle Malkin tries on new outfits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visibly sick Carly Fiorina divulges to President Trump that Ponzi scheme conmen are harmless. The maid wears a tutu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While cleaning up, Steve Scalise tries to convince President Trump that MSNBC pundits are waiting in the green room. Scottie Nell Hughes ignores reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedridden Jason Chaffetz reluctantly admits to Jeff Sessions that veterans are immortal. Sean Hannity watches through a peephole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Pete Sessions fails to convince Jeff Sessions that corporate executives are big supporters. Tila Tequila bids farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Scott Pruitt fails to convince President Trump that convicts are in the Oval Office. The valet admits to pranking Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terminally ill Elaine Chao calmly tells President Trump that rural youth are excellent chefs. Kayleigh McEnany posts comments on Facebook.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>