<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/Ym0aUG1sEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/qNXcmRLonH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/uI1GrW6GnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/cvSaVIMwuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/ZQ8CqQjWrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/gCSQdA4mJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/eHy0ExbyER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/pGN5jeAJHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/1f3kJ9Fm6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/L1Ft0kBH91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/ux6rt6cwZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/ORsOfHKWCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/L0jwZDGpGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/HK59YBG7n4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/DZvlvvzRDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/P6IRstSGzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/12VYvhOLIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/B5EDs3oxxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/X61BC3ULwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/SJnWBfOZyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/YmffoSCuwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/sHLPSV4HVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/0DbbjkD1LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/5hl8IdlrqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/F5dc8Nn3IZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/VQC01IWgLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/NJeF8ivwJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/1k53zuk9E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/tr6amLbOOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/6DyKVOS6P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/7dGdnd8WpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/vobLtKHBVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/B1JGqht3Ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/gkl47hSZ8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/wdv8r2kjRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/ECb66jmGDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/2hz1V8CRsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/Ik5fbaQpeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/Fo5Maa7zj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/Oy0ZvvoBcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>