<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: Whenever I see President Trump rail against "Fake News" or call us the "enemy of the people" I think "you can't handle the t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never quit" - @RedSox comeback win bottom of the 9th!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GwjcX1Ou4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Rejected by his parents, gay valedictorian Seth Owen's former teacher and mentor set up a GoFundMe page to help cover his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenhousenyt: Trump is right—the economy is strong. He inherited a strong economy from Obama. But job growth has been slower in Trump'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea ⬇⬇ https://t.co/ulfSBpo3iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: New #BorrowerDefense and #GainfulEmployment regulations are likely to hit low-income students the hardest by:

✔️ Allowi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: TRUMP: Creates fake university to scam students, pays $25 million fine for fraud 

LEBRON: Creates top-notch public high sch…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisCoons: I’ve been hearing @realDonaldTrump and @RudyGiuliani claiming that ‘collusion is not a crime.’ Well, I took the liberty of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianklaas: Turkey’s despot, Erdogan, faced a criminal investigation in 2013/14. He called it a “deep state witch hunt,” fired prosecut…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WillHitchUVA: I resigned from a think tank at UVa today because I felt it betrayed its principles in giving a senior fellowship to Trum…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WillHitchUVA: Hiring Marc Short to explain the Trump presidency is like welcoming H.R. Haldeman into your university at the height of W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @agearan: U.S. spy agencies: North Korea is working on new missiles https://t.co/XeOn6FfDCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: As Trump seems to intensify his baseless attacks on Mueller, we at @ForTheRuleOfLaw will be stepping up our defense of the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxBoot: It is not okay for the president to work with a foreign power to influence a U.S. election. It’s shocking that this argument e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimsciutto: And in 1968, the USSR offered Hubert Humphrey, whom the Kremlin favored over Nixon, financial help for his campaign. Humphr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: Just a reminder that someone stole George W. Bush's debate prep book (and videotapes!) and sent it to the Gore campaign and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hutch_mdrc: After just one semester, @CUNYStart has very large impacts on college readiness for students who have multiple developmenta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipRucker: Just in: Statement from NYT Publisher A.G. Sulzberger, who says he told Trump his “language was not just divisive but inc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1zJsSLXIPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UKMoments: When you only Tweet one word, people will get creative.
https://t.co/0MHcPu6Ond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must follow:  George Conway who speaks his mind and frequently trolls the Trump WH. Must make for some interesting pillow talk with his wife Kelly https://t.co/TTn3qCBetf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news at VA. Wilkie taking charge, pushing out the political hacks who were undermining VA's mission of serving #Veterans 
https://t.co/DxRf2K09tK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Colorado billboard replaces "O" in GOP with Soviet hammer and sickle https://t.co/z3xObb9mSf https://t.co/wvjN2gUueb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @crampell: This is an aluminum company founded by one of Putin's closest allies. For some reason we are trying to keep out aluminum from…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAtlantic: 23andMe has always planned to sell your DNA—and pharmaceutical companies are racing to buy it. @sarahzhang reports on its…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StreetsblogUSA: Uber and Lyft are increasing congestion and undermining transit in cities.
60% of trips would otherwise have been avoid…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: HUGE NEWS FROM @FTC:  Shutting down horrible websites that pretended to be US military, but were actually trolling for #4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iava: Our coalition's important ad in today's @washingtonpost. We're standing up with @GiBillRights and many others to protect troops a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: #veteran Jarrod Thoma and his wife testify @usedgov about the need for rules to stop lousy colleges from defrauding stude…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cspan: As a protester interrupts hearing with @Twitter CEO @Jack Dorsey, Rep. Billy Long (@USRepLong @auctnr1), a former auctioneer, ta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorLeahy: We have discovered evidence that Judge Kavanaugh misled the Senate during his 2004 and 2006 hearings. Truthfulness under…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jack: First, I wanted to step back and share our view of Twitter’s role in the world. We believe many people use Twitter as a digital p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jack: In any public space, you’ll find inspired ideas, and you’ll find lies and deception. People who want to help others and unify, an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Winston_Fisher1: Climate change is an existential threat to our way of life. When will Republicans wake up and realize it will not only…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kaepernick7: Believe in something, even if it means sacrificing everything. #JustDoIt https://t.co/SRWkMIDdaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RBReich: It is logically inconsistent to tell legislators they can limit abortions but cannot limit campaign contributions, yet that’s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulieFoudy: This is #RBG doc is fascinating. So damn good. Turn on @cnn now if you have not been watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNightlyNews: WATCH: @LesterHoltNBC closed out @NBCNightlyNews on Saturday with a look at a poignant moment from Senator John McCain'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: George W. Bush: "Above all, John detested the abuse of power. He could not abide bigots and swaggering despots." (via ABC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VVAmerica: John Sidney McCain III 1936-2018 https://t.co/UlrVnuFsEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs More like honoring a man who happens to be the opposite of Trump in character, service, duty, leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch live #JohnMcCain funeral.  Moving. Inspiring.  Important for America at this moment in time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipRucker: Literally every Washington power player -- Democratic and Republican, past and present -- is at McCain's funeral, except…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @crampell: Washington political consultant tells prosecutors that he arranged for an American citizen to act as a “straw donor” to give…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanchait: "By the early 2000s, a third of the buyers of Trump Tower’s most expensive condos were Russia-linked shell companies or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dweaverDC: WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration is withholding more than 100,000 pages of Brett Kavanaugh’s records from the Bush…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieAstor: I think every woman can look at Ariana Grande's face and body language and viscerally feel what she's feeling. The tension…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @awprokop: Papadopoulos team says that when he suggested setting up a Trump/Putin meeting, Trump "nodded with approval" and Sessions sai…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorLeahy: One-fifth of those documents are DUPLICATES. This hyper-partisan process has hidden more than 90% of Kavanaugh’s full rec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AaronBlake: FWIW, the entire Lester Holt interview has been posted to NBC's website ever since May 2017. If there's something exculpato…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tommyxtopher: Fox News debunks Trump claim that NBC 'fudged' his televised confession to Lester Holt https://t.co/uFjB6NcsW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: The staffer, who went to IMMIGRATION POLICY MEETINGS AT THE WHITE HOUSE expressed his enthusiasm for a "Judenfrei" (cleans…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonahGeffen: Well this is one of the least Jewish things I’ve ever read. https://t.co/a0AJYgYk8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: Food for thought: If the Administration is so concerned with the national budget, it seems absurd that it would propose…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmeacham: Hours-long line to pay homage to @SenJohnMcCain. Just spoke to a Vietnam veteran who waited 4 hours in sweltering heat. “He w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: Twenty-Seven Veteran and Military Service Organizations Submit Comments Opposing DeVos’ Proposed Borrower Defense Rule, w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nprpolitics: "The disease that took John's life – that took our friend Ted Kennedy's life – that took my son Beau's life – is brutal, r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColinCrowell: Former VP Joe Biden's eulogy of Sen John McCain https://t.co/KVujgKzXSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ABC: Joe Biden: "They look at him as if John came from another age,that lived by a different code...where honor, courage, character, in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNews: Former RNC Chair Michael Steele says he doesn't give Ron DeSantis the benefit of the doubt on his "monkey" comment toward Andr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: How many troubled colleges like ITT and Corinthian could have been stopped sooner if they hadn't actively managed their defaul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: @sethmoulton Veterans and military family members can contact us for direct support. Free services to tackle student loan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danpfeiffer: This is an example of the President of the United States abusing his power to enrich himself and his family https://t.co/m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: READ: McCain's final message to American people: "I lived and died a proud American" https://t.co/2ycrIKkhfD https://t.co/vxqH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you ever needed to take the measure of @SenJohnMcCain, just count the days and years he spent in that tiny dank place, and ask yourself whether you could make it through an hour" - @JohnKerry https://t.co/8SYdUOqm1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jameshaning: Trump supporters continue to question if Arizona State Rep. Eric Descheenie, a Navajo American legislator, is here ‘illega…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important from this morning's NYT:  @BetsyDeVosED abandoning oversight of taxpayer $ for college

https://t.co/akaLEiRMk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBushCenter: "Some lives are so vivid, it is difficult to imagine them ended. Some voices are so vibrant, it is hard to think of them…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeoShane: Statement from @BarackObama on the passing of @SenJohnMcCain: "Few of us have been tested the way John once was, or required…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @codykeenan: The other Senator scoffed in disgust and got off the elevator at the next floor. While he was still in earshot, McCain rais…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: In short, we will need more John McCains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Sen. John McCain lived a singular life.

The "maverick" Republican twice sought the presidency and served in the Senate…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindymccain: My heart is broken. I am so lucky to have lived the adventure of loving this incredible man for 38 years. He passed the wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @juliehdavis: “No, m’aam.” How many elected officials would do this now? https://t.co/F9p0Yh8trI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jschmeling: How do reconcile our "Support the Troops" rhetoric and letting for-profit institutions of higher education with terrible ed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WalshFreedom: This whole American flag debate can be so stupid. Yes, I stand for the flag, and yes I will defend that flag. But more im…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LindseyGrahamSC: America and Freedom have lost one of her greatest champions.

….And I’ve lost one of my dearest friends and mentor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#classact John McCain https://t.co/AskNm23ZqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AaronSAment: Important story on complaints persisting against several large chains of schools, featuring @CarrieWofford and @dfcochrane…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jonathanchad: These businesses purposely misled people - many of whom are vets using their hard-earned GI Bill benefits -  into believi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jonathanchad: For more on this fight be sure to follow @CarrieWofford at @GiBillRights and @iava.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: ICYMI: @usedgov's main justification for scrapping the #GainfulEmployment rule is debunked, as researcher who's work is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonathanBlitzer: Did the outcry over family separation surprise the Administration? Yes, official said. “The expectation was that the k…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: Reasons why the ED's repeal of the #GainfulEmployment rule is illogical and unjustified:

➡️ Misinterprets research that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SethAbramson: MAJOR BREAKING NEWS: Lanny Davis, Cohen Attorney, Says Michael Cohen Will Tell Robert Mueller of a "Conspiracy to Collude…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeDelMoro: Ainsley Earhardt, who interviewed the President earlier today for Fox, just told Sean Hannity that the President said he w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: So if you broke the law to win a close election, do you still get to appoint justices for life? Asking for 65.8 million fr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: Do you have student loan debt from a school that lied to you? Tell us your story. We can help you fight back and win. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricLiptonNYT: Here is an extraordinary/blunt admission from Trump-era EPA: between 470 &amp; 1,400 people in the US will die prematurely E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @costareports: NEWS: Trump adviser Larry Kudlow hosted publisher of white nationalists at his home https://t.co/zXGsYdNqs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stuartpstevens: Keep pointing out that Gore 2000 campaign received stolen Bush debate book, which would have helped tremendously in pre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonaldKlain: I'm grateful for Stuart continuing to point this out.  The Gore campaign NOT ONLY returned the book, unreviewed, but the p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Shireman: Conservative @dcexaminer: One thing Obama did that made a lot of sense was to stop throwing federal $$ at for-profit coll…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: Trump tweets that Robert Mueller is "disgraced and discredited" and has working with him a "whole group of Angry Democrat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesFallows: During 1976 Carter campaign, I was in cubicle in Atlanta next to then-foreign-policy-staffer R Holbrooke.

Overheard him…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lkatzenberg Sounds like you are on the way home. We're so happy for you.  Please ask Kris to email me your address :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CREWcrew: Trump’s Cabinet might be the most unethical in history. That has real impact on people who rely on government programs. 
http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @genebsperling: DeVos proposal to eliminate gainful employment rules on for-profits is a scandal &amp; disgrace. As Shireman writes, it was…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: The Times found more than 250 examples of exaggerated, misleading or flat-out false claims by President Trump about the Russia…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>