<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Natural Disasters, Household Welfare and Resilience: Evidence from Rural Vietnam http://t.co/h1VT2xFG2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Adapting the Supply of Education to the Needs of Girls: Evidence from a Policy Experiment in Rural India http://t.co/KjoU4itZuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Crop Diversification and Child Health: Empirical Evidence From Tanzania http://t.co/8IhG2kkCRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: Polluting Industries and Agricultural Productivity: Evidence from Mining in Ghana http://t.co/afu8lQLhl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Rural Policies, Price Change and Poverty in Tanzania: an Agricultural Household Model-Based Assessment http://t.co/VF2WtKPTC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WBRO: Front cover http://t.co/8XNbXT3qV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WBER: Front cover http://t.co/J2pYNyvMMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Beyond agriculture versus nonagriculture: Decomposing sectoral growth–poverty linkages in five African ... http://t.co/V4f6jY9ZM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Fertility, agricultural labor supply, and production: Instrumental variable evidence from Uganda: http://t.co/wcb10Sz6pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Return Migration, Self-Selection and Entrepreneurship in Mozambique http://t.co/fiEUc8qFFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The aid-income link revisited. How plausible and robust are the results? http://t.co/jR1Ybryxnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Facing the hungry tide : climate change, livelihood threats, and household responses in coastal Bangladesh http://t.co/F30wC41Qut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Historical Conflict and State Development http://t.co/7BCYYxyRN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: THE LONG-TERM EFFECTS OF CIVIL CONFLICTS ON EDUCATION, EARNINGS AND FERTILITY: EVIDENCE FROM CAMBODIA http://t.co/azYnx7IAPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Education, HIV, and Early Fertility: Experimental Evidence from Kenya http://t.co/YYmGjnAMBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender and Climate Change in Latin America: An analysis of vulnerability, adaptation and resilience bas... http://t.co/Uw9cB94uVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Should Foreign Aid Fund Agricultural Training? Evidence from Armenia (Working Paper) http://t.co/AxL62ugem0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: What Determines Access to Piped Water in Rural Areas?Evidence from Small-scale Supply Systems in Rural Brazil http://t.co/mfc7kGzPqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Household Shocks and Education Investment in Madagascar http://t.co/wP9jBN1Kvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural production and children’s diets: Evidence from rural Ethiopia: http://t.co/wxEvXThaS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Are the World’s Poorest Being Left Behind? http://t.co/IloAjF2kF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: “Show me the Numbers”: Examining the Dynamics Between Evaluation and Government Performance... http://t.co/x9c4O7OdrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Climate Change and Economic Growth in Africa: An Econometric Analysis http://t.co/t1NFOdtUJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Migration, Congestion Externalities, and the Evaluation of Spatial Investments -- by Taryn Dinkelman, Sa... http://t.co/82gfkg2VCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: The Evolution of the Financial Stability Mandate: From Its Origins to the Present Day -- by Gianni Tonio... http://t.co/urzAsAf2aZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Did the Aid Boom Pacify Sub-Saharan Africa? http://t.co/hPIuXtzzQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of India's rural employment guarantee on demand for agricultural technology: http://t.co/yzYoyJX3zL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do remittances not promote growth? : a bias-adjusted three-step mixture-of-regressions http://t.co/oeeBCea3eU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Beer, Wood, and Welfare http://t.co/DhGkxlwEZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Short and Long Run Effects of Earthquakes on Farm Businesses in Indonesia http://t.co/LuTKW3Ftja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Climate change, groundwater salinization and road maintenance costs in coastal Bangladesh http://t.co/uDqcoJ8DyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Summary of Cows, missing milk markets and nutrition in rural Ethiopia: http://t.co/6kaJ42MFWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Parental Attitude and Investment in Children’s Education and Health in Developing Countries http://t.co/oSHCR1CGKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Mobile Money, Remittances and Rural Household Welfare: Panel Evidence from Uganda http://t.co/DcrREC0Lo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Protecting Child Nutritional Status in the Aftermath of a Financial Crisis: Evidence from Indonesia http://t.co/ALBsn2hFe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Land rights knowledge and conservation in rural Ethiopia: Mind the gender gap: http://t.co/FCxyNReLJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittances and Governance: Does the Government Free Ride? http://t.co/y1UrK1lhc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Microcredit Puzzle: Labour Supply Behaviour of Rural Households in Bangladesh http://t.co/eMTPEVcbqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Household Migration and Children's Educational Attainment. The case of Uganda http://t.co/fetD8s0CS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Two Sides of the Same Rupee? Comparing Demand for Microcredit and Microsaving in a Framed Field Experim... http://t.co/9MESHvR4Em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The development push of refugees: Evidence from Tanzania: http://t.co/7Fl6jt7OEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JIE: Firm Heterogeneity and Costly Trade: A New Estimation Strategy and Policy Experiments http://t.co/gLa24WMj8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Source and Use of Insecticide Treated Net and Malaria Prevalence http://t.co/Q8IK0Srnze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of Ethiopia’s Community Based Health Insurance on household economic welfare http://t.co/G1u9Re4O3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Voting and Peer Effects: Experimental Evidence from Mozambique http://t.co/0NAVPTbYWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural factor markets in Sub-Saharan Africa : an updated view with formal tests for market failure http://t.co/5vYy2QOxPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Informality and Access to Finance : Evidence from India http://t.co/oQiW0uXbKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Coping Strategies in Response to Rising Food Prices: Evidence From India http://t.co/gqOkF6Upzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How Does Ethiopia’s Productive Safety Net Program Affect Livestock Accumulation and Children’s Education? http://t.co/ylR9Cn3gQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Health information, treatment, and worker productivity : experimental evidence from malaria testing and... http://t.co/hMpHBvwdes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Social Networks and Factor Markets: Panel Data Evidence from Ethiopia http://t.co/V69w9BLyRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Leveling Up: Early Results from a Randomized Evaluation of Post-Secondary Aid -- by Joshua Angrist, Davi... http://t.co/hmepM4he1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Distinguishing Constraints on Financial Inclusion and Their Impact on GDP and Inequality -- by Era Dabla... http://t.co/d8ngWIJYrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Domestic and Multilateral Effects of Capital Controls in Emerging Markets -- by Gurnain Pasricha, Matteo... http://t.co/UgiSybfVV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Preventives Versus Treatments http://t.co/DPJ4Wdlmvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Do "Consumer-Directed" Health Plans Bend the Cost Curve Over Time? -- by Amelia M. Haviland, Matthew D. ... http://t.co/nAoKM0k349]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Measurement of agricultural productivity in Africa south of Sahara: A spatial typology application: http://t.co/72Y3NhLn05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Value chains and nutrition: A framework to support the identification, design, and evaluation of interv... http://t.co/BhKpg1WKtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Determinants of Interest Rates in Microbanks: Age and Scale http://t.co/sybpVc4FQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Foreign Aid and Governance in Africa http://t.co/zKvqmHwZSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Income Convergence and the Flow out of Poverty in India, 1994-2005 http://t.co/iGwzEueVzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Poverty persistence and informal risk management: Micro evidence from urban Ethiopia http://t.co/MDVHv1X38M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Environmental and Economic Impacts of Growing Certified Organic Coffee in Colombia http://t.co/ID5snKfaD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Firm heterogeneity in food safety provision: Evidence from aflatoxin tests in Kenya: http://t.co/dTb3Tv3ocR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Food crop diversification as a risk mitigating strategy during conflict : evidence from Cote d'Ivoire http://t.co/lMD0kpEBXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Time allocation to energy resource collection in rural Ethiopia: Gender-disaggregated household respons... http://t.co/uxNXymEvv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How Does Health Promotion Work? Evidence From The Dirty Business of Eliminating Open Defecation http://t.co/397nAwSSdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: Property Rights over Marital Transfers http://t.co/dYwgFmMQ3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Preventives Versus Treatments -- by Michael Kremer, Christopher Snyder http://t.co/ehn8fNfTBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: Prenatal Sex Selection And Girls’ Well-Being: Evidence From India http://t.co/18xPasxEjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: The Rising Resilience of Emerging Market and Developing Economies http://t.co/B6HF47l0i2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Intimate Partner Violence and HIV Infection in sub-Saharan Africa http://t.co/P0yNHusQSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: How Does Health Promotion Work? Evidence From The Dirty Business of Eliminating Open Defecation -- by Pa... http://t.co/F9iiughnw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Your development or mine? Effects of donor-recipient cultural differences on the aid-growth nexus http://t.co/aKz6ekkbC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Of Donor Coordination, Free-Riding, Darlings, and Orphans: The dependence of bilateral aid on other bil... http://t.co/DfpaLXRU4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Minimum Tillage with Planting Basins or Ripping Raise Maize Yields? Meso-panel Data Evidence from Zambia. http://t.co/zixhmfY1IF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: To Have and Have Not”: Migration, Remittances, Poverty and Inequality in Algeria, http://t.co/nR3kRMS6gH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Drinking water salinity and infant mortality in coastal Bangladesh http://t.co/40s4XbTJeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Is increasing inorganic fertilizer use in Sub-Saharan Africa a profitable proposition ? evidence from Nigeria http://t.co/azuKNiHiKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender differentials and agricultural productivity in Niger http://t.co/SYgLcIM3JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Gender Matter when Evaluating the Economic Impacts of Smallholder Land Titling in Zambia? http://t.co/NQ0wxiBww8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Aid, Infrastructure, and FDI: Assessing the Transmission Channel with a New Index of Infrastructure http://t.co/RHjXYzAgq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do Input Subsidy Programs Raise Incomes and Reduce Poverty among Smallholder Farm Households? Evidence ... http://t.co/ZITJRqP0L0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Measuring Access to Food in Tanzania: A Food Basket Approach http://t.co/5k9cwXWs9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Competition in Kenyan markets and its impact on income and poverty : a case study on sugar and maize http://t.co/CNjNgsrPOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Same question but different answer : experimental evidence on questionnaire design's impact on poverty ... http://t.co/bHxYflAuvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Handling the weather : insurance, savings, and credit in West Africa http://t.co/2Ck8iBysu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: When Selection Trumps Persistence: The Lasting Effect of Missionary Education in South Africa http://t.co/lZIkjpXfOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do Agricultural Extension Programmes Reduce Poverty and Vulnerability? Farm Size, Agricultural Producti... http://t.co/AI3Ndl6A9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Impact of Weather Insurance on Small Scale Farmers: A Natural Experiment http://t.co/sczVOvbizj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Moral and Fiscal Implications of Anti-Retroviral Therapies for HIV in Africa http://t.co/OM4ZiJj5Ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Facilitating Savings for Agriculture: Field Experimental Evidence from Malawi http://t.co/RuVALBJfEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Bolsa Família and Household Labor Supply http://t.co/zz5K059Uzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Social Interaction Effects and Connection to Electricity: Experimental Evidence from Rural Ethiopia http://t.co/GeKzwRIfKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Taxation and Political Mobilization: Evidence from Andhra Pradesh http://t.co/wtB3BUhgzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Railways and the Local Economy: Evidence from Qingzang Railway http://t.co/Eqr2ahUqZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDCC: Health Outcomes for Children Born to Teen Mothers in Cape Town, South Africa http://t.co/c7PkcO9ijC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QJE: The Aggregate Effect of School Choice: Evidence from a two-stage experiment in India http://t.co/h96Rpa7EIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gone with the storm: rainfall shocks and household well-being in Guatemala http://t.co/WDcBQrca4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Two Sides of the Same Rupee? Comparing Demand for Microcredit and Microsaving in a Framed Field Experim... http://t.co/ieAoPvjVfS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>