<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/k0k7oVqP80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/eimA2B6Cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/kZGjsIanHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/pepB7OCc5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/xkqjp1wGMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/o4DMlTjyTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/vAFyPvUgjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/tR9iTHZs0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/iWd9NqaX12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAR TREK ENTERPRISE - Brake Light Vinyl Decal - ENGAGE!  --&gt; http://t.co/kkg8rWGnSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/8jPOJK3Yyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/ipUV4AxQjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/cpApeCScJb]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/BBEKgdrbUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/GcRLCyGf53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/fFqbscakh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/hRzoz4NFkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/zhDdPmIyEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/mpiLq8dgD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/TOpH50eKeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/iXI57LuEa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/HyfCo2qLMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/IXcUsASzSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/hwh0FQGq9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/EAE2jE0Etn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/6crverju1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/1Ev6BmZAF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/njFWsuQnMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/tjepDd0JD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/n9R4M9Kuni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/rRJRazjKIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/lqOGAtjffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/VwhinVF9Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/Pzmztra1I9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/EjNC8jY9Yw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/KFcv7ICsad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't tell how much spirit a team has until it starts losing. - Rocky Colavito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/XNDUvHdDTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/AGKykE1ABp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/OoHnZpKWaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/kv4XemW1mQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/oF3wPMGzH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/lUK5YQEdq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/CZbQVrn0GJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/AxZ2LdimI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/1Ev6BmZAF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>