<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/u2bkWoUH6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/F8Abx2E36h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/dyPM1r6jZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/7ngBSIrSO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/BximCiBCPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/NIotKmycJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/7FDLZKNbLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/8vSWkNj03g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/BcWDs7nGUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/tmAWKvoaKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/G898GN4HfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/ZACkKxuS75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/STExzErWTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/SC8JKf7zZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/u2bkWoUH6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/BximCiBCPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/FnBNmHG6uA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/tN6s4UMz9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/zbjejdItS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/rIqDNMj5Td]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/usXmkzKXvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chiffons   http://t.co/8itJFanIpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/STExzErWTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/SR7WASTBbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/zizcGgPKHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/eFdT7GGRJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/AYuLjtGf96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/8rqzkwe7hH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/6Qtt56MZqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/ox2cjVFkRI  http://t.co/VCIdAoPUm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/uCp0ws7hWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/mdmrdfsE7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/PJ3UnbHJQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/O4m9q3YOuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/qwbJeBIPJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/SR5lTOyHrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/TYuIzXpTeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/JbyWgffPm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/xiiuUeTSWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/q2UAB3CsPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/y0FxZta97e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/SsHUzEsbaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/guvok6KsjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/oZyf6ijaoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/ZDqDjFTMgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/N8m6HJja4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/o48Lgu5T1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/8eZ6FQpwvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/vlPGkIGGEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/9fecpyYDnf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>