<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/34h9ttDjIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/hqanM66ftE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/vn7hR9et34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/zApzAEF09q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/kNW7hagFmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/X3FMPp3001]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/VghYco67X9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/lAW7SKLUpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/PTL2hii7G6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/pNkYanDt5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/f79DJgzmQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/Opc0jWAqZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/mEpg29XZVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/pbuEF1xzDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/k5ThUVup6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/L4aWu8GOVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affiliate marketing has made businesses millions and ordinary people millionaires. - Bo Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/bp4OzrnRZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/sbdtinOcEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Tl71sY0XeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/l23xfXUPQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/zi6hEL1qw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/SlkwUcebUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/lkBJCCMj76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your time...don't live too fast, troubles will come and they will pass. - Simple Man - Lynyrd Skynyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/TmoDXemkQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animals are such agreeable friends - they ask no questions, they pass no criticisms. - George Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/2pEwaD4H4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/704AlO5x2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/GwtTQZuAtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/FsSgqGDcax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/hCkW3T9wDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9VWdnzzxT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/VIBN0q0IeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/PnkvVxnw9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/bvLdgVaM3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/eLvY1zDRlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/uxdp1dQ738]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/XFlaW2wYPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/6utKqyPqFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/DFzAuzdax8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/1qASVU7lCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has great marketing, among the best PR and marketing in the world. - Ron Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>