<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End (UI) Engineer: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/siWUlUeUXu https://t.co/s8tCSSB4Bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Technical Lead: At Panaseer, we exist to empower enterprises to conduct business in the digital world with confidence and control. We believe that automation and visibility are the first steps on the road to successful risk management and good… https://t.co/0s9iBXo6iE https://t.co/1mW7Cbi8Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/4fTQCDn7yi https://t.co/nTp4vHnu7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/lNTeVQ0aXM https://t.co/BsbBc2bPWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Systems Engineer: Network Security Systems Engineer Prestigious Organization is seeking a Network Systems Engineer. This position will have responsibilities across the development spectrum focused on creating and delivering a global… https://t.co/cpzoN3KRBH https://t.co/YW7gCPgYhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Automation Engineer with Python: Network Automation Engineer Sr. with Python Salary: $140k ($150k) $170k + 35% to 40% bonus Key: Networking background CISCO WAN LAN OSPF BGP and now is a enterprise automation expert heavy Python. This is for… https://t.co/QrbcJeFy1w https://t.co/zBFkURcbfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/To4aXfuL0b https://t.co/5hd2WhUvCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/SibAd2C3zE https://t.co/qOODQIoh3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/dGb5YmswvF https://t.co/eBmQBUkq7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/KerqHvIKWP https://t.co/16HkxHuoXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia asks Facebook to explain curbs on some media accounts: RIA: MOSCOW (Reuters) - Russia's communications watchdog said on Friday it had asked Facebook to explain why access had been restricted to the Facebook accounts of some Russian media… https://t.co/1t6c4BrrAK https://t.co/OeLaRR56hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software applications. Master’s in Computer… https://t.co/RTJIciFCPI https://t.co/oUHhuXM9WA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX: Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX – Parmesoft Inc. – Houston, TX – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/3OBetKu7ok https://t.co/S7Py48gcJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET): Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) At Skyhigh Networks, we created and now lead the Cloud Access Security Broker (CASB) category, which Gartner calls the fastest growing IT security technology of… https://t.co/QuUKEQvWgw https://t.co/XcR6cn0Wxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Software Developer: Prestigious Financials Firm is currently seeking a Web Software Engineer with Python development skills. Candidate will design, develop, deploy, and support batch systems. Candidate will help architect systems, optimize… https://t.co/Q4IfwbvMV0 https://t.co/naEWa6vxaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/3ZvNiL4EFK https://t.co/GQoHgWCFAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software/Infrastructure Engineer – Continuous Lifecycle Solutions Team: What We Do: The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process… https://t.co/PXBdPA1hLi https://t.co/jomqyUKb3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sailpoint Developer or MuleSoft Developer: Looking for Hands-on Security Developer (must have Java) with SailPoint Identityiq experience who will be part of an Identity Management team to ensure and enhance the availability, reliability and accessibility… https://t.co/Za2hg4dARi https://t.co/9YqqkiOswq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Since 2006, WMC Global has worked with digital services providers around the world to deliver insight into digital threats targeting consumers. By monitoring channels for threat delivery, analyzing relevant data, and… https://t.co/UGNNDiMOm8 https://t.co/DqB3EP50EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead- New Ventures: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/D1TlKNlV62 https://t.co/YS5NObAhRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS – Financial Crimes Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/HHrPKNwXHI https://t.co/ygpKQUfb4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer (Docker): Description: Innovate and create at Leidos! We have no shortage of challenging technical problems. Join Leidos team and apply your talents to solve them. If you are a DevOps Engineer wanting to work at either Reston, VA or… https://t.co/qYjcajz5SN https://t.co/EvPY5eOI6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: The QA Automation Engineer will be a member of the Software Engineering team and will report to the Manager, Quality Assurance. The primary duties of the QA Automation Engineer require the exercise of discretion and independent… https://t.co/XgLLzmABeG https://t.co/sxzMQbY3Mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: At Maxwell, we are inspired by the opportunity to make a difference in society by helping people make better health, wellness and financial decisions. We build applications that support a rich set of interactions among… https://t.co/0iJSr67VOE https://t.co/0UQ3bcnAYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/YVULYNIiTo https://t.co/oP5nroQq7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer – AWS Cloud Automation: DEVOPS ENGINEER LINUX INFRASTRUCTUREAUTOMATION (AWS) * MAKE POSITIVE DIFFERENCE IN OTHER PEOPLES LIVES THROUGH YOUR WORK – WERE NOT SELLING ADS – WERE REVOLUTIONIZING HEALTHCARE FOR ALL * JOIN A SMALL, PASSIONATE… https://t.co/mmXhj6i77z https://t.co/Ls7JxbQaPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/hsieJgk8AZ https://t.co/40rYVUPqDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C/C++, Linux Developer): MRA Member Career Opportunities Software Engineer (C/C++, Linux Developer) Sussex, WI 53089 Company Name: Dynamic Ratings Job Title: Software Engineer (C/C++, Linux Developer) Location: Sussex, WI Dynamic… https://t.co/APBr2cIiuV https://t.co/eo4KjGNQIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Programmer: Associate Programmer – Hertfordshire Hertfordshire N/A Skip Navigation Toggle navigation Account – Refine search – View my account – Sign in Job details Associate Programmer – Requisition ID: ****** – Position: Full-Time Regular –… https://t.co/6JETKZKp4g https://t.co/dlCMNKbLgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Product Development Architect: Treeline Interactive is searching for a Senior Software Engineer to join our growing Development Team. You will be responsible for architecting software solutions on a number different platforms and code bases,… https://t.co/A1ETcu12hL https://t.co/HOHU0Zt567]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Hey, we’re Article. We’re a digital-first furniture brand that’s re-engineering the furniture experience one sofa at a time. We don’t have brick and mortar stores, so we’re able to deliver remarkable value on beautiful,… https://t.co/ghGop0JU27 https://t.co/7L6bXLREMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Architect: Description:Leidos is looking for an experienced Cloud Architect with expertise in the following; designing and optimizing cloud infrastructure and services, a strong application security background, demonstrated success leading and… https://t.co/TJgFePKwsR https://t.co/amRzkz0Pfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python: A well-known prominent automobile manufacturing company is looking to add a Software QA Engineer to their R&amp;D team. In this role, youll be responsible for extending and customizing their existing Python automation framework. You… https://t.co/hrV9zRmQ84 https://t.co/N68GOY6PD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instacart valued at $4.35 billion after latest funding round: (Reuters) - Grocery delivery startup Instacart said on Thursday it had closed its series E financing round of $350 million, bringing the company's valuation to $4.35 billion. https://t.co/bT4kdC2sSd https://t.co/d4Nzww2iSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across… https://t.co/mNld5kA1Ot https://t.co/bhd7TF4r8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted 01/11/2018 Located in a beautiful office in the Mission District in San Francisco, we are an early staged funded B2C Fin-Tech start up that is combining Artificial Intelligence, Machine… https://t.co/U8pFERIxnO https://t.co/rWVRVnrCWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/682mYfpAIf https://t.co/URhMTIMLzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/HSEqEpvCMQ https://t.co/OFfHIdeHyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services (AWS) Engineer: Description: Leidos has an immediate opportunity for a Cloud / Amazon Web Services (AWS) Engineer to join a highly skilled team solving real-world problems.  As a center of excellence, we strive to provide engaging… https://t.co/r4mseqD1Xn https://t.co/YHkdzWg42A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Algorithm (ALG) Software Developer: Description:Leidos/Reveal has an immediate opening for a talented Algorithm (ALG) Software Developer in our Vista, CA office to develop solutions for our innovative X-ray CT based imaging devices used for detecting… https://t.co/uziVwBbNp5 https://t.co/vatLxF7Oft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/7hLzIeIcda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: We are looking for a Mid Level Python Developer for a full-time direct-hire role with our client in North Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Operate and develop within enterprise data environment hosted on AWS. Preferred experience/skills:… https://t.co/tCq3npcyMd https://t.co/i7WTy05618]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Relish Works: Relish Works is seeking a Full Stack Software Engineer to support a new innovation hub. Who We Are We are Relish Works, an innovation hub focused on challenging the status quo and pioneering the next evolution… https://t.co/C2qwEgxpK1 https://t.co/Ql7P7LUDox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/EOZPD7dWJh https://t.co/OdaCe7Wv3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/AukTpkgpqf https://t.co/NURd2gOfey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Programmer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or Computer Applications Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python Programming (either at college level or… https://t.co/HeFwe48reL https://t.co/hNFp7oI66U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Devops Engineer: Devops/ Build Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: software development, build infrastructure engineering experience Expertise in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery Experience with build… https://t.co/eVqgzTrJ2A https://t.co/6wk9SFxyve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/yC2bFd91Je https://t.co/u146XRm1LB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer – Trade Floor Systems: Are you DevOps Engineer looking to work for one of the most prestigious names in Financial Services? If building tooling and working on complex automated trade floor systems sounds interesting, then check this out!… https://t.co/6uQhaAf8q7 https://t.co/LfC11nfMHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metadata Specialist: Job Description Position Information Position TypePermanent Staff (SHRA) Is this an internal only recruitment?No Position TitleUniversity Library Technician – Advanced Working TitleMetadata Specialist Position Number******** Vacancy… https://t.co/nWQwQFAOdq https://t.co/81tJUnhIgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/QTmm2ag1BD https://t.co/DIi8Q90pJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Engineer: Position: Embedded C++ Engineer with IoT Principal Duties and Responsibilities: As an embedded software engineer, you will write software enabling our next-generation of cloud-connected, IoT wireless audio ecosystem of products. You will… https://t.co/cavWAa4dsr https://t.co/ufC0me8A3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Location US-NJ-Somerset | DE | US-NJ-Somerset # Positions 1 Experience (Years) 3 Category Engineering Position Description/Company Info Legrand has a great opportunity for a Software Engineer to work in multiple… https://t.co/hHxoWRcqRg https://t.co/PcOLtWGcjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/XT9plqc1Jl https://t.co/3eCafowfzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/Python Developer/ Software Architect: Responsibilities: Participate in requirement gathering and analysis. Research and investigate design approaches Build quick Proof of Concept (POC) and prototype and evaluate technical feasibility. Work in… https://t.co/0nztGdsGzm https://t.co/7QweA0b7Jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/YylmPDViRr https://t.co/LjVchtf5gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom completes move to U.S. from Singapore: (Reuters) - Broadcom Inc said on Wednesday it had completed its move back to the United States from Singapore, weeks after President Donald Trump blocked its $117 billion offer to buy Qualcomm Inc on… https://t.co/f8BqDyXL7n https://t.co/caUvLCd8e1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Location: Boston, MA Duration: Long term contract Pay Rate: $51 to 57/hr. on w2 with voluntary employee paid benefits No# of openings: 2 Required We are seeking a senior software engineer with background in… https://t.co/uN3Z6Ztr07 https://t.co/a8SogRiGOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Developer Engineer: We are looking for a brilliant mind to join our team, working on solving very real and important problems. You will take a leadership role in our algorithm team to develop machine learning and behavior… https://t.co/6hganWFVJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud / AWS Engineer: Description: Leidos has an immediate opportunity for a Cloud / Amazon Web Services (AWS) Engineer to join a highly skilled team solving real-world problems.  As a center of excellence, we strive to provide engaging careers and a… https://t.co/b6EpJZIBw6 https://t.co/vRbb2PfMtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Web Developer: Description:The Civil Health Group is currently seeking a Web Developer to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The candidate will be a member of the Wintel Operations Team providing development support… https://t.co/wlaCwlLHKV https://t.co/iEgtdPEKsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/RbwEHT2zv7 https://t.co/9iKg6Hfj87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) is seeking a Software Developer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for a real-time operational SIGINT processing system. The applications are implemented in C++… https://t.co/hnkJNS27JQ https://t.co/pBlKikK3bz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Window Server Systems Administrator: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Sr. Window Server Systems Administrator at Scott AFB, IL. JOB… https://t.co/KVxaDIprIZ https://t.co/AlrNmNrZHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – TS/SCI with Polygraph Required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment extends… https://t.co/UH0b0myR1w https://t.co/WWbJcsk77a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Linux Development (C / C++ / Python): Req ID : 355681BR Job Code/Title : E2564:Cyber Architect Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/M2lG02D64C https://t.co/CBMaH5aMDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Flask Developer (Contract, Part-Time): Croscon, a digital product studio, is seeking an experienced senior python developer to join our dedicated backend team focusing on distributed computing solutions &amp; bespoke business systems. You will… https://t.co/imCsBWtwHI https://t.co/onqFtOvZ1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Validate Health: Interested in being part of a small founding team, so you can see your direct impact on improving the healthcare industry? Validate Health is an early stage healthcare analytics company on a mission to… https://t.co/zklpmgWBDo https://t.co/0jPRkbVhMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/ITQeXV755Z https://t.co/g9h3NBtqU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/FcE8inEuHJ https://t.co/Rh72ReiTvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Engineer: ABOUT YOU You will be managing a distributed team of up to six (6) Data Scientists who are part of our client delivery team. The teams mission is to takes on complex fraud detection problems for their enterprise level clients using… https://t.co/OcXTKKnqbV https://t.co/8W8I6hgSlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: In this exciting role, CW will be part of a fast-paced storage I/O R&amp;D team creating and maintaining tools for running experiments and process data in support of… https://t.co/EGage1nYNZ https://t.co/n5GUl2tdi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/31xpmfcRVa https://t.co/dTYoxYhbqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/dYqkdv4Ru9 https://t.co/iqFKGXOJOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/QJW86VjtTV https://t.co/YWEBwU2EHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Tulsa, Oklahoma – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsPython,DjangoTax TermsC2COverview Python Developer 6+ Months Tulsa, OK Required Skills : * Python, Django and angular or… https://t.co/KVb8vlN0SA https://t.co/etOreK0jMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator – NMS: Description:The successful candidate will serve as a member of the Network Operations team responsible for ensuring the continued operation and improvement of the United States Antarctic Programs (USAP) network… https://t.co/0NGjFDP5fr https://t.co/86gdPzeysX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Houston, TX): Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As a world leader… https://t.co/PpGjVe5qIy https://t.co/8xx5hiD270]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook deletes posts linked to Russian 'troll factory': CEO Zuckerberg: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook is expanding its response to people using the platform improperly and on Tuesday said it had deleted hundreds of Russian accounts and pages… https://t.co/Vx7Iwwp8ap https://t.co/nDxaEkjB0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Description:Leidos has an opportunity for a Systems Administrator to work at Fort Belvoir VA.  The Systems Administrator will handle account management, Hardware and Software technical support, troubleshooting, and ensuring the… https://t.co/qNxDj9mcQC https://t.co/RYc33cgKQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist (NCI): Description: PROGRAM DESCRIPTION The Advanced Biomedical Computing Center (ABCC) provides technology development, scientific consultation, collaboration, data analysis and training to the NCI and NIH scientists and staff. The Core… https://t.co/TK5uSkRzyT https://t.co/4pzMhvN11R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/N2M54aPezh https://t.co/W6fhgqmgaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/nnaC1Nlkc3 https://t.co/KYXbeSPNRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer: Description: Leidos has an immediate opening for a Cyber Security Engineer located in Bethesda, MD. We are looking for an energetic, motivated, independent, self starter for a position supporting a dynamic organization that… https://t.co/ZdfwwmkKE8 https://t.co/PisweFxBX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/2QCLlTgVU9 https://t.co/ddyr0P31kO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/4FVWakbvVk https://t.co/XdZt4wXaQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/8NbgqMJvcc https://t.co/M3iISHIQ94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python and… https://t.co/oMD3jp4oqz https://t.co/73icaaqJa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Analyst (Ninja) – Greenbelt, MD: Description: Position Description: The Senior Security Engineer (Software) will work seamlessly with the Chief Security Engineer to conduct security engineering activities, to include:   Responsibilities:  … https://t.co/qLfJ2YYgrW https://t.co/BYL51HJJnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/PGmMvlPTBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Thesys Technologies is a high performance financial tech company with aggressive plans to push the envelope of US trading technology in the coming years. Formed in 2009, our technology already handles approximately 5% of the daily volume… https://t.co/tffPStUs2l https://t.co/4Z2MUBUCgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Boston): QuantumBlack helps companies use data to drive decisions. We combine business experience, expertise in large-scale data analysis and visualization, and advanced software engineering know-how to deliver results. From… https://t.co/Yl9wEH0coS https://t.co/RGz3XmU2tT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: WHAT DOES ORTHOGONAL DO? Orthogonal brings digital best practices to the internet of medical things. We work with leading medical device, consumer and software companies to build products that integrate devices, sensors,… https://t.co/yi1QNuFsFg https://t.co/RzuMn4hBXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA TODAY Network Storytelling Developer- Mclean, VA: Career Portals Job Search Login / Register We are now hiring Req #4109 USA TODAY Network Storytelling Developer- Mclean, VA Development &amp; Engineering Salary FT Monday, March 5, 2018 Gannett, owner of… https://t.co/cqjtRxQGM5 https://t.co/tfeADLTFpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Big Data: This is an opportunity to architect, scale, and maintain world-class analytics and optimization infrastructure that supports multiple LP digital businesses. This is a full-time position out of our Delray Beach office.… https://t.co/AvSxWVx8TH https://t.co/KXyDHJHf3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Full Stack Developer: Job Description DESCRIPTION Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the world leader in providing a highly reliable, scalable, low-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries… https://t.co/PI1uy4H6vI https://t.co/9I6DZcxDwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer (C++/ Python) Hillsboro OR Full Time position Job Responsibilities Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework… https://t.co/ej6LjsP17Y https://t.co/2FPf9KnYeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/0naVSlAK4n https://t.co/5AcW3VLlHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/pu3Otr2sSU https://t.co/AuZuUxI38H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/b6WwdJGUOa https://t.co/wHjK2MX9fQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>