<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/d0eIzl35Kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/YFoxRy1ORr https://t.co/BGGccu1PMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/d33jauHvJd https://t.co/mgg0zANn5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/bFqRQJTFwp https://t.co/c76vlxSoBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/t3Kntjcbp9 https://t.co/kMgmnRLPzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/YkdDEvqdS1 https://t.co/dZwAhp3fGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/0o60ZuSxs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/ZdAsFBJA0b https://t.co/2SsdKJR6sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/k73xQ1clKS https://t.co/iSmMv1mb7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/Uc787L6QPH https://t.co/YmVNdBG3rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Short History of Mark Zuckerberg's Privacy Gaffes at Facebook: Facebook has been updating its privacy settings for more than a decade. Will this time be different? https://t.co/hmN3khi2TX https://t.co/qXiTQs6RoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/2G583avFOY https://t.co/1RvzeTYLEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your paycheck being taxed enough? https://t.co/KFMXeJC217 https://t.co/6T3hiCtxwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/jKaoF2teG4 https://t.co/trDrNioVyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/YvYoirehNW https://t.co/nr2i2VnNfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/3tx5GQoZ7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/LxVyj72hM3 https://t.co/xX7jO3YD8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/4OBwwo8CGW https://t.co/c9jg0cXSFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/XqLBsOIYPh https://t.co/ShApBr4vJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Primary Skills JAVA,JAVASCRIPT,IBM ISIM,IBM TFIM Development Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: IT… https://t.co/rDFImwb4qu https://t.co/C8wrjuktsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/dAJBdcNAbP https://t.co/BE1N8k0STe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/1j69A6yCWs https://t.co/OSYRlJtNpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/p5XBJ0lOD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/Fn6D28i16j https://t.co/6dRA1hFagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/fyOluuzakF https://t.co/8WrhWhNno4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/l6HDzERmvR https://t.co/Qyluv2Zs03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/ICGsyqbXoB https://t.co/bfYGEIkAUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump called Roseanne after successful series premiere: After posting gangbuster ratings for the reboot of her late 20th-century sitcom, Roseanne Barr received a call from President Donald Trump on Wednesday. https://t.co/H2jXc7HurP https://t.co/3noBgzmtlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/HS1H0L3Dco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/UOmO45hpkE https://t.co/0NZdPMYKkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/xsW93mNZ4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/RCIrXnTk6f https://t.co/GZWKUTB9c8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/Ke7mBODO73 https://t.co/5Bn6GEey7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/dHZM5ZMOvt https://t.co/YVTauJZ7o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/D7wRjmN1Zc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Coders Are Fighting Bias in Facial Recognition Software: Facial recognition systems are better at identifying whites than people of other ethnic groups. Companies like Gfycat are trying to fix the problem. https://t.co/EUTeWYr1vq https://t.co/igrc6CIAsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/wT0RiK0R5d https://t.co/VUfC2JLqUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Account Manager OEM / OES: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 1 hour ago Category Sales Overview The Key Account Manager (KAM) is the owner of and the expert for the assigned Automotive Tier 1 Suppliers and their value chain… https://t.co/VRPCuzD9Q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: Oracle DBA detroit, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 02/27/18, Posted Date – 02/27/18 Primary SkillsOracle DBATax TermsC2COverview SR. Oracle DBA Interviewing ASAP 5 years of hard-core DBA with both stand-alone and RAC databases.… https://t.co/w899RjfW1k https://t.co/NQJx1tsfh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/Iq5C01W0Q3 https://t.co/v1kNGLHCmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Why Putting Porn in the Blockchain Won't Kill the Technology: Opinion: A new paper says dirty content encoded in the blockchain could make cryptocurrencies illegal. That's wrong. https://t.co/6OwWvYLsL9 https://t.co/Q2x9FiiGbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/NRPIW2vrGA https://t.co/Arx3w6QmrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/9wPiRJQMVy https://t.co/zB1ftAUdJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donations pour in for high school rifle team after school board rejects NRA money: A high school rifle team in Pennsylvania will be getting new gear thanks to community businesses rallying around it after the school board voted against accepting a… https://t.co/qd0LVwS0tn https://t.co/pOIPsL1jgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/jP40gcYz1v https://t.co/YXHUetclYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/uyBkvkNuaV https://t.co/SKyHMHHsUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/bzY9Xfhp5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/5PHxjViIq6 https://t.co/cO3A1K18pK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/RtpBi0Daeq https://t.co/sTFDVlFUrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/gDUcSjnUiz https://t.co/lfZjXqY9wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/xSp1AOKiRh https://t.co/qDVLffBYDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/6F2XXHtGld https://t.co/OpJRPUQHNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/4nhZQYvdw6 https://t.co/iadKpuekkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/9KdP27SCck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/b2B7bSHBjg https://t.co/qPkrrKKM8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/CJmRGiqSdo https://t.co/IywqNYXYmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Are New York Taxi Drivers Committing Suicide?: Drivers say competition from Uber and Lyft is lowering their incomes, contributing to four recent driver suicides. https://t.co/VERPYGLOcZ https://t.co/S5pljjNZ2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/XYh6pVtXhR https://t.co/Zx9r2t4U6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The race to militarize space is no joke: One of the first weapons in space was a triple-barreled handgun designed to kill Russian bears. Cosmonauts brought it with them into orbit in case their descent module landed in a Siberian forest. https://t.co/VrliLEbDho https://t.co/WXKVHcOkkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Primary Skills JAVA,JAVASCRIPT,IBM ISIM,IBM TFIM Development Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: IT… https://t.co/TDQJ7eETGD https://t.co/YUCvbJXP4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/E8ZpnNRbPT https://t.co/9LkWAWTTIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Download Your Facebook Data and What To Look For in It: Here's how to parse the downloadable file of data the social network has about you. https://t.co/RmsXmacVaE https://t.co/zAHWmUzg8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/EaPce0lXiQ https://t.co/l5TKG0lti5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Account Manager OEM / OES: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 1 hour ago Category Sales Overview The Key Account Manager (KAM) is the owner of and the expert for the assigned Automotive Tier 1 Suppliers and their value chain… https://t.co/87AvQSzYDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/LSUjeBXJNe https://t.co/Q4Dj1hBfBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/kKGipMgKwu https://t.co/aTKN0UZRl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Startup Makes Augmented Reality Social—and Ubiquitous: Ubiquity6 wants to be a platform on which others build AR experiences. https://t.co/mov44Qy0Pp https://t.co/wOS2qOU0Mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/ySzSrQ1ABO https://t.co/C7vI5Krzs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/hvO7xBMrRA https://t.co/0VgO9iZn7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Will Make It Easier for You to Control Your Personal Data: The changes put all the privacy settings in a single place, instead of being spread out across nearly 20 different screens. https://t.co/VYqHoO5Q0s https://t.co/ymxlbabA3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/S6eSUXVqsn https://t.co/tTAcdqeZez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/gJaTxq2X1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/PAlsG93Gdt https://t.co/VHzZslmymh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/9BUKScGMxP https://t.co/7bTYXSo5SR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Next Cold War Is Here, and It's All About Data: The General Data Protection Regulation coming to Europe this spring emphasizes how different societies value personal data and privacy. https://t.co/PyxkQbSIyW https://t.co/0roZuo2Joj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/EJVDh7yjPp https://t.co/iYF8sMBA4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/pzmfjwVOK6 https://t.co/lQUmZvWDAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How events backfired on Putin https://t.co/nX0DEtNCOL https://t.co/vIjUnyr7h4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: Oracle DBA detroit, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 02/27/18, Posted Date – 02/27/18 Primary SkillsOracle DBATax TermsC2COverview SR. Oracle DBA Interviewing ASAP 5 years of hard-core DBA with both stand-alone and RAC databases.… https://t.co/AJ5i3tAXM9 https://t.co/j0jJGiJwU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/XHjGBiGruM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/5guNFtE5GW https://t.co/3vVUp5RO8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/tlMbw6v85O https://t.co/mt4N1QiTmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/OXvnoCqMRs https://t.co/Txdwov4Gzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/EaQeOdJsie https://t.co/ZzRRBMJdwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/NVrrPDefC6 https://t.co/uR1utQdHoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Wins Latest Round vs. Google in Java Copyright Case: An appeals court rules that Google violated Oracle's copyright when it built a version of Java for the Android operating system, in the latest twist in an 8-year saga. https://t.co/5DswMWrNnp https://t.co/DDnMEuUAxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/WUf5DJUDb3 https://t.co/27J8nDjvwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/3zixf1H0nW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/oAz22qISX1 https://t.co/318IjD4lVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/UDLNCHRcRg https://t.co/xq3hInXlDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube and Pinterest Influencers Almost Never Disclose Marketing Relationships: New research shows how infrequently bloggers label affiliate marketing campaigns according to FTC guidelines. https://t.co/AYlqzDfVEr https://t.co/Vc8lNr00Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/Vr4dHw5TTz https://t.co/I9Epr8Mwl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Caribbean: Beautiful beaches and more https://t.co/Krx6Sws6vZ https://t.co/8qCtA9urKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/DAM6rweGYw https://t.co/SFlwYkKsHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/6HxFlPeVHM https://t.co/IJmnsSmUWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/4zopdT933Z https://t.co/ZpiVyfvcx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Going to Be A While Till We Find 'The Next Steve Jobs': Technologists like Elizabeth Holmes and Travis Kalanick may have been eager to claim the mantle, but the sense of magic that tech leaders once inspired has been replaced by suspicion and fear. https://t.co/Y1Dga3vQ7w https://t.co/KKI9VkO5SF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/B5yjyuBQ9q https://t.co/OlVTEWK5O6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Account Manager OEM / OES: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 1 hour ago Category Sales Overview The Key Account Manager (KAM) is the owner of and the expert for the assigned Automotive Tier 1 Suppliers and their value chain… https://t.co/M9rlk88HsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/grOF3m1plJ https://t.co/lyJPiQyHt0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>