<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/uYnkzGUZpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/bTj5XXauJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/lxt3VUIrho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/aSLbsFhzzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/W3TWa6uXlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/BrVSh17xRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/gF5jn4slCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/4wUJ4Mi6OY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/xeq7xRpMSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/DlSXPZyxgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/wl3FCFZ7dL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/Vw2pE6zBHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/7LNkZAjvWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/JyJaH9EfHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/GN58MWaXxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is the first milestone on the road to the stars. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/Jz46somJa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/XVpuWZ7EVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/skPqhkmG2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/xrGkD5iGyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/dp9aBwfJVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/JkHlnSrW1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD?  I prefer the term intellectual Bad ASS!  http://t.co/4oaqGJGpBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/Z7aBslBFvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/bKfOvDEytL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/hELfQpnilL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/p6f3JKbOqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/EinbL881U9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/FKSEv76G1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/VsiTu7n43v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/Sf3fWRiLmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/K3b614lQHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/55yzv6YF1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/uYnkzGUZpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/mWcLxYvcgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/lN2OEBQzmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/M19SOjSq1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/ohW8swZgJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/JfZ8wtVMOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/qsRTvojAaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/xf3K363XKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/aeDRivxUi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/MT4dqwr5GD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/DxE8TioR1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/JQTn2j2YTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/jqw9vtY0aq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>