<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Lead: Test Lead Ref No.: 18-25950 Location: Windsor, Connecticut Title: Test Lead Location:- Windsor, CT Duration: 12 Months+ Good communication skill,QE lead,Agile experience,Project test Mangement skillset Experience in Client ALM, Agile central,… https://t.co/yZtdWbX5FT https://t.co/fQvY4uZ7Wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPIC NURSE APPLICATION SPECIALIST I: Job ID 67346 Department ITS INPATIENT CLINICALS Category INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Position Type Full Time Benefits Eligible Scheduled Hours 40 Work Schedule DAYS Work Days MONDAY – FRIDAY, WEEKENDS IF NEEDED Work Hours… https://t.co/1wn3tmDyae https://t.co/fZaJZMBVru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded C, C++ Python Engineer: Embedded C, C++ &amp; Python Engineer Ref No.:18-01178 Location: Wilton, Connecticut Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different… https://t.co/HWkpGJ6kho https://t.co/iVtYeINWfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Microsemi in Simsbury, Connecticut is a key business in Microsemi’s Discrete and Integrated Solution Group. (DISG) The organization designs, develops and manufactures Surface Acoustic Wave (SAW) devices and subsystems. SAW is a growing… https://t.co/H7mnmOfjdG https://t.co/pCxNAq8EqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Electronics Development: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/20/2018 Functional areaProject Management BackgroundElectronics Referencereq1807 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together… https://t.co/3n1ttICa70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager (71306) Ref No.:18-00009 Location: Farmington, Connecticut Skill Type:Service Delivery NWN is recognized as one of the top 18 Cisco partners in the U.S. and a leader in the IT services industry with many awards and elite… https://t.co/4bXoxYZXpI https://t.co/caRjiHY6xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Project Manager: Agile Project Manager, #15688BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk Control… https://t.co/5Qw6NB0bAe https://t.co/lIpQllNcnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager- Interiors: Building and Land Technol Building and Land Technol Construction Project Manager- Interiors Stamford, CT 06902 Building and Land Technology (BLT) is a privately held, vertically integrated, mixed use real estate… https://t.co/bqNnPPIqm8 https://t.co/reFfRzUzpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect Big Data a plus: Solution Architect – Big Data a plus, #15567BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals… https://t.co/Sqq01CKVNI https://t.co/dJB6ZJIWp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genomic Technical Support Scientist: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and… https://t.co/nkAh3mpfHb https://t.co/RZ9fg9QERi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager Power Plant Decommissioning: Sr. Project Manager Power Plant Decommissioning A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a national engineering, consulting and construction management… https://t.co/L1iglEWhjA https://t.co/7NAjRb2Abi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer/Project Manager: Civil Engineer/Project Manager The selected candidates would serve as a Project Engineer/Project Manager for civil/site design, land planning and permitting for industrial, institutional, commercial, multifamily… https://t.co/Bl8RoC4knA https://t.co/FR1kBmzfuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Financial Applications Developer : Next Gen Internship: – Financial Applications Developer : Next Gen Internship Job Locations US-CT-Stamford Req. # 2018-2700Division Global Information Business Solutions Position Type Intern Position Overview If… https://t.co/PKi5tAKgnG https://t.co/SS4IQ3jxmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer: Sr .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-22758 Location: Bloomfield, Illinois Sr .Net Web Developer Bloomfield, CT 12 Months contract Job description: 6+ Years of experience required. Its regular .Net position Skills required C#,.Net, MVC, PL/SQL https://t.co/UMjDl03RRT https://t.co/jQeERINj59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Interaction Designer: Job Title Senior Interaction Designer Requisition # 7387 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US (Primary) Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Product… https://t.co/8tNsxm21Dr https://t.co/QSn8Flwxt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Site Investigation and Remediation Plainville, CT Office: Project Manager – Site Investigation and Remediation – Plainville, CT Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc., an employee owned, full-service multi-disciplinary engineering… https://t.co/IRYy9gzGuS https://t.co/vZePvs85C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst: Operations Analyst – Stamford, CT Scope: This analyst is responsible for supporting all aspects of operation for a capital markets business, including but not limited to trade settlement, trade verification, cash/activity… https://t.co/GjoOZvsUyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connect – Data Analyst: 6/11/2018 Connect – Data Analyst Tracking Code 3441-736 Job Description Ipsos Connect Data Analyst – Norwalk, CT Position Summary The Ipsos Connect Data Analyst position is an excellent opportunity for someone who is looking to… https://t.co/SBE9JxRweI https://t.co/84S58fVPub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Access Database Software Developer: An Access Database Software Developer job is currently available at Belcan in Windsor, CT. This is a full-time, direct job with benefits. Great candidates will have at least three years of professional experience in… https://t.co/NoRRZjjYv4 https://t.co/9OGj1zXtKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Programmer: Sr Software Programmer, #15511BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk… https://t.co/LcACpTvESz https://t.co/eb3zo6ddLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Analyst, Analytics API Program: Job Title Senior Quality Assurance Analyst, Analytics API Program Requisition # 8729 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager)… https://t.co/AB7AYt5k4x https://t.co/SkVURLDjSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Norwalk: Job Title Software Engineer – Norwalk Requisition # 7558 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Entry Level Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job Description FactSet is… https://t.co/AP4SO0lQqO https://t.co/VjFOVuA5iE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DATA ARCHITECT II: Job ID 66214 Department ITS DATABASE ADM &amp; ARCHITECTURE Category INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Position Type Full Time Benefits Eligible Scheduled Hours 40 Work Schedule DAYS Work Days MONDAY – FRIDAY Work Hours 8:00 – 4:30 Work Shift NONE… https://t.co/n6qcydubyv https://t.co/9Ee5jYBREn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Integrity Specialist: Data Integrity Specialist Business Stores – Kmart Hourly Job Description Promotes a positive shopping experience for members using the Welcome, Assist and Thank approach. Assists in maintaining and promoting accurate unit… https://t.co/RprQ70j2yf https://t.co/jxlmIkfHYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test Platform QA: Job Title Software Engineer in Test – Platform QA Requisition # 8219 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/xU4mmVxP81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/4/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and technology… https://t.co/USoSUBHV5l https://t.co/M2nW4MfA1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test Platform QA: Job Title Software Engineer in Test – Platform QA Requisition # 8219 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/x3TAXXvdox https://t.co/TEPcvq1qQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROJECT MANAGER – INFRASTRUCTURE PROJECT: Job ID 63905 Department FACILITIES DESIGN CONSTRUCTION Category NON CLINICAL – ALL OTHER Position Type Full Time Benefits Eligible Scheduled Hours 40 Work Schedule DAYS Work Days MON-FRI Work Hours 0800-1630 Work… https://t.co/NZhDw4GQXQ https://t.co/ahCj0h5yWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/4/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and technology… https://t.co/TlYtVaNzZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 5/9/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2880 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop… https://t.co/N4KHmSuwdB https://t.co/wObviVqESn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Web Developer: OVERVIEW: Immediate opening for web developer experienced in WordPress with an eye for design and the ability to work on multiple projects. The ideal candidate will have 3+ years of experience and the desire and ability to use… https://t.co/pFDj4kX2PU https://t.co/jbrYCbSb1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Architect – Technical Lead: – Systems Architect – Technical Lead Job Locations US-CT-Stamford Req. # 2017-2560Division Global Information Business Solutions Position Type Regular Position Overview Legg Mason is seeking an experienced Senior… https://t.co/VJGMmXRmz7 https://t.co/cjDgL5w4d4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager (71306) Ref No.:18-00009 Location: Farmington, Connecticut Skill Type:Service Delivery NWN is recognized as one of the top 18 Cisco partners in the U.S. and a leader in the IT services industry with many awards and elite… https://t.co/WLJ39Qd2bh https://t.co/aNDtx6ZuJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO Consultant in Naugatuck, CT: IT Partners is seeking local or commutable to Naugatuck, CT Mid tier resources with SAP FI/CO experience. We desire people who want to belong to a successful team. We value professionalism, enthusiasm and commitment.… https://t.co/5rYCl3r4B3 https://t.co/wDHAhqNbnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Modeler: Senior Data Modeler Primary Skills BI,Azure,TSQL,Erwin,SQLSERVER,EDW,Data modeler,EISL Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Senior Data Modeler for location Hartford , CT for one of our Top client.… https://t.co/aNK8F7L8xH https://t.co/O3MNJikMbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer: – Location: Stamford, Connecticut, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: June 12, 2018 – Position Title:Associate Developer – Company Name:Chubb About Chubb For more than 125 years, the Chubb Group of Insurance Companies has… https://t.co/FEGkpoqYZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer — Cognos preferred: Business Intelligence Developer – Cognos preferred, #15558BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity… https://t.co/YX72DgSvWQ https://t.co/aNrUF0bm9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer/Project Manager: Civil Engineer/Project Manager The selected candidates would serve as a Project Engineer/Project Manager for civil/site design, land planning and permitting for industrial, institutional, commercial, multifamily… https://t.co/PqhfiC3GhN https://t.co/dG4OxRIMwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Title Project Manager Requisition # 8836 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Temporary/Contract Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Project Management Education… https://t.co/HhL95Zm0cX https://t.co/nX9z7e2wno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Electronics Development: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/20/2018 Functional area Project Management Background Electronics Reference req1807 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most… https://t.co/ZnjVVLDnfL https://t.co/tNJlNPqPse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Salesforce Developer: Sr. Salesforce Developer Ref No.:18-09729 Location: Hartford, CT, Connecticut Start Date: 05/30/2018 JOB Discription : Job TitleSr. Developer Relevant Experience 3 years in Salesforce (On Premise) Technical/Functional… https://t.co/Vx6N9hxfe7 https://t.co/JVwI9xTO9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Microsemi in Simsbury, Connecticut is a key business in Microsemi’s Discrete and Integrated Solution Group. (DISG) The organization designs, develops and manufactures Surface Acoustic Wave (SAW) devices and subsystems. SAW is a growing… https://t.co/NSeXj28uHq https://t.co/LZkMXfH9gS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineering Project Manager: New Product Introduction: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 4/11/2018 Functional area Manufacturing, Mechanical Engineering Background Other- Technical Reference… https://t.co/jkT1jgyP7e https://t.co/KsYMQZnPI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Software Engineer: We have an immediate opening for an Associate Software Engineer who will be assisting in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and… https://t.co/A4ZcKM6RvD https://t.co/iHaaMRyplD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Analyst: The qualified applicant should have experience creating and executing test plans, specifically for web based applications. The purposes of the internal applications are to assist in managing finances, class planning… https://t.co/6EFuLD6Evx https://t.co/pL55MHlvdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack – Portfolio Services: Job Title Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack – Portfolio Services Requisition # 8338 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time… https://t.co/gcWeU1sboT https://t.co/55l2GWyPxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Mechanical Engineering (3 – 6yrs.): Project Manager – Mechanical Engineering Job Code : HC/JC/24160/18 | Location : East Hartford | Openings : 1 Education : AS – Administrative Job Experience : 3.00 to 6.00 years | Industry : NA Posted… https://t.co/ZUaRQWUjcI https://t.co/ER6zw8hAbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grains and Oilseeds Data Analyst: The purpose of this role is to support the global oilseeds and grains research teams to provide timely information and accurate estimates of US and Global supply and demand estimates to the traders. Specifically, it aims… https://t.co/cXRpmGCo6s https://t.co/e6Ke7ZjQr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Design Design Intern: Job Title User Experience Design – Design Intern Requisition # 8875 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Internship Career Level Student (Undergraduate/Graduate) Category Marketing Education… https://t.co/HiANBOuZlF https://t.co/icTOEAYUFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Development Project Manager: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/13/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2297 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/rwdBAUlKMc https://t.co/Ir9piU1RkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aftermarket Sales Manager, U.S. and Canada: Req ID : 435782BR Job Code/Title : E1004:Sales Representative Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying… https://t.co/r8NrICShsH https://t.co/2dHuqjkWp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrated Support Software Product Line Manager: Req ID : 434557BR Job Code/Title : L3285:IT Program Mgr Job Description : Integrated Support Software Product Line Manager This individual will lead a team of highly motivated software development project… https://t.co/L7KTyrOjMN https://t.co/Oe3dmeawLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Tracking Code 5202-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the world that will… https://t.co/mhxLzvs6gn https://t.co/CdkYwZJJEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer: Job Title UI Designer Requisition # 7375 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Product Development Education Bachelor’s Degree… https://t.co/PifDnue22I https://t.co/ishbjqZdR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Marketing Manager, Marketing Automation:   Job Description – Digital Marketing Manager, Marketing Automation (00020794) Job Description  Digital Marketing Manager, Marketing Automation – (00020794) Description   The Digital Marketing Manager will… https://t.co/5oZFIQi2ps https://t.co/jW3u4iCX7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager – Engineering (Client Service Leader): Job Description – Sr Project Manager – Engineering (Client Service Leader) Job LocationUS-CT-Rocky HillJob ID0318-18047 HNTB Job TitleSr Project Manager – Engineering Position TypeRegular… https://t.co/QBCnS1NA8G https://t.co/St62yS2laf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Programmer: Sr Software Programmer, #15511BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk… https://t.co/lHmhUoFu3q https://t.co/jhUJSmdAME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spark/Scala Developer: Spark/Scala Developer Primary Skills JAVA,PYTHON,Scala,Spark ML,TensorFlow Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Spark/Scala Developer for location Bloomfield , CT / New York City, NY for one of… https://t.co/5OsLzZHlm4 https://t.co/QRAatX7YUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: CLIENT REFERENCE CODE: ****** JOB SUMMARY Responsible for supporting and managing a program of business unit-focused initiatives designed to help business partners drive value from information. The role will contribute to… https://t.co/Vq7s1nahQc https://t.co/Y7OEPv4ooi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/pbjBvDAitb https://t.co/aGPv7HSXyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/yIW7OToiLG https://t.co/OIiKQ6XS81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy International Capture Manager: Req ID : 437111BR Job Code/Title : L3045:Program Management Mgr Job Description : The Deputy International Capture Manager is responsible for the management oversight and execution of Naval Helicopters business… https://t.co/sOH3vVK5kH https://t.co/LPte1CCKjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Planner- CRH: Req ID : 434037BR Job Code/Title : E4112:Program Planner Job Description : The Defense Systems &amp; Services (DSS) Finance &amp; Business Operations organization (F&amp;BO) is looking for an enthusiastic individual to provide Planning &amp;… https://t.co/8MIdlKaCpQ https://t.co/hhlqcwuu9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CH-53K Staff System Engineer – Pax: Req ID : 436318BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1464:Systems Engineer Stf Job Description : Seeking an experienced engineer for assignment to the CH-53K System Engineering (SE) team. The primary responsibilities for this… https://t.co/MMT8pSLo7T https://t.co/h1HEeJ3Bu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UH-1N Huey Replacement Sr. Program Program Planner: Req ID : 436463BR Job Code/Title : E4113:Program Planner Sr Job Description : The Sikorsky Army &amp; Air Force Systems F&amp;BO organization is looking for an enthusiastic individual for the role of Sr.… https://t.co/zGkHv6lmke https://t.co/D60xm43vCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Asc: Req ID : 436408BR Job Code/Title : E1461:Systems Engineer Asc Job Description : Job Description – Engineering Proposal Analyst in the Engineering Estimating Group located in the Proposal Center and US Government Business Office.… https://t.co/ngvCPpYBJ6 https://t.co/GJqk58dmkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Performance Management: Req ID : 435418BR Job Code/Title : E1754:Prj Mgt &amp; Plng Opns Rep Stf Job Description : This position is contingent upon Sikorsky winning the USAF UH-1N Replacement Contract in 3Q2018. Reporting to the Manager Business… https://t.co/DEi1563VWh https://t.co/v4Fxt5KBm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Commercial, TI ($110,000 – $130,000): Stamford, CT Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today Based in Stamford, CT we are a real estate development and property management group with over 30 years of providing solutions for residential and… https://t.co/lQqtNZc89p https://t.co/kJX8WUgONO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Controls and Autonomous Systems Engineer: Req ID : 435024BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Sikorsky Aircraft, a Lockheed Martin company, is the world leader in the design, manufacture and service of advanced… https://t.co/N8PMzGyutd https://t.co/DEDBm0RtGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.net Database Programming Analyst, Reporting Team: Job Description Database Programming Analyst, McLagan Reporting Team Aon is looking for a Database Programming Analyst to work in the Stamford, CT office As part of an industry-leading team, you will… https://t.co/5g0Yz94g2F https://t.co/6jV43IoQLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Aviation Safety Management System (SMS): Req ID : 432921BR Job Code/Title : E5405:System Safety Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : 1. OVERALL PURPOSE The safety manager is responsible for providing guidance and direction for the planning,… https://t.co/qvshLRIDgo https://t.co/vLb5XLkqRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Director, Network Security, Gartner Research:   Job Description – Research Director, Network Security, Gartner Research (00020611) Job Description  Research Director, Network Security, Gartner Research – (00020611) Description   What makes… https://t.co/7OLF03qxMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Minimum qualifications:BS degree in Computer Science or related technical field involving coding (e.g., physics or mathematics), or equivalent practical experience.Solid knowledge of Linux OS. Able to troubleshoot performance-related… https://t.co/L6VwRsVfqR https://t.co/uPpGInOAsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Technician/CMM Programmer: As part of the Quality Department, a CMM Programmer/QualityTechnician is responsible on the assigned shift for all Quality related activities and tasks required for all plant products and sub-components in close… https://t.co/WsnKAZb3ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/NnLzuFtO6k https://t.co/TvRoVQ6zVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience2-5 Professional Available since2/15/2018 Functional areaProject Management, System Engineering, Design Engineering BackgroundSystem Integration, Other-… https://t.co/PfqKyBpFmk https://t.co/Oa7ADY5sHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/Reg1RyBuYS https://t.co/A1PfRe8khN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Proposal Support Analyst: Req ID : 431888BR Job Code/Title : E4573:Procurement Rep Sr Job Description : Sikorsky Aircraft Supply Chain Management is seeking an experienced Supply Chain candidate to join the Business Process Management Group.… https://t.co/37Q2mc4gri https://t.co/ioPEmPpyQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Coordinator – Office Planning: Req ID : 433647BR Job Code/Title : E1513:Facilities Engineer Sr Job Description : In support of the Sikorsky Facilities Design, Construction and Engineering organization, oversee the management of major projects and… https://t.co/ANydon86iU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Analyst: User Experience Analyst, #16231BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk… https://t.co/OnsLe4pXfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer/Analyst 2 (UCP 8) OR Senior Computer Programmer/Analyst (UCP 9): Employer University of Connecticut Location Storrs, CT Posted Jul 04, 2018 Institution Type Four-Year Institution You need to sign in or create an account to save Job… https://t.co/5cNjky4KXw https://t.co/mCZmINjwg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Research Analyst, Data Security, Gartner Research &amp; Advisory:   Job Description – Principal Research Analyst, Data Security, Gartner Research &amp; Advisory (00018678) Job Description  Principal Research Analyst, Data Security, Gartner Research &amp;… https://t.co/LDt9xsgiuS https://t.co/JdwErolMTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Support Analyst: Job Description Since 1996, Surgical Information Systems (‘SIS’) has been dedicated to providing surgical care providers with the solutions and services they need to deliver improved operational, financial, and clinical outcomes.… https://t.co/Wi4lXWyiSo https://t.co/T72hAfM19U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-29383 Location: Bloomfield, Connecticut Role: .Net Developer Location: Bloomfield CT Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Strong exp. with .net development required. https://t.co/HM5cGgev7s https://t.co/G8DJU7LSxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 414651BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Turkish Utility Helicopter Software Supplier Management position to oversee software supplier activities. The applicable candidate will reside… https://t.co/nLRujjtFLS https://t.co/j35l0tPi7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Database: Thermo Fisher Scientific – Software Engineer, Database Job in Branford, CT – Home – Discover Our Stories – Career Areas – Engineering – Field Service – Finance – General Management – Human Resources – Operations &amp; Supply… https://t.co/bpdOxtWruS https://t.co/d6afvy93KX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic System Architect: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/4/2018 Functional areaElectrical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Research &amp; Development BackgroundElectronics, System… https://t.co/IcCkZumiXr https://t.co/AzRHvhm0IL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Electronics Development: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since3/14/2018 Functional areaElectrical Engineering, Design Engineering, Research &amp; Development BackgroundElectronics, Other-… https://t.co/5NkeRal0rG https://t.co/xyAKbjdJdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genesys Developer: Genesys Developer in Hartford, Connecticut, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/XYTMcDhOwz https://t.co/9y0eBPC4uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: Thermo Fisher Scientific – Quality Assurance Engineer Job in Branford, CT – Home – Discover Our Stories – Career Areas – Engineering – Field Service – Finance – General Management – Human Resources – Operations &amp; Supply Chain… https://t.co/6jJgeR3Tv7 https://t.co/ViISIFb5M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Kantar Worldpanel Shopcom is a data integration, activation and analytics firm connecting what consumers see, feel and do to help marketers, advertisers and publishers grow their brands through more impactful media investment and… https://t.co/zp7stE23mh https://t.co/udrOMLQw2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Front-End Developer: Sr. Front-End Developer, #15836BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk… https://t.co/3aFqwp6zmf https://t.co/1yhYCUN2sA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Designer Integrator Analyst: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 5/23/2018 Functional area Background Reference req3133 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/EMS20Vh2Z5 https://t.co/N0VdB7Ey5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: As a Senior Developer, you will be responsible for the design, development, and maintenance of complex technical solutions. The ideal candidate for this role will: Provide strong understanding of application, system, and integration… https://t.co/w8u9DmLPeR https://t.co/XznUDjMT1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Consultant: Sr. IT Consultant Location USA, Enfield Posted Date 07/03/2018 Job ID US7397 Category Information Technology Language Are you a JDA wizard who has experience building and implementing Supply Chain Planning Platforms in large… https://t.co/AaVPz7Uqf5 https://t.co/rYOr72ZUMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax Manager (140K+): Job Description TAX MANAGER • Must have experience in public accounting in the last 5 years* Are you looking for a public accounting position but want a better work/life balance? My Client is a mid-sized public accounting firm that… https://t.co/cmTy1IJDJD https://t.co/3im7BAU6ZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Job Title Application Security Engineer Requisition # 9090 Location Austin – Austin, TX 78701 US New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced… https://t.co/7sVKtESYXF https://t.co/oN216U7sjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services:   Job Description – Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services (00015163) Job Description  Research Director, Infrastructure Outsourcing Services – (00015163) Description   Conduct… https://t.co/rMHnw0gpQU https://t.co/drQS5tUuZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Programmer: Sr Software Programmer, #16306BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals Claim Finance IT Risk… https://t.co/9EdO7N7knK https://t.co/ZoVhbtWvKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/AqRnLnAIXn https://t.co/Rvx9DZ6OwL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>