<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL and BI programmer, Global Strategic Pricing: Job ID : 59634BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description Position Summary: We are looking for a SQL and BI developer who will be responsible for designing databases and ensuring… https://t.co/ntZsIBrDln https://t.co/yzDIzQqzNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Tencent invests $180 million in Brazil fintech Nubank: Chinese gaming and social media firm Tencent Holdings Ltd paid $180 million for an undisclosed minority stake in Brazilian financial technology company Nu Pagamentos SA, both companies said… https://t.co/7KMHpmjHmj https://t.co/MDOMXnSUZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG)’ is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its… https://t.co/aHxLwxJt7a https://t.co/XSBZwUoaAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Tencent to acquire stake in Brazil fintech Nubank: source: Chinese internet company Tencent Holdings Ltd has reached an agreement to acquire a minority stake in Brazilian financial technology company Nu Pagamentos SA, a source familiar with the… https://t.co/20gfePnjzS https://t.co/hxKDN7fptg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer – PITT: Developer – PITT Ref No.: 18-00700 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile environment. You… https://t.co/8nrQ2ETghH https://t.co/utyW6RJ3sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet shuts Google+ social site after user data exposed: Alphabet Inc's Google said on Monday up to 500,000 Google+ user accounts were potentially affected by a bug that may have exposed their data to external developers, and the company is shutting… https://t.co/qyY8OlTDAE https://t.co/INCT76NPL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEVOPS Engineer: DEVOPS Engineer Ref No.:18-16303 Location: West chester, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 09/11/2018 JD: Position: DevOps Engineer Location: West Chester, PA Duration: 6-12+ months Contract Job description :… https://t.co/LwTnFcyckO https://t.co/HrvuShSV3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google exposed user data, chose not to tell public: WSJ: Alphabet Inc's Google exposed the private data of hundreds of thousands of users of its Google+ social network and opted not to disclose the issue partly due to fears of regulatory scrutiny, the… https://t.co/PweMdn7uzR https://t.co/UcXgz4l7DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU regulators studying crypto assets case by case: The European Union's securities watchdog said on Monday it was examining every initial coin offering (ICO) to see whether it should be regulated, mirroring moves by its U.S. counterpart. https://t.co/2EK3mBJkH4 https://t.co/izbg0QZfPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon India denies it gives select sellers preferential treatment: Amazon's Indian business has denied accusations that it favors select merchants and brands, responding to a complaint lodged by an Indian lobby group. https://t.co/V2pxmbNGzt https://t.co/okadcum69D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Developer Healthcare Big data: Job Description Careers Job Description – About Us – knowledge Hub – Careers – Contact – Partner Login – North AmericaEuropeMiddle EastWorldwide – – Markets – Medical Technology – Enable healthcare technology… https://t.co/53bIH1p9bA https://t.co/7yepLpG3iV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK union calls on its Uber drivers to strike on Tuesday: A British trade union called on Uber [UBER.UL] drivers to strike in London, Birmingham and Nottingham on Tuesday for 24 hours by not signing into the app, in a push for higher fares and more… https://t.co/gpSHwpbxJi https://t.co/VkghXqvhcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Czechs join Ireland, Nordic countries in opposing EU digital tax: The Czech Republic joined opposition by Ireland, Finland and Sweden to the European Union's proposed tax on big internet companies in a joint paper warning that the measures may breach… https://t.co/anm75pJ5I1 https://t.co/zFEp1wldS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft testing new game-streaming service: Microsoft Corp is testing a new game streaming service called Project xCloud that is designed to work across PCs, consoles and mobile devices, the company said on Monday. https://t.co/Z24U8KO2bV https://t.co/P0t6U4guAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: RGP is a global consulting firm helping some of the most recognized companies in the world work differently. Our success comes from a shared belief in rolling up our sleeves and doing the hard work of solving complex challenges, executing… https://t.co/X7ApquUmfb https://t.co/1hMcJ1a7ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venture capital funding in Southeast Asia at record: industry: Funding by venture capital (VC) firms in Southeast Asian start-ups has risen to a record so far this year, surpassing the total investments made in 2017, industry data showed. https://t.co/EdAITcCLeS https://t.co/l9x1OpKiwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce, QA Engineer III: Job ID : 75315BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/lrUvaFVFDW https://t.co/2H8CHTrrhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiat Chrysler prepares to produce plug-in hybrid Jeep Renegade: Fiat Chrysler (FCA) said on Monday it had kicked-off preparations for the production of a plug-in hybrid version of the Jeep Renegade as the carmaker pushes ahead with its electrification… https://t.co/daiGijPIjF https://t.co/Nt5z48uX0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook debuts smart speaker for Messenger video calls: Facebook Inc on Monday released a smart speaker designed to ease video calls, but the company's history of privacy mishaps and the device's price and limited functionality could slow it from taking… https://t.co/IyyEtDbpT2 https://t.co/yxhcobdj4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Systems Developer – HARR: Open Systems Developer – HARR Ref No.: 18-00682 Location: Harrisburg, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and… https://t.co/45VDXRS8ur https://t.co/vF26ajEx00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FLIR launches new system for surveillance drones: FLIR Systems Inc on Monday launched a vehicle-mounted case, that holds several tiny surveillance drones to help soldiers and first responders to gauge their surroundings without exiting vehicles. https://t.co/eBxrM89nmm https://t.co/h1s2809b5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Specialist Developer-&gt;&gt; Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be responsible for requirements gathering and BRD/SRD preparation. Has thorough knowledge of the… https://t.co/X7nGszfasY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chickens and eggs: Retailer Carrefour adopts blockchain to track fresh produce: Europe's largest retailer Carrefour SA has adopted blockchain ledger technology to track and trace chicken, eggs and tomatoes as they travel from farms to stores, and will… https://t.co/z4QmG1dYJd https://t.co/gwi2hZrHZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass action against Google over iPhone data blocked by London court: London's High Court on Monday blocked an attempt to bring legal action against Alphabet Inc's Google over claims it had collected sensitive data from more than 4 million iPhone users… https://t.co/u4dUunSlE2 https://t.co/XL7QVIfhNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Job ID : 77874BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description DUTIES: Develop, support and manage business initiatives and technical projects relating to the AMPS application. Lead java code development efforts… https://t.co/7ZRcUhSjMR https://t.co/jLi5F6y7IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google welcomes UK court block on claim over data collection: Google welcomed a decision on Monday by London's High Court to block an attempt to bring legal action over claims it had collected sensitive data from 4 million iPhone users in England and… https://t.co/5QbATjJ73F https://t.co/ClrK9OCvNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C#: Software Engineer – C# in Bala Cynwyd, PA (Philadelphia Area) | Technology – Software Engineering at Susquehanna International Group – About – Trading – Quant Research – Technology – Campus Programs – gamer blog – Careers – – – –… https://t.co/T7DqXe3OsQ https://t.co/ssnGb1NsU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASP. Net with Azure Cloud: ASP. Net with Azure Cloud Ref No.:18-03871 Location: Chester Brook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery… https://t.co/ilqElESqzJ https://t.co/zQUxyAaOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive, GI Philly: **Account Executive, GI – Philly** Locations:Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Job Family: Sales New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Siemens Healthineers **Business Unit:** Diagnostic Imaging **Requisition… https://t.co/LjomJGGbAH https://t.co/PPQJQpSDmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Agile Coach: Senior Agile Coach Ref No.: 17-90299 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Start Date: 11/30/2017 DESCRIPTION: Artech is currently seeking to add to the below position Job Title: Senior Agile Coach Job ID: TMO-REQ-****** Location: 300… https://t.co/2po5xEkRlO https://t.co/SCtaZjQrRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant Developer Exton, PA: GSC-To-Field – Consultant Developer Professional Services Developer Incubation Program Who Are We? Guidewire exists to deliver the industry platform that P &amp; C insurers rely upon to adapt and succeed in a time of… https://t.co/5KPiUDoMrV https://t.co/DYhyn1RD7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart partners with MGM to boost video-on-demand service Vudu: Walmart Inc said on Monday it would partner with U.S. movie studio Metro Goldwyn Mayer to create content for its video-on-demand service, Vudu, which the retailer bought eight years ago. https://t.co/R8YGtxWh0Z https://t.co/oQLqpzC4t5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rail Transit Electrical Engineer (traction power): Job Description Rail Transit Electrical Engineer (traction power) Rail Transit Electrical Engineer (traction power) (******) About UsAt HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and… https://t.co/JeL65F42hn https://t.co/tiTfmDiFS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Programmer III LEAD: Job Description Must be able to apply standard programming procedures and detailed knowledge of pertinent subject matter in a programming area such as a record keeping operation (supply, personnel and payroll, inventory,… https://t.co/PsUytJPjxa https://t.co/AiBmyhYvWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – CRM: Job ID : 78436BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/Z3KswifdiU https://t.co/QpKbM9sKjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. approval for Bose hearing aid a blow to traditional makers: The U.S. approval of audio products maker Bose Corp's new hearing aid, which can be used without a doctor's assistance, could pressure traditional makers of the devices struggling to keep… https://t.co/4RfNexTEIa https://t.co/lEBYCUCg3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actuarial Data Scientist II: **Position is being reposted due to updated qulifications. Plans and manages predictive modeling, data analytics and data collection projects of moderate to high complexity, confidentiality, and impact on the business with… https://t.co/W7748HKsCz https://t.co/dLM2CwTWOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Specialist Developer-&gt;&gt; Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be responsible for requirements gathering and BRD/SRD preparation. Has thorough knowledge of the… https://t.co/W4BKUR08lY https://t.co/CWyLnDTzlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple tells Congress it found no signs of hacking attack: Apple Inc's top security officer told Congress on Sunday that it had found no sign of suspicious transmissions or other evidence that it had been penetrated in a sophisticated attack on its supply… https://t.co/kR3R3l2iAN https://t.co/UAqzyC6NeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer Java, Oracle, Kofax: Job Description Sr. Specialist Developer – Java, Oracle, Kofax Provides application software design, development and support services for applications supporting Document Custody Service related applications… https://t.co/jMCgbxKGBL https://t.co/zClnYoqyum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator II: Job ID : 73717BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description System Administrator II – 2nd Shift Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc. is the world leader in serving science, with revenues of more than $20 billion and… https://t.co/zgva86sPPf https://t.co/nx0opxesvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, DT, Enterprise User Experience and HR/EHS Solutions: Director, D &amp; T, Enterprise User Experience and HR/EHS Solutions Director, D &amp; T, Enterprise User Experience and HR/EHS Solutions Exton Pennsylvania West Pharmaceutical Services, Inc. is a… https://t.co/YLXlESZuNn https://t.co/zjVv0swoul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager (IT): Plans and manages large or highly complex IT projects. Duties and Responsibilities * Plans, monitors and manages large or highly complex IT projects from initiation through completion. * Leads project team while ensuring… https://t.co/PYtub7r3cz https://t.co/QBhPmVjZLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer: Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and tools for one of the Bank’s most important investment… https://t.co/QS9GsH6J53 https://t.co/BbRf7vTF0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Mainframe Developer Ref No.:18-16583 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 09/13/2018 Job Title : Mainframe Developer Location: Malvern ,PA Type: Fulltime Opening Duties and Responsibilities:… https://t.co/GyiEQX6Omt https://t.co/5frKDiwFBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Job no: MAM-****** Work type: Full time Location: Philadelphia Group: Macquarie Asset Management Division: Macquarie Investment Mgmt Recruiter: Jean-Philippe Graff As an experienced Project Manager, you will contribute… https://t.co/DFmMRqkUJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Technology Strategist – Project Analyst: BNY Mellon Technology Enterprise Production Services is dedicated to ensuring that our technology environments are best-in-class. We run the systems that keep BNY Mellon running. We deliver a full IT service… https://t.co/O8JN8ul1Ez https://t.co/5MPBKPzmjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workforce Planning Analyst (Specialist Business Process Analyst): TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/4hR39z9LBW https://t.co/p8YjVwZeu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Developer – Monitoring: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions… https://t.co/YueLOm3ezo https://t.co/4q0jXSQF8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Iron Mountain – Careers – A2C Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/D057noIXoZ https://t.co/mNfLpObk5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer: Specialist Developer-&gt;&gt; Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be responsible for requirements gathering and BRD/SRD preparation. Has thorough knowledge of the… https://t.co/Qjn6phemIU https://t.co/YUC3SO5N8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web UI Developer: Web UI Developer – AnexinetSkip to content – Services – Products – Company – News – Resources – Careers – Contact – Job Board – Benefits – Full Time Web UI Developer Anexinet is the leading systems Integration and Technology Management… https://t.co/6gOdfo7qn7 https://t.co/ioDbxdzywM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer Sr (DevOps): Job Description IT Systems Engineer Sr (DevOps) (45554) Main Line Health, with over 11,000 employees and 2000 physician practices, is suburban Philadelphia’s most comprehensive health care resource, offering a full range… https://t.co/EVci2Tw2HL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Backend Developer: Senior Java Backend Developer Ref No.: 18-51233 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Start Date: 09/12/2018 Job title: Backend Java Developer Location Pittsburgh PA Duration Long term Required Skills: Core Java, RESTful, Data… https://t.co/0BjH9s91XU https://t.co/CaB7UJdv9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: A Technician I will be responsible for resolving escalated issues from first level analysts. This position must have customer service skills with the ability to communicate face to face as well as via telephone to troubleshoot… https://t.co/slmMmLbmG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Risk and Regulatory Services Innovation Center sponsored by Pw: Job Description Project Manager – Risk and Regulatory Services Innovation Center sponsored by PwC (*******) Job Summary The H. John Heinz III College consists of two… https://t.co/NgOZwtYCFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer Job in US – PA – Jenkintown for Precision Castparts Corp. | Engineering Automation Engineer US – PA – Jenkintown Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 19150 Req. Id 235 Req. Code ******.9 Category… https://t.co/8xjpKSt2CI https://t.co/IJYUQ6r1Ik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant Developer – Exton, PA: GSC-To-Field – Consultant Developer Professional Services Developer Incubation Program Who Are We? Guidewire exists to deliver the industry platform that P &amp; C insurers rely upon to adapt and succeed in a time of… https://t.co/E68r6UrNk5 https://t.co/ot9FmRpnFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Guest Service Desk Team Member Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and always look for opportunities to go above and beyond guest… https://t.co/bG11czXqqS https://t.co/FZu6NnFqrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Scrum Master: About the position Prudential’s Annuities and Life Technology Group is on a journey to transform its Project Management Office (PMO) into a robust, outcome-driven delivery organization. We are seeking a Project Manager,… https://t.co/lnemM82jEb https://t.co/TL8O4ZJERI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Data Integration Developer Lead: Job Description Job Title: Analytics Data Integration Developer Lead Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: UPMC Health Plan Department: Community… https://t.co/KHo3csqacL https://t.co/pDCdqBwQLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Despondent' Musk's Tesla resembles Lehman, Greenlight's Einhorn says: Hedge fund manager David Einhorn lambasted Tesla Inc and its "despondent" Chief Executive Elon Musk on Friday, comparing the electric car company to Lehman Brothers Holdings Inc,… https://t.co/CyeK5Is2rQ https://t.co/6eMLU9TFZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP S/4 HANA Financials Development Architect -IBS Newtown Square: SAP S/4 HANA Financials Development Architect -IBS Newtown Square (PA) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP… https://t.co/dD3jqIZVXL https://t.co/268pkZnvnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOSQL Tech Lead: NOSQL Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-39425 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Title: NOSQL Tech Lead Location : Pittsburg , PA Contract Role Job Description Cassendra, MONGO DB Thanks &amp; Regards Karan Rajput Enterprise Solution Inc. 500 East Diehl… https://t.co/xWnCVbdH98 https://t.co/xGjmSPZlur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google shows progress in addressing competition concerns, says EU's Vestager: Google's proposals to increase competition in online shopping are bearing fruit, Europe's antitrust chief said on Friday, suggesting that the company may be able to avoid… https://t.co/iHf1zAcOWt https://t.co/dQJ2osfwGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procurement Operations Specialist (SAP Ariba): Procurement Operations Specialist (SAP Ariba) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/GZbQsfgWiW https://t.co/QDYNkfwIDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Project Manager / Scrum Master: Senior Project Manager/Scrum Master to join Corporate Trust Technology at Bank of New York Mellon. Key responsibilities include but are not limited to: ‘ Project Management ” ‘ ‘ ‘ ‘ ‘ Manage and oversee the… https://t.co/O74OIU0Vm1 https://t.co/ui6n4V6yXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Analytics: First Quality was founded in 1989 and, in nearly three decades, has grown to be a global privately held company with over 4,000 employees. Its corporate offices are located in Great Neck, New York, with manufacturing… https://t.co/9AMyFL7O8q https://t.co/vxl4FnZXLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap rises on report of CEO's profitability goal for 2019: ** Snapchat-owner's shares up ~4 pct at $8.10 in premarket, showing signs of recovery after touching their all-time low on Thursday https://t.co/QnzcUAvAro https://t.co/uvXxmFK9nE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo and ZTE tumble on fears over China hack report: Lenovo and ZTE Corp shares slid on Friday, hurt by worries about overseas sales after Bloomberg reported that the systems of multiple U.S. companies had been compromised by malicious computer chips… https://t.co/D0yXEs4pEV https://t.co/emnUkxy04v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK cyber security agency backs Apple, Amazon China hack denials: Britain's national cyber security agency said on Friday it had no reason to doubt the assessments made by Apple and Amazon that refuted a Bloomberg story that their systems contained… https://t.co/HxsDg1cf3N https://t.co/091bkXqdWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contact Center Online Banking Technical Support: Contact Center Online Banking Technical Support Williamsville, NY Candidates need to have open availability to cover shifts between the hours of 8:00am to 9:00pm Monday thru Friday and 9:00am to 5:00pm… https://t.co/mBgy9vAg00 https://t.co/h0P8Ri1zNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo, ZTE tumble as investors fret over impact of China's hack report: Shares in Lenovo Group and ZTE Corp tumbled on Friday, hurt by worries about overseas sales after Bloomberg reported that systems of many U.S. firms had been infiltrated by… https://t.co/iF3C29GPK6 https://t.co/0h7l28Zms2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: Provides leadership and is accountable for the performance and results of a team within a single complex operation, function or program. IT Manager to perform a Delivery Manager role in support of the growth in the Commercial Portfolio.… https://t.co/WUaXZVNu6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: SoftBank deepening ties to ride-hailing firm Grab with $500 million funding - sources: SoftBank Group Corp is closing in on a deal to invest about $500 million in Grab as part of roughly $1 billion that Southeast Asia's biggest ride-hailing… https://t.co/YRq5Ex1DXh https://t.co/z4ZABkSfW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barclays customers experience app outage in latest IT glitch: Barclays customers said on Friday that they were unable to access its mobile banking app in the latest outage at a British bank in recent weeks. https://t.co/7kcewAuTRM https://t.co/CYijt5qMWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's LG Electronics quarter-three profit likely rose 44 percent year-on-year: South Korea's LG Electronics Inc said on Friday its third-quarter operating profit likely rose 44.4 percent from the same period a year earlier, slightly below… https://t.co/Rr7zlHpGlP https://t.co/ohTdnIHpwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer/Support CICS MQ, API, COBOL, JCL: Specialist Developer/Support ‘ CICS, DB2, MQ, API, COBOL, JCL The Global Institutional Accounting and Risk Solutions Information Technology team is seeking an experienced Specialist Developer. The… https://t.co/Xum5T2zMPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Intermediate: Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Intermediate Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Information Services Department: HS – WPIC Info Svcs Location:… https://t.co/gQjuyUyM73 https://t.co/lptgDhgVpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo shares tumble, investors fret over impact of chip hack report: Shares in Lenovo Group Ltd and ZTE Corp plunged on Friday, hurt by concerns their sales could suffer in the wake of a Bloomberg report that U.S. companies' systems had been infiltrated… https://t.co/nZW4iRn4ia https://t.co/cLQ9QmMwH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager: Apply on Company Website Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager EQT Corporation Pittsburgh, PA Apply on Company Website Posted 16 hours ago The Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager will lead or assist in developing the… https://t.co/jCCp0Ia3zB https://t.co/OrwZihBP6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shares in Chinese tech firms tumble, Lenovo plunges over 20 percent: Shares of Chinese hardware companies fell sharply on Friday, led by computer maker Lenovo Group Ltd which lost more than a fifth of its value. https://t.co/4mVtE1barY https://t.co/faZNjFV2SH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Instance Lead, SFDC: Job ID : 76539BR_1 Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description This role is designed to provide the technical expertise to drive CRM solutions aligned with Thermo Fisher Scientifics strategic objectives. This… https://t.co/LUbLX4mdxI https://t.co/BRVXTFCwdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer: Sr. Specialist Developer Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for data, workflow, logical… https://t.co/42EUlPf5Lb https://t.co/SiYDH6m8wy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Architect: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Experienced System Architect IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THIS POSITION All applicants must be legally authorized to work in the United States. Visa sponsorship… https://t.co/t46EZ0fvuG https://t.co/XRuaNZNnal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us API Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 20464Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Malvern, PA 19355Security… https://t.co/a2yMCLAo22 https://t.co/9VZz7mK7ct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk mocks SEC as judge demands they justify fraud settlement: Tesla Inc's Elon Musk on Thursday mocked the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, just hours after a federal judge ordered him and the regulator to justify their securities fraud… https://t.co/r2TdrYI0V4 https://t.co/5Y8FVyWBOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enablement Manager (SAP Ariba): Enablement Manager (SAP Ariba) Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword… https://t.co/4bwNlIj9qd https://t.co/X9JZXVPow9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk, ordered to defend fraud settlement, takes aim at SEC: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk on Thursday mocked the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, hours after a federal judge ordered him and the regulator to justify their settlement… https://t.co/hs5WIo18Tu https://t.co/x6OU0oBUZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coinbase's institutional platform head stepping down: Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase Inc said on Thursday its head of institutional platform group and fifth employee, Adam White, is stepping down from his role. https://t.co/x7lj8Kzw1q https://t.co/H2xAwysC0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Careers Center | Mainframe Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/vfCWVhgXai https://t.co/X5sZ7X4NWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge orders Tesla's Musk, SEC to justify fraud settlement: A federal judge on Thursday gave Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission one week to justify their settlement to resolve securities fraud charges… https://t.co/IR4Zp8EJNx https://t.co/HELHNkQPik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon is working with Brazil's CargoX for logistics pilot project: BBG: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc is working on a pilot logistics project in Brazil with Goldman Sachs-backed CargoX, Bloomberg reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter. https://t.co/iUiXuPC5Oc https://t.co/sa7bjvgmeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C#: Software Engineer – C# in Bala Cynwyd, PA (Philadelphia Area) | Technology – Software Engineering at Susquehanna International Group – About – Trading – Quant Research – Technology – Campus Programs – gamer blog – Careers – – – –… https://t.co/3YeNhHHzJJ https://t.co/cNVudrst8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge tells Tesla, SEC to justify settlement of fraud lawsuit: A New York district court judge has asked Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to provide a joint statement by Oct. 11, explaining why… https://t.co/teDqWad9ch https://t.co/7gD4sj6HQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Investments Developer: US Investments Developer Job no: COG-****** Work type: Full time Location: Philadelphia Group: Corporate Operations Group Division: Technology Recruiter: Andrew Baker As a US Investments Developer, you’ll be collaborating… https://t.co/o5edwCGCh9 https://t.co/IytKINhzto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: The Upgrade Center provides a centralized group specializing in solution upgrades. Each client is assigned a team to work through the Soarian upgrade event with them to ensure success with testing and issue resolution. The team is in… https://t.co/Io9IxpYVrx https://t.co/95NWX9eaQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence says Google should halt Dragonfly app development: U.S. Vice President Mike Pence sharply criticized what he said was China's theft of U.S. technology on Thursday, and he urged Google to immediately end development of its "Dragonfly" app that would… https://t.co/yPobSy95eX https://t.co/Tz8NXWy94m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Ariba Systems Analyst: Description The Senior Business Systems Analyst in Procurement is responsible for the configuration of Citizens Procurement related systems, primarily SAP Ariba. Take your procurement or systems analyst career to the next… https://t.co/dCX0vljw9f https://t.co/pdVevZWUwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NENT takes on Netflix in battle for Nordic streaming market as it readies for listing: Nordic Entertainment Group (NENT) hopes to lure investors with robust growth in streaming when it is spun off from Sweden's MTG next year, betting that its Scandi… https://t.co/SHLaUJ1yOw https://t.co/lz7vlJEWQV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>