<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Operators: Arconic Fastening Systems is hiring. City of Industry has immediate openings. $5,000 hiring bonus for experienced Operators only. Centerless Grind Header Operator Single/Multi Die Operator… https://t.co/PcSSPdJIzs 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/WokFrdkTTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TEST ENGINEER III: Test Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Responsible for the commissioning and integration of cell sites and features for CDMA and LTE technologies.  Apply at… https://t.co/M9OaimVc4i 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/PbqMM7YLYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Specialist #XGGS18FC0318RIC2: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Specialist. Application Management Services in Richmond, Virginia and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations… https://t.co/3BrnLDh5g8 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/4DYPi8j8Yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer III, Sprint: Applications Developer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Responsible for development and production support for Sprint’s Network Centralized Access Management systems… https://t.co/BvJUpaxmBF 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/GWh3S9ErrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Development Technical Specialist: Applications Development Technical Specialist for Citigroup Technology, Inc. (Tampa, Florida). Lead the configurable architecture for company’s regulatory platform… https://t.co/1l88OQf4KY 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/iq0fR6hxBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software… https://t.co/a2QJkNCW3c 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/XeDQ0FWBp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Amazon Echo Speaker (2018): Amazon has a lot of Alexa-enabled Echo speakers, and these are the ones you should consider. https://t.co/lZ29obO0H7 #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/EomXYYfVWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Consulting: EMC Corporation (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Senior Manager, Corporate Consulting at our Palo Alto, CA facility to advise senior executives on company’s most pressing business… https://t.co/wpXex1LfWH 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/vVxkmxmHiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director/Engineering Supervisor: Director, Global Certification (Bachelor + 5 years progressive experience), Engineering Supervisor Body Structures (Bachelor + 5 years progressive experience) sought by Karma… https://t.co/Elg6sTGa9t 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/31Nq78oAGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethernet Product Manager – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 206657 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based… https://t.co/PB4nQqpOkW 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/gFcp9UrmXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/fs1KPTbgvC 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/4QKlM2AQND #tech #career #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/D1HB6udOla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist: IT Specialist Location: Pearl Harbor, HI Job Code: 2207 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT)… https://t.co/IzfuH8Cj6X 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/bH9qZmA4xC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Developer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Ruby on Rails Developer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position College experience and knowledge… https://t.co/65ozhIkmMA 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/OCH8GaoXJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer: 109654BR Principal Systems Engineer NM – Las Cruces Raytheon IIS/GIS provides Operations and Maintenance support for the Intelligence Community Job Description: This Principle Systems… https://t.co/O8gvGGgnwD 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/BJMtiCgyFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager:   Job Description – Project Manager (00019408) Job Description  Project Manager – (00019408) Description   Job Description: Working closely with architects, infrastructure staff and stakeholders… https://t.co/J6EU2zgSZT 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/EaRkDsQjPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work… https://t.co/v53QQRDLMf 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/L9u2nbvA5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Technology Analyst #1254: Enterprise Technology Analyst for Sacramento Municipal Utility District (SMUD), Sacramento, CA. Configure SAP and other enterprise applications to support system modifications,… https://t.co/c808u9pLuP 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/jvgGn71HNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, System Software: TECHNOLOGY Mountain View, CA Sr. Engineer, System Software Responsible for designing infrastructure and interfaces, developing integration software, coding quick scripts and… https://t.co/RfVVRaWhFJ 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/GpUf9vrgrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Developer: Full-time/Benefited Salary Range: $80,019.58 – $97,264.29 annually Exempt position. Open Until Filled Description: Under general direction of the Information Systems Manager, the… https://t.co/mI3FwmxoJ8 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Cmr3NMF2NQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Engineers #CHIIJA: Software Quality Assurance Engineers Cbre, Inc. has an opportunity in Chicago, IL for a Engineer, D&amp;T Quality Assurance. Experience with NetBeans or Eclipse required.… https://t.co/MUB4WnhbCo 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/NqaKxvYgmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allbirds Tree Skippers and Tree Runners: Price, Details, Release Date: The footwear maker famous for its wool has developed a new textile from eucalyptus. https://t.co/Nd4tt4AFZJ #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/uG32Cyuxzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Design Engineer: Senior Staff Design Engineer (Job location is Seattle, WA) Develop software solutions utilizing JavaScript, CSS &amp; HTML. Develop content pipeline to design &amp; develop video streaming… https://t.co/9ru1ORiCJ2 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/DKl7lfLEmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Engineer: Senior System Engineer Computer/IT Pall ForteBio LLC develops analytical systems that enable real-time analysis of biomolecular interactions in micro-volume sample sizes, providing… https://t.co/4UeecYfuUp 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/dzcBQhDBkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Aspire Systems Inc is looking for Senior Application Developer. Develop and write codes, interact with clients to understand and gather client requirements. Implement best practices,… https://t.co/59hESdFypj 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Interaction Designer: TIBCO Software Inc. has the following opportunities in Palo Alto, CA: &amp;nbsp; Associate Interaction Designer [Ref #8BO0823] Define all aspects of the user experience for Tibco’s… https://t.co/N0vk6mNrqm 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geographic Information System Technology Specialist: Utility Data Contractors, Inc is looking for Geographic Information System Technology Specialist in Denver, Colorado. Manage full life cycle development of… https://t.co/cQj3ZisFkB 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Z7LR5Y8NYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: A2Z Development Center, Inc. – Irvine, CA. Software Development Engineer – Assist senior engineers in the design and development of large-scale, multi-tiered, games, software… https://t.co/2ZiG9pN89c 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/PQmxiTNeIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R42120: Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, Virginia is looking for Master Software Engineer. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of… https://t.co/IuS0Z36wrD 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Xp9ZZ5tXMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Instructor #52911: Halliburton Energy Services Incorporated in Fort Worth, Texas seeks Senior Technical Instructor to deliver and assist with writing and editing of highly technical training and… https://t.co/gLHTIKpBxl 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/roALhd04B2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple Information Technology Positions (Pontiac, Michigan): Oakalnd County Michigan, Oakland County’s Award Winning Information Technology Department is hiring! Information Technology Business Analyst-… https://t.co/egfzAWWLYD 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ZTwfKEoJ7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: COMPUTER/IT: Senior Software Engineer for Siemens Medical Solutions USA, Inc. (Mountain View, CA) to dsgn &amp; dev healthcare app SW. Req Mast in Comp Sci, SW Eng, Biomdcl Eng or rel + 2 yrs… https://t.co/ZzA77NwpRX 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/lL2rcMPMfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS Systems Analyst: IT KeySource, Inc. has openings for the following positions: Software Engineer (ITKS180302) with Master’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering(any),Technology, Any Analytical Science or… https://t.co/yJfujppxKT 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/3DJWMnHwfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Do Augmented-Reality Glasses Look So Bad?: It's tough to pack in all the necessary tech and still make something people want to wear. https://t.co/rX64CZud97 #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Gojt2EVuhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications and Publications Coordinator: The National Association of Schools of Music, a not-for-profit specialized accrediting association founded in 1924, headquartered in Reston, VA, is seeking a full-time… https://t.co/8100TE5ko4 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Construction: Construction Professionals, are you ready to take your career to another level with an organization that will have your best interest in mind? Since its inception, Timothy Jon &amp;… https://t.co/u8IwNQa9Xh 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/IpTCHdJQvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As a Senior Software Engineer on the Carbonite Recover team, you will be part of the agile team responsible for designing, development, and maintenance Carbonite’s new Disaster Recovery… https://t.co/NTYIadGiUE 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/KtR4itiB7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/fs1KPTbgvC 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/gZMTkkUYLd #tech #career #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/9tnMmqiSXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Receiving Inspection Supervisor: 15513BR Receiving Inspection Supervisor General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General… https://t.co/0qXhvMByzI 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/pv0101bLeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: 107185BR Systems Engineer CO – Aurora Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems… https://t.co/3NTdtRl9pE 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/0X2JHuMkzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst – Rockford: Overview Wolverine Worldwide is a global marketer of branded footwear, apparel, and accessories. With an established global footprint that spans approximately 200 countries and… https://t.co/zmAXNHc8HK 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/TadevcjCfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GMP Systems Specialist I, Engineering: Job ID 11022 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Manufacturing More information about this job Overview… https://t.co/XBA71nncQI 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/edo6SwWLOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Data Analyst The Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco’s Information Technology department has an immediate opening for a Data Analyst within the Advanced Data and Analytics Competency organization… https://t.co/3CIFqyFGoB 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/bQaazApSXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Solutions Consultant: TIBCO Software Inc. has the following opportunities in Palo Alto, CA: &amp;nbsp; Associate Interaction Designer [Ref #8BO0823] Define all aspects of the user experience for Tibco’s… https://t.co/j7NhBK6KRY 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: Saicon Consultants seeks Senior AWS Architect in Overland Park, KS. Architect &amp; design complex apps. Req. Bach.’s/foreign equiv. in Electronics Engg., Electronics &amp; Comm. Engg., CE, CS / reltd. + 5… https://t.co/kkPE4GsJWK 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software… https://t.co/64V5qGettR 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pi Day PC Deals: Microsoft, HP, Dell, Lenovo: We don't need to give you 3.14 reasons why these are stellar discounts. https://t.co/s68KTapWti #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ib24Ae24IO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Avaya Inc. seeks a Software Engineer III to develop software system or application &amp; provide system &amp; Network Management System administration. Requirements: Master’s in Comp Science or… https://t.co/yjK35Iha8K 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: IT Positions available at Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: SYSTEMS ANALYSTS: Analyze, design, develop &amp; test applications. Prepare test plans. Create &amp; automate… https://t.co/GbWwFYMcgp 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42119: Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, Virginia is looking for Senior Software Engineer. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of… https://t.co/C5NJM0Og11 👈#IT #job #hiring  #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Information Technology Senior Application Developer in Stillwater Campus. Job Summary: The application developer will work closely with Division of Agricultural Sciences and Natural Resources administration and faculty to create… https://t.co/gQ6B3zIba3 https://t.co/jG1ZhiM8jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer Ref Job #0246 Las Vegas, NV Design, develop, test, code &amp; integrate software products. Requires: Bachelor degree in Information Technology (or Foreign Equivalent), plus 5 years of progressively responsible… https://t.co/uWKyVbhtmR https://t.co/rgK3AqZaXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Senior Developer job open at Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA. Job # R10001338 Job Description: Senior Developer sought by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA to utilize solid technical… https://t.co/ytapclZf3a https://t.co/iB4tYyuA7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Carroll College, a private, Catholic diocesan, liberal arts college, is seeking a Network Administrator, who will serve as a member of the Network team within the Information Technology department.  This… https://t.co/NcLeII6TQ8 https://t.co/2BhF60WOMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Contract Compliance Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/tBa83xDpJT https://t.co/q9WZJp35so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Engineer: JOB SUMMARY Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings, industrial systems, vehicles, equipment and grounds. Working under limited supervision, monitors building system… https://t.co/vunvwZ841w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Feds most… https://t.co/Gj9XcxDCfj https://t.co/LnOQ9TAMFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer – Need Only: Applied Thought Lead Java Developer – Need Only W2 Irving, TX Type: Contract Duration: Long Term Rate: Negotiable Mode of Interview: Telephonic Job Description: Need Only W2 Candidates. – Looking for a lead developer with… https://t.co/mrGnN3iy4F https://t.co/Z8d3D5tKe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integration/Test Engineering Manager – Orlando, FL: Req ID : 427689BR Job Code/Title : L1785:Sys Integratn/Test Eng Mgr Job Description : Test Equipment E&amp;T Manager that will be responsible for the Design Deployment Team. Responsibilities include… https://t.co/qPtCWWKe0v https://t.co/tNQ1D0vtmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Solution Architect: ETL Solution Architect Ref No.: 18-14650 Location: Deerfield, Illinois Kindly find the JD below and let me know if you are available for the same. Position :ETL Architect Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Deerfield, IL… https://t.co/6WTxZZAwLe https://t.co/eewwDqWB4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer: Informatica Developer ===================== Apply now Date: Apr 10, 2018 Location: Blue Ash, OH, US, 45242 Company: Kroger Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business: Corporate… https://t.co/Jt4YegExSR https://t.co/GfJWp6xJ1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer, Senior: Careers Center | Network Engineer, Senior Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/fPzvHlxA5M https://t.co/F7kz29MLWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT *Permanent full time role* RESPONSIBILITIES * Create detailed technical specifications including interface design, class diagrams, and architecture diagrams * Drive alignment on solutions with architecture teams… https://t.co/rRoOX1LTsA https://t.co/z5hpt8ul6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: Vistex Consultant Full-time with Denken Solutions, Irvine, CA. Position based out of Irvine, CA HQ, but may be assigned to various client/project sites anywhere in USA. Configure/design/assist with Vistex-based admin &amp; analysis of complex… https://t.co/XjTQBFb7po https://t.co/JIsapbGnVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Scientist: Morris College, a private four year Liberal Arts College in Sumter, South Carolina, is seeking to fill the following position(s): Computer Scientist To teach introductory Computer Science courses and introductory Cybersecurity courses… https://t.co/mPZ8RtLGnO https://t.co/J6bpyH92t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Specialist: Marketing Specialist to research, gather data &amp; analyze market conditions to develop online sales strategies. Bachelor’s in Business Admin. or Marketing reqd. Mail resumes to job location: Ahn Marketing Inc. (Super Bunny’s Beauty… https://t.co/JhqNe1nSlT https://t.co/7eGPbdHXHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analysts: Business System Analysts Washington State University seeks detail-oriented, skilled Business Systems Analysts for WSU’s Finance, Payroll, and Human Resource Modernization Initiative. Incumbents play a pivotal role in analyzing,… https://t.co/7hbqLSE1Tc https://t.co/mUzIBSqFSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Automation Test Engineer #R44491: Master Automation Test Engineer Requisition ID R44491 Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Lead overall engineering, design, development and execution of complex automated… https://t.co/KMdNEjG48q https://t.co/9jNoEHNXqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Risk Consultant 4 (Enterprise Escalation Leader): Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at… https://t.co/pNXiBUJRnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close Support Desk Specialist(TS/SCI w/Poly): Job Description What Youll Get to Do: This role is for the tech savvy individual who receives satisfaction when working one on one with people. The Close Support Specialist is responsible for receiving,… https://t.co/ePuicgYkt5 https://t.co/A9IihvUvtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/QEKPh4F7mN https://t.co/6cJSQOFHsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP ALM / Quality Center | Software Test Analyst: HP ALM / Quality Center | Software Test Analyst Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your… https://t.co/ouztUJMaY0 https://t.co/xH0Pct9tOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Cloudious LLC is one of the fastest emerging IT Solutions and Services Company headquartered in San Jose, CA with their global offices in Canada and APAC. Roles &amp; Responsibilities: Experience of the build and deployment of software using… https://t.co/QYAM7o7Nax https://t.co/sOj5RDcX1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Privacy Compliance Project Manager- Principal Associate: Job Description Job ID: R44335 West Creek 3 (12073), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by… https://t.co/YhcEdqOiuv https://t.co/x8lynaE7Qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer and Full Stack Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Houston, TX Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/13/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of… https://t.co/tZ9HoRQ0gP https://t.co/e1pkGCNotb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: IT: Senior Developer job open at Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA. Job # R10001338 Job Description: Senior Developer sought by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA to utilize solid technical… https://t.co/sDlFjDt6lm https://t.co/dsAPPluNYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Academy District 20 is seeking a skilled Network Engineer to manage the ongoing day-to-day support for a network that serves 35 different locations. This individual will primarily manage firewall, web filter, storage… https://t.co/4y7TM1jMgv https://t.co/9bDUMXes5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Threat Analyst – Tier 2 Shift Lead: Description:Department of Homeland Security (DHS), Security Operations Center (SOC) Support Services is a US Government program responsible to monitor, detect, analyze, mitigate, and respond to cyber threats and… https://t.co/zlWzN3tMeW https://t.co/lJM8pyd7JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/JVM Senior Engineer: The Nerdery is seeking a Senior JVM Software Engineer to work on a wide variety of projects as part of our team. About the Software Engineering Team At the Nerdery, our Software Engineering team believes strongly in quality… https://t.co/2JfzqLCFsu https://t.co/UYHcvkfgES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer / Web Design – WordPress: Ebeacon is looking for experienced WordPress designers/developers to work with our team either as a project-based contractor or contract-to-hire, or a part-time employee. Remote work is anticipated.… https://t.co/0pdTamBtxJ https://t.co/hHJ7X1u0DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager- Heavy Civil ENR 400 GC: San Fernando, CA Full-time $140k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Senior Project Manager with Heavy Highway/Heavy Civil/Structures experience, please read on! We have delivered unparalleled service to our… https://t.co/MFaU7mzHvn https://t.co/TTzDi4d0Qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Systems Architect Job: Windows Systems Architect (Job Number:434881) Description: Job Description – This position will provide Engineering oversight and project based engineering in the areas of MS Windows, Desktop Windows OS, Exchange, Active… https://t.co/rPJLx8FNVb https://t.co/wuutfW7O8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Test Engineer II: 109223BR Sr Test Engineer II CO – Aurora 109223BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems that make the world a safer… https://t.co/hs5a9lWdKr https://t.co/L42iezEYm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/10/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology… https://t.co/vCwJ3L69pg https://t.co/9kYfFNWPwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: Job Description Project Manager I (19514) This position works closely with the Project Managers and various Regional and Corporate staff. This is the first step towards management responsibilities. It is viewed as a junior Project… https://t.co/W0P192eu1z https://t.co/Myv4tVHOoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Data Analyst – Responsible for extracting, consolidating, transforming and analyzing data from different systems. Make recs about data methods to improve data quality &amp; systems efficiency. Use stat methods to analyze data &amp; generate… https://t.co/lvzykdjtiD https://t.co/kxKkZuEFYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted Today Based in San Francisco, CA we are an extremely fast-growing innovative startup that offers a very unique product directed toward a specific segment of the financial services… https://t.co/sCPROifZkO https://t.co/gzQmDjZp0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator 1:   Job Description – Systems Administrator 1 (18003111) Systems Administrator 1 Requisition ID : 18003111 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/Dj7kMCPlj3 https://t.co/qWMJaB31x4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18007388) Sr Java Backend Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18007388 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/Zqm2fLkFJe https://t.co/QvJNGVim1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tableau Developer: Tableau Developer Ref No.: 18-14726 Location: San Antonio, Texas Title:- Tableau BI Developer Location:- San Antonio TX Contract Role Developer Digital : BI Data Visualization – Tableau, PL/SQL BI – Tableau reports and Dashboards.… https://t.co/3Vh9mUkif6 https://t.co/abiusuSukX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer: MASTER SOFTWARE ENGINEER – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Mult pos avail: Lead overall tech design, dvlpmt, modification, &amp; implementation of comp apps using existing &amp; emerging tech platforms. Requires Master’s… https://t.co/1Rm8VizCwj https://t.co/hJadOtSpi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer-ServiceNow Implementation (Hoffman Estates, IL):Implement integrated solutions using ServiceNow management platform, encompassing strategy, support and tools, to enhance delivery of project management to users, and… https://t.co/z2D3XrxUyS https://t.co/bEs7bOewW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE ENGINEER: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Arlington, TX for Software Engineer Advanced to design, develop, modify &amp; implement software programming for Teamcenter Application products. Mail resumes to Attn: Tiara Robinson /Req#223896,… https://t.co/iX1upAC12r https://t.co/6zregJJysH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Occupancy Planner – Corporate Space Planning: * IMPORTANT NOTE: This is not an IT-type job, but more akin to those who have commercial space planning experience. JOB SUMMARY Guide and execute the development, communication, and deployment of… https://t.co/kVh8pNdamw https://t.co/E5zx5HMcLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: AT A GLANCE The System Administrator will be responsible for maintaining a variety of technologies encompassing a Post Production and Business based IT infrastructure, as well as, providing direct support to end users. Ideal… https://t.co/ijmm2nqf8J https://t.co/Bi8l0U1Xjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Location: _This position is located in Portland, Oregon_ Department: _Project Management_ ABOUT FICTION: Fiction is a strategy and design studio based in NW Portland. We work with global brands and local companies to create work that… https://t.co/fzKyf8Wsrh https://t.co/U6uBfkn9ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer 3:   Job Description – Systems Engineer 3 (18004097) Systems Engineer 3 Requisition ID : 18004097 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance… https://t.co/pM8cLNnG3A https://t.co/tKF3erXWjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Apps Technical Consultant: Oracle Apps Technical Consultant Ref No.: 18-00597 Location: Tampa, Florida Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/28/2018 Job Level Specific Duties – Performs specific delivery activities in support of broader delivery… https://t.co/asH9PmL0IY https://t.co/S5SJkQVlRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II, Analytics: Software Engineer II, Analytics with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox… https://t.co/QdaE5IEC2n https://t.co/MaDkQwy9Ui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Embedded Software 3/4: Northrop Grumman Mission Systems Sector is seeking a Software Engineer Level 3 or Level 4 with the desire to learn new technologies to join our innovative Embedded and Intel Software team to help develop, enhance and… https://t.co/MIpvMQWuX4 https://t.co/Y5iXM3Tcjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Engineer Systems Integration: Location: Granville, Ohio – United States PURPOSE OF THE JOB The Sr. Engineer (SE) is a key leadership and execution role for delivering outcomes that are aligned with the Global Manufacturing Technology (MT) portfolio.… https://t.co/vpqDwZ58bn https://t.co/iCxclmDehm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>