<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightHouseD7 how is it working? When will the screen be open to claim our seats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder @majakristek @garden_brewers that was her first ever brew as well @HomebrewClubIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder @majakristek @garden_brewers congrats @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeoirFinder: @majakristek well done- you won Best Of Show at the @garden_brewers competition  (don't tell @adamski8)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abvfest I've two tickets for tomorrow afternoons 12-5pm sold out session if anyone is interested. #abvfest #tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail are there bus substitutions for the belfast dublin trains this sat (tomorrow)? If so which ones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abvfest @tubboy79 so is it 1 brewery 1 beer per session or is this just the specials each has?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder *half you mean :) seem to remember a certain someone getting a full pint of voyager the other day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder oh i am. Thats what im saying its worth it. I actually nearly exclusively buy halves anyway no matter what the %.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder what about a fancy pants sour that say only 4% id accept a half!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains @AerLingus more Mr. Pushek! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder not today im afraid, physio :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelinden well its because its so good you will eat and drink so much that you will be shitting yourself on the jax the following day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder @thebeernut thats fine, like i said i was off too, burritos bought @Boojum_Dublin eurovision awaits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abvfest cant wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut @BeoirFinder just spotted him in alfie byrnes. No equipment just pints.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheNotoriousMMA: Myself and my team are urging everyone to please VOTE YES TO EQUALITY! Every human deserves equal rights #WeAreAllOne …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaleOfAle thanks for the spoiler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thornbridge what chocolate was used and in what form in the cocao wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cara_eire @Ruddspumps @emagine_media ah no bother, you looked crazy busy alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons @Ruddspumps @emagine_media i was there a few hours ago and didnt see the stout or weiss?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons heading off to simons to try their range today with @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SevereMMA @SeanSheehanBA where was it announced it was on December 5th and in calgary? It could be on the fox show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brian_con beer mile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Breadandbonesir: We've got new beer and you can win all of them with a lil retweet. Get em down your gullet! #win #craftbeer http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeerFest tweeeeet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PLL08 @danawhite @laolse dont have that capability. Watched on laptop, not everyone lives in the USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danawhite @laolse disappointing that people who legally pay for the card cant rewatch it without paying again. I paid like a sucker i guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewsWePlate @mnixon86 i guess spent grain is used for feed. So added value of processing. Two products for 1 makes flour cheaper?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewsWePlate malting process?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chadmendes #respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brk3 bt sports subscription or else pay per view kn the ufc website. 18e for hd for tonight's event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys i got in trouble for tweeting you during the ceremony. Enjoy tonight! http://t.co/jAW68Ng95Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys fair enough but their are other organizations they can go to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys for a sport that incredibly young its not so bad. How much were the fighters making 10years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys look what the fighters on the undercard at these boxing events get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @BeoirFinder 2 other irish fighters and gunni nelson on the card too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @BeoirFinder well conor is primarily a counter striker anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @BeoirFinder i dont think anyone get tapped with a heel hook these days bar palhares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @BeoirFinder mendes isnt a bih kicker though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains @kenearlys boxing is way worse but i dont remember you taking so much of an issue with Mayweather making his money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains @kenearlys what other sport does the leading star have to do all the work for the smaller guys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VHov6kP6ZM so excited for tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GarethADaviesDT can you stop being such a dickhead, get out of other people's interviews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uglyducklingdub: Last chance to enter our comp for a FREE lunch for two people to try our new menu in our Georges St diner. Rt &amp; follow…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut that was a quick flight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_um_clark any plans to come to ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation you think we will see zagreb dublin any time soon? Maybe with the new terminal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys how did you an mma hater get the ufc189 gig? Still looking forward to hear what you think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SoderandKo: Want to win a complimentary brunch for you and four friends? RT this post for your chance to win! #FreebieFriday http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski  no its shit today and tomorrow! Only two good days in croatia it seems!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski @Oblivious_ @brewdog 4.20e for jackhammer in ireland in the beer shop. Probably 10e then in an irish pub!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski @Oblivious_ @brewdog 7.2% though and it comes with this view http://t.co/Gonqunkxy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @Miro_zlikovski @brewdog 7.5ish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @Miro_zlikovski @brewdog good enough for me, for croatians its expensive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @Miro_zlikovski @brewdog http://t.co/4CvdvnZCEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski drinking some nice fresh @brewdog in zadar at the garden bar. Surprised! http://t.co/BkHAr8er7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryeriverbrewing @Tesco selling your beer after its bbe, got caught out today http://t.co/6GWEQK9JWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryeriverbrewing how is your pilsner on sale with a BB of oct 2016 if you bottle with a 12 month expiry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brk3 blocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob @BeerOClockShow where you going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoopersDIYBeer how do you make beer kits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryeriverbrewing you guys have to do that watermelon beer again. Whats the next festival your at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Balthazar___B: What a revelation @ryeriverbrewing have been at #icbf, take a bow lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons great day at the @IrishBeerFest great pale stout! @majakristek http://t.co/bi2DxvI1O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majakristek @IrishBeerFest @ryeriverbrewing i completely changed my mind on them, awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OBrotherBrewing: We are giving away a pair of tickets to the @IrishBeerFest this weekend. Just follow us and retweet #IrishCraftBeer ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SevereMMA: Video - UFC 194: Aldo vs McGregor "Stacked" Promo 

http://t.co/OZZhjcfBGT #UFC194 http://t.co/1Icpb0v3JH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @publinie: RT to win a pair of tickets to the All Ireland craft beer fest in the RDS. http://t.co/1AAJucDYUy http://t.co/rjAv2vdn1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Thetaste_ie: RT to Win Tickets! The Irish Craft Beer Festival Returns – http://t.co/ylfRubQq6e #WinTicketsToIrishCraftBeerFest http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SLambertSons: @rickoshea @IrishBeerFest @BeoirFinder We'll be bringing some tasty specials from our #YellowBelly range! http://t.co/t4v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @socialmedia_ie: Win tickets to Ireland's largest celebration of craft brewing with @connector360 RT this post &amp; FLW @IrishBeerFest http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WaterlooBarD4: Fancy winning 2 tickets to the @IrishBeerFest in the RDS, Ireland's largest #craftbeer festival? Just RT http://t.co/MZq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani @PKelly121 so what are your top 3 sporting cities in the world so?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @radikale_brews: Who wants to win 2 tickets for the @IrishBeerFest the following week end. RT this to enter. Winner will be announced Th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlfieByrnes very nice beer http://t.co/6SVKkmSCjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craft beer bars of dublin, tempt me for an evening beer?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomebrewClubIrl @Themottlybrew @Thehomebrewcomp @minchmalt review of the Summer Session comp is now up http://t.co/1Z9vrGRa8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons what beers of yours will be on tap this weekend? Ive got a thirst already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Thehomebrewcomp: Build your own all grain kit with liquid yeast: https://t.co/oc6WAcT4LL now added #homebrew #allgrain http://t.co/V9Hg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majakristek @CapitalBrewers @minchmalt @Themottlybrew @Thehomebrewcomp looks great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @majakristek: Prizes ready for the @CapitalBrewers summer session competition,thanks to @minchmalt @Themottlybrew @Thehomebrewcomp http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CapitalBrewers: Thanks to @Themottlybrew @minchmalt @Thehomebrewcomp for the prizes for the summer session comp today. I will keep ye u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biggrillfest is there any discount for @BeoirOrg members?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaRunda is there nova runda in split?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oblivious_ @brewdog are we doing ground work for a multi million business now, let them find their own place :p PS http://t.co/lrNgqc0JrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cantillion brewery, twas excellent. http://t.co/IUc26G7lDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themottlybrew @DubBeerLadies @CapitalBrewers @HomebrewClubIrl tis good. Loads left and we have to organize a meet up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryeriverbrewing: We've now only got 20 DAYS to our 2nd Birthday. To help celebrate with us with a free case of beer, just Fav &amp; RT! htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@57theheadline does the irish times count?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @57theheadline: Who wants to win Birthday vouchers? RT for a chance. Valid until end October https://t.co/sq8vUNojWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryeriverbrewing: We have 3 WEEKS before our 2nd birthday. To celebrate with us just Fav &amp; RT for your chance to win a case of beer! htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @57theheadline: Lots of vouchers to be won to celebrate our 2nd birthday.  RT to win.  First winner by 2pm https://t.co/8SygZakl8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danawhite @PaddyHolohanMMA you gotta love this guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fireworks and @SLambertSons beers, great night https://t.co/StKsxO67Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChicagoTownIre: It's competition time folks and we have another #BuddaBag to give away! RT to be in with a chance of winning! http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lidl_ireland @lidl_ireland strawberry, burger, tomato? #TasteofSuccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whitehagbrewery @Pmacspub @Cassidys27 @BlackbirdRath @majakristek damn cant make it but can't wait to buy this beer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>