<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Engineer – Automation: Job Description Section 1: Position Summary The Software Test Engineer position is a hands-on role that contributes to the success at Ascensus by designing and developing automated tests, scripts and tools to champion… https://t.co/Y6PjppWntY https://t.co/aIicFq5w3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: As part of the TPGSI business team, Business Analyst (BA) will elicit and document business and technical requirements in support of TP strategic objective to design a new eligibility and enrollment system. This new system,… https://t.co/eV3cOE05PX https://t.co/a6YdjlzaEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With new plan, Macron wants France to win AI 'arms race': PARIS (Reuters) - French President Emmanuel Macron has set his sights on artificial intelligence as the next technological frontier France cannot afford to miss, and will launch a major… https://t.co/BF1d3nQLpw https://t.co/ULNqlC5Eyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior RedHat OpenShift Technical Architect: Overview At Perficient you’ll deliver mission-critical technology and business solutions to Fortune 500 companies and some of the most recognized brands on the planet. And you’ll do it with cutting-edge… https://t.co/Hd0tintiFx https://t.co/PMTLx9OL0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: Senior Project Manager is responsible for leading teams to deliver project(s) that span across one or more business units. Manage resources, schedules,… https://t.co/tHW8mFZhon https://t.co/BeDJ764iuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer (Jr. to Sr.): Welcome to DataFinch Technologies! With the autism prevalence rate jumping as high as 1 in 42 live births, clinicians, parents and teachers are relying on technology to streamline effective treatments and in turn are helping… https://t.co/YEdNoW3GLv https://t.co/xOADR8jVOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: There are 7 billion people on this planet. And by 2050, there will be 2 billion more… many moving into urban centers at an unprecedented rate. Making sure there is enough food, fiber and infrastructure for our rapidly growing… https://t.co/H2Ol2p8j8O https://t.co/bmFkC6hAwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10518 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Pittsburg, PA //… https://t.co/9qLRJfpUDS https://t.co/qCZM433amP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cboe urges U.S. regulators to move forward with bitcoin ETFs: NEW YORK (Reuters) - U.S. securities regulators should not stand in the way of exchange-traded funds that hold cryptocurrencies like bitcoin from coming to the market as they are essentially… https://t.co/XmsGTAt5lh https://t.co/LQpjucdRgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager and Agile Coach: Position 1. Title: Project Manager Agile/Scrum Location: Chicago, IL Duration: 9+ Months Contract Job Requirements: Owning, managing and driving the plan Work with the team to define scope, develop estimates and plan… https://t.co/cZCRqzykem https://t.co/doynhUQ4h4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: ABOUT THE ROLE The Digital Project Manager role is a pivotal position within Relequints organization, responsible for the coordination and execution of the deliverables of our inbound marketing accounts. In so doing, the Digital… https://t.co/hqvia6D8Fv https://t.co/iyY7BYczSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey applications and custom… https://t.co/SqURhfjaD0 https://t.co/CBGPSBntVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/aiKEnxflTv https://t.co/koMeV33cij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager /SCRUM Manager: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global… https://t.co/lrRAJrK3SH https://t.co/bX3zdeoc2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: AmpThink is looking to hire a full-time UI Developer who can build beautiful, responsive front-end web applications based on existing design patterns. The ideal candidate will have a passion for front-end development and work closely with… https://t.co/iGXJbDsDKZ https://t.co/AlYFnn0RdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook: call, text history logging requires users' permission: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc, responding to reports in some technology industry media that it has been logging users' call and text history without their permission, said in a statement on… https://t.co/HAwhx76eCQ https://t.co/bNSaO1E4F8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Analyst – Software: Equus Software is a growing global mobility software provider in downtown Denver! We are looking for a Senior Tax Analyst to help ensure we stay at the top of our game with respect to our clients, software and tax modules.… https://t.co/kl7adRsTJW https://t.co/NsHYZ5O56Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: At 605 we are engineers, analysts, data scientists, media experts, marketing strategists and political operatives. Our team of data scientists pioneered the field of TV data analytics. We offer unique, independent audience measurement… https://t.co/NAi1jNsV7a https://t.co/grab1Q3tpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Tester: Job TitleQA Automation Tester – ID:31160 Duration3 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job SkillsAutomation, Selenium, SAlesforce, CRM LocationDallas, TX Date Posted03/05/2018 Qualifications: An ideal candidate will be an enthusiastic,… https://t.co/ePUwJmdZWr https://t.co/GrhkDxTOhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer, .Net, C#: Requisition Number 18-0249 Post Date 2/9/2018 Title Sr. Software Engineer, .Net, C# City Atlanta State GA Description Designs, modifies, develops, writes and implements software programming applications. Supports and/or… https://t.co/6dIljRpDIW https://t.co/vQkpm87OoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager / Scrum Master: Senior Project Manager / Scrum Master Description Position Summary * Responsible for the successful delivery of one or more medium to large sized Waterfall or Agile, and moderately to highly complex projects, which… https://t.co/SJ10OiyARm https://t.co/cUz0SoObWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South Pacific Jobs – Latin America &amp;… https://t.co/UWqxAKHowb https://t.co/Ro4fyFT4gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo CEO says its tech would have handled Uber self-driving incident safely: LAS VEGAS (Reuters) - The head of Alphabet Inc's autonomous driving unit, Waymo, said on Saturday that the company's technology would have safely handled the situation… https://t.co/tLY3uczLKq https://t.co/8LF0ApVKS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that determine how… https://t.co/NIMZ4qhxuU https://t.co/2PwF3fY0eA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Sales Architect (SE): Company Overview Do you want to be part of a fast-paced environment, supporting the growth of cutting edge technology in cloud computing? Silverline employees are passionate about what they do. Were a diverse group of… https://t.co/aGNVATDRWO https://t.co/y2M0jQRw69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Developer: Our Digital Media team is dedicated to creating and improving products and services used by millions of Canadians. Our developers, quality assurance specialists, product owners and scrum masters focus on all YP products that change… https://t.co/Ror7LZfVBW https://t.co/0bF2KGlJm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior, IT Development Manager: Requisition Number 17-1748 Post Date 11/20/2017 Title Senior, IT Development Manager City Bridgeton State MO Description On March 1, 2017 McKesson Corporation (NYSE MCK) and Change Healthcare Holdings, Inc., formed a new… https://t.co/7DZLx1gxXa https://t.co/rSpcgaXb5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Commerce Business Analyst (US): Zaelab is a dedicated team of focused, agile and innovative consultants who work to bridge the gap from vision to delivery of B2B commerce technology projects. Our commitment to evolving commerce beyond traditional… https://t.co/uACKmz079t https://t.co/2ANg7EHKxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans less likely to trust Facebook than rivals on personal data: Reuters/Ipsos poll: NEW YORK/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Fewer than half of Americans trust Facebook to obey U.S. privacy laws, according to a Reuters/Ipsos poll released on Sunday,… https://t.co/nnD8zhAKOX https://t.co/6t27HCJSmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer I, Applications: Sysco Associate Apply – Click Here Company: CORP Enclave Location: US-TX-Houston Zip Code: 77077 Minimum Level of Education: Bachelor’s Degree Minimum Years of Experience: 1 Position Type: Exempt Travel Percentage: 0 More… https://t.co/a4t1qxwXJZ https://t.co/ql5N06VdE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/MdozoDIq6N https://t.co/Cge1o1JNB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master I, Partner Solutions: Scrum Master I, Partner Solutions at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox… https://t.co/HKoh1Ttvk1 https://t.co/M8llNhFBif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master III (Release Train Engineer):   JOB INFORMATION Promotes the agile mindset in agile teams, challenging and removing organizational and cultural impediments. They are constantly guiding teams in discovery and learning. The Scrum Master also… https://t.co/xDnRrcc49C https://t.co/LsNqmSo1nW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fullscreen – Senior Ruby Engineer: The Senior Ruby on Rails Software Developer within Fullscreen Engineering team supports the architecture, design, development, and deployment of applications, API services, and client integrations for Fullscreens Brands… https://t.co/1ChxtoGdNu https://t.co/MgXzKExzA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian agency denies reported security lapse in ID card project: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - The semi-government agency behind India's national identity card project on Saturday denied a report by news website ZDNet that the program has been hit by another… https://t.co/A0jUjPulLf https://t.co/w1OzPyZ4u8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Javascript Web Developer: We are seeking a Full-Stack Javascript Web Developer for a client that specializes in agricultural biotechnology. This company’s mission is centered on finding agricultural solutions for a sustainable future. Twenty… https://t.co/jxyyqorOyT https://t.co/TuS6bWHXpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Position Overview: The Sr Project Manager is responsible for managing key projects as it relates to Operations, Vendor Implementations, New Product Development and major software enhancements. Additionally, the Sr. Project Manager… https://t.co/hP4vtDqXgi https://t.co/x5FR9mySBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Architect: Overview Jellyfish, delivers digital marketing solutions across the world for a host of impressive brands from their offices in the US, Europe, and South Africa. The agency’s award-winning combination of technology and talent help it… https://t.co/uZFEy07Roh https://t.co/ZIWULS2s7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DCGS-SOF Project Manager – 15507: DCGS-SOF Project Manager Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company) Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants for… https://t.co/05e9Dzwyam https://t.co/u1lj3BbAsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer: Test Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in… https://t.co/TLvyL0tFFT https://t.co/JG5ZZQmmdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Senior Technical PM with Strong Mobile application and API Contract: 6+ Months Location: Chicago, IL Qualifying area : Strong mobile application and API/Integration. Responsibilities: * Standard PMP project management… https://t.co/qhRRv569E0 https://t.co/EHejzQh7Jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk deletes Facebook pages of Tesla, SpaceX after challenged on Twitter: (Reuters) - Verified Facebook pages of Elon Musk's rocket company SpaceX and electric carmaker Tesla Inc disappeared on Friday, minutes after the Silicon Valley billionaire… https://t.co/vzErVVabUw https://t.co/McBFlFr1cX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: As part of the TPGSI business team, Business Analyst (BA) will elicit and document business and technical requirements in support of TP strategic objective to design a new eligibility and enrollment system. This new system,… https://t.co/cx4wizkUx8 https://t.co/qHiqdT4gQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Certified Scrum Master) for HP Inc.: Paradigm is looking for an experienced Project Manager to support our client, HP Inc., in San Diego, CA. The individual were seeking is skilled in managing technical design projects from initiation,… https://t.co/cIe8WDnhUq https://t.co/M9DepEIUd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Test Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python… https://t.co/fu5SBYM9xy https://t.co/hfgi9TmZku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 2: At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our work preserves freedom and… https://t.co/KRw4lJcHdR https://t.co/hfQ3UT1ovz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/cFA8QgXBbQ https://t.co/eihkcRQqoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India queries Cambridge Analytica over alleged Facebook data breach: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - India has set a March 31 deadline for London-based political consultancy Cambridge Analytica to respond to a query on whether it was engaged to improperly harvest… https://t.co/KeR0zsj8ut https://t.co/M7zQm4mP74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Full-Stack Developer, Consignor: Looking for a challenging job with opportunity for growth? Do you like to find ways to improve, teach and inspire to achieve goals? Come build a career at The RealReal a successful, growing, luxury fashion startup!… https://t.co/mYZQ33xBIJ https://t.co/f1KJeciVZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – EA: Scrum Master – EA Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates. Daily… https://t.co/RBezTbLqhZ https://t.co/gX2sYL9hKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Scrum Master: Software Developer/Scrum Master Morrisville, NC Brightree Home Healthcare &amp; Hospice (Morrisville, NC) seeks Software Developer/Scrum Master Company Overview Brightree, the leading provider of cloud-based software for the… https://t.co/U5vV826Gsx https://t.co/TpvFK4BlBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Architect: Overview Jellyfish, delivers digital marketing solutions across the world for a host of impressive brands from their offices in the US, Europe, and South Africa. The agency’s award-winning combination of technology and talent help it… https://t.co/EJUUygpEFF https://t.co/3F0ygUL517]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect: We are a small team of passionate problem solvers working to radically change how ambitious organizations and federal agencies build software. We think differently and have developed amazing solutions for interesting problems for… https://t.co/Z4ed39dXPv https://t.co/itah0Gq6B4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Application Developer CSI Leasing (CSI) is one of the largest independent equipment leasing specialists in the world, with customers in more than 36 countries. Established in 1972, we have helped thousands of organizations… https://t.co/fvlKxLlGxy https://t.co/6CtoIe55fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm re-elects board of directors with tepid support: SAN DIEGO (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc re-elected its board of directors on Friday with weak support from shareholders, who grilled the U.S. chipmaker over its strategy following its successful… https://t.co/ae6OoXyh1P https://t.co/hddiunkutk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Bentonville, AR Full Time/Contract Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level… https://t.co/9PIraCIhl2 https://t.co/AC6eSaZ9rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cache Developer: Join Our Team: Do Meaningful Work and Improve Peoples Lives Our purpose, to improve customers lives by making healthcare work better, is far from ordinary. So are our employees. Working at Premera means you have the opportunity to… https://t.co/tICXoJmcty https://t.co/MGz4nDCZE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer (Jr. to Sr.): Welcome to DataFinch Technologies! With the autism prevalence rate jumping as high as 1 in 42 live births, clinicians, parents and teachers are relying on technology to streamline effective treatments and in turn are helping… https://t.co/W0AVPkKbPn https://t.co/jGenjFwBGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Coach: Scrum Master/Coach (******) Plano, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/05/18, Posted Date – 03/05/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview * escription: We are looking for a really strong SM/coach for our registration team… https://t.co/GDtgiqEOqF https://t.co/P8xtqqh2JB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Programmer Analyst: We have an immediate need for an experience .Net Programmer Analyst to join the team of our client, located in Lansing Mi. This is a Contract role and the manager is looking to hire someone immediately.Please send me your resume… https://t.co/mGCyVxXM2s https://t.co/AESCymiCZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Looking for an experienced Agile Coach to join our team supporting SSA in Woodlawn, MD MUST be US Citizen or green card holder Key Required Skills: Agile Coaching, Training, Agile Implementation experience using Scrum, Kanban, Lean, etc.,… https://t.co/UpiryxUZOf https://t.co/wmlNWYCdGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK investigators search London office of firm at center of Facebook data storm: LONDON (Reuters) - Investigators from Britain's data watchdog searched the London offices of Cambridge Analytica, the data analytics firm at the center of a storm over… https://t.co/PQwsEfWikt https://t.co/Fs3xwtSM7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/cd7W109Akk https://t.co/3f6lGWrFsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II: JOB INFORMATION Suports one or more delivery teams within the fast-paced application development environment. Helps build high performing teams, build shippable product, and responsible for leading Agile project coordination to support… https://t.co/lMWQVBPJBG https://t.co/SF8Z9JNeZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB SUMMARY: * MANAGING BOTH WATERFALL AND AGILE PROJECTS. * THESE PROJECTS WILL SUPPORT WEBSITE UPGRADES AS WELL AS OUR UPGRADES/UPDATES WITHIN OUR SYSTEMS INTEGRATION CAPABILITY. RESPONSIBILITIES AND DUTIES: * CREATE AND… https://t.co/N78PjtF4Kx https://t.co/WdGijhgfwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: ***CLIENT UNABLE TO SPONSOR AT THIS TIME** NO C2C VENDORS JOB DESCRIPTION Plans and coordinates all aspects of internal information system-specific projects from initiation to delivery. Projects often involve network, server,… https://t.co/MuVjSDDmcU https://t.co/bBVXLiMxOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/zcaQRggKbr https://t.co/etpvZ5Y9o6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Systems Analyst st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 02/23/18, Posted Date – 02/23/18 Primary SkillsAgile,Scrum,RallyTax TermsC2COverview POSITION DETAILS: Team Info: * Team: Digital Security Technologies Operations and… https://t.co/2lysOHVUnp https://t.co/sFkZOhyVoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify to list shares in direct offering: (Reuters) - Streaming music leader Spotify Technology SA on Tuesday filed for a direct listing of its shares. https://t.co/JshOt6qfjP https://t.co/plnTVHEG01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – US: Role Project Manager – US Auto req ID 27609BR Domain Banking Skillset Automation Testing Service , Test Automation Tools Country USA State / Region / Province Delaware Work Location Delaware City, DE Company ITL USA Job Description… https://t.co/XMKMOYC7eM https://t.co/YgwLYro8JQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager /SCRUM Manager: Imagine being surrounded by intelligent, driven, and passionate innovators all working toward the same goalto create groundbreaking solutions that leave our world in a better place than we found it. Emerson is a global… https://t.co/9UrfMDyUdf https://t.co/ILgkcPqJOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Specialist – Full Time opportunity: DevOps Specialist – Full Time opportunity This is a full time opportunity.Qualifications and Skills Required:?Bachelor?s degree or higher in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or Electrical Engineering.?… https://t.co/A5miZkGGa8 https://t.co/ateActy5pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer III: Overview Experienced in Java/programming? Enjoy poking holes? We’re looking for a fast-learner with strong technical skills and an Agile background to join our team as a Senior Automation Test Engineer, where you’ll help ensure quality… https://t.co/1i3cWj4Isd https://t.co/JjIhmgDIl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F-22 Pilot Training Software Engineer, Mid-Level: Are you interested in learning to fly an F-22 while developing and maintaining F-22 Pilot Training Software used to train F-22 fighter pilots? The F-22 Vehicle Simulation Team within Training &amp;… https://t.co/tUh0kuJ1yl https://t.co/qqarRgRbaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta ransomware attack throws city services into disarray: NEW YORK (Reuters) - An Atlanta cyberattack has caused widespread city-run program outages and raised fears about the security of financial and personal data belonging to government workers,… https://t.co/2hf1JxGppE https://t.co/A09io6kZid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead: Description: Location: Carmel, Indiana ABOUT MISO MISO ensures reliable operation of, and equal access to, high-voltage power lines in 15 U.S. states and the Canadian province of Manitoba. MISO manages one of the world’s largest energy… https://t.co/8iT1UZTmue https://t.co/T1n69bbpn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest people you will ever meet in any particular… https://t.co/chc6VSXR2v https://t.co/z5tW7itV7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/1GPSUZyvBw https://t.co/g7P9tyFuN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst I: The IT Billing team in Macon Georgia is seeking a creative and self-motivated senior-level Developer to join the team responsible for the delivery of the new GEICO Billing System. Candidate will be presented with an… https://t.co/R1wjeLVZDp https://t.co/arVhaL6eSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers formally ask Facebook CEO to testify on user data: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. lawmakers on Friday formally asked Facebook Inc's Mark Zuckerberg to explain at a congressional hearing how 50 million users' data got into the hands of… https://t.co/fFnpNN30fi https://t.co/hVEX1Deah7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: As a DevOps Engineer at Athlinks, a division at Life Time fitness, you will be an embedded member and hands-oncontributor of an Agile/Scrum Delivery team. You will be in an environment that fosters cross-functionalcollaboration as… https://t.co/gpQccfPdkc https://t.co/tzIlesQNuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Engineer: Cloud Engineer Location: Boston, MA Position Summary: Act as part of cross-functional team to ensure QuickPivot’s cloud platform is highly available, scalable and secure on the AWS platform. Assist Engineering and Operations teams in… https://t.co/Tw2WqzUokV https://t.co/gzZwFmXZxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that determine how… https://t.co/ubVB2tfCku https://t.co/iup0hzoxK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer 16404: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology, Federal Civilian, and National Security, Aerospace &amp; Defense and… https://t.co/jnPDzjK4Gz https://t.co/r6RjnPmyKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify says about two million users suppressing ads without paying: (Reuters) - Music streaming service Spotify Technology SA [SPOT.N] said on Friday about 2 million of its non-paying users were suppressing advertisements, highlighting a potential… https://t.co/HYv1TuT0tl https://t.co/iiBJO73w5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – US: Infosys Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Project Manager Java, Agile Scrum Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital… https://t.co/XIx1si6Aq0 https://t.co/0La0YQLV9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Masters: Scrum Masters MEMPHIS, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/07/18, Posted Date – 03/07/18 Primary SkillsAgile,ScrumTax TermsC2COverview Requirements * Requires thorough knowledge of general management methods within non-profit… https://t.co/vj4R0YZos1 https://t.co/8lC4YMS7EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Project Manager: Scrum Master/Project Manager (data) Dunwoody, GA 12 month contract Education/Experience Bachelor degree in IT, finance or related discipline 5-7 years of progressive work-related experience, particularly Project Management… https://t.co/k7ZyUlz37K https://t.co/SArQ54i78n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Automation Engineer: The Senior Cloud Developer is expected to work on, and often lead, software engagements with customers. The software engineer will work alongside infrastructure architects and will engage both in presales requirements gathering… https://t.co/AvFe6bS07i https://t.co/lDlaSkQ2C9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Ruby on Rails Developer: THE OPPORTUNITY KleerMail is looking for a experienced and talented Full-Stack Ruby on Rails developer to contribute to the implementation of our Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) product offerings. Your primary focus will… https://t.co/80vMA6gwbC https://t.co/dNJeAWEozj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli social trading firm eToro raises $100 million in private funding: TEL AVIV (Reuters) - Israeli social investment platform eToro said it raised $100 million in private financing, bringing total funds raised to $162 million. https://t.co/dtdeaqYFIz https://t.co/y8MUAmga6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Engineer – C# or Java: Senior Software Development Engineer – C# or Java at Go Daddy Skip Navigation Careers Open Menu – GoDaddy Life – Our Teams – Benefits – University Students – Blog – GoDaddy Home – Facebook – Twitter –… https://t.co/ajBTVq9mom https://t.co/uGGqKEq4ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scrum master: scrum master Ref No.: 18-10389 Location: plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Columbus ,Ohio //… https://t.co/WjEbu4bOzY https://t.co/3bs0a8xFFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: globaledit, the brand behind the leading secure cloud-based creative collaboration service for professional digital photography and digital media, is seeking an experienced, digitally savvy Project Manager / Scrum Master to help to drive… https://t.co/IWlH8tqocv https://t.co/dRrIb2ReqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Back to Jobs Location: Atlanta, GA, United States Salary: DOE Posted: Oct 12 Reply ASAP to – ******************* OR Call at- ************ Android Application Developer Atlanta, GA Hire-type: C2C/W2 RESPONSIBILITIES: Work collaboratively with… https://t.co/6JqqZ5qvQp https://t.co/HdM21lnh6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer with 8 plus years’ experience: W2 DIRECT HIRE ONLY! NO C2C OR SPONSORSHIP ALIS Software, is currently seeking an experienced for a C# .NETSENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WITH 8 PLUS YEARS EXPERIENCE for a DIRECT HIRE opportunity with… https://t.co/UlU5TgDNo2 https://t.co/ke3oETvyo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Analyst – Software: Equus Software is a growing global mobility software provider in downtown Denver! We are looking for a Senior Tax Analyst to help ensure we stay at the top of our game with respect to our clients, software and tax modules.… https://t.co/d4a5gI7q3f https://t.co/vkBCBySB0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBA leaps on esports bandwagon with new league: LONDON (Reuters) - The inexorable advance of esports will break new ground next month when the NBA becomes the first American professional sports organization to operate an esports league. https://t.co/1UogUf8Ktr https://t.co/UJZzPz3gzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect (JAVA): The Software Architect is responsible for development activities for FanThreeSixtys back-end RESTful web services and data integration application, collaborating with Product Development, Mobile and Web Development teams. In… https://t.co/TSJg0RpRFy https://t.co/YI7AX93nwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DCGS-SOF Project Manager – 15507: DCGS-SOF Project Manager Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company) Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants for… https://t.co/O6VkP5FtM4 https://t.co/r3BHP73t6J]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>