<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Move on, give the victims families whatever they need to get closure on this and stop going on about this all the time #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nelson McCausland is a proper prick #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My uncle moved to Cavan a few years ago, I haven’t seen him since, I refuse to go to Cavan #ThisCrowdedHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Portroegirl @blackcoffeecup But the Taoiseach said it so it must be true, he’d never lie to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Taoiseach says by 2019 there’ll be more houses built than needed #CBLive https://t.co/mcn9OPZKfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure what would he know, he’s from Donegal #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly forgot Lucinda Creighton existed. Good times #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that air turbulence has seemed to knocked any banter out of Antonia, as much fun as a 10 hour flight #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Pete he’s trying his hardest but this Antonia one is giving him daggers whenever he opens his mouth #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is too much now, Ophelia has done more damage than we first thought. Stop pushing the weather forecasters on us #RayDarcy https://t.co/jWPVPOv3k7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy has giving up trying to control Peter Kay so he’s pretending to enjoy himself #LateLate #LateLateShow https://t.co/EVtJNBXG1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Kay channeling his inner Father Ted #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/BdHYwlkJRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking pricks laughing at the idea of getting a loaf of bread for free while the lady that makes is in the audience, ungrateful shites #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Tubridy would fuck up a cup of tea it seems #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mel Gibson: your heart goes out to the victims of sexual harassment.....once they ain’t Jewish  #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Gibson just slag Mickey D? GO FUCK YOURSELF MEL! #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When’s Ryan gonna give them some fucking Irish rugby jerseys he always gives them rugby jerseys #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to this girl only in comedy a year now, and now has her own tv show. #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christy Moore mixes humour current affairs, social issues and tragedy into his songs which is why he’s so well received everywhere. He mirrors life in his songs #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like listening to Christy Moore walking home from the pub drunk it’s brilliant #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy always looks so awkward sitting beside someone who’s playing a guitar and singing #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pogba, Ibrahimovic and Rojo back in the United squad tomorrow. #MUFC https://t.co/VnG62wkEnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkjlkjl They’ll have anything you want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkjlkjl On any street corner just look for a shifty fucker hanging around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of smokes has he been smoking? https://t.co/Te0Ucq7kot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italia 90 wins simply because in that moment when we beat Romania the whole country was on the streets going crazy, I don’t remember the same thing with the rest #irelandsgreatest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moment 5 #irelandsgreatest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennonFiona Yeah of course it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennonFiona Yeah saw it as well 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david_o_cleary Haha, cheers I’m RTÉ famous now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendangavin1 I nearly died when they read it out, fucking hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your tweet slagging David Davin-Powers hair gets read out in front of David-Davin Power #CuttingEdge https://t.co/Ifawxqh8Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there loads of nude women on the #CuttingEdge hashtag, it’s very disconcerting while I’m trying to read people’s views about PMT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Davin-Power saying what most of us who haven’t brainwashed by McGregor mania think about McGregor #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s confirmed David Davin-Power does not wear a wig so we should all shut up about it now but it does look like a wig, I bet ya it’s a wig #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#COYBIG #IRLDEN https://t.co/12paBhKiCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think John Delaney should step down tonight not because of the result just because he’s a bit of a cunt #IRLDEN #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bendtner scores now, I’m finding the nearest rock and hiding underneath it. #COYBIG #IRLDEN https://t.co/P7F0Rs7YaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I’m older I’ll tell my grandkids about the bogey man Christian Eriksen how he came to Dublin and slaughtered every man and woman #COYBIG #IRLDEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole of Ireland right now #COYBIG #IreDen https://t.co/EgocOyQxKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 50 minutes to go, I’m not a bit nervous come on ta fuck boys #COYBIG #IRLDAN https://t.co/fC0shD5FMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Claire Byrne show is now just a condensed version of the #LateLateShow it’s light entertainment at best with a bit of politics thrown in the mix.  #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkjlkjl  https://t.co/NjYqBGxKuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJVillan Yeah but he asked for a 13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkjlkjl I’ll be honest I wasn’t really paying attention to what she was saying if that’s what she said he’s probably better off perving at the young ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oskar seems so urban and cool #FirstDates https://t.co/mffxuDz08K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkjlkjl And he had the roving eye for the young ones he wanted a 26 year old not a 66 year old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pure Irish reaction from Michael ‘she told me off’ so fuck that, we seriously can’t handle being told off we’re bold kids. Seriously  #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Buffon making his final appearance for Italy tonight.  It’s just sad #ITASVE https://t.co/OWb1buDb2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve watched over 450 minutes of international football since Friday and I’ve seen zero goals. International football is a big pile of horse shite #WCQ2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Randolph tonight #COYBIG #DenIre https://t.co/RDVceq9yv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tommy Tiernan and his loyal followers at the next mass #LateLate #LateLateShow https://t.co/3gS4mzGPRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Vogue Williams aged 65 in the  #LateLateShow #LateLate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus Ryan will you let the ma... woman talk #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s like the pissed up auntie you’d run into at a 21st #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well Philomena I’m the good lord and I’m ordering you to stop right now. #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ll rewrite that ‘she’s not representing us Ryan, she’s representing America get your facts right’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s not representing us Ryan she representing America get your faces right #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She forgot to mention Obama’s heritage in Offaly while talking about his heritage that’s a big no no on the  #LateLateShow #latelate https://t.co/VKR8eTtvcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruanep1 Yeah probably but a man can’t help how he feels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendan Gleeson is the best person ever to walk this earth  #Latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aoife_pugh: Hi Never thought we would have to do this, but my Mam Sinead Pugh has  been missing since 8am Thursday morning 9th Nov ....…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never heard of @garyyounge until tonight I’m five minutes into show and I have nothing but utter respect for the man. A great man #AngryWhiteandAmerican]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine going for a pint with Joe Brolly, the man never shuts up #IrelandsGreatest https://t.co/HtH0t8Ydq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moment 3 #IrelandsGreatest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamienolan3 Stop lying it was you, you fancy Sheldon. https://t.co/iKaJZEc9iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When nobody views your profile on Plenty Of Fish https://t.co/7Klueopt4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarksofKarl Haha, I’ll never eat an apple tart again without the ladyboys of Bangkok being close to mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gino09071959 Haha you can have them mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These girls have lovely Adam’s Apples #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t think Brian has mentioned his sexuality once all night  #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hen Parties are one of the worst groups for sexual harassment, getting caught up in the middle of one is horrible and embarrassing. #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raising the prices on alcohol you buy in a shop won’t make one bit of difference people will still buy it and the price increase will become normalized in no time #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulallen86 Ah nice one, you won me over Paul, you’re my favorite know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulallen86 Brian had a Limerick FC Jersey, have you Paul?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulallen86 Nice bunch, but do you wear them with as much pride as Brian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian making his breakfast when he moves out of home #ThisCrowdedHouse https://t.co/BdWtaGUT1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulallen86 Fair play to ya, but Brian has the evidence I need to see evidence that you have more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brian lad has more sports gear than Lifestyle Sports.  #ThisCrowdedHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sue is back, I love Sue, Sue is life   Sue is also like every middle aged English woman I have ever met #FirstDates https://t.co/DRQZctFJ9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked Sophia until she said she don’t like dogs and prefers cats #FirstDates https://t.co/6C2P2taRRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He spent a lot of time by himself getting to know himself, we all know what that means.  #FirstDates https://t.co/H54kmFaNl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of the 3 women I’d choose to go on a date with Al Porter #BlindDateIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Conor just talk in his normal accent instead of talking like Frank Stapleton on Apres Match #latelate #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A McGregor fan can hear you say anything bad about him from 5 miles away #latelate #LateLateShow https://t.co/iCtjRkIl7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caoimhedory There’s a lot of people on Twitter tonight who are making much worse comments than that, are you telling them off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine been caught up in that world in real life fuck that I’d rather live a boring no craic life than looking over my shoulder everyday to see if I’m gonna be whacked #CardboardGangsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OFAHCentral: Retweet if you think Trigger is an absolute legend😂😂 https://t.co/dUdyaQRWD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleLostLad: Two men on my train are laughing at a group of young Star Wars fans because they've dressed up as their favourite charac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevoflatz It’s Graham actually, I realised it was in bad taste that’s why I deleted it. Call me a wanker all you like but a nasty one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sure there’s plenty of young talented comedians around the country who just need a platform but no RTÉ brings these two wankers on tonight #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the 1980s with ya Brendan and take your comedy back to where it belongs #LateLateShow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a stammer and wear glasses, Ed and I are so alike except I’m piss poor both financially and vocally #latelateshow #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He really was like Buddy the Elf expect Buddy the Elf is funny #LateLateShow #LateLate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergro30 Was just thinking the same.But since it happened in a North Dublin working class suburb they don’t want to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland is a big rug we just sweep everything under it and hope it goes away, couldn’t have said it better myself.  #aftertheheadlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 84 lived in the area until I was 15. My parents and neighbors told me all about it. The word ‘Stardust’ still sends a shiver down my back.  #aftertheheadlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbbrown35 It’s the truth it’s all a cover up why these people have no justice. People in positions of power protecting their own interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was Ireland’s Hillsborough but unlike Hillsborough these families still have no justice for their loved ones. The authorities don’t want to know it seems.  #aftertheheadlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fuck would Michael Barry feel if he or one of his family members were taken off this drug and basically told ‘ah well shit happens’  #cblive]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>