<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Analysis Associate Director: Research and Analysis Associate Director The Global Refined Products Supply Manager (GRM) will be a key member of the IHS Markit Oil Markets, Midstream &amp; Downstream (OMD) team. This position will play an… https://t.co/2u2VIr1pl8 https://t.co/eFQnjHAw3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Student Intern (SSE, KZ): For Siemens Application Support Engineer Student Intern (SSE, KZ) job – Internal Services – Houston, Texas Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/tXRlmkqBSL https://t.co/LNLIb1zRpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection, visualization and… https://t.co/bW8KuX1CF5 https://t.co/if4LuvMbjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator ==================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Sam Houston, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an immediate opening… https://t.co/hI7tyn1xVE https://t.co/Z63uuvXigw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Customer Support Specialist: Job ID : 74564BR Location : US – Texas – Houston : Job Description Job Title: Software Customer Support Specialist Requisition ID: 74564BR Location: Houston, TX When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be… https://t.co/LyELG8N081 https://t.co/Ge5V8TbDyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travelling Construction Operations Manager- Oil and Gas industry: Houston, TX Full-time $120k – $140k Posted 08/15/2018 If you are a Travelling Construction Operations Manager- with experience in the Oil and Gas industry please read on! Top Reasons to… https://t.co/2pOh7umkW9 https://t.co/u32vZNU7eK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HHPC – Temporary SharePoint Developer at NASA: Careers Center | HHPC – Temporary Point Developer at NASA Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/gnjWtLSONl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead and Process Engineer-PLM: Technical Lead and Process Engineer-PLM at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobs Working at HP Blog Faqs Sign in &amp; apply Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCollege… https://t.co/QjQi4Q095I https://t.co/jwOcoRuuM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect (100% remote/virtual) Job: AWS Solutions Architect (100% remote/virtual) (Job Number:439208) Description: Position is 100% remote/telework, with up to 25% travel required. JOB DESCRIPTION: – AWS Cloud Solution Architect SAIC is… https://t.co/UPjgMpGmbi https://t.co/aWjHraSFw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposal Specialist – Houston, TX (31603): Requisition ID 31603 – Posted 07/03/2018 – Marketing – United States – Texas – Permanent A WORLD LEADER IN TESTING, INSPECTION &amp; CERTIFICATION SERVICES Bureau Veritas offers dynamic, exciting employment… https://t.co/PL7r6ERCLT https://t.co/9qHaJmDe0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr/Lead JAVA Developer: Project Description A well known institutional banking client is undergoing a front-office technology overhaul for their commodities and financial markets businesses. One component of this programme is a new deal entry and… https://t.co/uigwMKXbQ2 https://t.co/IYxAlG71ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Application Developer: Business Systems Application Developer – Houston, TX – ********** – Find Jobs – Company Reviews – Find Salaries – Find Resumes – Employers / Post Job – Upload your resume – Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/FhgCaBGydS https://t.co/D1wsUxNI1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Systems Specialist: Job ID : 59149BR Location : US – Texas – Houston|US – Texas – Remote / Field : Job Description When you’re part of the team at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll do important work, and you’ll be valued and recognized for your… https://t.co/VrIl4pfltO https://t.co/3koIUT3Uok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. banks teach financial literacy with hands-on experience: Last year, Abbey Jones’ high school routine had a twist. For 45 minutes each week, she became one of 15 student tellers at the Community Spirit Bank branch at Red Bay High School in Red Bay,… https://t.co/A4KGlFxb0q https://t.co/dAlUlyXrlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Title Senior Software Engineer – .NET Summary We are looking for an innovative, passionate software engineer to join our development group. You will work in a collaborative, multi-functional team environment to design, develop,… https://t.co/ArxScRaT8f https://t.co/ClueIyBZhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Manager – Houston, Tx (29688): Requisition ID 29688 – Posted 05/24/2018 – Sales – United States – Texas – Permanent A WORLD LEADER IN TESTING, INSPECTION &amp; CERTIFICATION SERVICES Bureau Veritas offers dynamic, exciting employment opportunities… https://t.co/ux5RaQ0zC5 https://t.co/XeLuPLnvPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: This position works closely with the Project Managers and various Regional and Corporate staff. This is the first step towards management responsibilities. It is viewed as a junior Project Manager (PM) position within the organization… https://t.co/L9cL2kXaIQ https://t.co/vMei7caKiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Healthcare or Higher Education) Project Architect -RELOCATION: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted 08/09/2018 Title: Project Architect/ Senior Project Architect/ Associate Architect Compensation: Base, Bonus, Benefits, 401k, additional perks… https://t.co/ZAMzRwwslB https://t.co/jGmYzSWPhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA engineer: ******/QA engineer Ref No.: 18-32814 Location: Houston, TX, Texas JD: Strong QA Experience with 8+ Year of Leadership role. Experience with Agile and Other Methodology. Experience with Test Plan ,Test Strategy Experience with Automation Good… https://t.co/aX73oUd0lP https://t.co/cexyNPD0rO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, United States Posted By Total Safety Date Posted 34 minutes ago Expires 09 Sep 2018 Qualifications None IT Support Technician in Houston, TX, United States Houston, TX, United States… https://t.co/6fiV0dM85O https://t.co/5Hzw13BLSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Description Project Manager (WD***********) What you will do Under general supervision, responsible for the overall execution and performance of Electronic Life Safety (Fire Alarm, Security, Nurse Call systems) Construction or… https://t.co/5md848LqFE https://t.co/1ZZYmCQjpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Database-Developer: A major hospital in Houston needs an SQL Developer with healthcare industry experience to come aboard in a contract-to-perm engagement. Please llok at te description below for more detials: SQL Duties ? Write complex SQL Code,… https://t.co/VpRITlk4U6 https://t.co/glPDu5vVdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Research Analyst: Principal Research Analyst The Principle Research Analyst will be responsible for providing oil and gas industry expertise as well as team leadership on projects within the consulting side of the company. Focus will be on… https://t.co/pgguFnYLrc https://t.co/nerNW9suoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major Tesla shareholders trimmed stakes last quarter: filings: Two major Tesla Inc shareholders cut their stakes in the electric automaker during the second quarter, before Chief Executive Elon Musk announced he would try to take the company private… https://t.co/cm8R0hRssy https://t.co/00c0368aot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scheduler: Requisition ID 2018-27457 Work Location US-TX-Houston Department / Discipline Project Control Position Type Agency / Contract Overview / Responsibilities Wood is currently recruiting for a Project Planner/Controls Specialist with… https://t.co/StptLUxLHo https://t.co/HxZjqRZWk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer II: 117020BR Job Description: Raytheon Intelligence, Information &amp; Services Division (IIS) has opportunities for TSA IT Specialist. As a TSA IT Specialist you will perform a wide variety of task with respect to TSA computer hardware,… https://t.co/mKmu4r8tTF https://t.co/4Zc4XlNjo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kroger to sell private label products in China through Alibaba: Kroger Co has partnered with Alibaba Group Holding Ltd to sell its private label products on the e-commerce giant's Tmall platform in China, making its first venture outside the United States. https://t.co/bIS5pvDzFy https://t.co/oSQlcq0Zq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Sales Executive/Business Development: Sr Sales Executive/Business Development This role is to provide software demonstrations to potential customers, with the goal of selling our engineering software. The individual will be working closely with… https://t.co/vxL85zQI5P https://t.co/qpEF7etOjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Objects Visualization Developer: Functional Area:IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): No Travel Relocation Provided: No AIG Employee Services, Inc. AIG is looking for an experienced Business Intelligence Reporting… https://t.co/GZIQEOmoFw https://t.co/vbIF3ojzXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NIO seeks to raise $1.8 billion in biggest U.S. listing by China automaker: Chinese electric vehicle start-up NIO on Monday filed for a $1.8 billion initial public offering of its American depositary shares, the biggest U.S. listing by a Chinese automaker. https://t.co/lBTrxXeiBU https://t.co/MfbcVVECNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fault Management Engineer: 22-May-2018 Fault Management Engineer Space Colorado, Texas 434611BR B.S. or higher degree from an accredited college in Engineering or Computer Science or a related discipline  – Experience with requirements derivation,… https://t.co/VvVrTGs2zI https://t.co/GgibYdISUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filenet Developer: Filenet Developer Ref No.: 18-32929 Location: Houston, Texas Title:- Filenet Developer Location:- Houston TX Contract Role 1. Proficient knowledge in IBM FileNet CE API and BPM (Java Based) 2. Proficient knowledge in core java and J2EE… https://t.co/ygi7JhE2vD https://t.co/yGNOuLVfUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: Consultant ·  Understand identified client problems well ·  Structures an approach for own analysis with some assistance ·  Finds needed data from internal and external sources with limited guidance ·  Has good knowledge of basic analytic… https://t.co/FK601Am1fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP PRA Business Analyst: Chevron is one of the world’s leading energy companies, with approximately 60,000 employees working in countries around the world. We explore, produce and transport crude oil and natural gas; refine, market and distribute fuels… https://t.co/0X5EHSN3YU https://t.co/6Esl5RPcek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk talking to Saudi fund, others as he seeks Tesla buyout financing: Elon Musk on Monday explained what he meant by tweeting "funding secured" to take Tesla Inc private: he is confident a deal can be done but has not yet finalized a plan. https://t.co/3VxXAxBJIk https://t.co/bWzif53p9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping Tesla shares may not be an option for some big funds: Elon Musk wants to take Tesla Inc private, but some of his big investors may not be able to follow. https://t.co/OrLSIUwJiL https://t.co/RGg9A7VOQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Consultant: SAP ABAP Consultant Ref No.: 18-32455 Location: Houston, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s… https://t.co/jiCw4r2sOU https://t.co/XgQCT2ktmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Automation Engineer: Cloud Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-35141 Location: Houston, Texas Location: Houston, TX Requirements listed in order of importance: 1. Experience automating deployment of IIS applications (I.e. Windows platform). This means… https://t.co/4WROE2kaFQ https://t.co/FtZCrJCBSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer ================= Date: Aug 9, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start apply with Seek Help * * Apply Now… https://t.co/M8NmdlYBc8 https://t.co/lgjFxVKQBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer STAR-CCM Houston, TX: **Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Houston, TX** Locations:Houston, Texas Job Family: Engineering New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/GyLl5Rt02O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's slow disclosure raises governance, social media concerns: Tesla Inc’s handling of Chief Executive Elon Musk's proposal to take the carmaker private and its failure to promptly file a formal disclosure has raised governance concerns and sparked… https://t.co/0Dpt4BxArT https://t.co/mQvR1Hefgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer Microservices: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop, support and integrate software systems in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Systems capabilities include… https://t.co/d3q8mws2e8 https://t.co/4PLZeFCGTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Agile Coach Ref No.: 18-31757 Location: Houston, Texas Job Title: Agile Coach Location: Houston, TX Type: Full Time Position Overview: – 3+ years of experience coaching agile frameworks and various frameworks (i.e. Scrum, Kanban, XP, etc.) –… https://t.co/QZI1bqRAKD https://t.co/tiP2ZHOH5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Java Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/fUdwv5bxmo https://t.co/pdyM3FWLs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liquid Solution Architect: Job Description Liquid Solution Architect ABB is a leader in power and automation technologies that enable utility and industry customers to improve performance while lowering environmental impact. The ABB Group of companies… https://t.co/TWLIpFaVJq https://t.co/lDSAQiLqJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net lead: .Net lead Ref No.: 18-31583 Location: Houston, Texas Job Title Sr. DotNet Full Stack Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs) 6-10 Technical/Functional Skills Functional Good Communication and Interpersonal Skills Good analytical and… https://t.co/QtH5XYekQW https://t.co/zRQiystJzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timeline: Main events in Tesla's history as a public company: Here are some of the key events in Tesla Inc's turbulent history as a public company. https://t.co/nXudrAwumL https://t.co/sL5KbZjxLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End-Software-Developer: We are seeking an enthusiastic and experienced front end web developer to build our internal operations portal. Using best of breed technologies in the front end and public cloud, you will build a data-driven solution to… https://t.co/xTqjP59RvR https://t.co/UinHHViIVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Agile Coach Ref No.: 18-31757 Location: Houston, Texas Job Title: Agile Coach Location: Houston, TX Type: Full Time Position Overview: – 3+ years of experience coaching agile frameworks and various frameworks (i.e. Scrum, Kanban, XP, etc.) –… https://t.co/EU5F2l7eO8 https://t.co/HhyikgSHZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: We are seeking a Data Feeds Business Analyst to join our expanding Commercial Technology teams in Houston, TX. This is a client-facing Business Analyst role responsible for working with customers and partners to define… https://t.co/8xcqRxboqg https://t.co/gR5VEKFdVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Security Lead Regional Solutions Architect: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Leading Solutions Provider partnered with Cisco, EMC, VMware, NetApp and Citrix is in rapid growth mode and is currently looking for a CCIE level… https://t.co/iu7Wnk5XRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Developer: Market Developer – Career fields – Commercial and business – Engineering – Finance, accounting and tax – Geoscience – Human Resources – Information Technology – Law – Operations – Project Management – Research and technology – Safety,… https://t.co/4McbzTazoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple says it is monitoring Infowars app for content violations: Apple Inc said on Wednesday that an app belonging to popular conspiracy theorist Alex Jones remains in the company's mobile App Store because it has not been found to be in violation of any… https://t.co/ULbiOOv64K https://t.co/fQ3gGm1aUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commodity Pricing Business Analyst: Description : This position supports Calpine’s Retail Platform’s Supply Team. This position is primarily responsible for supporting and updating the pricing, contracting, and deal-close software, including updating key… https://t.co/L5Z07d6lrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asset Project Manager: Job Description – Manage and establish a governance process to ensure the supply partner fully delivers the asset management plan to the agreed timeframe – Represent Property Operations – Lead the operational requirements for the… https://t.co/vvWGHcopiQ https://t.co/holALaZiRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer (Full Stack): SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER (FULL STACK) HIGHLIGHTS LOCATIONS: Houston, Texas JOB TYPE: Contract-to-hire or direct hire SALARY: BOE JOB SUMMARY GTN is seeking a Sr. Full-Stack Software Engineer to join our fast growing… https://t.co/W8o9NYWeVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/NNQ9qrK2ZI https://t.co/hl65jp7rbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer STAR-CCM Houston, TX: **Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Houston, TX** Locations:Houston, Texas Job Family: Engineering New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/47fYxau3Ls https://t.co/Fh7uyIEuq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tesla buyout would reengineer take-private deals: Billionaire investor Elon Musk has always done things his own way, from designing space rockets to manufacturing electric cars. Now the Tesla Inc CEO is looking to reengineer how a company can… https://t.co/NJPgqMjAzc https://t.co/pbOc1U9nkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German start-up trials solar car that can charge as you drive: (The Aug. 7 story corrects to show Sion cannot be charged from other electric cars, removes reference to production taking place at German plants and corrects number of orders to over 6,500) https://t.co/XCkZ9zFt8P https://t.co/jU9Z5oZUDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer Ref No.: 18-31848 Location: Houston, Texas Network Engineer Houston, TX 12 Months W2 contract Job Description: 4 years of experience required. Expertise in Network and Wireless technologies Good Knowledge of Network… https://t.co/jv7f5WgSw4 https://t.co/VateM0H9It]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Objects Visualization Developer: Functional Area:IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): No Travel Relocation Provided: No AIG Employee Services, Inc. AIG is looking for an experienced Business Intelligence Reporting… https://t.co/PnqJbtq3oP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/52bjXf5l4h https://t.co/yN02ltK99B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Water / Wastewater: The AECOM Houston office, Water and Wastewater Group, is seeking a Project Manager responsible for the planning, design and construction phases of public works projects in central Texas. The ideal candidate for this… https://t.co/geEPorAlQd https://t.co/w9xUBJAczb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Our client is located in the Heights area and currently has an opening for a full-time mid-level application developer to participate in the design, development implementation of new features to several existing internal software… https://t.co/gXGZVkUcig https://t.co/Vxzoivp7JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Engineer: SnapStream Media – Jobs: Software Quality Assurance Engineer – online All jobs Software Quality Assurance Engineer Software Quality Assurance Engineer Houston, Texas, United States Engineering Description Do you find… https://t.co/a6EB5QFtAe https://t.co/OwYYVtvKsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Process Specialist II – Houston, TX: Job Description CEVA Logistics, one of the world’s leading non-asset based supply-chain management companies, designs and implements industry leading solutions for large and medium-size national and… https://t.co/ejQsH9qHaj https://t.co/mKaN08PnCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary SharePoint Developer at NASA: MEI Technologies: Open Positions MEI Technologies Employee Sign-In (eMIS) Account Self Service Portal Facility &amp; Weather Status – Home – About Us – Capabilities &amp; Services – Newsroom – Careers – Contact – Events –… https://t.co/VOCCGUL3bJ https://t.co/t6XUx3GjO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Land GIS Analyst: Land GIS Analyst ================ Date: Jul 6, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start apply with Seek Help * * Now Help * Start* Please… https://t.co/NAcNu9YUMV https://t.co/n5ddt56QSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Developer: Market Developer – Career fields – Commercial and business – Engineering – Finance, accounting and tax – Geoscience – Human Resources – Information Technology – Law – Operations – Project Management – Research and technology – Safety,… https://t.co/7vASuQlIay https://t.co/uda404Btil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple iPhones get bigger and pricier, Watch turns to health: Apple Inc introduced its largest-ever iPhone and a watch that detects heart problems on Wednesday in an attempt to get customers to upgrade to more expensive devices in the face of stagnant… https://t.co/GNzt8nTqLB https://t.co/DFYYC4CqGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG Display struggles for footing after LCD forecasting error leads to crisis: The chief executive of South Korea's LG Display , Han Sang-beom, was determined to deliver a strong message when he appeared before 1,000 employees at the firm's main… https://t.co/PYvy1hxFkA https://t.co/byNYpaIsmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Senior Manager, Global Indirect Procurement, Legal, &amp; Internal Audit: Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCollege InternCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceHuman ResourcesInformation… https://t.co/TOqDV0GuWa https://t.co/eN8FpMSXkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Estimator Project Manager: Civil Estimator &amp; Project Manager – Houston, TX in Houston, TX at BO-MAC CONTRACTORS LTD. – Careers Home – Benefits – About Heico – Internships – Featured Careers – Professional Services – Engineering – Manufacturing –… https://t.co/JOb1CgPypF https://t.co/rjgYVY7yLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renesas in $6.7 billion deal for IDT to boost chips for self-driving cars: Japan's Renesas Electronics Corp said it had agreed to buy Integrated Device Technology Inc (IDT) for $6.7 billion, its second major acquisition as it deepens its push into… https://t.co/qMfnMK76Gx https://t.co/Iu8Mjo8JP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Consultant: Day to Day job Duties: (what this person will do on a daily/weekly basis) The resource would be working in SAP Netweaver 7.4/7.5 EHP3 Envirnment and may be involved with Implementing Standard Fiori Apps, Creating Custom UI5 Apps… https://t.co/Q3tHG0xCLM https://t.co/8bBzBgFDUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major Account Executive – South Texas: The Opportunity:  We are looking for a top flight Major Account Executive with extensive IT infrastructure sales experience and burning desire to win. You will be responsible for winning new customers and expanding… https://t.co/FLv0DEE0nQ https://t.co/DPX7w8TtW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular Architect: Houston, TX Full-time $80k – $120k Posted 08/23/2018 If you are a Angular Architect with experience, please read on! Location: Houston, TX Top Reasons to Work with Us – Excellent benefits – Cutting edge technologies – Room for growth… https://t.co/gd4oBGjWxS https://t.co/OqtUvJceLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEM Developer: AEM Developer Ref No.: 18-38131 Location: Houston, Texas AEM Sr. Developer / Lead This team member will be tasked to deployingAdobe Experience Manager (AEM) to power all of our product brand experiences. This individual will develop… https://t.co/3QnO9RFwP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Cisco Solutions Architect: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted 09/05/2018 A leading technology Solutions Provider and Cisco VAR is seeking an experienced and motivated Senior Network Solutions Architects/ Pre Sales Engineers with… https://t.co/otTOC5OSwI https://t.co/TE42IxloQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Job TitleSenior Solutions Architect – ID:32495 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsMinimum 7 years related experience in designing technology solutions for mid-market organizations and higher preferably in an IT… https://t.co/DhBXpLjSIw https://t.co/HebEQmKKmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Estimator Project Manager – Houston, TX: Incorporated in Texas in 1966, Bo-Mac originally focused on providing civil, pipeline and other construction services for the petroleum exploration industry. In 1974, pile driving capability was added and… https://t.co/uuO6t7adOE https://t.co/wZ0C0JDEm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY The purpose of this position is to lead individual, multi-disciplined K-12 project solutions for clients, with direct accountability for project delivery. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES Manages… https://t.co/xEsSfnNZjS https://t.co/hytFijZmtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Job TitleSenior Solutions Architect – ID:32495 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsMinimum 7 years related experience in designing technology solutions for mid-market organizations and higher preferably in an IT… https://t.co/VsJFHswwbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Solutions Architect: Job TitleSr. Solutions Architect – ID:32495 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsMinimum 7 years related experience in designing technology solutions for mid-market organizations and higher preferably in an IT consulting… https://t.co/S1xRYPM6kg https://t.co/FtKt55VznV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator – Houston, TX: Sr. Software Engineer – NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator – Houston, TX Tracking Code ******* Job Description At Micro Focus, everything we do is based on a simple… https://t.co/rb95JzsY4V https://t.co/fF38SEhM2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager External-TX: **Project Manager External-TX** Locations:Houston, Texas Job Family: Project Management New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Process Industries and Drives **Business Unit:** Process Automation… https://t.co/gv6qrG7nQ3 https://t.co/OCb5b1Ho5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Developer: Required: Experience of setting up applications in Microsoft Active Directory Federation Service , any version is fine. Troubleshooting SAML and OAuth protocols Powershell scripting is a must. Active Directory knowledge… https://t.co/WoOJJB1mSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Web Developer: Job ID 2018-9481 Overview Aegion Corporation is looking for a Sr. Web Developer – Asset Integrity Management Aegion combines innovative technologies with market-leading expertise to maintain, rehabilitate and strengthen infrastructure… https://t.co/77MH27khcx https://t.co/EFTtsWJbJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hydrocarbon Resins Market Developer: Hydrocarbon Resins Market Developer =================================== Location: Houston, TX, US Company: ExxonMobil [IMAGE] Job Role Summary The Hydrocarbon Resins Market Developer leads and progresses products and… https://t.co/hu4W3NCZh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: 08-Aug-2018 to 07-Oct-2018 (CST) Stratas Advisors – Analysts Houston, TX, USA Full Time POSITION DESCRIPTION: Hart Energy Publishing LLC is seeking candidates with a Master’s degree in Petroleum Engineering, Operations Research Analyst or… https://t.co/ncxvphMc62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[developer: developer Ref No.: 18-39071 Location: houston, Texas Key skills required for the job are: – Elastic Search-L3 (Mandatory) As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of analysts, developers, testers or engineers and drive delivery… https://t.co/827JBUDKYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Administrator-Advisory Consultant: ServiceNow Administrator-Advisory Consultant at Dell Careers Skip to main content – Life at Dell – How We Work and Lead – Who We Are – How We Hire – FAQs – Working at Dell – Why Work Here – Diversity &amp;… https://t.co/Mb5cQaips9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP MM Consultant – S/4HANA – Houston, Texas – 6 months: SAP MM CONSULTANT – S/4HANA – HOUSTON, TEXAS – 6 MONTHS Our global client is looking for a SAP MM Consultant to be based in Houston for a long term project. SAP MM Consultant Location: HOUSTON,… https://t.co/rx6qItM89T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon to open checkout-free store in New York: https://t.co/ljXqBSqXgj Inc said on Friday it plans to open its checkout-free 'Amazon Go' grocery store in New York, expanding beyond Seattle where it is headquartered. https://t.co/ur1LExRl6m https://t.co/pcy88QVNkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solution Architect – REMOTE: Job Title Senior Solution Architect – REMOTE State Texas Description The Senior Solutions Architect (SA) effectively penetrates and drives solutions within targeted accounts and expands penetration in existing… https://t.co/Lrnj0WIOnv https://t.co/V2K8fL3urL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Service Specialist (Software Electric Controls): AutoReqId 60853BR Title for Posting Field Service Specialist (Software Electric Controls) PSA/Division DRILLING SYSTEM Division Drilling Systems Job Discipline Operations PTEs, Engineers &amp;… https://t.co/K35YL9LELG https://t.co/WW4Pn0dklY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla rocked by latest executive shakeup, Musk's behavior on webcast: Tesla Inc's shares dropped the most in two years on Friday, rocked by the departure of its accounting chief after just a month and mounting investor concerns about Chief Executive Elon… https://t.co/k7U2iGJ2Pm https://t.co/Qtx8Okauvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer Student Intern: For Siemens Application Support Engineer Student Intern (SSE, KZ) job – Internal Services – Houston, Texas Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard –… https://t.co/MAQYxSNJAY https://t.co/mSSzUAjgpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Structural Technical Support Engineer: Structural Technical Support Engineer Close This website uses cookies to improve user experience. By using our website you consent to all cookies in accordance with our Cookie Policy. Read More Accept – Careers Home… https://t.co/lco9wCExf9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>