<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Let me know if Wyden has found Iraq on the map yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefanMolyneux Innuendos and headline fodder passed as questions.  These hearings are such a joke.  Same questions phrased slightly different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't already subscribe to him on YouTube, do yourself a favour https://t.co/Oh1suIN9ND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewStoeten: Some background probably worth a read here on Draft Day is how I grappled with the Jays selections a year ago... https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deir_in_DC Flat earth believers are funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about flat galaxy? #FlatEarth https://t.co/uPQt3ZboEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djboptics Screw flat earth..we are living in a flat galaxy https://t.co/E6rjg5Ikin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Don't like Trump, but this isn't right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RPGpowaaaa @NatachaDKemp @iamAtheistGirl In that train of thought, didn't God provide the Earth with 4-5 massive extinction events?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild I'd buy you a pint if I could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild update tonight or tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_SaintsBuilds any updates for working add ons?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @everythingbbird: Why Mariner fans need not worry about all these Canadians https://t.co/vOB3bV5BPo #BlueJays  #Mariners https://t.co/Ej…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewartmcdowall  https://t.co/nmO3OE14KN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamAtheistGirl  https://t.co/9sewlO4WJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddow Mid evil....Merica fuck yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1stTryScience Looking forward to the flat universe posts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDeplrbleMBA @CNN @BillWeirCNN It's the same of the right when there is a democrat in office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JB_Dawgfan @Mikeggibbs Just people who have moved to Vancouver from Southern Ontario ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @BillWeirCNN Reunite is bad for MSM business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Basically he suggested staying off Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulianAssange: Comey's a lousy leaker:
1. No leak that Trump wasn't under investigation or Lynch
2. No leak of memo FULL TEXT
3. Delaye…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DunkNastyFLEX @CNN 50s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN How about we all cut the left vs right bs..rise up against all politicians who continually screw us regardless of political affiliation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN So basically Ryan is saying he needs to get better at lying and hiding everything from the public, like the rest of congress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild crappy..wookie wizard seems to be done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderDan75 @CNN It would be nice if we could stop with the left vs right bs and hold all politicians accountable..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_ARamsey @CNN Tweet of the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN  https://t.co/ADkOfMvXYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Larpenstein @CNN I don't get it.  You can't be against Trump and against corruption on the left?  It has to be one or the other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Larpenstein @CNN Well if the original post was about Trump golfing then yes, I would have ripped him...but it was about Pelosi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Hey Pelosi, still using US aircraft for your families personal vacations that cost taxpayers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleallen1 @RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump I wonder if it was literal?...(cough) Seth Rich (cough)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleallen1 @RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump 3.  But like he said, it wasn't a hill worth dying on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleallen1 @RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump 2...softer language which her campaign echoed moving forward when ever the subject came up.  That painted her in a more favourable light]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleallen1 @RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump Comey politicized the FBI when he took direction by Lynch to soften the language of the investigation into Clinton....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beavon11 @RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump I know,  but he definitely plays like one on tv ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBlumenthal After taking office how long do you think it would have taken Hillary to fire Comey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @democracynow: Constitutional rights lawyer @ShayanaKadidal says to assume James Comey's memo is protected by executive privilege is "ri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderDan75 @CNN Wake up.  It doesn't matter who is in office.  Doesn't matter which party.  It's the same people pulling their strings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @FaithandFreedom  https://t.co/yN3ubCo6dU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Ask him about the chemical weapons attack recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Meanwhile the US is using a chemical weapon...
https://t.co/NSZjqtV68u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NSZjqtV68u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @palestininianpr: Can we stop pretending: 1. The US doesn't use chemical weapons and 2. US bombs don't kill civilians in the ME https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderDan75 @CNN MSM goes on and on about Russia and the elextion.  How about the other countries who tried to interfere...look up Ukraine :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderDan75 @CNN He not her ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderDan75 @CNN I bet her doesn't last the year, but it won't be from the fake narrative the left media has been pushing since day one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN There is so much stink from this past year.  DNC conspiring to keep Bernie from the Nomination, basically Trump in general..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN I don't care what anyone else used.. that isn't the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN ..hence politicizing the FBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN I never implied it obstructed the investigation..though it definitely benefited the campaign as they used that specific language onward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN Describe the reaction if Sessions had been the one to order Comey to soften the language for a Trump investigation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmsERRN @vidalexperience @Larpenstein @CNN That politicized the FBI when he took direction from Lynch to soften the language to "matter" that helped the Clinton campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild By chance do you know what number this build is?  300+ builds to scroll through :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RJSzczerba @realDonaldTrump Why can't both be liars?  We're talking about politicians here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Doubtful... trades please. Get ahead of the retool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @caperguy33  https://t.co/0x8oLiBj8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Trying to bait Trump into tweeting..like he did to Comey lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kelownascott: And if Hillary and DNC hadnt cheated America
Bernie might be POTUS https://t.co/B2jl9peSnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN And while everyone was distracted....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN So, corruption on the left, corruption on the right. Intelligence community with leaks everywhere.  Business as usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN He was baited by a tweet to leak info to the press.  Hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WLD01 Why can't we question both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN "I can't answer that in a public setting"...leaked a few hours later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question the MSM BS narrative and I'm a Trumpbot. Question the validity of Trump's sanity and I'm a libtard. How many of us do both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBowenWilliams @adamgoldmanNYT @GenePark @nytimes I've read...but keep drinking the kool aid bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieT123 @CNN Let me be clear, I'm no Trump supporter.   It's just I can't stand this utter BS spewed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieT123 @CNN Directed him to call a criminal investigation (because that what the FBI investigates) a "matter", which her campaign later referred back to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieT123 @CNN  https://t.co/DUbTdl8SNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onesarahjones @iamAtheistGirl People are so conditioned to this Left vs Right BS they don't realize both sides are bought and paid for by the same evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxBusiness @mediamonarchy Politicians bought and paid for.. democracy is such a shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Both.  The thing with politics is NOBODY tells the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jill_woodie @KeithOlbermann He'll do something sooner or later to warrant it, but this Russian narrative is bogus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @strombo No doubt there is collusion, it's just the evidence part we're all waiting for I guess lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ @ReviewTheEarth Funny how this gets passed over https://t.co/894wJtwvjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sailingflyingd: @MarkDice Here is John McCain's point that I summarized for him bc he was unable to articulate it https://t.co/AZrbCMw5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamgoldmanNYT @GenePark @nytimes What is clear is that you in the media do not care about getting it right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild Ok.  Thanks.  Tried other builds but I like this one the best.  Just trying to get through this week you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyleruggles @CNN Not making excuses, but these scum bags felt this way long before Trump was around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Yet CNN probably won't touch this https://t.co/n90f8gYgUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawneheath55 @CNN  https://t.co/6VAPojbOtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkLacedPoppy @CNN They won't touch the story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Comey Testifies ‘No Doubt’ Russia Hacked Elections, Admits He NEVER Saw Evidence.  Hmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sean_spicier @ReviewTheEarth https://t.co/894wJtwvjC how about other countries involved with the election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DoctorSekzi: @Flkittie @RealVinnieJames @OriginalFiboman Democraric Party is in chaos. Keep reminding Bernie supporters that the DNC to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Deir_in_DC: It was. And even more interestingly, Chalupa, who reported the "DNC hack", was behind the story! https://t.co/ss5PcoIyUy ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN  https://t.co/G3yhsrNL3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawneheath55 @CNN https://t.co/Jrp58uSLPe enjoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawneheath55 @CNN They had an investigation, was told to call it a matter instead, which he went along with even though it wasn't true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawneheath55 @CNN "We had an investigation open at the time. So that gave me a queasy feeling," Comey says on AG Lynch asking to call email probe a "matter"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN "We had an investigation open at the time. So that gave me a queasy feeling," Comey says on AG Lynch asking to call email probe a "matter"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxBlumenthal: FBI reviewed Flynn's call with Russian ambassador and found nothing illicit: https://t.co/NC0qd29TVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN "We had an investigation open at the time. So that gave me a queasy feeling," Comey says on AG Lynch asking to call email probe a "matter"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deir_in_DC You forgot the feelings of Comey and the innuendoes masked as questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deir_in_DC Amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mark4124NH: @jaketapper What is clear is that you in the media do not care about getting it right, you and NYT https://t.co/UI6aaT5zNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenCarpenter06 @Jason_toronto @CNN https://t.co/1soKfnhc9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN I guess he was the cheapest to payoff]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>