<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. - Marcia Wieder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/PhzaIR5CaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/37r8HPeBDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/bghgpfAPnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/O9SdFfa5Xj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/y4WR2wgCyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/YNKEDrq3kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/tGQcWxWQz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/uvG5Ywl3wG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/AmoOvKGG4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/O7OWcTxjcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/5LTnGTCcdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/Xzz5wrCQSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/MpNCgbyO6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/JDmVCChzpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/9VGXDnlMg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/wioIRe1qP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/urzluOBTcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/CS4Jftp9QE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/DDZD7Zihh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/Zeozw2Dl7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/FeyA3nV4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/dmOp63vuSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/JhjbF1kOf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/fDDrBVqQIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/GpVPbNGERE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/5AUcuYC3li]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/bKh4ddTxUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/2HuXKl4jDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/77VLT23p0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/hskXXJYpP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/KK06AqTr2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/gjUgT7r6Ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/lQwetq00n6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/GlRjTxTTWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/PlEG5HhYD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/6CSmvt5N2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/lLqOGukEt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/KV9oS1pGO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/Okg3jPXkOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/btRVd5z2GL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/EABtYGU9bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/zQ3rQ9j3Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/6QJ8L83WeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/JE50ERlDLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/p5f1eW4Ryp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/R4vpPVpa9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/y4wfwTCJix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/bng6IvHj4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/Zeozw2Dl7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/PjMu8tDCC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/Typ8q5ogug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/WmtikEbPXm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>