<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/RBXszgKsF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/uxt5kGujvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/liuFUhllsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/BrVSh17xRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/uLlqxhCTIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/Fu8b4PWsqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/qXSP09NJnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/u4IvACsGKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/kBTNEiZmby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/LE0v21PB0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/DRNn4K4T3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also learned that I love making money. Anyone who is not afraid of work will be happy with the money they make.  Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/lYTgzSqbir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/hIqMyDSl6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/GUAttUalwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/wCk9iflMxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/5zbV0Mq2jQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/wnoFmNZbQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Xp4G9ScOxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/Njxff1kOkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/9l3pKotqiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/5fYdwGdGt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/ROp8qxJ61W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/O94WeVFa0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/yCySJQmfdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/RH6QYQY3XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/cW03lRtVx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/0i0ExsMdRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/bKMRT7iAyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/KGoq0YQLNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/fHEZ4navQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of America  http://t.co/f5SDQTbqaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/Ry61BoXz5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/WJVXRyfUTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/iedPo6m1wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/KYFFQ2Dkq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/GTpth9adI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/KKXig66f2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/dPJ9wJ31xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/Nqtgrxk8xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/KS4AjLFRvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/NYemuuGsLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/aIx54ZWPWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/MmlAf6hwI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/BrVSh17xRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/AqssIkO4lK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/hzfk3TOfbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/gYElCbqb3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/LRz5JCJI1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/JepCWU4Kti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/TQGlhtYz6p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>