<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing up in Colorado I was addicted to Sergio, and Tom Jobin and all things Brazil. And one day I was truly... http://t.co/8uo02MrUnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letting go is an act of profound courage, just ask the few who have tried it. http://t.co/GlytRTnP1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/bFmjWLIrL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Os brasileiros parecem muito mais alegre.

The Brazilians seem so much more joyful -  

From designer Stefan... http://t.co/JloNyPl6QY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Five-day storm finally broke last night. http://t.co/FLTMFiP9OQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/stC4ep46Kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/67kX5XaktK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chill and alluring video with real nymphs on skates. http://t.co/xEdSYDsWJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An aching heart on a long lonesome road http://t.co/IpQn5bz896]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic desert highway cool. http://t.co/h97yaPk745]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young school girl or Spider Woman? http://t.co/yj8L0w06qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got rid of those nagging e-mails in a few clicks, quick &amp; easy. http://t.co/4nZLvStsJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needs something to read in the pity pot? http://t.co/4Kj6w1Qm0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/i11DQwWNJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez Miret, tell me all about your life in a tweet! Put your lovely face on here. Would be nice to see you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took up running again as well swimming. The mermaids like to frolic here. http://t.co/JWLJLwWnHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/9GS2eCkg8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmanamarie Hi A. Did you send me a tweet? Seems so.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmanamarie A. Where is your beautiful face? Nice to see your name in my e-mail after such a long while. Hi sweetie! Tell me news. M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly awesome gal trio! http://t.co/f35HdIaVhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Layton: The Man Who Could Have Saved Canada From Its Present Misery http://t.co/THBDFaPDo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sight of Christo on the Corcovado takes my breath away. http://t.co/ElCFEhaNkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platinum4orce very cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why wealthy politicians are clueless about the honor of risk. http://t.co/55Z9wnpoBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty buildings flourish and their foreign owners pay no property taxes. http://t.co/LG7DwSJeUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despair brought my ancestors to America and they got a helping hand. http://t.co/mhSRN1vAX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/vZKuQRkdiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/FtDX6EHVwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two greats at their prime. http://t.co/fezxL6hOpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new way to get to space. http://t.co/z0u3cVlVtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/NRYLvIXJzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hVw5yuO5JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Harper is still at large and dangerous. http://t.co/6cChjAOjTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Either Harper Is Psychotic Or He Was In On It http://t.co/Gwm4sbmOkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/6lJ5ekrkYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool! http://t.co/7Zkd1dzUtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buddhist Extremist Cell Vows To Unleash Tranquility On West http://t.co/ILkvQflv2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Ew10vBVKM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/MWCtAUgfku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Taylor introduces a choir from Charleston, S.C., proving love conquers all. http://t.co/iOHcosIg5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/U3GhxpfJhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Muslim woman taking on the prophet and 1.3 billion Muslims to free women from a lie. Amazing. http://t.co/GN7MwUyMXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old media, old ideas being buried by the New media savvy Left. http://t.co/Rzx9L1Lr5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/DVxIYpAhyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone close to me suggested my strange sketches from life drawing class look like the artist Magdalenian. Well... http://t.co/fyuwbj9PaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear that Delma Godoy, a fabulous sculptor and plastic artist from Rio, is getting back to the studio. We... http://t.co/o1oej3kzDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/oaukbHwykQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/pV4codydQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/b11C7dHF7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students merge a loom with a digital system from scratch.
. http://t.co/SaicvX9oiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/1LxkVZreJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Vwhni4Ip2q http://t.co/lG2ZT1jGZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/OtrycDh2N6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Colorado in Boulder, where I graduated from, is beautiful, nestled in the fall colors of the Rockies. http://t.co/bxeUXeuzmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't this what we humans were meant to do!? Yea, cool. https://t.co/XAwwxNRtFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZAs3hzDtHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely Gal Costa singing from the past in Rio. http://t.co/315R5KZguN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trevor Noah passed the test and Jon Stewart passed the torch http://t.co/yUPABHBI7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic http://t.co/f8QBfHyJjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skyline http://t.co/UnAUMN3yJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/vifOdHtWn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your family toxic at Thanksgiving? A good reminder to practice your assertiveness this holiday. http://t.co/rzZpM5MA6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/sFSRHmRaJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/CyPQVrK7H1 http://t.co/3eQTYeLt3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis Lays Hands On Ailing U.S. Infrastructure http://t.co/AQKokOrKIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis Lays Hands On Ailing U.S. Infrastructure http://t.co/Wv3VaTubJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He doesn't wait for permission. http://t.co/66sUYdYuDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's #1 funnyman cuts down a tree with the leader of the Green Party, whom PM Harper won't let into the... http://t.co/e78rq8jWWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's young people didn't show up in the last election and we got Harper...again. http://t.co/drfouwlyzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His holiness visits mental lepers on his tour of the halt,lame and the blind http://t.co/bU9gtrIXYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiriouslySusan Susan, You must have a voice that comes with a warning label - and I 'd like to hear it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Amen!"  The Christian god is back on the bench. http://t.co/U8xh987A3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had the privilege on occasion to be an aide to Mr. Chretien, who writes to warn Canadians how Harper is taking... http://t.co/7y6odcXaf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My yoga teacher from the Netherlands sends this gift to me, always timely, from one of my favorite singers, Tina... http://t.co/AfUSdz9Ebe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Carlos. http://t.co/qJO79R7z3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live like life was a road. http://t.co/Xz3zljmfG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty Queen Walks Out In Nursing Scrubs—Then Looks Up And STUNS Everyone http://t.co/IQyW548lb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are few if any condor left in California because of hunters. Nice to see one released into the wilds of... http://t.co/6ZiSjZDCF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Davis living proof why southern Christians inbreeding should be a  criminal offense. Does anybody else hear... http://t.co/rg7Ad1iLIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephLIngram @GaleStanley pitch me a funny movie on wob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Joss Whedon Endorses Mitt Romney https://t.co/drE9h4OU61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to dust off this campaign add for this next batch of GOP zombies. https://t.co/g1W99Jzq42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gal playing for change brings back ...Janice...tell me if I'm wrong. https://t.co/ckzKNvSFgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you can't stop yourself from imagining why you do what you do.

https://t.co/blsbrFvxrn https://t.co/IJX5r4FGu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vrttJ2LfHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't never stop doing what I do and here's why... https://t.co/NJ8mZ9KuYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dance riot broke out https://t.co/ERnQRvZLM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurrayNewlands I was a columnist for a start-up business newspaper in S.F. in the 80s during Reganomics. The town seems to have grown up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diário do Rio on Instagram: “Quem é do mar não enjoa! Bons sonhos #cidademaravilhosa Click show... https://t.co/HKLRF1oP5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fall putting on a show and most people...miss it. https://t.co/c9BDOJ9u8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iceland just did what the US won’t-- 26 top bankers sent to prison for role in financial crisis https://t.co/7xVdFadsVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tearful Stephen Harper boards spaceship for return to home planet - The Beaverton - North... https://t.co/y9QQG8e2uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shared dorm restaurant the hottest place to eat - and it's successful https://t.co/pFibRFvxuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialLore Interesting and timely work in today's world. I most write about love and beauty  in a world of contrast. Nice to meet you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2qxEgDnKmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fall on my street https://t.co/2JLNcvwoc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UxrKhcdSU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found myself getting emotional seeing Justin Trudeau address all Canadians after a decade in obscurity building... https://t.co/j4coNK1W1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa  write me @ michael.shandrick@gmail.com we can sort out our schedules. how is that?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>