<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeWantBornToDieTour @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say that the world was built for two, only worth living if somebody is loving you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want you like I never wanted anyone, you give it to me fast like free and fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always fall for the wrong guy, things that are bad always taste nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if BTD: The Paradise Edition by Lana Del Rey will be one of your #Top10FavoriteAlbums — http://t.co/vHsE9377]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if Born To Die by Lana Del Rey is one of your #Top10FavouriteAlbums — http://t.co/Q7Ch8d6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't that hard boy to like you or love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't leave me now, don't say good bye, don't turn around, leave me high and dry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Days until The Paradise Edition! So excited! http://t.co/Q4uHVo8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey #TeamLana love you! Lana Del Rey Is Our American Dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey Is Our American Dream. http://t.co/OuIEO53A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey Is Our American Dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You tell me how I need to be, that ain't up to anybody else but me, I don't care what you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/q0veoyyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're forever young in paradise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: Ugly photo of Lana Del Rey! http://t.co/LArW0JaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GO FOLLOW → @LanaSingapore !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You fit me better than my favorite sweater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: I love you! Lana: ... Me: ... Lana: ... Me: ... Lana: ... Me: Its okay, take your time :) — Mum: Stop talking to your posters!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you say makes me want to stay, but everything you've done makes me wanna run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jAEqUY1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving you isn’t right, it’s original sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite Lana Del Rey's quote. — https://t.co/h5i3nvgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey Tour 2013: Europe tour dates. http://t.co/kf5zetf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelReyINDO Iya min! Semoga Lana bisa ke Indonesia :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought that I could change you like the others, but I don't know how.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel so alone on a Friday night. Can you make it feel like home, if I tell you you're mine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Min, ada kemungkinan gak ya kalau Lana Del Rey bakalan ke Indonesia? cc: @LanaDReyINDO @LanaDelReyINDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MDNA_Monster: @LanaQuote #TeamLanaProblem You live in Europe but Lana isn't touring your country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamLanaProblem You don't live in Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know, when you really love an artist, I think it's better to admire them from a distance." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's a fire for every experience &amp; an obsession of freedom that terrified me to the point where I couldn’t talk about it." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-Order Born To Die: The Paradise Edition Album — http://t.co/GEsupDYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana and Jaime. http://t.co/EKqhQm1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open up a beer and you say get over here, and play a Video Game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When God created Lana Del Rey... http://t.co/ERapvlFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my wildest dreams I never knew, I’d find somebody like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 days! Are you ready #TeamLana? http://t.co/sPVDlWNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think Lana Del Rey is Flawless #LanaVersace http://t.co/1TpiltoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even if you're the best singer in the world, there's a good chance no one will ever hear you." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be that fantasy that you got on your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm like a child belong to nobody, so I wear you like my clothes. Hold you close to my body, because you hurt so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gramma said that somewhere out there there's a good man, waiting for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey South East Asia Tour dates please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would say my music is film-made, really visual and reflective." —LDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Lanaween! http://t.co/dnERSdGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one compares to you, but there's no you, except in my dreams tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were just teenagers when we fell in love. Driving in your fast car, looking at the star above.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Lolita hey! http://t.co/5dbmzHtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to have a life where there’s just one man in it, and I haven’t found that." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got the medicine I need. Fame, liquor, love. Give it to me slowly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of life, wasn't meant for the good girl. Try as I might, in the end it's a cruel world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 WEEKS !! http://t.co/vgnIODms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm interested in the gorgeous side of life, but also familiar with the dark side too." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be young. Be dope. Be proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love me hardcore, then don't walk away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CantWaitParadiseEdition Please come fast November. We're waiting you. Sincerely, All Team Lana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ReplaceLanaSongsWithPotato Potato Anthem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got the ice, you've got the fire. I've got the stuff to take you higher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for Lana Del Rey &amp; Fav for Lady Gaga http://t.co/BDRaWBZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my friends tell me I should move on. I'm lying in the ocean, singing your song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our kind of love, it was once in a lifetime. It couldn't last, it was doomed from the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the land of gods and monsters, I was angel looking to get fucked hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have right to live your life. Like no one else does, like no one else might.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You do things so fast, you end up having so many different lifestyles all in one short time when you're teen." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Interscope: PREMIERE: @LanaDelRey - #Ride (@MJCole Remix) via @EarmilkDotCom 

http://t.co/qt8qAqGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You so fresh to death and sick as cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't know what you've done to me. You're heavier than heavenly. Life on the run has set me free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Die young is just an inspiration to live everyday like it was my last day, even if I keep going." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey: "Team Lana, I tell you all the time..." http://t.co/B3ImEKY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I write about what I know and I try and find the most beautiful melodies I can." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he's bad he's bad, but when he's good no one's better. Cause we're a match made in heaven and this kind of love's forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you judge me, I will kill you!" —Lana on haters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 days until... http://t.co/oaDExKmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don’t always go on Tumblr but sometimes I do because the people on there are really funny."  —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey will be writing soundtracks for two movies out early next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And I will show that nothing can happen more beautiful than death." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I retell my life stories in the form of stories." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read and Retweet! http://t.co/BGUz8eJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Taking time for your art is taking time for yourself." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honesty and being a good person." — Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see why Lana Del Rey haters talk to me, you're never going to change my opinion on Lana. You're so irrelevant and annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He doesn't mind I have a flat broke down life. In fact, he says he thinks it's why he might like about me, admires me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of feeling like I'm fucking crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paradise. Edition. 19. Days. http://t.co/vG0H3fj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Big Sleep is Lana Del Rey's favorite old movie. #DelReyFact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel at home wherever I lay my head, I'm in a different place every day but I love being with my boyfriend." —Lana Del Rey ( @ELLEUK )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important thing is tone and quality of a voice. Writing is my passion, but melodies are what you notice first." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Me and the band always say a prayer before we go on stage. Other than that anything goes." —Lana Del Rey ( @ELLEUK )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love Lauren Bacall. I'm also inspired by Natasja Kinski and Natalie Wood." —Lana Del Rey (@ELLEUK )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God has saved me a million times, so I think He must've enjoyed my song." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ELLEUK: @LanaDelRey will be answering questions LIVE on Twitter in just 15 minutes (2.45pm UK time) so make sure you tune in! #asklana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful. http://t.co/CixyWdrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey cuts the ribbon to officially open new Mulberry store on Orchard Road, Singapore. http://t.co/r1RTemDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey meet the fans before the Mulberry event. http://t.co/cloOLqZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey at Mulberry Mandarin Gallery Singapore! http://t.co/ERAcNf1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for Lana Del Rey at the Peoples Choice Awards for 'Favourite Breakout Artist'. VOTE HERE: http://t.co/soh4yOIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else is gonna put up with me this way? I need you, I breathe you, I'd never leave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my dreams and all the lights mean nothing without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say I'm wasting time, they said that I'm no good. Cause Imma love my life, not doing what I should.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>