<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/SH8YZWVubY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Commerce Secretary Pritzker on Saving the Future of Jobs: Former Commerce Secretary Penny Pritzker, co-chair of a task force on the future of work, says the nation needs to "relink education, work and opportunity." https://t.co/M3WCvhDhSg https://t.co/idayuZPvq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/RGWpRLuO8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/rk296jf9nX https://t.co/WU5wQDaChX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/bixklk37Nq https://t.co/oZ3aw230TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/jifQo5XkV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/WwnC35q6cf https://t.co/qXFLwBFPSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/zdVLCfZOgt https://t.co/VLRNi5BY4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg Answers to Congress For Facebook's Troubles: Tensions around Facebook's privacy and ad practices have escalated dramatically since the last time the company sat before Congress. https://t.co/46vPMQzXOs https://t.co/D3rAnMiBiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018's 'Dirty Dozen' fruits and veggies: Once again, strawberries top the list of the 12 "dirtiest" fruits and vegetables, according to the Environmental Working Group. https://t.co/t8ai9XNWlU https://t.co/k5htZW1maM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/xWxafnzgIo https://t.co/M6Q5dWR3UU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Material Handler: ID 2018-3728# of Openings 3Location: City DetroitLocation: State/Province MIPosted Date 2018-02-14 Alro Steel is currently seeking a Material Handler to join our team in Detroit, MI. Join the Alro team and start building your tomorrow!… https://t.co/qckNI9FwNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/KHyWeX3jOc https://t.co/Om5oHuKOcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/uJWYhQFuQM https://t.co/qNfokvkOYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/ON92xyoO7U https://t.co/dWuyAtyXzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/OYe1OfIS1B https://t.co/DeUUcuNvji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/XZbiygkCvA https://t.co/Zxt0Uw66JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/o3qdpRixW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/fPbAugVzWO https://t.co/rDO62wqakd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/gVqX66jWvZ https://t.co/Sf7JtW28jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Watch Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg Testify Before Congress: On Tuesday and Wednesday, Mark Zuckerberg will testify before the Senate and House of Representatives. Here's how to make sure you don't miss a minute. https://t.co/aGYlQJgHIy https://t.co/1W9tkjYbBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/5fgcZ3RQOc https://t.co/X795GT3AEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/Z951mdkAur https://t.co/S0urufBqU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/Sm5XSn8GGR https://t.co/eGYGdNN1dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/5oeTZxlYF5 https://t.co/HOohUoU2pB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Schumer warns Trump not to fire Mueller https://t.co/AXvs3uChD9 https://t.co/xAhRhqYWu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/Pwvc6MLhtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/ZG2htNMoWP https://t.co/T8wRaKbXbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/DvkesTniLB https://t.co/y7ULc5EeVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/mMKK3YNCHs https://t.co/bmiqyTMafG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/oTqogXHxYd https://t.co/SuVIcaxY3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/Y869n65528 https://t.co/XuwlYE4KIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/05yQJmeQP4 https://t.co/DgNHFQi4Fo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Material Handler: ID 2018-3728# of Openings 3Location: City DetroitLocation: State/Province MIPosted Date 2018-02-14 Alro Steel is currently seeking a Material Handler to join our team in Detroit, MI. Join the Alro team and start building your tomorrow!… https://t.co/O4N7IPivcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/8NHONyalbA https://t.co/Hho1vqyynJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/zUvhdtZza6 https://t.co/EQMSu6zuxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/VISKFIViUM https://t.co/pk9xkr2mrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Android Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for an Android developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. The… https://t.co/ob9Drbihis https://t.co/lF9n3wHLfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/GUzzJFjA6A https://t.co/GmIycpGNuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt is 'the wrong person' to lead EPA, GOP senator says: Republican Sen. Susan Collins, of Maine, is calling embattled EPA Administrator Scott Pruitt "the wrong person" to head the agency "on policy grounds alone." https://t.co/5nFAMhFl3J https://t.co/ZamJuEr2V2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/z3qVP22GCw https://t.co/DmU6MMOx8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/ToCJyE2PUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/ztZfNdnC5G https://t.co/rUIt0rcXjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/OfIVI63fIQ https://t.co/pj8Y1biB5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/DtAkSJDWyj https://t.co/gfprpxsUMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/zUGD20sBSS https://t.co/G0TgcB6zOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groups Allege YouTube Is Violating Law That Protects Kids: In complaint to the FTC, child-health, privacy, and consumer groups say YouTube is targeting kids improperly. https://t.co/PHpA6I8AEF https://t.co/frcr1mdCXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/lnyGgbLUuP https://t.co/rsL7FeM2Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/GuTR081yUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/SQofWdQVos https://t.co/ECB6p1A2Ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Android Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for an Android developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. The… https://t.co/NcF5A9mbvY https://t.co/tciMX76I8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/ac6HLAGasa https://t.co/BFvOh4FNHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/cvkE2cDwkI https://t.co/16mbGqgFJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/f7sXkXEsfr https://t.co/IaFVju5Maf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 savings accounts pay 10x what your bank pays https://t.co/yysJ1fjckQ https://t.co/oOpxgLhBgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/cvvQTnBgES https://t.co/gq2ogzInS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/BaEVXkDivi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/7AR92nRrZE https://t.co/T8iAZn52RE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/443Xvk7XXR https://t.co/KRgKh8eO7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/jQuzfk0LPf https://t.co/TGFHGYdqPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/WknHAtftTs https://t.co/QJTghW7OQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/Xs3uRiEiKJ https://t.co/AQPr00HKWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/NHyyy33TAC https://t.co/SahgNnB1nC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Material Handler: ID 2018-3728# of Openings 3Location: City DetroitLocation: State/Province MIPosted Date 2018-02-14 Alro Steel is currently seeking a Material Handler to join our team in Detroit, MI. Join the Alro team and start building your tomorrow!… https://t.co/7irUTTwl48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/YpYP50WGVM https://t.co/dr2jgIXZKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/BEN02m15qP https://t.co/taMlFJWwt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/Wkmoy1FANj https://t.co/jcuAuiwa2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/KwyrhHr8P5 https://t.co/gB3V3WDxRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Facebook Debacle Proves It’s High Time for Stronger Privacy Laws: Opinion: The Cambridge Analytica scandal makes it clear: The US needs to pass a privacy law that gives consumers the protections they deserve. https://t.co/RDUaj9BAAK https://t.co/n6rXfB0PRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/aVYg2pgQ7v https://t.co/GPFdvrYTrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's most over-the-top hotel rooms: Thought you'd seen luxury? Think again. These hotel suites, decked out with everything from basketball courts to water slides, redefine the very meaning of luxury. https://t.co/TVAa2LPl5r https://t.co/uGlmewnajm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/SRyptfFCkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/WFppKl6ruN https://t.co/btF31ExMUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/wGiVhQfTAh https://t.co/LDantbOm83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/45zaXa41Lm https://t.co/Dp2sltOrQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/AwjH1oyAzQ https://t.co/o49A3NbExy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/2S5LZuxvl7 https://t.co/9yJTDwHzNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/ca6R9WzYaQ https://t.co/Ot7jMxEaw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/5tXOE4MG6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/o306TuPthY https://t.co/mLqEMLqSd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/58tWCKusBp https://t.co/FTFYyKyKg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/nBVl8wx6pr https://t.co/7ulnDbsasy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/7lEZCE4AaD https://t.co/S4ADTGNjS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/3j4v8vwhL5 https://t.co/KGWZGIjNXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Masters 2018: See photos from the 2018 Masters tournament in Augusta, Georgia. https://t.co/PtcRUN6J2I https://t.co/WLK8EEycNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/p33YXO3nee https://t.co/QE2qKok3Zl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/Cobswh1B1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/ntJqooYXKr https://t.co/CQGsloSCfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/xVLQ0fyent https://t.co/0xXFSCl2aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/oXl2PsmMVQ https://t.co/TqpjltF0Bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/fCoGVhlU0Z https://t.co/ZwWJUC2aYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/BOmLOd7KlV https://t.co/FF9SXnT3iC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/yf4GpoWbiU https://t.co/GjmCu1B9j1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/elZxlwyqah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/PHIWOb7WR0 https://t.co/5Xp5lzgRgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/7BfsKNzy3O https://t.co/lXNFk6Zttw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Sanctions, Spectre Fixes, and More Security News This Week: Russia sanctions, Spectre fixes, and more security news this week. https://t.co/LuyApNkN6x https://t.co/VMevQNX7vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/lEH7QXY4RE https://t.co/mCZJlXAWVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/9eywTGjs5p https://t.co/OkIbL6F0V8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/3X3KrWc5vG https://t.co/TUGL3LiLHU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>