<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/pqLtp2dNXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/aCKrnpS0vE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/ShVjxynah9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/4OXfEb6BJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/Nb9LUeDaD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/Cf1Thc6shr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/XiJXkz9grZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/DnPZx7Lv2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/HcZhL8fj10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/oA0XX5m1V5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/07ctqPwqxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/KNWE0PUmXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/z0Mse2a4jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/9f5FzaboWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/jeEKDAT3PG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/AUhgbndAFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/qxUQS9tQcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/OvJWTXyMhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/rAD3YBdEwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/6RHZioSexx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/TZ30PpJpbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/wvhxh6CuyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/FPzgjGUqBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/ei89CJJULq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/oO3VXy4Iqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/hPjDK09OtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/meMOdme3dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/hEVOI214is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/8vY72QMGIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/jqXnGbCZwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1ifE3Kh75b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1q9KkAnOew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else. - James M. Barrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/NVvRrCvZSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/7LESkQokrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/n0mPyUVtVV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>