<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/lK6GlBGRhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/mo25Sexl6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/eeVk0jI7ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/rZ4LDb52vV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the J. Geils Band  http://t.co/VjJEklw7A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/AxUdkNATrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/jJ1kThQjLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Introduction to Ray Bradbury  http://t.co/RmU9BuZC5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/pYuZwwKGQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/N8rgr9wKSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/pW5ONnlc80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/0nAYphpvbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/n1PfxCEfPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/vMkJGOXEOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/pYuZwwKGQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/XFH3XubCln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/fOCqaXJuGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/W4D3BREz4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/6aqLatOv8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/nV01wghPNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/EOWUXcxDBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/8IoeLB0qaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/7yZdrMK9As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/NTn740mmun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/Chm05Zys8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/eeeblHUFWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/pSTHILzY0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/MmrJTa1G8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/nGg3R9UORB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/fDPQUz7vwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/haYsszt0t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/jvmjjvMV1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/jDzyCbzPKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/IjgwYGBPKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/ooi4C38lYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/D3bRyoy8T5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/QtTuAtiWKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/0lz12ET7En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/pW5ONnlc80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/wtbUU1NlHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/BY7MIZejVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/eeeblHUFWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/NPmCFtrDaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/vkJSDoLNiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/cmNrXQKSpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/Yc3YFSx1zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/PdHyrTNfRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/URmW4Rxdlj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>