<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[8. Are you one of those who wait only for special occasions like Valentine's Day? #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. When last did you date your spouse? #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. Dating helps couples to create time for deep &amp; meaningful communication which eliminate misunderstanding and suspicion. #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. Dating makes marriage fun and exciting, giving couples something to look forward to. #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. Are you too busy to nurture your relationship with your spouse?#DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. You may have a good relationship, but your busy schedule may be robbing your marriage of romance. #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. Dating in marriage is a spicy romance tool that couples can take advantage of to transform their marital experience. #DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Dating in marriage is setting apart a special time to connect &amp; bond with your spouse,eventually nurturing your marriage.#DatingMySpouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marriagetoday: "Whenever you have sex with your spouse, you are saying 'I do' again." @seanreed2  @LanetteReed #XO17 https://t.co/wRDAQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the unexpected happens and by every human calculation, nothing seems to add up, encourage yourself, stand... https://t.co/8o5pCY6mX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine Series – No To Seasonal Love! – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “Thank God next week is… https://t.co/8bLypGS0vQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thank God next week is Valentine, at least mum can smile again", said Louis

That comment, coming from a fifteen... https://t.co/g2dLJaajfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine Series – No To Seasonal #Love! – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: “Thank God next week is… https://t.co/KS7EbuTUYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love goes through different phases. Dr. Gary Chapman expressed it as "four seasons of marriage", while some other... https://t.co/pMmj9Ud2a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VALENTINE Series – Stick Together! By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Love goes through different… https://t.co/RNqjcUO3es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VALENTINE Series – Stick Together! By Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: #Love goes through different… https://t.co/94O0wmtvxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VFJPQBZ0xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countdown to VALENTINE: Make your spouse's happiness your mission 

As we walked through the mall on Valentine's... https://t.co/7q8zTqCLm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countdown to VALENTINE: Make your spouse’s happiness your mission – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna… https://t.co/SPlCOOuZjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countdown to VALENTINE: Make your spouse’s happiness your mission – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna… https://t.co/sNyJOQY6yB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. Commitment is tested in tough times, let's do our best, counting on God for strength. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13.This is crucial because under pressure,there's a great tendency to blame each other,to relieve pain.#StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Also, refuse the temptation to see each other as the problem, even when you make mistakes. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. I know that when you go through any challenge as a team, you come through stronger and better. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. Do not let challenges pull you apart, consider them to be opportunities to bond. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @ChrisInspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9b. ... you won't let it ruffle you and tear you apart from your spouse. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @BridgetElesin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9.If you see any tough time as an opportunity that can launch you to the next phase,... #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @BridgetElesin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. Your approach and disposition to tough times determine how you go through it. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @AyodejiJohnson7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. When spouses go it alone, they rob themselves some benefits.  #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @praisefowowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. Stick with your spouse, work as a team, there is power in synergy.  #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @bisiadewale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. ...one of the beauties of marriage is that you have someone you can face the world with.  #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. In the face of a challenge, some people would rather go it alone, but ... #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. ...what matters is how we handle them.  #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. Some people quit in the face of tough times, but the truth is that there will always be challenges. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Tough times reveal who we are. #StickWithYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/0px7uFWAP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a father, a mentor, a phenomenal leader! Meeting you ignited a journey of personal transformation in my life! @sam_adeyemi https://t.co/dU0zsSmSHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media is often awash with stories of domestic violence, break ups and cheating spouses. Any time such pops... https://t.co/xOM9fqal1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Great Marriages by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Social media is often awash with… https://t.co/yMDFco5Yzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Great Marriages by Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Social media is often awash with… https://t.co/pjtg2UxWFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being emotionally attached to a married man/woman, holding on to the fact that you both are not sexually... https://t.co/Yy2rlzOgvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free download is available on our website until 31st March, 2017.

Free download link: https://t.co/S117cwoPCw https://t.co/WNEjcvj5M2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KK4NRKBJCR https://t.co/JdxdJ6GT91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KK4NRKBJCR https://t.co/tORnqVaWnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Iy6veXgA8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/dZLEg9RCcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DCISUwsE55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great Escape! by Victor Akunna: They never attended parents-teachers meeting. They… https://t.co/klzhFQXFha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great Escape! by Victor Akunna: They never attended parents-teachers meeting. They… https://t.co/8wL0z3YuDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No flower can receive sunlight without opening up. There is no intimacy without vulnerability. Victor Akunna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YfwLJaVFNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ayodaniels: "You don't achieve greatness by luck. You achieve it by mastering details that no one else bothers with as small things mat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying "I love you" is good, but showing it is better! 

#MakingSacrifices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True worship gets rid of the feelings of disappointments, hurts &amp; rejections, thereby making you a better spouse!
Photo credit:Growtheheckup https://t.co/v4ZIokSWka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is more than a feeling, it is a daily commitment to accept someone unconditionally" |Victor Akunna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couples who are best friends enjoy deeper marital intimacy. Nurture your marital friendship! -Victor Akunna

#FriendshipFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 35. Putting so much burden on your spouse could make him/her snap.  #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 34. It is good to have expectations when going into a r/ship, but do not overwhelm your spouse with your expectations.  #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 33. Apart from distraction, another factor that may be responsible for the emotional disconnection is unmet expectations.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 31. stop allowing the gulf between you to get wider, approach him and do a reality check ASAP. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 27. ...or having thoughts of this person fill your mind. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 26. ...seeking suggestions on sensitive issues you should ideally go to your spouse for suggestions,... #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 25. You may not be physically involved with this person, but you may be spending a lot of time with the person,... #Emoti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 24. Another distraction could be a new flame. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 23. Your spouse may notice that and withdraw, accepting the fact that he/she is not priority afterall. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 22.If you are giving more time to that relationship than you are giving to your marriage,it could affect a lot of things.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 21. Distraction could even be your relationship with a friend - friend of the same sex. Oh yes! #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20b. ...they give their all to the success of the project and do not realise that their homes are suffering. #EmotionalIn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 20. Sometimes, when couples are preoccupied with so much at work or committed to a certain project,... #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 19. Stop! Ask yourself, what could be the distraction? Could it be work? #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 18. You may even shrug your shoulder, click your fingers and scream, "God forbid!" #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 17. Distraction could be subtle. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 52. Finally, no marriage is beyond repair if the couples are willing to play their role.#EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 50. Couples must try to get to the point of being emotionally intimate with each other. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 49. There is trust between them and communication is key. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 48b. ...when they share their inner thoughts, fears, excitement, etc., freely, without reservation.#EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 48. Emotional intimacy is that level of connection spouses have, ... #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 47. Emotional intimacy is very necessary if your marriage must thrive. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 44b. ...which you think may be of help to your spouse, but presentation is important. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 44. Now, there is nothing wrong with pointing out something that you appreciate in someone... #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 43. You need him or her to be like someone else in order to be loved. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 42. Comparing your spouse to someone else simply means that you think he or she is not good enough. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 41. Comparison is another factor that could drive a gap between you and your spouse. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 40. Do not just retreat and allow a gulf between you both. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 39. If you feel overwhelmed by the expectations your spouse has of you, discuss them with him or her. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 38. Review the expectations you have of your spouse and see if they may the affecting your marriage.  #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 37b. ...or that his or her spouse is taking him or her for granted.  #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 37. On the other hand, the other spouse may withdraw, feeling bad that his or her expectations were not met, ...  #Emotio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 14. Commitment is very vital. #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 13. It is important for spouses to stick together in challenging times and not allow the situation to overwhelm them. #Em…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 12. When spouses go through challenging times without strategies in place for handling such, it could affect them badly.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 11. However, I will highlight some things that may be responsible for emotional disconnection between spouses. #Emotional…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 9. Truth is, nothing just happens, there are issues that, if left and not handled properly, become 'monsters'. #Emotional…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8b. ..."I don't know how we became like this, it just seems we both were possessed by something we do not even know". #Em…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 8. In a conversation with a woman in a similar situation, she said to me, ... #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 7. How do people who used to be so intimate become roommates? #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chidi_akunna: 6. How do people get to this point? How do people who used to be lovers become haters? #EmotionalIntimacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacknJilLive: Life teaches us to be careful what we say and whom we say it to. @LekeAlder https://t.co/b0xUIPfhSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacknJilLive: Insulting others to have ones way is nothing but immaturity. @LekeAlder https://t.co/40eLm34IfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacknJilLive: To live successfully in this life you need some guts. Don't live in fear. @LekeAlder https://t.co/fdCXzaZiuB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>