<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IVR Application Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The IVR Application Developer isresponsible for designing, developing, building and testing routing scripts in a contact center application developed by inContact on behalf of our… https://t.co/wW1bKKOvqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineers II (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10695 Job Location United States Overview Sr. Software Engineers II (.NET) for American Institutes for Research to work at our Washington, DC loc. Perform full lifecycle devpmnt. Participate in… https://t.co/vmWYFgEZkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Resource Planning: Job Description Job Description This person is responsible for Workforce related analysis, focused on our forecasting and staffing for Customer Care and Sub Prime lines of business for the National Resource Planning team.… https://t.co/JAoydoGjl7 https://t.co/Wf7YAdTubM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-20498 Location: Montvale, New Jersey Role: .NET Developer Location: Montvale,NJ Duration: Full Time Permanent Skillset requirements NET, C# Angular, ability to design and develop systems, must be able to work… https://t.co/sWJtuvr0HA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer/Support Roles: .Net Developer/Support Roles Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 02/23/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview C#.NET Developer Wells Fargo Remote Our Enterprise Information… https://t.co/DdUw362FVA https://t.co/xvPfjvA5Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAIMS Senior .NET Applications Developer: LOCATION:Reston, VA (May have future relocation to Falls Church, VA/Baileys Crossroads) POSITION DESCRIPTION: This position is for a Senior Applications Developer to work on the HAIMS project at the Defense… https://t.co/3F4PDrRaAW https://t.co/a90fIoum4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst-.Net,IIS: System ************,IIS Ref No.: 18-20635 Location: Mt Laurel, New Jersey 5+ years of experience working in .Net Framework which includes IIS Good Hands on working with windows &amp; Sql server Should have very strong communication… https://t.co/kKCyT9Y6r5 https://t.co/yfuCe2WwDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Software Engineer: Tyvak Nano-Satellite Systems Inc., a Terran Orbital company, is seeking a motivated Flight Software Engineer for our Boulder, CO location. Tyvak is a leading worldwide provider of nanosatellite and microsatellite vehicles,… https://t.co/CHXNoyLBQS https://t.co/BXKCSevD2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI Developer: Job Title: Mid-Level ******* Developer (03-013) Location: Cambridge, MA Strongbridge LLC in support of the Volpe National Transportation Systems Center, located in Cambridge, MA has an immediate need for an… https://t.co/qQiQDfdBap https://t.co/nX4b3KKSNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.:18-02316 Location: Franklin Lakes, New Jersey Position Type:Right to Hire This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and… https://t.co/FS8CNUvvL0 https://t.co/i2IW7r0Gu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET DEVELOPER: .NET DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-21801 Location: PLANO, Texas My name is Gaurav Chaudhary and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc.I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available for a project. Our… https://t.co/KJrGItCqYJ https://t.co/mdFpqF7bVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build and Release Engineer with .NET/Oracle: Position : Build and Release Engineer with .NET/Oracle Duration : 4+ Months Location : Farmingdale, NY Requirements Skills: * 3+ years experience in build/release engineering and configuration management with… https://t.co/cATVlzlIhO https://t.co/V9dXSnn0lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with React JS: .Net Developer with React JS Ref No.:18-08782 Location: Madison, Wisconsin Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/11/2018 Get local GC/USC- CTH &amp; FT Please help on the below demand. We have 3 .Net with React JS… https://t.co/GyWMMIWfJY https://t.co/VobgxNNaGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (Bigdata/Hadoop): Java Developer (Bigdata/Hadoop) Ref No.: 18-01189 Location: Plano, Texas Position Type: Contract Start Date: 05/28/2018 Required Skills: Java, Scala, AWS, Python, Big Data/Hadoop, Spark, SQL . 5+ years of experience with… https://t.co/IpOevt0TBr https://t.co/6Oapiu3YRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/Python Developer (Treasury): Job **************** Developer (Treasury) – ID:31627 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job *************, Python, Micro Services, C# , AngularJS , MicrSQL Server , Oracle LocationPlano, TX Date Posted05/02/2018 FOR… https://t.co/PO5ktQh4d0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: As a Project Manager II, you will manage the cost, quality, and schedule of wireless infrastructure projects for new site builds and for modifications to existing facilities. This involves preparing the scope of work, pricing,… https://t.co/jqfTTcDViP https://t.co/MtmpJ046p8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 9301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers,… https://t.co/PiTFHlwKlj https://t.co/FLq4n4YzWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Developer: .Net Software Developer ======================= Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description As an emerging authority,… https://t.co/KeruGITMKU https://t.co/Gi8BzbbeiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Web Developer: The Web Development Team is a growing group working within a progressive IT environment that encourages innovation and creative thinking. This is an outstanding opportunity for a highly skilled full stack .NET WEB DEVELOPER to… https://t.co/trShkPyIMf https://t.co/JXKH0dvxFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMOTE MANAGER of Software Development – C#/.NET/Live 1-2 hrs of Gaithersburg: HOT!!! AMAZING SMALL COMPANY SEEKING A SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT MANAGER The company has been around for over 15 years and is looking bring on a manager that can help further… https://t.co/erYyKHbmYZ https://t.co/1a75gIV191]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parts Inspector: Parts Inspector Eckel Manufacturing Company is looking for a Parts Inspector. Must have experience with parts inspection, assemblies and finished products to drawings and specifications. Perform limited and repetitive visual, mechanical,… https://t.co/rDpdLUZewE https://t.co/5rzjkUJCp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer for CACI in Quantico, VA 22134(map) Job Description What You’ll Get to Do: CACI International, Inc. (CACI) has an immediate opportunity for a Senior .Net Developer onsite in Quantico, VA supporting the Naval… https://t.co/XAyfxtUYQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Developer Engineer: We are looking for a brilliant mind to join our team, working on solving very real and important problems. You will take a leadership role in our algorithm team to develop machine learning and behavior… https://t.co/9S49FZ9HOI https://t.co/O43JFrGZsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .Net Developer: Resourcesoft Inc. provides Information Technology Professionals, Consulting Services and Subject Matter Experts (SMEs) to match the exclusive business requirements of our clients. Resourcesoft is among the fastest growing IT… https://t.co/1oZwmUpLOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer/Analyst Interns (entry-level): IT Developer/Analyst Interns (entry-level) ========================================== Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: AdministrationSecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be… https://t.co/Yvfr0Dvwrl https://t.co/b4gqbn27Kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Analyst: About the Company: Since 1843, we’ve set the standard for excellence in everything we do. No company on earth has a stronger or more compelling history of delivering the hardworking, innovative, powerful tools that help… https://t.co/g5wnQ1UsNT https://t.co/qNWpuWRmpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .NET Developer: Sr. .NET Developer Ref No.:18-00085 Location: Sacramento, California Skill Type:Service Delivery NWN is recognized as one of the top 16 Cisco partners in the U.S. and a leader in the IT services industry with many awards and elite… https://t.co/CaUIBpzWsu https://t.co/qURLeyrhkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .NET Developer with Angular JS: Microsoft .NET Developer with Angular JS Ref No.: 18-22296 Location: Washington, District of Columbia – Candidate should have 7+ years if IT experience – Candidate must have minimum 4+ years of relevant… https://t.co/tNrW7bkh9l https://t.co/c5EoZLmfyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Applications Developer: Senior .NET Applications Developer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10309 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Senior .NET Applications… https://t.co/QwNu3kiXcw https://t.co/DsiGXMyYas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .Net, Web Services: Software Engineer – .Net, Web Services Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta –… https://t.co/VgerbfC9FC https://t.co/6kOXabm0MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer – Remote: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:21st May 2018Location:Atlanta, GeorgiaContact Name:Robert CappucciTelephone:646-604-2838 (ext 3410)Reference:78467456754 Salary: Full-stack .NET Developer – REMOTE We are looking for an experienced… https://t.co/OEyVd81tBN https://t.co/CEgixvsecu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Applications Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Quantico, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/3/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/isuiiyyNCT https://t.co/5DOVBzzsCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Image Scientist / Phenomenologist Job: Date: Mar 24, 2018 Location:Herndon, VA, US Company: SAIC Image Scientist / Phenomenologist (Job Number:423412) Description: SAIC is seeking a Image Scientist/Phenomenologist to join our team. This position will… https://t.co/Fj878QwV4Z https://t.co/A0o8Htssa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer (Backend): Senior .NET Developer (Backend) Ref No.: 18-01317 Location: Los Angeles, California Position Type: Contract Start Date: 05/24/2018 Requirements C# Web Services API Integration SQL SSIS Banking is a plus https://t.co/UvOGpILrjF https://t.co/C58xywVmDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: Role: .NET Web Developer Salt Lake City,UT 9 months Contract Summary Client is looking for a strong development candidate to create a publicly accessible bilingual (Spanish and English) School Grade Reporting website/tool. Candidate… https://t.co/WMJaoLlfa9 https://t.co/J0jGYpt2hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-22733 Location: Redmond, Washington Position Title : .Net Developer Location : Baltimore, MD Duration : Full Time Permanent Job Description Good Experience in C#, SQL, .NET. Be able to work on a team. Work through https://t.co/hDmZT4rHgY https://t.co/JG4dS9Xr8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#.NET Developer: Great opportunity for strong C#.NET developers from intermediate level all the way up to lead level to join a fortune 500 company located in the Cleveland area. 6 month and 12 month contract-to-hire/permanent positions available.… https://t.co/wIolQYL0kw https://t.co/4OrJGIHCex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Web Developer 3 C#, https://t.co/7mXPWx9VgK, SQL): BI Web Developer 3 (Angular4, C#, *******, SQL) Ref No.: 18-20870 Location: Redmond, Washington Role: BI Web Developer 3 (Angular4, C#, *******, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: Full time Job… https://t.co/5mZnbHk9zO https://t.co/pRcnhVGEJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Be part of a P2’s engineering team that is adding new features and refactoring an energy market trading application. The team is composed of senior-level software developers making a number of complex enhancements while also driving down… https://t.co/lkrrLIIysB https://t.co/YJ3zgzPLFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Specialist: Application Specialist OAKLAND COMMUNITY HEALTH NETWORK Application Specialist Starting Salary: $44,465 (Annually) General Summary of Position: The Application Specialist is responsible for having a deep understanding of Oakland… https://t.co/aRqK1A8iWB https://t.co/Ue89TRctmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .NET Developer: Title Sr. .NET Developer ================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national… https://t.co/DHAIFqWnhJ https://t.co/L8sKJB7P3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-21597 Location: Sunrise, Florida Job Description: Must have Expert knowledge in Object Oriented Programming and design patterns. -Must have Expert knowledge and hands on experience on the C Sharp programming… https://t.co/Tv0S7Q75kJ https://t.co/K01ggWrkLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Riverbed Technology is hiring in Sunnyvale, CA: Member of Technical Staff (Software Engineer) (#D163): Drive the definition, design, development, and delivery of new networking features Member of Technical Staff (Software Engineer)… https://t.co/jF14KkB0fu https://t.co/OxEF6pCNPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Arlington, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsC#,DotnetTax TermsC2COverview Hello, I have a Senior .Net Developer role that I need candidates to! I have put… https://t.co/3CRDjViqGS https://t.co/cTtGU0GOfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Architect/Developer (CONTRACT): Our enterprise technology strategy and solutions engineering team is in need of both part time and potentially full time seasoned .NET architecture / development talent. Our two technical leaders on this… https://t.co/hLnvBL8sC7 https://t.co/rJnWV1tVsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineers II (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10695 Job Location United States Overview Sr. Software Engineers II (.NET) for American Institutes for Research to work at our Washington, DC loc. Perform full lifecycle devpmnt. Participate in… https://t.co/d1OdxA0UTX https://t.co/JrNBnu7NDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer pasedena, California – United States Job Start Date – 05/09/18, Posted Date – 05/09/18 Primary Skills.netTax TermsC2COverviewNeed .net developer in CA * Job CodeSG – 13361 * Pay Rate/SalaryUSD – 55/ * Experience8 Years *… https://t.co/KaC7D2OBRs https://t.co/hC4hkzYPQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Job Title : .Net Developer Location : Houston, TX (Local consultants) Duration : 3+ months &amp; Extendable Work authorization status: US citizen &amp; GC only. Skills: ******* MVC, Web API, C#, JQuery, Knockout, SQL Server, Entity Framework Job… https://t.co/6KPwcX6pGD https://t.co/pWjiLjFUGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst – PeopleSoft: POSITION SUMMARY: MULTIPLE OPENINGS IN CRYSTAL CITY, VA. Plans and manages system-wide data analyses regarding the allocation of enterprise application functions for the IPPS-A program. Manages data analysis of systems… https://t.co/DZscabw2Qr https://t.co/iZd4UNVFl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SW Developer .NET: SW Developer .NET Ref No.: 18-23075 Location: Blue Ash, Ohio SW Developer .NET Blue Ash, OH AngularJS, Digital : Node.js, ******* 2.0, Foundation : JavaScript, Foundation : ******* 4.5 SAFe Agile Process, Experience in web application… https://t.co/ibXog5Dtjq https://t.co/e9aM3omJfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#.Net Developer: C#.Net Developer Ref No.: 18-01294 Location: Ipswich, Massachusetts Position Type: Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/23/2018 Location: Ipswich/MA (or) Birmingham, AL Job Title C#.Net Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs) 2+ years of… https://t.co/aFWxgf80iK https://t.co/URCcFuIQqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Business Analyst: IT-BUSINESS ANALYST (Morrisville, NC): Design liquidity reporting &amp; monitoring application to meet U.S. regulatory reporting requirements. Review business requirements, apply business knowledge, &amp; determine implementation complexity… https://t.co/CsAuzFf6bM https://t.co/mSCX0GjW74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Architect: .Net Architect Ref No.: 18-21501 Location: Madison, Wisconsin Role: .Net Architect Location: Madison, WI / Chicago, IL Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Should have strong exp. on .Net technologies with Lead/Architect exp.… https://t.co/mgWYmAocAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Program/Project Analyst: Job Details Company Medtronic Job Title Principal Program/Project Analyst JobId 41469 Location: Santa Rosa, CA, 95404, USA Description Principal Program/Project Analyst Location: Santa Rosa, California, United States… https://t.co/DB5w6M42KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Time Operations Analyst: VIGILINT is a unique medical operations company that provides advisory, planning, logistics, medical operations, and crisis management services to high-net-worth individuals, Fortune 500 companies, and government clients.… https://t.co/mNis6umKAN https://t.co/CLLIkdQC3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: RESPONSIBILITIES: * Hands-on development of mostly web-based applications using ******* MVC (.NET Core where appropriate). Our clients are mostly private sector, specializing in the Financial Services industry * Make design… https://t.co/PIhV8WjoPf https://t.co/lZnZZwzgjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: escription : We need a programmer with the listed skills below. The resource will be building a staging and production area using the proprietary CMS for the new site before USBE can go live. The resource will also be utilized build an… https://t.co/EDbztue9dY https://t.co/C6JC7Ag4Vc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer C# .NET: Job Title Software Developer C# .NET Education Bachelor’s Degree Location Kiev, 04073 UA (Primary) Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category IT/Software Development Job Type Full-time Job Description Requirements: –… https://t.co/GUJ6IsDgOe https://t.co/yVVMxF3DsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead .NET Software Engineer: Trimble  is recruiting for a  Software Engineer/ Tech lead to fill an opportunity in Westminster, CO. Virtual Site Solutions (VSS) is a joint venture between Trimble and Caterpillar Inc. responsible for the development of Web… https://t.co/TuKemVx5VT https://t.co/yPC7ySX6jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer:   Job Description – .NET Software Engineer (1803519) Job Description  .NET Software Engineer – (1803519) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-Remote Employees Job : Molina Medicaid Solutions Organization : Medical Systems Job… https://t.co/9jHxwPWfHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controller (Relocation to Atlanta, GA): Tallahassee, FL Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Controller with experience, please read on! Based in Atlanta, we are one of the top five real estate companies in the country. We are looking for an… https://t.co/Qn3zEvI0g0 https://t.co/bGaOGklyp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Architect: .NET ARCHITECT AZURE CHEVY CHASE, MD INTERVIEW: PHONE AND SKYPE There will be a coding test The candidate must be a strong coder. Proven track record in establishing and implementing architectural solutions that have resulted in… https://t.co/RBTWX5CHHo https://t.co/nj1laBDNgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung's second quarter profit seen flagging as smartphone innovation dries up: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics Co Ltd is expected to post its smallest profit growth in more than a year in the second quarter, as lacklustre sales of its premium… https://t.co/Zzr3oCr7Z1 https://t.co/QiPwIJnMVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer (C#/.NET): Web Applications Developer (C#/.NET) Ref No.:18-00009 Location: Quantico, Virginia Provide Web Application Development for a federal client Ensure security of applications and data through design, testing, and… https://t.co/XppKIzm4Vm https://t.co/HIaRcn16R6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: F2F interview is must Job Title: .Net Developer WORK LOCATION: US-PA-Pittsburgh # POSITIONS: 1 Our Client is looking for a qualified candidate for our .NET Developer position in the PITTSBURGH, PA area. Please see details of the position… https://t.co/cPknu8YgVn https://t.co/6dOC4dU07X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump moves to block China Mobile's U.S. entry on security concerns: SHANGHAI/HONG KONG (Reuters) - The U.S. government has moved to block China Mobile from offering services to the country's telecommunications market, recommending its application be… https://t.co/uGZ5Auu4Xb https://t.co/zmfARjhi59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claims Data Analyst (QA, Non-IT): Employee Type: Seasonal/Temp Location: Dallas, TX Job Type: Policy Operations Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/10/2018 Job Description Essential Duties and Responsibilities: Following is a summary of the… https://t.co/Oc8y2blKLY https://t.co/2HT5a6aKYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Identity Software Engineer: *This is a 3 month contract to hire, with no 3rd part candidates being considered at this time* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking a Microsoft Developer with systems support skills. Candidate will… https://t.co/brUL06xpQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net Software Developer: LINQM has been engaged to help a client with a search for a .net Developer. Requirements: * 10 years direct experience is required. An advanced degree may offset some required experience. * A bachelors or a masters degree in an… https://t.co/1UJQyJfkUG https://t.co/vB1Kqk9A7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-26345 Location: Jacksonville, Florida Role: .Net Developer Location : Jacksonville, FL Duration: Full Time Permanent Job Description Very Strong inASP Dot Net and C# and JavaScript working in Linux would be… https://t.co/JINGlpI6Tg https://t.co/Wd94AwXpth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer Corporate IT: Senior Systems Engineer – Corporate IT Ref No.:18-00103 Location: Columbia, Maryland Position Type:Full Time Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 06/05/2018 Senior Systems Engineer – Corporate IT FEi is a leading IT… https://t.co/ZlVAzYzhqu https://t.co/UqFQkonDfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer/ Web Programmer/ Software Engineer: JOB TITLE: .NET DEVELOPER DURATION: 12 MONTHS LOCATION: 701 EAST BRYD ST, RICHMOND, VA 23219 REQUIRED: * Client is seeking an intermediate level .NET developer who is experienced with developing new… https://t.co/QtpM3IRD73 https://t.co/6gxx3ZQnDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-14697 Location: Houston, Texas Job Title: .NET developer Job Location: Houston, TX Job Duration: 12+ Months Responsibilities: – The applications are manufacturing and business supporting. – The candidate must… https://t.co/h3rLKz7bSo https://t.co/VV8z1E6YzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cognos Lead: Cognos Lead in Marlborough, Massachusetts, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values… https://t.co/JpKBzVApKY https://t.co/nrArfwKYQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer king of prussia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 07/09/18, Posted Date – 06/25/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Full Stack Software Developer Summary: The Change Healthcare Value Based Payment (VBP)… https://t.co/n6jGm8xRQ4 https://t.co/fz8nZsVhfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. This role will require developing innovative ideas leveraging emerging technologies and demonstrating viability through rapid prototyping. – Developing the design and software for applications… https://t.co/qPKzkmdpak https://t.co/s4AHdMgbRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead .Net Developer: Requirements Bachelors degree or above, preferably in Computer Science or Engineering. At least 10+ years of progressive hands-on experience with architecture, design and development of web applications using Microsoft ******* Web… https://t.co/RM2kCCOA17 https://t.co/yx9C8bZlqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary Skills.netTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12+ months contract. Phone and Skype interview. This is a .Net Developer role with heavy AWS… https://t.co/FAnFLc40VH https://t.co/bxkaIZB9PS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Job Description Mission The Senior .NET Developer is responsible for designing, developing and troubleshooting high performance and high availability web applications using .NET 4.5+, ******* MVC, C#,… https://t.co/AopbM10Fz5 https://t.co/IxXCzYoaGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientists: DATA SCIENTISTS Home Depot USA, Inc. Has multiple openings for Data Scientists to formulate and apply mathematical modeling and other optimizing methods to develop and interpret information to assist management with decision making,… https://t.co/aNeqzkyI8N https://t.co/An1LVh7yXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack/Devops Engineer ( https://t.co/u4Dv6f6aiR): Seattle, WA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today *** DISCLAIMER!!! You must be comfortable working for a company that is in the Cannabis Industry*** If you are a Sr. Full Stack Engineer with… https://t.co/Y5o0rMvx8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 12 minutes ago(6/18/2018 9:45 AM) Job ID 23422 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/6j9qNdGcAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Requisition ID 2018-41090 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply***… https://t.co/WlMTuxIFoj https://t.co/QLKcsCIJOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registered Nurse-Continuing Care/PHP-Part-Time: ***This position is 16 hours weekly-2-8hr shifts. You may work at our main campus in Lemont, as well as our Orland Park Continuing Care Office on LaGrange Rd. No weekends. PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES –… https://t.co/sQ5dRwHBNT https://t.co/IjeHagOuMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Applications ERP: Job Description Tracking Code 7253 Job Description Manager/Senior Manager, IT Applications Administrative Services/ERP Reporting to the Director of IT Applications, the IT Manager/ Senior Manager, ERP Applications is… https://t.co/ivAdcygxgY https://t.co/KAPhSkapYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-28685 Location: Minneaplois, Minnesota Design, Development and implementation of critical Mobile application using Restful services, WEB API, C#, .NET Frame work and SQL server. Expert knowledge of ******* MVC,… https://t.co/ZW0kbQzXz2 https://t.co/Lel7jSonpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/31/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/THC1mVJuoa https://t.co/lJipTBzbXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer I, II – .Net: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Worth, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/7/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position is responsible for analysis, codes, tests… https://t.co/26O1H30hAW https://t.co/tSt5z8iUKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/C# Software Integration Engineer: Comeet – Collaborative Recruiting {{*************}} @ {{************}} {{position.department}} {{getLocationName(position.location)}} {{ position.experienceLevel }} {{ position.employmentType }} ID: {{… https://t.co/TO51r2pTR4 https://t.co/uuu3nJLmIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Architect: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/Wgvay1G6Ft https://t.co/0IcHAhyHDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Energy Services – Rhode Island Office: Project Manager, Energy Services – Rhode Island Office Loureiro Engineering Associates has an immediate need for a Project Manager, Energy Services primarily in our Exeter, RI office. Our goal is to… https://t.co/0uKMwXWRwa https://t.co/3g8m3Kc5xI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Specialist, User Experience ( UX ) Analyst: Performs and leads moderate to complex user experience activities that include user research and testing, user journey map creation, information and interaction design Interacts with internal teams and… https://t.co/watbRJPJZ7 https://t.co/jHfqro4xt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Software Developer: C# .NET Software Developer, Willis Towers Watson Job #*******C, Ann Arbor, MI Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Glassdoor – Linkedin – Twitter – Facebook – English – Espaol – Franais (FR) – Franais (CA) – Join Our Talent Network –… https://t.co/YkN0C9RZE2 https://t.co/myQAUOJXrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: ******-Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27673 Location: rolling Meadows, Illinois Strong in Core Java/Spring/Spring boot *Have knowledge on JSON &amp; JSON Parsers preferably Avro *Expertise in REStful Webservices *Cloud – Preferably AWS *Awareness… https://t.co/z4Y6ng6Uew https://t.co/NdAZfMBgWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer .NET/Sitecore: Description RESPONSIBILITIES Lead the team forward with Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployments Continuously improve our release process ******* MVC/WebAPI/Core code investigation or fixes Angular… https://t.co/yKu6FDcj6Z https://t.co/pz9uKshg56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Johnston, Iowa – United States Job Start Date – 07/15/18, Posted Date – 06/26/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Desired Role: .NET Developer Responsibilities: * Working on web/mobile based applications. * The… https://t.co/Bxal9ifE42 https://t.co/GHhPVPugqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer: Sr .Net Developer in Georgetown, US-KY, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/AjvFCOdEs1 https://t.co/tAHOk6ivP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead – .Net: Tech Lead – .Net Ref No.: 18-26267 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania – Expertise in DOT NET Architecture; Administrating and managing both Windows and Web Application using ******, C#.NET and .NET MVC. – Expertise in Relational Databases… https://t.co/87npW2LOOw https://t.co/RhzwZzT8ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Software Engineer Enterprise Content/Data Management C#, .NET, FileNet, DataCap: Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Information Technology Schedule Full-time Description: Position… https://t.co/3z3eo09QXm https://t.co/rEAqa8wZ5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Java Developer: For BNY Mellon Specialist Java Developer job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers – Investor Relations –… https://t.co/ObMpr0Ukb3 https://t.co/rxuP2ONGnz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>