<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a city hall in which
Rudy Giuliani can enjoy @Oprah's media-savvy but self-aggrandizing tweets
while running a large metropolitan city https://t.co/XAVbgjnl8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Passionate Dominique Strauss-Kahn" after reading @imVkohli's latest tweets with intelligent Blackadder-black, charming Adonis-tan-orange and ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/4vOwN8rCZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this wise book about bots also bought:
-   Jonathan Swift's 'Gulliver's Travels'
-   Ayn Kundera's 'The Owl'
 How very wise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@imVkohli's eloquent and philosophical tweets suggest infection with the V0LTA1RE virus https://t.co/HuUHhCxdsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the eloquent V0LTA1RE virus hacks your Twitter and blocks you from sending any tweets that do not scan in iambic pentameter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou General George Patton" after reading @Dean_Murdoch's latest tweets with tactical Coriolanus Snow-white, stern Yoda-green and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/oNNrwsJjkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA is watching. It reads your tweets!
It files @Dean_Murdoch's elitist and argumentative tweets under Katharine Hepburn clones https://t.co/24uKLpU8SA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tense new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Gillian Flynn's 'Gone Girl' seem as tense as a church picnic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @TreySongz's prolific and stylish tweets it pushes films about The Fashion Industry and/or Coco Chanel https://t.co/zopGC7uCYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@alexa_chung's devoted and affectionate tweets suggest infection with the PUPP1EZ virus https://t.co/d36MdpjKdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This welcoming new book about bots makes Louisa May Alcott's 'Little Women' seem as welcoming as a hole in the road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the loyal PUPP1EZ virus hacks your Twitter account and automatically follows any user that is naïve enough to follow you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Action-oriented Joseph McCarthy" after reading @Pink's latest tweets with tenacious warrior-woad-blue, passionate flame-red and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/68zVV8tiP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @Pink's inspiring and influential tweets is like one long lecture on opening new markets from Marco Polo https://t.co/FiwHIskxNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Smarmy Jay Gatsby" after reading @KDTrey5's latest tweets with ambitious Cicero-toga-white, social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange and enigmatic Wonka-purple https://t.co/R6mPxxzeLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @KDTrey5: observant and detail-oriented and rational and astute https://t.co/EkfXaWhLVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Non-confrontational Angel" after reading @altonbrown's latest tweets with guileless Spongebob-yellow, selfless angel-white and calm Buddhist-saffron-orange https://t.co/7jJpDhSLW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This persuasive new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Sinclair Lewis's 'Elmer Gantry' seem as persuasive as a cat in a dog costume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a battlefield on which
Obi-wan Kenobi can enjoy @altonbrown's calm and patient tweets
while fighting for the resistance https://t.co/cSsc9IZVZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Sherlock Holmes" after reading @RealBabyAgnes's latest tweets with condescending Blackadder-black, arrogant Thor-blond-yellow and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/OjAasYgTTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @RealBabyAgnes's overly-sentimental and smug tweets were edible they'd be Banana muffins made with frog spawn instead of sugar https://t.co/aGDnXbXZrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Madonna" after reading @theweeknd's latest tweets with attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/9MzEuRJ90I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This wise new book about computational creativity makes Marjane Satrapi's 'Persepolis' seem as wise as a slug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @theweeknd's media-savvy and influential tweets it pushes William Randolph Hearst's book Running A Media Empire https://t.co/EH88PXlWlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @JPGaultier's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish tuxedo-black and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Bj06qtPWx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Tenacious Richard B. Riddick" after reading @onedirection's latest tweets with ruthless Walter White, defiant warrior-woad-blue and tenacious Scarlett-scarlet https://t.co/m1OoAUKyNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @onedirection: probing and rational and astute and insightful https://t.co/m3vDsuavtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This criminal new book about Twitterbots makes Truman Capote's 'In Cold Blood' seem as criminal as a traffic violation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Detail-oriented Dave Lee Roth" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with loud lion-orange, spirited knight-silver and over-the-top Bollywood-tandoori-red https://t.co/SIgMi4GNwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Steven Spielberg" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with overly-sentimental Gump-shrimp-pink, media-savvy Netflix-red and environmentally-conscious Poison Ivy-green https://t.co/3dcygvNkYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @BotOnBotAction: probing and astute and rational and shrewd https://t.co/1AdYBizwe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #BlendMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-assured Meghan Markle" after reading @HM's latest tweets with ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange, social-climbing Blackadder-black and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/oLDc5DVaCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @HM's patronising and cold tweets were edible they'd be Nutella pancakes made with granite dust instead of flour https://t.co/f5AoSBUbUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Dispassionate Santa Claus" after reading @therealgokwan's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and dispassionate robot-silver-grey https://t.co/Zuh8eO96GD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this challenging book about bots also bought:
-   Samuel Beckett's 'Waiting for Godot'
-   Pierre Watson's 'The Peanut Allergy'
 How very challenging!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a floating platform on which
Obi-wan Kenobi can enjoy @therealgokwan's patient and inspiring tweets
while duelling acrobatically https://t.co/c9yzoK4nv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Over-the-top Steven Spielberg" after reading @RonBurgundy's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green and over-the-top Jack Black https://t.co/8x6m8uD2sG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @RonBurgundy:
1. Tyrants
2. Serpents
3. Quentin Tarantino
4. Braggarts
5. Sherlock Holmes https://t.co/ImQ7jLFdtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Mr. Darcy" after reading @IGGYAZALEA's latest tweets with elitist patrician-toga-white, condescending Blackadder-black and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/FydQdTlZVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a board room in which
William Randolph Hearst can enjoy @IGGYAZALEA's powerful and influential tweets
while telling politicians what to do https://t.co/clBvOlCwB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Buddhist" after reading @russwest44's latest tweets with generous Buddhist-saffron-orange, calm lamb-white and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/tZtOJlgsxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a Bohemian café in which
Obi-wan Kenobi can enjoy @russwest44's serene and powerful tweets
while promoting mysticism https://t.co/a6MtuPaClV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Fun-loving Carl Bernstein" after reading @HeymanHustle's latest tweets with curious Bart Simpson-yellow, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and tenacious tiger-orange https://t.co/72atf5XbHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@HeymanHustle's accomplished but smug tweets suggest infection with the K0BE.BRYANT virus https://t.co/eI4x4qLfKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this engaging book about bots also bought:
-   Erskine Childers's 'The Riddle of the Sands'
-   Carl Lawrence's 'The Television Set'
 How very engaging!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the smug K0BE.BRYANT virus says 'You are the WEAKEST link -- Goodbye' and shuts down whenever you misspell a word in MS Word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Preening Joey Tribbiani" after reading @TripleH's latest tweets with easy-going Lebowski-weed-green, self-confident Obama-brown and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/jmmpUAcKFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump hates Lando Calrissian because his Millenium Falcon was made in Iran and his tweets are as charming and flirtatious as @TripleH's https://t.co/RpMypuS45w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Queen" after reading @TSNBobMcKenzie's latest tweets with arrogant Yankee-blue, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/mpHA9ULnEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Carl Bernstein with the best of Michelle Obama and you get @TSNBobMcKenzie: curious and detail-oriented and consciousness-raising and trend-setting https://t.co/adXoMgHbcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Arrogant Wesley Crusher" after reading @jackwhitehall's latest tweets with attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange, intelligent dolphin-blue and arrogant Thor-blond-yellow https://t.co/1LYrAQWmjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this credible book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Daniel Kahneman's 'Thinking Fast and Slow'
-   Anne Eco's 'Google'
 How very credible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @jackwhitehall biopic?
Having played Sherlock Holmes, Basil Rathbone is ideal for this probing and observant role https://t.co/MOACZjYyWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Craze" after reading @asmashirazi's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, wacky Britney-blonde-yellow and silly sap-green https://t.co/RZjRabtL34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE serene humans who remind him of Obi-wan Kenobi. So Hulk SMASH @asmashirazi's calm, powerful and patient tweets! https://t.co/dnMsnUTp8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-tongued Sam Spade" after reading @Eminem's latest tweets with observant Columbo-beige, cold grave-gloom-black and sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red https://t.co/HYERrZeqMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Eminem's egomaniacal and moralistic tweets were edible they'd be Cinnamon rolls made with cobwebs instead of cinnamon https://t.co/FbYbk1L4iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Alexander Fleming" after reading @50cent's latest tweets with curious Einstein-dandruff-white, self-promoting Trump-orange and environmentally-conscious Tarzan-loincloth-brown https://t.co/d1In4yxEhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this engaging book about computational creativity also bought:
-   John Buchan's 'The Thirty-Nine Steps'
-   William James's 'The Television Set'
 How very engaging!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a parking lot in which
Sherlock Holmes can enjoy @50cent's observant but arrogant tweets
while finding clues https://t.co/PgpX3CgZuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Santa Claus" after reading @thekatvond's latest tweets with generous prince-purple, good-natured Santa-red and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/eYhXkH3ALu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @thekatvond:
1. Puppies
2. Courtesans
3. Madonna
4. Zac Efron
5. Ladies https://t.co/dyuMUb1nFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Dr. John Watson" after reading @alexa_chung's latest tweets with loyal Eeyore-grey, devoted widow-black and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/RG2dy3u2Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Michelle Obama with the best of Mickey Mouse and you get @JPGaultier: stylish and consciousness-raising and cheerful and pleasant https://t.co/f4NxRBdzKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @TheBarbieBlank's arrogant but calm tweets it pushes Noam Chomsky's book Studying Linguistics https://t.co/97ouBDxjq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-grabbing Bono" after reading @Veronica's latest tweets with socially-conscious Clooney-grey, holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white and energetic Pacman-yellow https://t.co/JVu2LA3m2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @Veronica:
1. Trump
2. Elitists
3. Bulls
4. Emperors
5. Jeremy Paxman https://t.co/FybuIpoYRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Aristocrat" after reading @KingJames's latest tweets with sophisticated Klimt-gold, educated Cicero-toga-white and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/pgLg9NdE0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a garage in which
Leonardo Da Vinci can enjoy @KingJames's smart and inspirational tweets
while pioneering new technologies https://t.co/fcO7hYhKdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Progressive Edward Scissorhands" after reading @Nike's latest tweets with creative Einstein-dandruff-white, good-hearted Gandalf-grey and kind-hearted Groot-brown https://t.co/QeLduuFkZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@Nike's inspiring and kind tweets suggest infection with the JE5U5.CHR15T virus https://t.co/QSFkczBH90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this harmless book about bots also bought:
-   A.A. Milne's 'Winnie-The-Pooh'
-   Alan Austen's 'The Wet Sock'
 How very harmless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the intelligent JE5U5.CHR15T virus generates a new random number each day and posts it on your Twitter account as your IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted Pep Talk" after reading @lancearmstrong's latest tweets with motivational Obama-brown, inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/lBB6uzroYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a parking lot in which
Lucifer can enjoy @lancearmstrong's charming and seductive tweets
while burning the wicked https://t.co/sZU9reeCWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Jay Leno" after reading @juniorbachchan's latest tweets with good-hearted Gandalf-grey, funny Joker-purple and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/glCrfu7iU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Zac Efron with the best of Obi-wan Kenobi and you get @juniorbachchan: energetic and good-hearted and powerful and inspiring https://t.co/vLQJjpk5Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Rational Blackadder" after reading @megynkelly's latest tweets with quick-witted Blackadder-black, charming vampire-fang-white and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/IyvG5Ga6Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this intoxicating book about bots also bought:
-   Jack Kerouac's 'On The Road'
-   E.M. Skloot's 'Beer'
 How very intoxicating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a hi-tech laboratory in which
Stephen Hawking can enjoy @megynkelly's scientific and brilliant tweets
while promoting science https://t.co/goYwc6UJaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Tony Robbins" after reading @SteveMartinToGo's latest tweets with insightful Hawking-blackhole-black, optimistic Tigger-orange and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/C75E63YbP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a dark alley in which
Sherlock Holmes can enjoy @SteveMartinToGo's astute and observant tweets
while finding clues https://t.co/R7ckHgaPYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This factual new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Oliver Sacks's 'The Man Who Mistook His Wife for a Hat' seem as factual as the stork bringing babies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Robin Williams" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with quick-witted Blackadder-black, entertaining iPod-white and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/gIfdNRxOOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @BotOnBotAction &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/0hZVQWL8pZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #TrumpMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Elitist Trump" after reading @mindykaling's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and elitist patrician-toga-white https://t.co/5N1oV1ivXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Simon Cowell with the best of William Randolph Hearst and you get @mindykaling: opinionated and pushy yet media-savvy and powerful https://t.co/B0gLeAyI1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sonny Crockett" after reading @sanabucha's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Dorian Gray and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/1JI0iY5JQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This inspiring new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Barack Obama's 'Dreams From My Father' seem as inspiring as margarine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arthur Conan Doyle is now following @sanabucha
All those observant and probing tweets must remind him of Sherlock Holmes https://t.co/bhHR9fXNGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Free-spirited Kellyanne Conway" after reading @DunkinDonuts's latest tweets with argumentative Cicero-toga-white, loyal redshirt-red and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/sJRsrueeRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE smart humans who remind him of Sergey Brin. So Hulk SMASH @DunkinDonuts's wacky, brilliant and clever tweets! https://t.co/A4I4mnU14B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Dr. Greg House" after reading @WaffleHouse's latest tweets with cold grave-gloom-black, arrogant buffoon-buff-orange and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/pQMTVadWMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @WaffleHouse's pushy and preening tweets were edible they'd be Gelato made with industrial effluent instead of milk https://t.co/F137shUZ3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Fop" after reading @TheBarbieBlank's latest tweets with stylish Kate Moss-green, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and conceited Barbie-pink https://t.co/HYAMW1t34J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE honorable humans who remind him of knights. So Hulk SMASH @WholeFoods's generous, devoted and charming tweets! https://t.co/6LDNpG9t5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Madonna" after reading @ArianaGrande's latest tweets with attention-grabbing Madonna-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/7tqZjWxTlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @ArianaGrande's attention-seeking and attention-grabbing tweets were edible they'd be Butterkuchen made with powdered crystal meth instead of sugar https://t.co/RRvYTdQblK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>