<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@daniel_swensen I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saucymincks I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okayshort You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeriesAttic You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElinaSrar You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BennKeezy You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wienerdawgy We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quatoria You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enimmij You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uItrahardcore You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so proud of everything that my friends have done. That means you, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecampo12 The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomensWorkNY I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patheticmeera People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaKPerry Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suc4ke You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomensWorkNY Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JWall7z You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaKPerry You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go look at a picture of your loved ones and think about how much they care about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thelmaniaca You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deciido You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Folletto It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJacksonNM Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you danced today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm. It can be easy to forget stuff in the morning. Did I remember to tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's give it all we've got today! We can do it together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASampleRWBYFan Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarySueSays This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night and sleep tight and have wonderful dreams!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CattyFae We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpsterKitty You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dn_charles You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthecool_Andie I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spookyezra21 You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talyaelaine You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you're feeling a little tired, you're making progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nerdsherpa Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@semiotic_pirate Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kris_keyser Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each one of us possesses more strength than we realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traceyulie You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to be kind to yourself, isn't it? But it's well worth striving for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoolPeanutDream I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuniwaaa You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doomsterfire You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tense? Let your shoulders drop, loosen your jaw, unclench your hands, and take a deep breath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowdyxrah The universe is better for having you in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe space matters. Please care for one another during hard times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGKage You're such a good friend to reach out when you need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Merc_Rustad It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your hands and face need exercise too! Make some silly faces and shake out those hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahunsaker You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swellyn Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shebacr You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SashaDevlin Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're kind to your friends when they get frustrated and sad. Please be nice to yourself too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeptimusReviews You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeptimusReviews The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, you! You look really good today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_sayheykate You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AeeDee You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AeeDee I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raksha You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasra You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@powerupkirby You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you decide for your body is right. No one else knows better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayhaughtearper We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@decertatio You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atvk55 I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinkerbellsway You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Earperdemic I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to offer hugs. Someone probably needs them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinkerbellsway It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miichellefuller I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darwingdotcom You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true that you only live once, but a life of self-care is a happier one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMenedes It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>