<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lidsville: MEMO to all who think it's clever to say those protesting #KinderMorgan pipeline are hypocrites because they use #fossilfuel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a sunny 12-degrees Celsius in Vancouver today so of course half the city's got sandals and shorts on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son and I have an ongoing bet — if Starbucks’ employees ever spell my name right, I give him $40 towards a Nintendo Switch. He’s been waiting weeks. Crushed again! https://t.co/PSBdYimzB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, #ThePush is intense. What a mind f*ck.  But I wouldve told them to pound dirt at the sausage rolls. #vegan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nine-year-old son’s reading @jk_rowling’s Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban. He devoured 226 pages of it today before bringing it to Wreck/Tower Beach for sunset. Spoiler alert: he missed the sunset. https://t.co/T9dmIM6kWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good story. https://t.co/wgQq6xeJ3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajjunop Or 420,000?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fonterrible. https://t.co/boHdxmtVcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend: Let’s go. https://t.co/HXEBdzRnRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior writer. https://t.co/GkC7boDWcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to do these silly interviews with my son. I'm so glad I did.

https://t.co/1ZbQkX9aZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s a lot of procrastinating. #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/eKOSAfBnDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh. I miss this age.

https://t.co/gwBqyAIU1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost $90 to fill up the GTI today. That’s a five-year high for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb long-read in the New Yorker.

https://t.co/ujVoePjM4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kainagata @jkenney I’m not anti-pipeline, I’m pro-coast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe "thermostat" bit would be more accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, Daddy's Home 2 is fairly stupid and I blame my son but the temperature bit was pretty great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatEschner Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatEschner Thanks — not my birthday though!Just lamenting my age. Turned 47 in Nov.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So close to 100%. Realizing how much of my mental wealth relies on pain-free movement. Also, check out my quad. I’m huge. https://t.co/fOqcFpptJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I book all my vacation time for 2018 and then someone calls to try and book me for a job in an exotic location. Why? Why does it have to be so hard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A colleague just referred to this look as a cul-de-sac and my life will never be the same. https://t.co/zeY5HfMFkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @SuzyPatrick! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[47. https://t.co/KK4pv4ib3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes a dude comes and sits right in the middle of your shot. And that’s okay. Wreck Beach — Trail 4 — Vancouver, BC. https://t.co/TzFODxYdug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT He's making my softwood duties so hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old friend has a beautiful place for rent in Split, Croatia. Hit them up if you're heading to their hood...

https://t.co/MmLS0tWFhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More rocks and logs. Wreck Beach — Trail 4 — Vancouver, BC. #Photos #photography https://t.co/wujk1eFSuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youu could not get the tone more perfect if you tried to recreate this a billion times... 

https://t.co/3WR7gOYCYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bunch of rocks and some logs. Wreck Beach — Trail 4 — Vancouver, BC. #photography #photo #ExploreBC https://t.co/tRmlHsoTaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kids love my Dragons' Den impression: "You guys are great. And I think you have a lot of potential. But at this time, the parenting space isn't working out for me. So for that reason, I'm out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew it. | Study says cats would kill you if they were bigger https://t.co/okFtZnSW1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscar party. https://t.co/zA6azOlqm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was supposed to start writing at 8 a.m. Instead I took a look at my son's hiking light, which needs new batteries for our hike in ... July. I couldn't figure out how to open it though, so I did laundry, went to Starbucks and surfed the Internet. 

Starting to write now, at 3 p.m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzbishop I'm comfortable with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the money...
Follow the money...
Follow the money... https://t.co/srWgblF5eC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played. https://t.co/x4xe3fhxFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth a read. https://t.co/T8ExtWMugl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uncanny. https://t.co/uNd3nix6HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you buy stock in Birkenstock?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes @SuzyPatrick and I can't decide on what vegan pasta dish to have for dinner and we have to bring in a carbitrator. 
#thankyou #hereallweek #dadjokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible. These kids must have been absolutely terrified. | BBC News - Indian school bus plunges into gorge, 'killing 27 children' https://t.co/E0b98S0GPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like we're moving to White Rock. #thuglife cc: @SuzyPatrick https://t.co/7xqxbT2QZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, but, the economy ... | How Trans Mountain Project Will Pump Profits to Its Texas Owners  via @TheTyee https://t.co/MFrivQRkuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good. | Molly Ringwald Revisits “The Breakfast Club” in the Age of #MeToo https://t.co/cNLBHJwiMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it true they’re replacing “Wild Rose Country” with “Don’t Mess With Us” on Alberta license plates? #KinderMorgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tragic. We drove this highway in a taxi from Dharamsala to New Delhi in 2012. It was a disconcerting drive... | School Bus Plunges Into Gorge in India, Killing at Least 21 Children https://t.co/OLMMTpytrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why she doesn’t just open worldwide chain of pubs called Arm Bar. #yourewelcome https://t.co/0eMmajOXUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kainagata: Today is not a victory. It's a request from #KinderMorgan for Ottawa to do its dirty work. The statement by oil minister Jim…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: #KinderMorgan shareholders to form human chain to get buckets of oil to market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t believe in polls. https://t.co/sDB7VYvxwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie  https://t.co/FjDsy8Uu4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are going to be pissed when the Sedins announce their summer tour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like @TheNotoriousMMA's next fight will be in court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robinblackmma @TheNotoriousMMA @ufc @YouTube Seems weak-minded on McGregor's part. No room for thuggery in a sport that already gets a bad rap.  What a goon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillAicher Eerily similar to my commercial storyboarding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s true. I’m a hoser mule. I sneak Canucks across the border in the stomach of my tauntaun. https://t.co/A4HZl8IMpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched The Shape of Water. I mean Splash. Mostly meh for me. Also, I might have ruined it for @SuzyPatrick by yelling “Merman ... Merman!” at the end of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pulmyears Nice! Congrats on the book, Paul!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHORT STORY: When I was 17, I passed out drunk on my friend's front lawn. It rained on and off all night. In the morning, someone told me it was the sprinkler. https://t.co/Vuq7Pc7WfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott should write an autobiography just so he can name it MeMoir. 

#youarewelcome https://t.co/3unHPW4xar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KMaximick Congrats. This is a huge accomplishment. Kudos to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Outsider reminds me of the time I went to Japan and joined the gyoza.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't condone chaining bears but this commentary is pretty great. Also, the kid here is going to fight for a UFC title this weekend so it just goes to show, you want to be champ you gotta wrestle a bear in Russia. Or something. https://t.co/0vhCKDkUsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had today marked down on the calendar as first day back from spring break so my son got an extra day of vacation and I continue to be the greatest parent alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever been looking at your phone while lying in bed, only to drop it right onto your face?

Yeah, me neither. https://t.co/PxTuqoLJJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canucks fans bid goodbye to Sedin twins with farewell riot https://t.co/x7jJ6JEGOl via @TheBeaverton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/05WhQuBBR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your motivation for being an unsolicited asshole? https://t.co/w8yVKR4VrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomsonjennifer @canadaposthelps Are you still sending Nickelback fan-mail via post?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ye$. https://t.co/0tSWhqEJ91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benfowlkesMMA April Fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's as good a place to read as anywhere, really. @SuzyPatrick https://t.co/A1IO1XyQc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cue the fairy. #Easter https://t.co/x84uvdgX8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for a run in the forest. If I'm not back in an hour it means I've also gone to Thailand. Sorry kids. @SuzyPatrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're looking at possibly moving to a house in Ladner, so my transition to Ray Liotta at the end of Goodfellas is almost complete. @SuzyPatrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son on his way to the Hipster Academy. https://t.co/gAYPFYZQHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stayed up until 4am this morning watching The Zen Diaries of Garry Shandling. What a lovely tribute. Fantastic work by @JuddApatow and all the contributors. @bobsaget made me cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh sweet baby Jesus this is great... https://t.co/rTVqPFG6xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomsonjennifer I have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climb that goddamn mountain. Mount Brunswick, British Columbia. #photography #photo https://t.co/hv6so7ZqAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPOkenny Left my earplugs in the car so ... yes. It was basically a 90-minute punch to the face. But an awesome punch to the face. Crowd is always entertaining at those shows, too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status. https://t.co/wdp3tbFumn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fun. The writer doesn't get the hand she wants but makes the most of it. https://t.co/oPRf484UgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Daddy! I just farted and coughed at the same time!" 

-- Life update from London, age 9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The median is the message. https://t.co/Spdb9hqBj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter will only fall asleep for me if I’m hugging her. While standing. And dancing. There MUST be dancing. If I stop moving she kicks me with her heel and makes a disgruntled noise, as if to say, “Come on — giddy up.” @SuzyPatrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see you didn't have the foresight to omit "visionary" from your bio...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having all the neighborhood kids over for an Easter Egg hunt on Sunday. 

(April Fools, there are no eggs.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I enjoyed this. Maybe you will, too.

https://t.co/i4dZ56qD6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billgood_news @rodmickleburgh Already is, technically. https://t.co/ZJ5b49ocAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DixonTam I had that phone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet he's got a Canadian flag stitched to his backpack. | Kim Jong Un's China visit may be start of his world travels https://t.co/TJQXQe2oLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But wait -- there's more! Call now and we'll give you a second case of super-resistant gonorrhea at no extra charge. That's right. You get TWO CASES of super-resistant gonorrhea for $24.99 -- but only if you call right now! 

Offer void in Quebec. https://t.co/3Ulgm1LlIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grown-ass woman wrote this. https://t.co/l59hg09E5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robynallan: British Columbians deserve the facts and data to make informed decisions. Ignorance or deliberate misinformation from indus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I randomly thought of this commercial today. It's so good. 

Volkswagen Commercial: Mr. Roboto (feat. Tony Hale) https://t.co/3jah5jmo57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's proof. Hawaii 88. Grade 12. I'm on the left. In the YELLow. https://t.co/nkNI2xOdgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild Wild Country reminds me of my first trip to Europe.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>