<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Communications Project Manager: Crawford Group ( ********************* ) is looking for a Marketing Communications Project Manager consultant for our client located in Santa Cruz, CA. The Marketing Communications Project Manager is the liaison… https://t.co/hNqVmDpW2W https://t.co/LibZ1vwsL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government says it's lost track of some parents: The Trump administration said Friday that it may need more time to reunite the immigrant families it separated. https://t.co/hN1MzxCMo5 https://t.co/PiAP2NAZxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Tech Deals: Breville, Ecobee, Ecovacs, SNES Classic: Plus: Whether your PC needs zippy storage or you want to play your 16-bit Nintendo faves, we've got some deals for you. https://t.co/nXpDiVD5CY https://t.co/uyFrVLL1WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: 109463BR Software Architect CO – Aurora 109463BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems that make the world a safer… https://t.co/qLsHiVyfOL https://t.co/YsXZhtCr9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Management Support Specialist: Req ID 98403BR Business Title Data Management Support Specialist Group MSS Location USA MARYLAND Annapolis Junction Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech… https://t.co/qawHl1Quh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Business Systems Analyst: Job Description Associate Business Systems Analyst Job Number:******* Description If you have talent, initiative, and a desire to join a thriving global company with a wealth of career opportunities, you can make a… https://t.co/pWohE6KkDu https://t.co/O14PVh9U7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Statistical Programmer, Late Stage Development Oncology: Principal Statistical Programmer, Late Stage Development – Oncology – Language – English – French – Worldwide Careers Site – Sign in – Accessibility – Working at Merck – Why Merck? –… https://t.co/ioxWE5IrVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Location: Edmond Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers Jobs About Us: GE is the world’s Digital Industrial Company, transforming industry with software-defined machines and solutions that are connected,… https://t.co/0qy9c2Oc4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network-Administrator: One of our outstanding clients has an excellent opportunity for a talented Network Administrator in Salisbury, MA. This is a permanent, full time position within a business making a difference for the needs of hurt people and… https://t.co/O1fATw7AKw https://t.co/H3WMU90gWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Change Management Specialist-Senior Level: Systems Change Management Specialist-Senior Level Jobs in Everett at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial… https://t.co/1n6IMzc2Sk https://t.co/7OeZ9MkD50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Ref No.:18-13095 Location: Omaha, NE, Nebraska Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/24/2018 Role: Dev-Ops Consultant Duration: 1 Year Location: Omaha, NE Skills Required CI ServerJenkins 2.0 with pipeline as code Version… https://t.co/brf2ktgwUo https://t.co/We8Y1dWHo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff, Software Engineer: Staff, Software Engineer job at E*TRADE – 10526 – E*TRADE CAREERSOpen MenuHide Menu Customer Service Find a Branch ********** Home Why work here Our people Our benefits Career areas Brokerage Corporate Marketing Operations… https://t.co/Gc2AcUjW89 https://t.co/fEXETaLS4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Employer helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers, Employer… https://t.co/nRXxHQWozg https://t.co/k7IoZhDqHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA is on a mission to touch the sun: Humanity's first visit to a star begins this weekend. NASA's Parker Solar Probe will explore the sun's atmosphere in a mission that is expected to launch early Sunday. This is the agency's first mission to the sun… https://t.co/WTPgxIqLNs https://t.co/moFUz6KsxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Web Developer: Propensity Media, LLC. | Front-End Web Developer A Consumer Engagement Agency Digital. Mobile. Social. menu – Contact Us – – Client Login – – Careers Contact Us Client Login Careers Accepting applications for… Front-End Web… https://t.co/IUrzf0UX61 https://t.co/4XDLARwE6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens if we don't deal with superbugs now: In a sweltering room in the corner of the Chatinkha nursery in Queen Elizabeth Central Hospital in Blantyre, Malawi, Lilian Matchaya is expressing milk. https://t.co/trLWS4S4Nq https://t.co/3vliF6sB4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US | Programmer/Developer-Developer / Software Engineer: US | Programmer/Developer-Developer / Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-30634 Location: Maryland Heights, Missouri ***INCLUDE CHARTER VERIFICATION FORM AND PHOTO ID AT THE END OF THE RESUME. NOT… https://t.co/2cSYiEVH2K https://t.co/QvtSwImag0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Analyst: The OTS Division is looking for a Senior Project Analyst who is a highly motivated individual with a combination of business systems and process optimization skills to assume a role within the Division. Ideal candidates will… https://t.co/Rp1g7tnThR https://t.co/RjDdl6Qztr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Verizon Connect is guiding a connected world on the go by automating, optimizing and revolutionizing the way people, vehicles and things move through the world. Our full suite of industry-defining… https://t.co/uHePxNxgti https://t.co/Hvv68542uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afloat Network Engineer: Overview Clearance Level Needed Top Secret Job Duties and Responsibilities: The Afloat Network Engineer is a deployed position that provides underway end-to-end C4I system support on U.S. Navy ships. Acts as the Sr. Technical… https://t.co/koYVqfbQm8 https://t.co/5QNu0uwbKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Ref No.: 18-31546 Location: Cary, North Carolina DevOps Engineer Cary, NC 12 Months contract Job Description: Java developer skills. Familiarity with: Teamcitey, Artifactory (or Nexus), Git, Eclipse/Jboss. Sikuli/Python… https://t.co/8kP82Y2DdI https://t.co/eMjZRMyztG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Programmer III: Job ID 11480 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Information Technology Overview Cures Start Here. At Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center, home to three Nobel… https://t.co/mBxCS2W3re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Remote) Meditech Systems Integration Sr. Specialist: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:11 At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/LqYvZMyuiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time, a woman is in charge of a Marine infantry platoon: First Lt. Marina Hierl is making Marine history... again. https://t.co/bHBtsx01aJ https://t.co/iTAFgLwnYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ABAP Developer: Senior ABAP Developer Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – ABOUT US – Our Company – Our Employees – Total Rewards – Employee Wellness – HOT JOBS – Accounting/Finance… https://t.co/AYOmRdnqD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks is getting into the kombucha business https://t.co/OSGZPmY58P https://t.co/cN7hxVCxji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer:  Position: Senior Software Engineer  Company: Estrada Consulting  Location: Sacramento, CA with required travel to client locations throughout the USA     Estrada Consulting Inc has openings for the following positions: Senior… https://t.co/0cZoWEskIP https://t.co/R1WKV5gNWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP – Principal, Developer – Java: Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior technical… https://t.co/XZeAUYTbSY https://t.co/yoaHhzISuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Upton flaunts husband's World Series ring: Watch as Kate Upton tries on her husband Justin Verlander's Houston Astros World Series ring. https://t.co/DKheWCn8VU https://t.co/Mu1schAadn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Delivery Manager: Job Title IT Service Delivery Manager Job ID(Requisition ID): 3603 Job Summary No calls, CV/Resumes will be accepted from outside firms. Applicants should apply directly online to be considered for this position. We are open… https://t.co/DRatULupTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Specialist: Careers Center | 2018-3197 Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/MuJvTTvKhm https://t.co/XDuc5MOctB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Supply Chain 2:   Job Description – Mgr Supply Chain 2 (18012884) Mgr Supply Chain 2 Requisition ID : 18012884 Location : United States-California-Manhattan Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/mHdFU9LycT https://t.co/599XFdEZuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager TS/SCI Hawaii: Requisition ID 2018-39827 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides technical, administrative, and operational leadership to… https://t.co/V84p2eNZyk https://t.co/j9FJDVCz1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Caldwell Community College and Technical Institute is currently accepting applications for the position of: Systems Administrator Qualifications: Associates degree in programming, computer science, or technology related field… https://t.co/jG3YNCR0ce https://t.co/1mUsJh5Xpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are these elected officials so afraid of the voters?: A democracy should be responsive to the will of the people. https://t.co/HN0Ejkw4pf https://t.co/bhk9DwwSNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Note 9: Price, Specs, Release Date: The newest version of the oversized Samsung Galaxy Note smartphone has arrived, stylus and all. https://t.co/THJaf6UTX2 https://t.co/1NysobkE6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What went wrong with MoviePass: CNN's Frank Pallotta explains how MoviePass went from the talk of the entertainment industry to running out of cash in under a year. https://t.co/qgtvfupQUT https://t.co/ILzxRP4zrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer – Clearance Required: Requisition ID 2018-37215 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT), a… https://t.co/s4qXjsfGqe https://t.co/q8eBCH3l2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 07/18/2018 Location Seattle Washington United States Job Description With more than a century of experience, Boeing’s knowledge in bringing innovative service solutions to… https://t.co/jSnnGV0rLJ https://t.co/VzvnMfmwsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of eCommerce Development $250k: Philadelphia, PA Full-time $200k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Director of eCommerce Development with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the… https://t.co/X7vQfoNlFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Note 9: How to Watch Live Stream, Date, Start Time: Samsung's big summer show, Galaxy Unpacked, kicks off today. Here's how to tune in. https://t.co/J9rnm7jWUd https://t.co/XZm6pytyVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect – Amazon Web Services: Job Description Solutions Architect – Amazon Web Services Location: US-IL-Chicago Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Job Description Do you like helping customers implement innovative cloud… https://t.co/IzMTeOFWYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: Alexandria, VA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Role: Systems Engineer (direct hire), salaried plus benefits Location: Alexandria Skills: AD &amp; Exchange, VMWare *** Sorry but we can only consider US.Citizens because you will need to… https://t.co/yHFjVGfvND https://t.co/7Z0k6QazE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Lifecycle Management Solutions Architect: Division Information Design Group is a leading Engineering, Systems Integration, and IT consulting firm, capable of providing complete operating solutions for consumer products, life sciences, and other… https://t.co/w7QQFudkbm https://t.co/B95iCLwswX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-34301 Location: Chantilly, Virginia Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for Project Manager in Chantilly, VA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me… https://t.co/bdnDgKoK2A https://t.co/MafYqOdkvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TECHNICAL LEADER QA: What You’ll Do The Cisco Data Center Group (DCG) provides next generation data center and cloud management solutions with its Application Centric Hybrid Cloud Management platform, Cisco CloudCenter. Lead by the some of industry’s… https://t.co/NGStkrUO4u https://t.co/1nHRM52n8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo Smart Display Review: Google Shows Off: Google Assistant finally gets a screen, making it an ideal kitchen companion. Our full review of the 8-inch and 10-inch models. https://t.co/Ltzzq3PLOd https://t.co/6omy4F9dwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Analyst (Mortgage Servicing): Requisition Number 18-0080 Date Posted 7/9/2018 Title Senior Analyst, Mortgage Servicing Systems City Mt. Laurel State NJ Description POSITION SUMMARY: Responsible for and support of a diversified array of… https://t.co/QIoD3Nmz35 https://t.co/KlTWlnTBKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-31508 Location: Englewood, Colorado Job Responsibilities: Develop, implement Stored procedures, Functions, and Triggers using Microsoft SQL Server Review and interpret ongoing business report requirements Research… https://t.co/ju1etis01Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Range – Chief of Operations: Job Description IBM X-Force Command Cyber Range Chief of Operations. Leadership role in managing the Cyber Range. Expectations are building, facilitating, organizing, marketing the major customer experiences and… https://t.co/NthjA4sIt3 https://t.co/JKe9B7AQi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CISB-IT Sect-Systems Engineer: Job Description The Systems Engineer reports to and receives work direction derivatives from the Project Manager. The Systems Engineer will perform the following duties: ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES – Administers,… https://t.co/wekH8DaC5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Project Manager: Lead Project Manager Launch innovations in nearly every commercial and defense aircraft platform Leads key, complex engineering program(s) &amp; projects and/or strategic business process development &amp; execution. May lead a matrix team… https://t.co/ckWudv2SyQ https://t.co/twJJ03N1dP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher picks up tab for Keith Urban: A retired New Jersey teacher helped a man who was short on cash, only to discover it was country music singer Keith Urban. https://t.co/U2t91jHjhc https://t.co/aoTA46O1N9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/kw1TBdqO2S https://t.co/ka8ly1ovLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look inside 'The Brady Bunch' house: The granddaughter of "The Brady Bunch" house owner gives a tour of the iconic home now that it's on the market. https://t.co/pIpp6kdoX9 https://t.co/JXLO2O5rWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moto Z3 Play Review: Unlocked and Loaded: Motorola goes all-in on Mods and glass with its new Moto Z3 phones. Our full WIRED review. https://t.co/gTfmRCoEiW https://t.co/u4JICFIDOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethical OS Helps Tech Startups Avert Moral Disasters: A new guidebook for tech companies helps them imagine future scenarios where their tech might end up causing societal harm. https://t.co/uuIKVU7VfC https://t.co/0EAoQMPpF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Analyst: Requisition Number 18-2330 Title Sr. Data Analyst City Herndon State VA Description SUMMARY: The Senior Data Analyst will be responsible for oversight and execution of all operational reporting with the Product Development group. In… https://t.co/TxvhM6g1xk https://t.co/AJqFg7TErk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hailstorm left 2 animals dead, 14 hurt at zoo: Chunks of hail the size of golf balls rained havoc on a Colorado zoo on Monday, shattering windows, damaging cars and sending animals and humans running for cover. https://t.co/D01Vz3Rj0e https://t.co/oqpQBISHY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Operations Analyst: Job Description Customer Operations Analyst (WD***********) What you will do Under general direction, works in concert with the Area HVAC Installation Operations/Sales Leadership and Area HVAC Installation Managers, Project… https://t.co/OHwjD5cm7d https://t.co/SDA4ko7ly6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: IT Project Manager :18-02800 Ref No.: 18-02800 Location: Pleasanton, California Akraya is looking for a IT Project Manager for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Ajay at… https://t.co/xCC5hRK6zd https://t.co/gjwot0hKId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator – Heavy Civil: Bellingham, WA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Heavy Civil Estimator Job Location: Bellingham, WA We are seeking to hire an experienced Heavy Civil Estimator in Bellingham, WA. The Estimator is responsible for… https://t.co/RrmjCDMgib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Incident Response Lead: Recruiter BAE Systems. Location Boston|New York|McLean|Raleigh|Fort Lauderdale|Denver|Atlanta|Chicago|Los Angeles|Dallas|San Francisco|Colorado Springs|Milford Salary Competitive Posted 31 Jul 2018 Closes 29 Aug 2018 Ref… https://t.co/zNSbX9GhZc https://t.co/f8xXrSzNRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to save $1 million in your 401(k) https://t.co/OpBv9wtXx5 https://t.co/OZG1xaNsB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Testing Software Engineer: QA TESTING SOFTWARE ENGINEER RESPONSIBILITIES * Develop platforms focused on the development of test plans and regression tests of all components, ensuring comprehensive test coverage. * UI automation and testing. * Validate… https://t.co/91KKd8185g https://t.co/AFONrAS3VB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Android 9 Pie: The 5 Best New Features: Here are five key features from Android Pie, which was released today. https://t.co/jDoIicqTex https://t.co/RQ7Nedm2CE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo customers lose homes after glitch https://t.co/Ac7lXm2BgZ https://t.co/g44fA5AS5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business-System-Analyst: Business System Analyst Populus Group seeks a Business System Analyst in Beaverton, OR to provide computer business systems analysis and support; design, and develop system applications on various information technology platforms… https://t.co/PBEbR1Ir0U https://t.co/pIDnoccnEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44 people shot in 14 hours in Chicago: Chicago police records show 44 people were shot on Sunday, including five who were killed. https://t.co/mt1yIO86EU https://t.co/PUXO9Zb8Au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Wixom, MI, United States Here we grow again! Hexagon Metrology, Inc., part of Hexagon Manufacturing Intelligence, has a career opportunity for a Project Manager in Wixom, Michigan. This is an exciting opportunity for… https://t.co/ZMspNsYKAf https://t.co/kp5vhLHTmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: Senior Embedded Software Engineer Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77762BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible Yes Position… https://t.co/2szhCf9W3x https://t.co/nMAt0diM8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway: I don't believe journalists are the enemy: White House counselor Kellyanne Conway said Sunday that she does not believe that journalists are the enemy of the people. https://t.co/p9ZsvciSHj https://t.co/XxtwFf3ec1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular Developer: Angular Developer Ref No.: 18-33652 Location: plano, Texas Angular Developer Plano, TX 12 months contract Job description – Solid experience of Angular 2-6, HTMLS, CSS, JavaScript. – Create custom, general use modules and components… https://t.co/1QpDkryDKL https://t.co/ennIUb8HCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PeopleSoft Technical Solutions Modeler/Developer: Manages the interface development, unit testing and deployment and integration of technical solutions for the IPPS-A project. Provides data models from business systems planning and data requirements… https://t.co/a4hA5C8QVe https://t.co/SPLSdxz3Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR TECHNICAL ANALYST II: Job Description Join a diverse and dynamic team that makes and delivers the most valuable services in the world: electricity and natural gas. At Consumers Energy, our customers are at the heart of everything we do. Our employees… https://t.co/mekpJITO7y https://t.co/7wnITSmbd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Analyst (Professional Services): A global professional services firm seeks a Senior Analyst to join their dynamic team. Responsibilites include the following: Analyzing historical data, modeling fee arrangements, coordinating approvals… https://t.co/j4IJpv4Rbu https://t.co/ttOPKjUEFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position Title PLC Technician: Requisition ID 2018-12450 Division Kerry Position Type Full Time Recruiter ME1 Posting Type LI Posting Type CB Company Overview Want a job you can feel good about? Leading to better encompasses everything we do at Kerry,… https://t.co/Hf09sJjaG6 https://t.co/1OiI8GGlsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Specialist- Headquarters Operations Support: Sr. IT Specialist- Headquarters Operations Support ================================================== Req #: ******Location: Springfield, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance:… https://t.co/H0d1XHv2V9 https://t.co/sANlAwACwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Curriculum Developer: The Product Education Specialist is responsible for the design, development and facilitation of product training programs for the Experian Decision Analytics (DA) sales team. In this role, you will work regularly with… https://t.co/25ht06R67c https://t.co/u10TYpmuED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRM Platform Development Manager: We are seeking a CRM Platform Development Manager to join our expanding Commercial Technology team in Lewisville, TX. Reporting to the Director of Software Engineering, this role manages Cardinal Health’s new Patient CRM… https://t.co/MDoWkN1kuO https://t.co/QVPpWwx6ZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Applications Developer: Excellent Full Time Direct Hire role with a rapidly growing company in the Transportation industry. Must be local to the Detroit area and a not require sponsorship. * Great company culture, collaborative team, and casual… https://t.co/beIhNPsUyL https://t.co/XE1QeLpae1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS devops Architect: AWS devops Architect Ref No.: 18-29696 Location: Bothell, Washington Role: AWS devops Architect Location: Bothell, WA Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required: Strong exp. with AWS devops engineer. https://t.co/9tyg0dpRpV https://t.co/3cRep1kH69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-29664 Location: Mount Laurel, New Jersey Position: Project Manager Location: Mount Laurel, NJ Duration: 12 Months – Experience in managing large projects in Retail banking space – deployment planning, release… https://t.co/hUbRIRAHmp https://t.co/sECSZoItie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Software Engineer II job in Merrimack, New Hampshire, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans –… https://t.co/NF3JHKzyK1 https://t.co/ukrEj7eMyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They ate raw centipedes, then headaches struck: After two people in Guangzhou, China, were admitted to the hospital with headaches and other neurological symptoms, doctors pinpointed an infection with a unusual backstory: They had eaten raw centipedes,… https://t.co/kmhdGYmAsd https://t.co/5Z2J4CsbNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketplace Support Analyst- Small Commercial Insurance: – Location: Whitehouse Station, New Jersey, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: July 6, 2018 – Position Title:Marketplace Support Analyst- Small Commercial Insurance – Company Name:Chubb… https://t.co/9XyD3LEFFs https://t.co/jNlVYBn3no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator:   Job Description – Systems Administrator (17008527) Systems Administrator Requisition ID : 17008527 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance available Clearance Type: Secret… https://t.co/eGTF44tDvQ https://t.co/FiRSCYa4m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/gw37tR68ol https://t.co/LQK6zdjshk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family scrambles as scooter catches fire: A man pulls his daughter to safety as an electric scooter catches fire while charging in the family's living room. https://t.co/jqynNUDvhm https://t.co/5I1jxe8D16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-33165 Location: Pleasanton, California Job Description: Scrum Master 12+ Months Pleasanton CATechnical Skills: Rally,Jira,Microsoft Project, MS Office, Scrum Extensive Experience Leading Data warehousing Projects in… https://t.co/eW1R0vjaTu https://t.co/Koc0tZOT2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INFORMATION SPECIALIST I’S: University of KansasMedical Center – Information Specialist I’s in Kansas City, Kansas Responsible for full-stack development &amp;computer programs associated w/resource scheduling of scientific equipment, project tracking… https://t.co/IUD4lW5YlG https://t.co/hb3rEIPfrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer I #AZ0208: IT Position Multiple positions available in Irvine, CA. https://t.co/mNWLiF8m83 Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Software Development Engineer I, Job Code AZ0208: Design, develop,… https://t.co/BKt3WeIicu https://t.co/1nBd6yVOh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horse-riding, gun-owning Democrat shakes up Idaho race: Paulette Jordan gently nudges her horse into the Idaho field, her yellow riding gloves loosely holding onto the reins as the sun begins to set on the nearly triple-digit temperature summer day. The… https://t.co/6Q9lWCTQSe https://t.co/IzMFeLdkEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member Of Technical Staff: ENGINEER: Aquantia seeks Sr Member of Technical Staff in San Jose, CA to co-design product &amp; develop manufacturing processes &amp; test strategies. Send resume w/ad to 91 E Tasman Dr #100, San Jose, CA 95134. Attn:… https://t.co/E7wkYjSF2d https://t.co/4r99HiCEa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web QA Analyst: Web QA Analyst sought by RGB Systems dba Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Complete QA test planning &amp; test execution. recblid ov7o1kr61ybhrb5tpo9sfk71uiteoh https://t.co/PFGZ3eGC8b https://t.co/hR3BHk3PZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer Responsible for design and development of software for user interface, database artifacts, data interfaces and application programming interfaces for various modules; must have a Master of Science… https://t.co/Q2bhGYs2dH https://t.co/Su5IXNiAsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Programmer Analyst, Systems Engineer: Computer Professionals Multiple Openings – for Senior PositionsOm Tek Inc., Irving TX Software Developer, Programmer Analyst, Systems Engineer, QA Analyst at Irving, TX. Provide Advisory,… https://t.co/Y9d8YwADTr https://t.co/fINIvY27nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DJI Mavic Air Review: The Drone to Buy: Packed with automated features that make flying and filming fun and easy, the $800 DJI Mavic Air is our top pick. https://t.co/3jj2lD1X61 https://t.co/VNQuZWzz38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Job Description PSI Title: Data Scientist (Analytical Methodologist) Work Location: DC – Washington Description This position located at Bolling AFB supports the development and application of analytic methods within the process of… https://t.co/d1IlJZNVEB https://t.co/XCfafJKnyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Software Developer – Lead: Openings – About – History – Leadership – Events – Products – DataARCH – DocZone – REnDER – RSuite – Services – Solutions – Careers – Benefits – Testimonials – Employment Information – Contracts Our Openings… https://t.co/cz3Fv4CLFN https://t.co/6ONmUxf6t1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>