<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[China's August industrial profits up 9.2 percent year on year, slowest growth since March: Profits earned by China's industrial firms in August rose 9.2 percent from a year earlier, slowing for the fourth straight month with growth nearly halving from… https://t.co/shhp3Vh9Go https://t.co/3Ek3ISLOtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keppel, SPH offer to buy rest of Singapore telco M1: Keppel Corp Ltd and Singapore Press Holdings Ltd (SPH) said on Thursday that they have offered to buy the remaining shares in Singaporean telecom operator M1 Ltd that they do not already own. https://t.co/NcB40H68V0 https://t.co/93xh6R0NGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent &amp; Alibaba chase remittances in battle for Southeast Asia: For Chinese tech giants Alibaba and Tencent, Southeast Asian domestic helpers in Hong Kong may prove key to their global ambitions in financial services. https://t.co/xblERFdVHy https://t.co/TVK4Zb2XGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst II- Rev Cyc: Job Description Job Title: Operations Analyst II- Rev Cyc Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Revenue Cycle Department: Rev Cyc Systems Support Location: 2… https://t.co/TPlQ0N7gNM https://t.co/4z4XOuwdXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Intermediate: Software Engineer – Intermediate in Pittsburgh, PA – UPMC Toggle navigation Login – Career Pathways – Nursing – Allied Health Professionals – Physicians – Advanced Practice Providers – Professional &amp; Administrative –… https://t.co/8D8JlC1MoF https://t.co/oujPDxHq2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swiss startup SEBA raises funds to build crypto bank: Swiss startup SEBA Crypto AG has raised 100 million Swiss francs ($103 million) to build a bank offering cryptocurrency services to companies and investors while extending traditional banking services… https://t.co/Ksa1t4M9rP https://t.co/cCwcnlundp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darktrace hits $1.65 billion valuation after latest funding round: Cyber-security firm Darktrace said on Wednesday it has raised $50 million in its latest funding round led by European private equity firm Vitruvian Partners LLP, valuing the company at… https://t.co/t0MXhvJTDH https://t.co/pOln3VpMON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. judge sides with CFTC on virtual currency oversight: A federal judge said on Wednesday that virtual currencies meet the definition of a commodity and fall within the jurisdiction of the U.S. derivatives regulator, allowing the agency to pursue fraud… https://t.co/VsJlwRrfxS https://t.co/oWfjxLc2PI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon turns to toys, home goods in latest brick-and-mortar trial: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc on Wednesday said it is opening a general store in New York City that will sell toys, home goods and a range of other products that were highly rated on its… https://t.co/Mn2Fc8HHRO https://t.co/mxVFVJU8Cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge sides with CFTC on virtual currency oversight: A federal judge said on Wednesday that virtual currencies meet the definition of a "commodity" and fall within the jurisdiction of the U.S. derivatives regulator, allowing the agency to pursue… https://t.co/IgMs4oY14U https://t.co/aBORV38OEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon to open new retail store in New York City in latest brick-and-mortar push: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc on Wednesday said it is opening a store in New York City that will sell products ranging from card games to skillets that are highly rated on… https://t.co/o4IuxUbOEl https://t.co/HKAc1bbfK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. fintech startup Stripe valued at $20 bln in latest funding round: Payments startup Stripe said on Wednesday it has raised $245 million in funding, better positioning the company to expand to new markets globally and attract bigger customers. https://t.co/y6ZVret5gn https://t.co/KmnqudtnBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peugeot invests 80 million euros in electrified gearboxes: union: French carmaker PSA Group will build electrified gearboxes in eastern France for a new generation of hybrid vehicles, in an 80 million euro ($94 million) investment with supplier Punch… https://t.co/klHVGBDswi https://t.co/HQySoKDA53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber settles for $148 million with 50 U.S. states over 2016 data breach: Uber Technologies Inc has settled with the top legal officers in all 50 U.S. states over a massive data breach that the company failed to disclose in 2016, resolving one of the more… https://t.co/y70ecZ947i https://t.co/1fiK4qv9xN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency giant Bitmain chooses Hong Kong for IPO: Bitmain Technologies, the world's largest designer of products used for mining cryptocurrencies, confirmed it was bringing its IPO to Hong Kong in what will be an important test of institutional… https://t.co/XEFAOSRiDE https://t.co/4SvpZv65xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhatsApp co-founder Acton flags tensions with Zuckerberg: Forbes: WhatsApp co-founder Brian Acton had disagreements with Facebook Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg and Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg over monetization of the messaging service… https://t.co/cBBQQPIOaK https://t.co/yoOx3yi87y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Softbank's ARM unveils dedicated chip design for autonomous cars: Driverless car features are moving closer to mass-market production, with British chip designer ARM introducing the first in a new line of safety-hardened processors for building features… https://t.co/8Z9tZfXZCs https://t.co/FYMuXHmBkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Echo customers face issues in Europe: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc's Echo smart speakers faced outages in the U.K. and some other European countries on Wednesday, according to outage tracker https://t.co/dVx4RE7iq9. https://t.co/JTtSa1OtUf https://t.co/T1obSGwfkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook, Google to tackle spread of fake news, advisors want more: Facebook, Google and other tech firms have agreed a code of conduct to do more to tackle the spread of fake news, due to concerns it can influence elections, the European Commission said… https://t.co/XgbHu7wvXB https://t.co/iO0aTl6Xeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Uber executive disciplined last year after probe into office conduct: WSJ: Uber's head of corporate development, Cameron Poetzscher, was disciplined after a probe found he had a pattern of making sexually suggestive comments about other co-workers,… https://t.co/wEUV1zMMHj https://t.co/wbmYCLeaqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WPP merges Young &amp; Rubicam with its digital ad firm VML: Advertising group WPP said on Wednesday it was merging Young &amp; Rubicam, the U.S. agency it bought in 2000, with digitally focused VML to offer clients a broader range of creative and data-driven… https://t.co/7AD2kmZ7KU https://t.co/2HlXQ1sHLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook, Google agree to tackle fake news: EU: Facebook, Google and others have agreed voluntary measures to tackle fake news due to concerns they can influence elections, the European Commission said on Wednesday, a move intended to stave off more… https://t.co/hp5vcOGeo5 https://t.co/JfKYoCtDkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Uber executive disciplined after probe into office conduct: WSJ: Uber's head of corporate development, Cameron Poetzscher, was disciplined after a probe found he had a pattern of making sexually suggestive comments about other co-workers, the Wall… https://t.co/c64vlPEoHq https://t.co/2I5shgAH1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: JPMorgan in talks to lead Lyft's IPO - sources: JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co is in talks about leading Lyft Inc's upcoming initial public offering as an underwriter, after rivals Goldman Sachs Group Inc and Morgan Stanley decided not to pursue such a… https://t.co/uAOcZxbtNB https://t.co/dXXYrIRfW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech companies agree to measures to tackle fake news: EU: Tech companies have agreed to measures to tackle fake news and concerns that it can influence elections, the European Commission said on Wednesday. https://t.co/lnAqQtfHQx https://t.co/3IesRyA7yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 34703BR Domain Engineering Services Skillset Systems , Electrical Systems Country USA State / Region / Province Pennsylvania Work Location Erie, PA Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys –… https://t.co/oU6bMkxWM8 https://t.co/H1nLlN5DhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: RGP is a global consulting firm helping some of the most recognized companies in the world work differently. Our success comes from a shared belief in rolling up our sleeves and doing the hard work of solving complex challenges, executing… https://t.co/0bDYidMORj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal Audit Programmer/Analyst: Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority Serving Bucks, Chester, Delaware, Montgomery, and Philadelphia Counties – Getting Around – welcome – service – schedules – fares – parking – maps &amp; stations – system… https://t.co/3K8LcHL7NG https://t.co/4K2o9nn2zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer/Engineer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the… https://t.co/v4kbBka1oo https://t.co/ZDCsE7fSp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce, QA Engineer III: Job ID : 75315BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With… https://t.co/5rTCynR6r7 https://t.co/nxNNfyw9AL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer/Support – CICS MQ, API, COBOL, JCL: Job Description Specialist Developer/Support – CICS, DB2, MQ, API, COBOL, JCL The Global Institutional Accounting and Risk Solutions Information Technology team is seeking an experienced Specialist… https://t.co/kAB6OfuWMz https://t.co/25a1aeih8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Dept meeting with state officials focuses on data privacy: A U.S. Justice Department "listening session" with state attorneys general on Tuesday focused on protecting consumer privacy when big tech companies amass vast troves of data, but… https://t.co/IHfLXKh94t https://t.co/lL6jNIWBbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to acknowledge privacy mistakes as U.S. seeks input: Leading internet search engine Google will acknowledge that it has made "mistakes" on privacy issues in testimony an executive of the Alphabet Inc unit will deliver to a U.S. Senate committee on… https://t.co/idRYseVlB7 https://t.co/b8bY1fcPyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple shaves cost from displays in newest iPhones: analyst firm: Apple Inc shaved some parts from the display in its largest new iPhone, helping keep costs under control in what has become the priciest component of its phones in recent years, according… https://t.co/13KiN1mL3u https://t.co/Efs8UyCFiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google will acknowledge prior 'mistakes' on privacy: Senate testimony: An executive from Alphabet Inc's Google unit will acknowledge the company has made mistakes on privacy issues in testimony to be delivered to a U.S. Senate committee on Wednesday,… https://t.co/BMLyfp070x https://t.co/6E3PHJBPO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Developer: Job ID : 60953BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description Sr. Software Developer – Commercial Applications When you’re part of the team at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll do important work, like helping… https://t.co/SaRP9ZbZqA https://t.co/5WAkXyuCMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Intern: Performs data analysis and statistical modeling, using advanced statistical and computer techniques while working with experienced departmental staff. Develops statistical models designed to enhance business decisions. Areas of focus… https://t.co/3t7NQBzBCb https://t.co/hsL7ccTn8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department meeting with state officials focuses on data privacy: A U.S. Justice Department "listening session" with state attorneys general on Tuesday focused on how the government can safeguard consumers online, the Justice Department said after… https://t.co/hRclhpls4U https://t.co/W6c0UC1UuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst (Wireless and CSM): Sr Business Analyst (Certified Scrum Master) Only US Citizen and Greencard (Contract To Hire Opportunity) Inperson Interview A Must Primary Skill: – Recent BA experience required. Insurance and Wireless (Cell Phone)… https://t.co/Y3RqgWMxiE https://t.co/djO2vioutT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify, Deezer and others call for stronger EU action against U.S. rivals: Music streaming services Spotify and Deezer joined European business and industry bodies in calling on EU regulators to take tougher action to curb what they say are the unfair… https://t.co/Vv8POijUqv https://t.co/PRup4fYHH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No class action for unhappy Uber drivers: U.S. appeals court: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] won a legal victory on Tuesday as a federal appeals court said drivers seeking to be classified as employees rather than independent contractors must arbitrate… https://t.co/D9wHcfy37A https://t.co/Da5gYSRfEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Department meeting with state officials focused on data privacy: A U.S. Justice Department "listening session" with state attorneys general on Tuesday focused on how tech companies handle user data and whether privacy issues can be addressed… https://t.co/ZrUGJW2oHO https://t.co/JcP5OZDZfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China-backed Byton to work with Bosch on powertrains, brakes: Automotive supplier Bosch is to team up with Chinese-funded electric vehicle startup Byton in the areas of powertrain, brake and driver assistance systems, Byton said in a statement. https://t.co/dXZWs8b0OU https://t.co/o5Dz1ChtQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. seeks input on privacy rules to protect consumer data: The U.S. Commerce Department on Tuesday said it was seeking comments on how to set nationwide data privacy rules in the wake of tough new requirements adopted by the European Union and… https://t.co/APPPKpb7YH https://t.co/Ml1H7gZYOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber can force drivers into arbitration: U.S. appeals court: A federal appeals court on Tuesday granted Uber Technologies Inc's request that drivers be required to use arbitration to pursue claims made in three lawsuits that they were misclassified as… https://t.co/TwUGCsAvAQ https://t.co/S7Rs5vs14P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google ends cryptocurrency ad ban: CNBC: Alphabet Inc's Google has joined Facebook in ending a ban on advertisements for cryptocurrencies, CNBC reported on Tuesday. https://t.co/Zn3FivKVI5 https://t.co/efS8FHjURI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook shares slip after Instagram founders quit: Shares of Facebook Inc fell more than 2 percent in early trading on Tuesday after the two founders of photo-sharing app Instagram left the social networking giant under unexplained circumstances. https://t.co/pYNYxdHVvd https://t.co/OgE4xnopc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm accuses Apple of stealing its secrets to help Intel: Qualcomm Inc on Tuesday alleged that Apple Inc stole its trade secrets and gave them to Intel Corp with the goal of improving Intel's chips so Apple could replace Qualcomm's chips, the latest… https://t.co/JmGJXoo5od https://t.co/4sZ8AYveJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram departures hit Facebook shares: Shares of Facebook Inc fell more than 2 percent in early trading on Tuesday after the two founders of photo-sharing app Instagram left the social networking giant under unexplained circumstances. https://t.co/JSkLNE8w9f https://t.co/04vXidcirM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Engineer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the… https://t.co/ViFRbENOkz https://t.co/k1Wi5GZxte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In latest change, Uber launches 24/7 phone support in Britain: Uber on Tuesday launched a 24/7 telephone support line for its users in Britain, in the latest change the taxi app has made to meet the demands of regulators. https://t.co/oduHsxBbnK https://t.co/SrmJHVuoz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Manager of IT-Web Portals – PITT: Team Manager of IT-Web Portals – PITT Ref No.: 18-00675 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a… https://t.co/ZPeXm2RMlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany's Merkel says EU battery cell production 'extremely important': It is "extremely important" that the European Union develop its own battery cell production to secure its role in the automotive industry as it shifts to electric mobility, German… https://t.co/kzOiiUzcZn https://t.co/ElPVrewQQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Entry-Level): Job Information: Software Developer (Entry-Level) – ******* Job Email Opening Title Software Developer (Entry-Level) – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon University is an Equal Opportunity Employer/Disability/Veteran.… https://t.co/UANuyMJ0fD https://t.co/M2rCbzk4VR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A swipe is not enough: Tinder trials extra control for women: The Indian edition of dating app Tinder is trialing a new feature which gives women an additional level of scrutiny and security before they allow men to start messaging conversations, with a… https://t.co/5XLrJBUdDq https://t.co/gcfkkIVERf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASP. Net with Azure Cloud: ASP. Net with Azure Cloud Ref No.:18-03871 Location: Chester Brook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery… https://t.co/wEErI7dvkR https://t.co/Od2rrwWVKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Professional Services Manager Advanced Technology Services: Senior Professional Services Manager – Advanced Technology Services in Pittsburgh, PA – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join… https://t.co/K9n1wPjaKL https://t.co/DxGuhHK2zU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram co-founders resign in latest Facebook executive exit: Instagram on Monday said co-founders Kevin Systrom and Mike Krieger have resigned as chief executive officer and chief technical officer of the photo-sharing app owned by Facebook Inc, with… https://t.co/TVzgIXNUUy https://t.co/m8RkHOXpcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX (Frontend) Designer: UI/UX (Frontend) Designer What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a difference, both in small and large ways, is our passion. At… https://t.co/9PkSptDkFI https://t.co/QKPXIcvsFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Department to discuss consumer protection at social media meeting: The U.S. Justice Department said on Monday it will hold a "listening session" with officials from more than a dozen states on Tuesday to discuss consumer protection and the… https://t.co/WscD0KGYas https://t.co/U8kzAdF9U9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Dept to discuss consumer protection at social media meeting: The U.S. Justice Department said on Monday it will hold a "listening session" with officials from more than a dozen states, including nine attorneys general, on Tuesday to discuss… https://t.co/mUBgBsCOkP https://t.co/VRz9qocYBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer Spring, Hibernate, IBM MQ, Active MQ): BNYM Technology has a mission to provide our business partners with technology based solutions that enhance their ability to be successful through world-class software solutions maintained on a… https://t.co/wkrpdXs6AE https://t.co/xRFcXXDU8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Senior Software Engineer: Translates and develops requirements into workable software solutions. Maintains and develops programs for use in business and IT automation. Incorporates various accepted methodologies to design software and… https://t.co/3aQjX9JpbO https://t.co/DNUoEyeCEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla is making its own car carriers: Tesla Inc is building its own car carriers, as the electric carmaker faces vehicle distribution problems. https://t.co/SAS8DNVpxo https://t.co/faV0gU2MD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avvo settles New York probe, to reform lawyer ratings: New York's attorney general on Monday said the lawyer review website Avvo agreed to reform its rating system and improve disclosures after a probe revealed shortcomings in how it presented… https://t.co/rjmXAV3rO7 https://t.co/CAFHrkdIyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart, Sam's Club to put food products on blockchain: Walmart and its unit Sam's Club said on Monday leafy greens suppliers will be asked to implement real-time, farm-to-store tracking using blockchain technology by next September, as the retailer… https://t.co/mHhFRApCh9 https://t.co/cRbAPRuJio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK watchdog considers fining Tesco Bank over cyberattack: Sky News: Britain's finance watchdog is considering fining the banking arm of Tesco Plc more than 30 million pounds ($39 million) over a 2016 cyberattack, Sky News reported on Monday. https://t.co/YZyhQwuXpt https://t.co/2VYoxiwS2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat ties up with Amazon for point-and-buy: Snap Inc said on Monday it is testing a new way to search for products on https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 through its Snapchat app's camera, allowing users to shop directly using the messaging app. https://t.co/SYDEzNZu7Q https://t.co/4xCBdGObjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook not protecting content moderators from mental trauma: lawsuit: A former Facebook contract employee has lodged a suit against the company, alleging that content moderators who face mental trauma after reviewing distressing images on the platform… https://t.co/gqkZFx21W0 https://t.co/3y0jN68myG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride-hailing firm Careem purchases Commut app: United Arab Emirates-based ride-hailing app Careem said on Monday it has acquired Commut, the Hyderabad-based mass transportation app. https://t.co/aL2rHATQsf https://t.co/3NS04ZG2gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple completes deal to buy Shazam: Apple Inc has completed the acquisition of music discovery app Shazam, it said on Monday, weeks after the European Union approved the deal. https://t.co/UvKIyhdp83 https://t.co/l8US8d1ylF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP, Microsoft and Adobe announce data alliance: Business software companies SAP, Microsoft and Adobe said on Monday they were forming a data alliance that will make it easier for clients running their applications to get a better overview of the customer. https://t.co/PqCZFgCYPW https://t.co/yBsm1X3Drh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-Mobile revamps prepaid brand to spruce up image: T-Mobile US Inc said Monday it is renaming its prepaid brand to Metro by T-Mobile and adding two new unlimited phone plans that will include perks like Google One cloud storage and Amazon Prime, in an… https://t.co/uWUna3f5Lc https://t.co/vR7UYrsU85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple, Salesforce team up to bring Siri to more business apps: Apple Inc and https://t.co/qByMsGkcTf Inc are entering a partnership in which the iPhone maker will help Salesforce build the iPhone maker's features such as its Siri voice assistant deeper… https://t.co/hx26qOql8L https://t.co/sfX5eKLuBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's strongest growth comes in depressed Argentina -- minus commissions: Uber's fastest-growing market in the world is now Argentina, company executives say, attributing the expansion to the nation's sudden economic unraveling, which has boosted… https://t.co/UIWavXtws9 https://t.co/zduBFNhxqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer PITT: Senior Java Developer – PITT Ref No.: 18-00637 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile… https://t.co/PMp0w5Nmjz https://t.co/5w3gs4YQi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contact Center Online Banking Technical Support: Contact Center Online Banking Technical Support Williamsville, NY Candidates need to have open availability to cover shifts between the hours of 8:00am to 9:00pm Monday thru Friday and 9:00am to 5:00pm… https://t.co/jzAuMdUH8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ride-hailing firm Careem enters India with Commut app purchase: United Arab Emirates-based ride-hailing app Careem has acquired Commut, the Hyderabad-based mass transportation app, marking its entry into India, the firm said on Monday. https://t.co/QadLc267BG https://t.co/psuXTzx4CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice Operations Manager: 09-Sep-2018 Voice Operations Manager Enterprise Operations California, Colorado, Connecticut, Florida, Georgia, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Texas 450590BR Demonstrated experience in team leadership Demonstrated experience in… https://t.co/jeNQtZz78p https://t.co/HVAc5drMAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure IoT Architect / Data Engineer:   Job Description – Azure IoT Architect / Data Engineer (41037) Job Description  Azure IoT Architect / Data Engineer-41037 Description   Azure IoT Architect / Data Engineer About Hitachi Consulting As Hitachi, Ltd.'s… https://t.co/V7PWEqFqe6 https://t.co/8woqn2Rdjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The night a Chinese billionaire was accused of rape in Minnesota: With the Chinese billionaire Richard Liu at her Minneapolis area apartment, a 21-year-old University of Minnesota student sent a WeChat message to a friend in the middle of the night. She… https://t.co/N9mqKdtMog https://t.co/vxOsj5ShTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home modems, routers hit by U.S. China tariffs as 'smart' tech goods escape: U.S. tariffs that hit some $200 billion worth of Chinese products on Monday spare many high-profile consumer technology items such as "smart" watches and speakers, but the less… https://t.co/MCjd2pwiK9 https://t.co/1rXURvf65D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore competition watchdog fines Grab, Uber $9.5 million over merger: Singapore's anti-trust watchdog fined ride-hailing firms Grab and Uber a combined S$13 million ($9.5 million) over their merger deal, and ordered Uber to sell vehicles from its… https://t.co/GXf3AsPKFM https://t.co/8rC96EnE0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore competition watchdog fines Grab, Uber $9.5 million: Singapore's competition watchdog fined ride-hailing firms Grab and Uber Technologies a total S$13 million ($9.5 million) and announced other measures to address competition concerns arising… https://t.co/PoXWgbqWHG https://t.co/iWlofM2VZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's Flipkart may appoint new group CEO in place of Binny Bansal: Mint: Walmart Inc's Flipkart unit is considering naming a new chief executive officer (CEO) at the group level in place of Binny Bansal, the Mint daily reported on Monday, citing two… https://t.co/9EYsuRbkoK https://t.co/uXww1ibBDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist, Strategic Planning (Data Analyst): The Specialist, Strategic Planning (Data Analyst) is responsible for working in conjunction with business units, support groups and technology teams to define and build out the data repository and data… https://t.co/TgtekAYCqY https://t.co/s1VYBedpDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Testing Analyst (Unix/Linux/ Shell Scripting): Develops testing plan scenarios for complex unit, process, function, integration and acceptance testing with a focus on automation Responsible for definition, planning and execution of… https://t.co/PUDkw0nhnL https://t.co/IOTkU73ZB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key companies to attend White House quantum computing meeting: The White House will hold a meeting on Monday on U.S. government efforts to boost quantum information science, with administration officials, leading companies including Alphabet Inc, IBM… https://t.co/LEuVyRuBrY https://t.co/4ivH7EqDqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global advertising expenditure to grow 4.5 percent in 2018: Zenith: Global advertising expenditure is predicted to reach $581 billion at the end of 2018, with most of the growth coming from sponsored content in search engines and social media ads,… https://t.co/zjCi6W9sdZ https://t.co/D0xz9hJs1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global spending on digital marketing nears $100 billion: study: Spending on digital marketing grew by 44 percent last year in the United States and Britain to $52 billion, a study has found, estimating that global outlays on such tactics are approaching… https://t.co/JkvKqBsIjA https://t.co/aKhvOkog0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell revisits IPO option amid tracking stock deal pushback -sources: Dell Technologies Inc is exploring an initial public offering (IPO) after shelving this option earlier this year in favor of going public by buying back a special type of stock from… https://t.co/w6ykcKFEI6 https://t.co/2F8XplIXZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead Artificial Intelligence: The Center for Analytics and Insights IT is looking for an expert engineer that is well-seasoned in implementing and developing data science IT solutions. The chosen candidate will partner with the Center for… https://t.co/NX3Zb2oFIm https://t.co/XnHcApsMhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Careers | Aramis Interactive – Home Careers Come join the Aramis team! We place a strong emphasis on our company culture and work environment – firmly backing the work hard, play hard mindset. We absolutely love what we do! We… https://t.co/hqmnQmi6Nt https://t.co/j2Kd4bdU70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell to interview banks for IPO instead of acquisition: WSJ: Dell Technologies Inc plans to interview banks this week to potentially go public through an initial public offering rather than doing so through a proposed acquisition that has drawn… https://t.co/p7fHXPxmYi https://t.co/Z81gpbsqZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-Leg Tech – HARR: Programmer Analyst-Leg Tech – HARR Ref No.: 18-00673 Location: Camp Hill, Pennsylvania We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a… https://t.co/2TJ6t60C5f https://t.co/vJ4n4yYfIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media Group… https://t.co/eA56WfJ0Fe https://t.co/6SCTDuxvDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Intermediate: Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Intermediate (Cardiology/Neurology) Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Information Services Department:… https://t.co/WNzZZp9hxp https://t.co/St5YXPWYEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Siemens CEO pushes plans to boost Iraqi power infrastructure: Siemens said its boss Joe Kaeser met Iraq's prime minister on Sunday to discuss a proposal by the German company to expand the Middle East nation's power production. https://t.co/ifUa8hHcLt https://t.co/n7SoLSyeXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Coatings Recipe Administrator: Apex Life Sciences is looking for an Data Entry Admin! Main Activities/Duties/Responsibilities Data Entry Administrator will be responsible for data entry of formula, processing instructions and quality… https://t.co/vSdQ7rP7mg https://t.co/ll33wyFaMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN SUPERVISOR PHYSICIAN OFFICE GI LATROBE FULLTIME: The RN physician practice supervisor assists the practice manager with the daily supervision and coordination of clinical services provided to the patients in the physician practice. She is responsible… https://t.co/5mWUYYLc30 https://t.co/ovvK0K1vxu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>