<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/1Rb0E43d0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/1fPFXF8PIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/gGtUd4sBaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/PKeM9Mzjo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/O1NkdlriyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/on9cv2tBq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/9t7XgRBdRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/8VYHwfJ0Un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/1tpjNYbnly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/9hEJXCgqDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/cZ2kKVLgDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/zI5QWpiLcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/ElUlnW3pEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/0gvjnBP7Qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/TaxRMhv6fM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/zUBdKcLkke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/7dIhITdZsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/cmAfpN2oIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/bnVKPbDVHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/G6yoEnHcWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/qqyPlY0glF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/USCLLGbt9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/FOPvCuMU7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/eg3QenlCjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/dz8LZXRP0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/9jBRDeHSVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/imUnWAt2G1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/8JYpPnvUg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/5U0qEDwNid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/ZHkekRaGnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/GTJqs9wGXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/AwDF2EevDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/oyXdSFpTiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/qh8gVgy1sK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/cZ2kKVLgDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/Prm6HZpne7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge : " Your wife charges that you haven't spoken to her in  5 years. Why is that?" Defendant: "I didn't dare interrupt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/GWUxZvpDx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/TOP0TrKOkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/mZcBhw5mhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/xN0THXoBJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to think about big things while you're doing small things, so that all the small things go in the right direction. Alvin Toffler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/EHafdUIctD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/30PURhnbWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/slHszczI6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/TaxRMhv6fM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedestrian is someone who thought there were a couple of gallons left in the tank. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/UnmidXcPjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that when things seem to go wrong, stay calm and wait till you see the bigger picture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/ohCtuqaFM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/U0WjiRHEQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/qmxoG7bcju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/86b2OvgNBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/38b1anTTdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/PAQW5c4cW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/MjavCbxJRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/BNIYoKUuli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/F4Uark14f6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>