<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tom_Gatti Great.  But I'd also love John Jeremiah Sullivan to turn his essay on Michael into a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent from @TonyBarber8 on how the EU's rebuke to Poland lays bare east-west tensions in the bloc https://t.co/dl4emct8Mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see @leorobsonwriter on the 2018 Man Booker judging panel https://t.co/oX25QXfslI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoyed @SoulJazzRecords' screening of Ted Bafaloukos's wonderful 1978 film 'Rockers' last night. Here's the trailer https://t.co/pvMNeev8zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rbrtrmstrng: A+ kook/nerd battle.
This round goes to the nerd. https://t.co/N056dKwpfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empiricism and the scientific method vs Lysenkoism in the letters page of the @FT this morning https://t.co/1VdwjFC5h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Year in a Word: Dotard  https://t.co/AORchR09vM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinwolf_ on inequality, pluto-populism, and threats to democracy https://t.co/o37jj8Kquv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece by @davidtorrance on how tax changes have set Scotland on a new course https://t.co/CApfP9mA3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's new aircraft carrier is leaking. But, as @LawDavF argued in @ftcomment last week, procurement squabbles are tributaries of much deeper questions about what the UK armed forces are for https://t.co/rrYFrM8M68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just what you want on your morning commute: Streeck on Anderson in the @LRB https://t.co/jPhGGpjrdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We mustn't give up on Ukraine, says @TonyBarber8  https://t.co/OUyGHRGadL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bernard_Spitz: Pour les entreprises européennes, il y a pire que le “no deal #Brexit”: le flou total d’un gouvernement britannique qui…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ANC has voted for self-preservation, says @davidpilling https://t.co/IPZVUVGMad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loveless loyalty to Theresa May comes at a price for the Tories, says @JananGanesh https://t.co/B4wxW8gyVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the first two entries in the @FT's Year in a Word ('Maybot' and 'Xi Thought') here https://t.co/wOJGWMakaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European businesses demand clarity on Brexit, says @medef's @Bernard_Spitz https://t.co/TyE1i5PMZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DianeCoyle1859 on how the public sector can harness platform technology to deliver essential services https://t.co/zpMO9kqzwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent review by @danielsoar in which he wishes @BananaKarenina would start writing essays again https://t.co/QdEPfSdMHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent column by @gideonrachman on why economics is one of the moral sciences https://t.co/hOPdk7353K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rbrtrmstrng: logical positivists have no idea how bizarre they appear to the rest of us https://t.co/p0W9O7Uzmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign up to the FT Opinion daily email, featuring me, @SebastianEPayne, @greenmiranda &amp; @frederick65 https://t.co/4fceW9uaIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrudaSpruyt @nickbarleyedin @RetfordLT @edbookfest Wonderful novel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the ANC leadership contest goes to the wire, worth re-reading @davidpilling's column from last week https://t.co/DLS5HeE36n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: Before the UK leaves the EU...

After 15 months of data...

Brexit has cost Britain roughly...

£350m a week

https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmmanuelMacron: Je travaille pour les Français, beaucoup de mesures ont été prises dans le pays et pour le pays. #MacronJT20HWE https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting take on net neutrality and the power of Big Tech from @RanaForoohar https://t.co/I1vqPCHhXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Elif_Safak on #catperson for @ftcomment  https://t.co/14868WBwO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawDavF: My attempt to stir the pot a bit in today's FT. Britain faces serious questions on its defence capability https://t.co/FOHdEL1…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmerich_mike: Manchester aims for integrated transport system via @FT
 https://t.co/0o55DHVTct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sindap: Did Rupert just disown James here? https://t.co/nCSsSwrmrs https://t.co/5QqCDIEd4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JeanBirnbaum: Vu dans les toilettes de l’Ecole des hautes études en sciences sociales, dite @EHESS_fr. https://t.co/5r7xpJ2285]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splendid obituary by @MADarbyshire of Simeon Booker, civil rights pioneer and journalist https://t.co/Cbz9kiwZIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olivialanguage I loved CWF. So intelligent - and funny, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Sinfield was one of the people who made Sussex English so exciting in the late Eighties and early Nineties https://t.co/zSkN6ENCh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all the @FT's commentary this week on the dizzying pace of technological innovation in one place https://t.co/zFPs8HqtGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essential reading from @alexebarker and @GeorgeWParker: inside the UK’s messy deal to secure an amicable divorce  https://t.co/30mISYrZ7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HamishH1931: Remembering Max Sebald https://t.co/7cTsttVbLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain has been mugged by reality on Brexit, says @martinwolf_ https://t.co/593Hq2QDcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacobHeilbrunn: As always @EdwardGLuce makes journalism great again. Another prescient column: https://t.co/uUYzfUb2Ba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good column by @rafaelbehr on the limits of Labour's constructive ambiguity over Brexit https://t.co/BtPulIQOrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@rodrikdani's essay on globalisation is a stirring plea for the primacy of politics https://t.co/L0f2yZGpBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akiwudon: I present to you.... Kamaal Williams on Black Focus Records. Support independent music @yussefkamaal https://t.co/nYGAnw39Cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanshainin A tautology surely? That which is objectively real exists *by definition*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahoconnor_: After 3 years, this is my last day as FT employment corro! From tomorrow I will continue to mine the rich seam that is t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@fromTGA makes the conservative case for a common European home https://t.co/uT9QEbZIO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @FT's Person of the Year is Susan Fowler https://t.co/nIz9jl07Ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sarahoconnor_ on false choices between productivity and unemployment https://t.co/yUEpxKOuvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating column by @johnthornhillft on the dawning of Pax Technica and the political challenges that lie ahead https://t.co/q3od4EYkwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnmcternan: A guide to the excellent food available in my manor https://t.co/XtnFe0CbdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPittBrooke I thought he was astonishing today. Second half as false nine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/FvO3oBj2kt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belatedly enjoying Sally Rooney's sharp, smart and very funny novel https://t.co/IaHRObkSKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gideonrachman: A certain confusion in Brexiter ranks this morning. Daily Mail commands it readers to "Rejoice!" because "we're on our w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tconnellyRTE And second, @fotoole's analysis of the fate of hard Brexit https://t.co/h0PVj7FZda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two excellent pieces in the Irish media on the week just gone: first, @tconnellyRTE's riveting tick-tock  https://t.co/HctIRILNpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChassNews @FT I have to say that I prefer "la tenue d'Ormesson" in those photos ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHarford He's right, you know. Pulled The Spire down from the shelf and soon came across this passage https://t.co/gDFsyTmNMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant column by @TimHarford on what Golding's The Spire tells us about Brexit https://t.co/klFl0pxhP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent @FT big read by @muradahmed on @ManCity's business model https://t.co/Ldp3UllYon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnharris1969 Yup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DulwichHamletFC: We’re working closely with the @IsthmianLeague to get this resolved as quickly as possible, however punishing the club…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnharris1969 Absolutely. The NME was also the first place I encountered the name Jacques Derrida. Ended up studying with him in Paris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnharris1969 First jazz record I ever bought - it, along with Kind of Blue, always made it into the NME's top 100 albums https://t.co/g5YsDC7Pc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathancoe @NewStatesman I adore Rendell, though. Those albums he made with Carr in the mid-60s are inexhaustibly rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathancoe @NewStatesman And he's inspired me to put this - from 1976 - on the turntable https://t.co/uTokvX0KEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see @jonathancoe paying tribute to Neil Ardley (&amp; other luminaries of 60s/70s UK jazz) in @NewStatesman https://t.co/bMBlYJtwvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nybooks: “The couples live in Tarbox. Come. It is in places marshy. There are trees, lawns of fine description, bodies, houses like the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sarahgor and @PickardJE explore Labour's evolving relationship with business https://t.co/V191SNCggq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: Brexit: Watch the Swiss border for a warning on trade https://t.co/sFnNR0AATF via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belatedly reading The Sparsholt Affair. Hollinghurst's 1970s Chelsea has a delicious, pungent whiff of mid-period Murdoch and early Amis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lemondefr: Macron qualifie de « regrettable » la décision de Trump sur Jérusalem https://t.co/N2fclUCsqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good: @johngapper on the new economy and the "antitrust paradox"  https://t.co/5XVW5NjkYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyTassell: Here is the video of Davis in June: "I don't make guesses .... we make those based on the data .... we've got 50, nearly 6…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CER_EU: UK govt did not make a formal quantitative assessment of economic impact of leaving customs union before it made that decision,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Un home resté l'enfant qui faisait le rêve tout bleu de Nashville" - Macron on "Johnny" https://t.co/TStZpPXHH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May's Blue Monday | by Fintan O’Toole  https://t.co/ukSCtoD1Cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH It is Jubilee Crescent, built in 1935 https://t.co/PC90ieh5Vt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Obviously, Manchester Road comes before Trinity Sq in second set. Intrigued by housing at Mcr Rd. struggling to find info online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Second set (clockwise): the Thames at Island Gardens; Victoria Park; Trinity Church Square; Manchester Road, Isle of Dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Clockwise: Greenwich Foot Tunnel; Isle of Dogs (Manchester Road); Smithfield Market; Robin Hood Gardens, Poplar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnauthers: WORTH READING: Stop worrying about Chinese debt, a crisis is not brewing https://t.co/eMojXb45nq via @FT Case against an i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Access, SE22 https://t.co/llvTZCohS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHale_ Trinity in Trinity Square, off Borough High Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @econbuttonwood: Time to recall this extraordinarily prescient piece https://t.co/XBg1aBKR76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PickardJE: who'd have thought it would get this complicated? https://t.co/aKFW4To2wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WWTht8i1ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day off, so took a dérive on two wheels through east and southeast London https://t.co/WVxLkyGy6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @areasvellas: ...building Eero Saarinen´s TWA terminal at jfk airport New York 1960
photos by Balthazar Korab... https://t.co/rG6niLJAgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @alexebarker is right, we might be better advised to look to 1961-3, rather than 1971, for clues as to how the Brexit talks will pan out. Excellent @FT Big Read https://t.co/nEU0ZfNf6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RanaForoohar gives the Republicans’ faith-based tax plan both barrels https://t.co/cEEUuvb3zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An arms race in AI is the last thing we need, says @kaifulee  https://t.co/DnLb96ihcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£50bn doesn't buy you much these days, says @EuroBriefing  https://t.co/KQnwQzd0u0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CER_Grant: My piece in @FT: Brexit is like accession in reverse, the EU sets the terms and Britain has to take them if it wants a deal.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @martinwolf_: Martin Wolf: The world economy hums as politics sours https://t.co/4DLqJFrnVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamfleming: Spokesman for @EU_Commission on David Davis “no deal” letter: “we are surprised that the U.K. is surprised that we are pre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenbarrett Natürlich https://t.co/dLi9dFLCgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenbarrett  https://t.co/IpEkBf4Qcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftbrussels: David Davis attacks EU’s ‘damaging’ no-deal Brexit planning https://t.co/ZqywV9U4tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BGPrize: We're partnering with @frontlineclub to launch 'Thinking Allowed', a new event series in which our speakers tackle questions o…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>