<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/brHQYO711W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the Cecil B. DeMille of science fiction. - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/kiCTCrO3Dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/D9aQii3Ipl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/XlzCqV3A0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/MdGRt7tp6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/iDS0IJxptU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/PTvDA3Ub8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/tkpMBbdubo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/2ZjBLr7bee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/GttBeYpHyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/7uLL6meLgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/gCFAbbd81U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/RoMwpj5RKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/B8n9XC6cHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/r5eu9CC7XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/ZscBERoFcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/HTR0i1fEPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/t9uYk8fHT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't tell how much spirit a team has until it starts losing. - Rocky Colavito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/C3eGlgJu3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/Ku2RGC8St1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/ok4mXeu1wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/mHZDkZx1Cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/5qhiLtFP65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/G83Xw8r6gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/zsnq790F0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/Dzu7UAs0qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/Cu507rRPSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/tTaCVUXMIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/Zn7rgavn4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/BBtlBOpLkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/CFppjNGtFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/5CSoX0mJKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/hpXe0eBdUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/6DUiQd0Vrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/hVNo5zsZKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/iBZv5739XZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/5HSmaBpNVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/05EF66UsYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/NefYeRr8yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/gINVw6TsXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/ENfpGwrDV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/0Hf0jUTsNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>