<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java developer: Jobs Toggle navigation – Sign In – Sign Up – Help Career Portal – Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully – Position… https://t.co/hZu4nuMjOA https://t.co/CTzNExyVcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer: At NTT DATA we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees have been key factors in our company’s growth and market presence. By hiring the best people and… https://t.co/c0ElMx6JlB https://t.co/WRRO1IyHZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The medieval code no one can crack: Naked women in pools of green liquid, strange looking plants, and text written in an unknown alphabet; they can all be found on the delicate parchment pages of a mysterious manuscript from the 15th century. And nobody… https://t.co/kp1TYcCG9B https://t.co/osmllC0v1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/JEE Technical Lead: Job TitleJava/JEE Technical Lead – ID:31769 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsJEE framework LocationPlano, TX Date Posted05/21/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of us direct, referencing the… https://t.co/ieMLQmb3MB https://t.co/9mu296oU0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer: JAVA Developer | Marathon Consulting MENU – About – About Get to know who we are – Approach See Why We’re Different Right from the Start – Leadership The Vision Behind Everything We Do – Marathon Gives Back We are Committed to Our… https://t.co/S70q5BvLes https://t.co/8DswqD50L0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyoncé and Jay-Z drop joint album: Beyoncé and husband Jay-Z released a joint album, "Everything Is Love," on his Tidal streaming service. The couple also released the first video off the album, "Ape S**t," which according to a rep for the project was… https://t.co/KtF38GpbFD https://t.co/yBklmdPkQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer in Springfield, Missouri, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/WWcGRaBfAt https://t.co/BjwTOqWaS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-23136 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey JAVA J2EE EJB 3.0 Spring WAS 8.5 – Excellent experience on Java 1.7 – Excellent work experience on complex EJB 3.x – Experience on Websphere Application Server – Experience… https://t.co/FPmdqs9Mkt https://t.co/oDsB9e8VWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Technical Lead: To provide senior level IT technical lead services, including the direction, evaluation, selection, configuration, implementation, and integration of new or existing technologies and tools. This position is for an NGA technical lead… https://t.co/guCKhgLrz5 https://t.co/0cl9cqBw4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Jersey City, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 05/23/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsFull TimeOverview Title:- Java Developer Location:- Jersey City, NJ Salary:150k per annum Candidate should… https://t.co/mIf5cDIstJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer III: Java Developer III Richmond, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Java Developer – 8 openings Interviews: 12-2 PM starting 5/16 running through 5/31 Duration:… https://t.co/fCwjsAeR8c https://t.co/Ntet2ovrf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Web Engineer: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/1yVbYPUVMx https://t.co/5gCh2yMEf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack developer with Spring and React JS: Java Full Stack developer with Spring and React JS San francisco, California – United States Job Start Date – 05/29/18, Posted Date – 05/29/18 Primary SkillsSpring,React,Full StackTax TermsC2COverview… https://t.co/jKSteLHroM https://t.co/jfQ7YzihHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer Engineer with JMS, JDBC, Spring framework, Hibernate, Oracle, Tomcat and Anuglar: BDC is a clearance and settlement platform handling government securities mandated to replace GSCX as a service provider in this domain. BNYM clearance… https://t.co/rDlwAGzxtt https://t.co/qHqEbQmLe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer with Full Scope Poly: Req ID: 20883 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market… https://t.co/dimF98YDN5 https://t.co/Q4pyuqWBUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java/J2EE Developer Ref No.: 18-22239 Location: San Diego, California Role: Java/J2EE Developer Location: San Diego, CA Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required: Java/J2EE, Spring, Hibernate, SQL, REST, DevOps Tools https://t.co/4rECbomiPx https://t.co/SpdBglolxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News books wrong guest, rips Trump: Producers for the Fox News morning show, "Fox &amp; Friends First" meant to book Arizona congressional candidate Ann Kirkpatrick to discuss her pro-ICE views. Mid-interview, the show realized that the woman speaking on… https://t.co/42qw70lDvJ https://t.co/sAuRMT8wPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSA leader creates task force to fight Russian cyberattacks: The President might have claimed that Russia stopped hacking the US, but intelligence officials know otherwise -- and they're stepping up their fight against the ongoing threat. Recently… https://t.co/2cENhDCkx8 https://t.co/cBW7rx69dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Development Lead: ITC Java Development Lead Zachary Piper Solutions is currently looking for a Java Development Lead in Springfield, VA to work with an established business solutions provider to coordinate and lead cloud-based software development… https://t.co/r9qTZ9AN10 https://t.co/pnIrARGFA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27980 Location: Deerfield, Illinois Job Details:- Position : Java Developer Location : Deerfield, IL Type : Contract (12 Months) Skills Required:- Good knowledge on JAVA/J2EE and JAVA Webservices. Thanks &amp;… https://t.co/7HqI8Jlj6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer (Java / AWS): System One is seeking a Senior Software Engineer who can design software systems solutions and lead software development teams in implementing those solutions for customers. The candidate will have demonstrated… https://t.co/Miwf6bK5ZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher asks: Is a longer life a happier one?: One of the biggest questions in ageing research is whether there is a ceiling on how long human beings can live. https://t.co/xuCNTN4GaW https://t.co/NO2kQsWLjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CORE JAVA DEVELOPER: CORE JAVA DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-29331 Location: Richmond, Virginia 7+ years of Core Java development experience using J2EE Must have experience with working with Micro Services Must have experience with service implementation using… https://t.co/y96s2yWaPI https://t.co/q2JufIA8FQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right away.Your… https://t.co/YVSU5EggZy https://t.co/EckualFV2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Requisition ID 2018-41137 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description ***ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply***… https://t.co/0QHKgvTTHj https://t.co/wDdjw4PbIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Java Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Laurel, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Full-Stack Java Developer Key Role: Work independently to design, code,… https://t.co/XIg11rIXj5 https://t.co/u0aUhSWjQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Services Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Web Services Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Web Service Developer who is responsible for the web services… https://t.co/IBP0XU8mMt https://t.co/weCNtuisu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer (Production Support ): Job Details ************ – Home – About – The Company – Our Team – Why Sayva – Solutions – Sayva Consulting – Sayva Financial – Sayva Technology – Sayva Accounting Services – Careers – Search Open Positions –… https://t.co/NeHey8o7bq https://t.co/udNUFZAIua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Applications Developer – Lead: For Siemens Java Applications Developer – Lead job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – –… https://t.co/XnjXYHOd8j https://t.co/JKl54JcBMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java lead: java lead Ref No.: 18-27471 Location: o fallon, Missouri JOB ROLE:-JAVA LEAD Location: O Fallon, MO POSITION:-Contract Key skills required for the job are: Microservices-L3 (Mandatory) JAX-RS – Java API for Restful Web Services-L3 Spring… https://t.co/rtQaeEbaBN https://t.co/xRxyvLA5PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic governors set to take on the bigger names in 2020 race: A handful of Democratic governors are wading into the early stages of the 2020 presidential contest. https://t.co/C2lEabwBNM https://t.co/OEVsNCwZ08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer with frontend experience: Senior Java Engineer with frontend experience Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover… https://t.co/m97hFzF1gA https://t.co/OLabjFUrzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer IV: Java Developer IV Philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 07/16/18, Posted Date – 06/26/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: Middleware Java Developer Location: Philadelphia, PA Duration: Contract… https://t.co/Diz0DdjoyR https://t.co/rsUa3W0c5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-40141 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Researches, designs, develops and/or modifies… https://t.co/y5pmjuiIEl https://t.co/y5102H7Ysm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP Principal, Developer Java: Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior technical… https://t.co/cm3WSD9jNA https://t.co/Xz3enpBKyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other fatal duck boat incidents: Thursday's sinking of a duck boat in Missouri isn't the first time trouble with the tour vessel turned fatal. At least 39 people have died in duck boat accidents in the past 20 years. https://t.co/HqVJmhjRhK https://t.co/4xV5KppvUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – Java / AngularJS: Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support.’ Proficient software development skills with the following:’ AngularJS, Java,… https://t.co/EFnjm7iGvJ https://t.co/znnyRYTqzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer – Mid-level: Job Description Full Stack Java Developer – Mid-level Provides Java application software development services or technical support in situations of moderate complexity. Has thorough knowledge of the Software… https://t.co/zWzmtQaP7D https://t.co/y8nhYO76dF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot Senior Java Engineer: Project Description Our program was started as the migration of the financial instruments trading legacy mainframe system to a new technical, highly-scalable platform. The success of the program in both the migration and… https://t.co/MKgo4XBGlD https://t.co/fg5n1TcKuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2 – JavaScript: Software Engineer 2 – JavaScript | Asurion Careers – Why Asurion? – Departments – Corporate – Customer Solutions – Device Repair – Supply Chain – Technology &amp; Product Development – Work At Home – Job Listings – Why… https://t.co/xIAu1ouK3r https://t.co/t4l4H9aJ7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaky ceasefire restored after Israel and Hamas exchange fatal fire: Hours after violence flared between Israel and Hamas for the second time in a week, prompting renewed fears that Gaza could slide quickly into an all-out war, reports that a ceasefire… https://t.co/0Ow4Vbaisw https://t.co/rm3CB3WA5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Java: 18302BR Job Description and Requirements Did you know that Synopsys acquired Black Duck Software? Together we help organizations around the globe secure and manage open source in their applications and containers. Open… https://t.co/SLPENPsw9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java API: Java API Ref No.: 18-27904 Location: Mountain View, Virginia Java API – Angular JS-L3 (Mandatory) – JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services-L3 – Amazon Web Services – AWS-L3 As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of… https://t.co/XF5tanYeiH https://t.co/bv5p2OXE5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Star Wars: The Clone Wars' to return on Disney's streaming service: The original run of Star Wars: The Clone Wars ended after five seasons and a bundle of "Lost Missions" episodes on Netflix, but now the CGI series is coming back. Today at Comic-Con… https://t.co/VazaRGqoJW https://t.co/XpDr5nS92S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Java Developer: We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Front End Java Developer, interested in joining our team in Arlington, VA and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Plans, conducts and… https://t.co/KqTR2kQR7A https://t.co/FjctHzR3g3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML: Sr. UI Software Engineer – Java, JavaScript, GWT, CSS, ReST, XML Tracking Code ******* Job Description At Micro Focus, everything we do is based on a simple idea: The fastest way to get… https://t.co/E4kLdWptrp https://t.co/UiaYYmOiG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her many roles: Grad student. Gun rights activist. Alleged Russian agent: The list of allegations against Maria Butina reads like a plot from an international crime thriller. https://t.co/eRzmRy98Bh https://t.co/wGNPapqkAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEVOPS engineer with strong Java knowledge: DEVOPS engineer with strong Java knowledge Ref No.: 18-29394 Location: San Antonio, Texas Role: DEVOPS engineer with strong Java knowledge Location: San Antonio TX Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required:… https://t.co/Yx1mLWhDXk https://t.co/olQVAz0C0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP Principal, Java Development: Consults with internal business groups to provide’ application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior technical staffs.… https://t.co/XHgoDJlqDB https://t.co/vaEDjC7qHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mamma Mia' sequel will have you singing 'Fernando': At a moment where gloom feels pervasive in many quarters, "Mamma Mia! Here We Go Again" rides a tide of joy, fun and mother-daughter bonding, again set to a jaunty array of ABBA tunes. This… https://t.co/2b7XHvkgdr https://t.co/9BZXgnDszo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (Spring / ActiveMQ / SOA): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity – Performance Ratings –… https://t.co/OxvH1lsgxa https://t.co/IMSxP7yExx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer – Agile Java Angular Python: This position is in the BNY Mellon Information Lifecycle Management group, responsible for building and buying solutions to support Cyber Security Data Masking, Records Management, Application Archive and… https://t.co/NdU4j0Tm3U https://t.co/pbYXup1MSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ webservice product specialist: Java/ webservice product specialist in Woodbridge, New Jersey, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant –… https://t.co/XSpLFDsXzd https://t.co/OQfMKg7ys9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-28465 Location: Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Key skills required for the job are: – Spring Integration-L3 (Mandatory) – Core Java-L3 (Alternate) As a Senior Developer, you are responsible for development, support,… https://t.co/iOrEaiE9bx https://t.co/NzF1p70ZuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Lead Developer: Java Lead Developer Ref No.: 18-28572 Location: Bellevue, Washington 6+ Years Java Lead Developer – 5+ Years of experience in Java Web Development – Experience in Java / JEE technology frameworks – Good development experience in Java… https://t.co/Hlj5Anec33 https://t.co/DJZuNQkhPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-39053 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Researches, designs, develops and/or modifies… https://t.co/fe2KiENI2J https://t.co/zsUmAWYiCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Java: QA Automation – Java Ref No.: 18-28564 Location: Irving, Texas Knowledge and experience with automation development techniques, methodologies and best practices. Understanding of the SDLC process and principles. Understanding of Agile… https://t.co/EsKFCAdBHS https://t.co/zhPPeQ0Ylt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer: Craig Technologies &gt; ERDC-ITL Recruiting information Position: JAVA Developer Location: Jacksonville, FL Job Id: 1878 # of Openings: 1 Title: JAVA Developer Location: Jacksonville, FL on client site in Cecil Field Clearance: Clearable –… https://t.co/UVkGFtgtiu https://t.co/2VPwjLZlAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer with Tech Lead experience: Senior Java Engineer with Tech Lead experience Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility –… https://t.co/IGYcvqGofP https://t.co/uRM42blSXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors: Russian agent traded sex for access: Prosecutors said Mariia Butina should be held in jail until her trial because her life in the US has been predicated on deception, including attempts to exchange sex for political access. She appeared in… https://t.co/xLuL0uek2n https://t.co/hKn7TwDxiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riding an autonomous shuttle through Times Square was reassuringly boring: Yesterday afternoon, I rode an autonomous shuttle down a short section of Broadway in the heart of Times Square, and it was easily the most boring part of my day. I'm not saying… https://t.co/DpsjoQQd6z https://t.co/ManImJlfvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First it was Pfizer. Now Novartis has frozen drug prices in the US https://t.co/W1sgM8VTKK https://t.co/dSboHkF5Cz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple’s MacBook eGPU is a step toward winning back creative pros: Even though Apple makes a lot more money on iPhones and iPads, Macs are still crucial to its bottom line. For years, they were widely loved by creative folks and influencers because they… https://t.co/8NpOUTc9f2 https://t.co/gLljjxftrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe hits Google with a record $5 billion fine https://t.co/AOnzWXMPEq https://t.co/Lz4mM9YUex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer (TS/SCI) – Herndon, VA for CACI in Herndon, VA 20171(map) Job Description CACI is seeking a Java Developer to be a part of our DTRA team in Herndon, VA. What you’ll get to do: Responsible for researching, designing,… https://t.co/VJ1jptyHi6 https://t.co/kf5oxFBHJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A storm ruined her beach wedding. Then a total stranger saved the day: It was a wedding-day nightmare. The sky was dark, thunder rumbled, lightning cracked across the sky and large raindrops soaked the flower-petal pathway and chairs waiting for wedding… https://t.co/hbEXUY769p https://t.co/xTIv015R9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core JAVA: Core JAVA Ref No.: 18-29302 Location: Richmond, Virginia JOB ROLE: -Core Java Location: Richmond, VA &amp; Plano, TX POSITION:-CONTRACT JOB DESCRIPTION: Strong Hands On experience with Core Java, J2EE technology. Experience and Hands on Rest API,… https://t.co/ur6WN4R7LF https://t.co/jiXGIqVeIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Technical Lead: Java/J2EE Technical Lead Ref No.: 18-26204 Location: syracuse, New York Hi, Hope you are doing great!! We are currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java/J2EE Technical Lead with the client based in… https://t.co/vlHMEwpOZL https://t.co/TADz66CFX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Tech Lead: Java Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-30728 Location: McLean, California Position: Java Tech Lead Location : McLean,VA Duration: 12 Months "Must Have Skills – Total experience of 15+ Years with 7+ Years in Java/ J2EE Development – Knowledge of… https://t.co/wAzMn4lVQp https://t.co/1axPoMegaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Sacha Baron Cohen still funny?: Sacha Baron Cohen's act hasn't changed, from "Da Ali G Show" to "Borat" to his new Showtime series, "Who is America?" But the world has, which, in light of the media uproar he's triggered, raises the question whether… https://t.co/ocaVmwOfYw https://t.co/72218zDsXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: Sr Java Developer Location : San Jose, Dallas, TX Roles and Responsibilities: -Experienced java developer with very good programming skills. -Should be able to write clean, readable,maintainable code with Unit tests to verify code. –… https://t.co/PbK1X4r4A0 https://t.co/d7egyG092L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day sales soar, despite glitches https://t.co/cmSjn4vgV3 https://t.co/3EQPGnuROe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Dev, Senior: SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER RESPONSIBILITIES/QUALIFICATIONS * Bachelor’s degree in CS or a technical field. * 5+years experience in application solution, design and development. * 5+ years experience with XML, Java EE, JBoss, Weblogic, JSP… https://t.co/KYdZmDdsRo https://t.co/TaLawCs5WT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['David Bowie Is' coming to your home through AR and VR: Did you miss your chance to see the David Bowie is museum exhibition and pay tribute to the late, great musician? You won't have to wallow in regret for very long. The David Bowie Archive, Sony… https://t.co/9gTzGQaxcz https://t.co/krWxeSBQ08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER: FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-27566 Location: CINCINNATI, Ohio Minimum 5 years in Java Executed a minimum 2 projects using Spring Boot ecosystem Executed a minimum 2 projects with a Frontend JavaScript Framework… https://t.co/9GbPbjAKuV https://t.co/U6VejHsUqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Onlookers scream as lava bomb slams into boat: A lava bomb hit a tour boat in Hawaii, injuring 23 people, the Hawaii County Fire Department said. https://t.co/CNfU5aPD3E https://t.co/6eLg1Uy2FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job ID: ********-11836-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: Senior Java Developer ClaimXperience is searching for a dynamic and creative Senior Java Developer who has the knowledge and experience to help shape our industry… https://t.co/tmimQYJYBG https://t.co/nODUg0F4qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Developer (C# or Java): Job Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial,… https://t.co/66HljPZuGb https://t.co/VEXrIco4dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer – Active Clearance needed referral bonus available!: Java Software Developer – Active Clearance needed – $10,000 referral bonus available! ==================================================================== Req #: ******Location:… https://t.co/lD3A1jtLCI https://t.co/X7VlBQOo8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Engineer NET ,C# or Java: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management,… https://t.co/PhcYtOvwTd https://t.co/MInutKqmZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper defends calling Trump's actions 'disgraceful': CNN's Anderson Cooper says he has never seen a US president "kowtow" to a Russian leader until President Donald Trump's summit with Vladimir Putin in Helsinki, Finland. https://t.co/8bHzSvGoLi https://t.co/oavJFVCGgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Blue Ash, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 07/23/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Job Description Video Screening Process: Once submitted, your candidate will receive a link to complete… https://t.co/esx3R3ZRl8 https://t.co/cYBATFqw7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer (Data Warehouse / Cloud / Java): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity –… https://t.co/04xuWbqFxs https://t.co/q1I2g6WwpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer (Java): Sr. Software Engineer (Java) ============================ Req #: ******Location: Hanover, MD USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description Summary Are… https://t.co/94NosWoSZq https://t.co/jiiTOf5UpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blake Shelton blames alcohol for stage fall: Blake Shelton has no shame in his falling game. https://t.co/wLVaJuPdBv https://t.co/Q4yEMYjZNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: Sr Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27995 Location: Plano, Texas Role: Sr Java Developer Location: Bloomfield, CT, Denver, CO, Plano, TX Type: Contract Duration: 12 Months JD: Mandatory Skills: Java, J2ee, Spring, Hibernate, Webservices,… https://t.co/imWb60aWoW https://t.co/lORGSesQWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Suitland-Silver Hill, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/Yjx4wYmDN0 https://t.co/iOkunFhZHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Employer helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/yvwmX6ytLu https://t.co/fd1rzor2PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Javascript Engineer: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today Are you a Senior Javascript Engineer who believes that "being healthy" is achievable for every US household? If so, read on… We are a team of serial social entrepreneurs &amp;… https://t.co/rfTBfMDDZS https://t.co/b0KqXNcjpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, JAVA, C/C++, Android Development: Req ID : 432499BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : This dynamic Software Engineer position is responsible for hands-on software engineering, programming, and scientific… https://t.co/8jMzsRFcE4 https://t.co/GQSs2KnJde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer I: Bring your talent and skills to the Employer Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) State College Engineering team! Our team is focused on providing solutions to challenging problems to enable the success of our customer’s… https://t.co/yMx3cMYjk2 https://t.co/XXXibuDgqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:: JAVA DEVELOPER (JSF/GWT) ::: :: JAVA DEVELOPER (JSF/GWT) :: Ref No.: 18-30610 Location: EDISON, New Jersey JOB TITLE : JAVA DEVELOPER (JSF/GWT) JOB TYPE : FULL TIME JOB LOCATION : EDISON,NJ Should have expertise in Core Java,spring, hibernate Java web… https://t.co/fH88f3fBPz https://t.co/BJw91gEOCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer – Back-end: The Sears ecommerce order management team is seeking an experienced Back-end Developer with a strong engineering background, experience and passion for managing Java/J2EE applications and MySQL databases at large… https://t.co/748Y8ZoIys https://t.co/jWDjcL4G4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Patuxent River, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/0WasCPPALr https://t.co/cilMIKunyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer – JavaScript: UI Developer – JavaScript – RJSabol LLC – Arlington, VA – 06-26-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career… https://t.co/a7kyowZswO https://t.co/krBFMGd3Wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Why Trump is the distraction Putin needs: When Russian President Vladimir Putin meets President Donald Trump in Helsinki, Finland, on Monday, he will be riding a symbolic high: The Helsinki summit comes a day after the World Cup final in… https://t.co/HRzlfr492c https://t.co/D1KQ1xBmK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Software Developer: JAVA Software Developer in Fort Detrick, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent… https://t.co/YuncJwzfbG https://t.co/IG8VLBUizI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Heck's Atari 800 handheld: What are your favorite 8-bit computers from the '80s? Ben Heck's is the Atari 800, and what better thing to do as a final project than make it portable? That's right, it's time for a teardown. After pulling the Atari apart… https://t.co/vhHTUcbKIm https://t.co/JDFEqzJLvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Description As a Java Developer and member of the Serco software development team, you will share responsibility for the design, development, automated tests, builds, and deployment of application solutions and delivery of the company… https://t.co/vPA30pJnhZ https://t.co/ui0zPvaCcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer with Aws: Java/Python Developer with Aws Ref No.: 18-26773 Location: Los Angeles, California Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested for, send me updated resume along with best time to contact.… https://t.co/ioTIqSNk7s https://t.co/Rh4L5XktOY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>