<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/ZXlY7SnxQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/XPNXARMGmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/JFnAxjnzSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/WbDE9rA1Ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/OptgzfKex3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Everyday Impact of Math  http://t.co/Atr4oAwdgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/3GUzopfZVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/lPewiWEtvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/fI0wgjsplz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/EzZmkRDDN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/4iGSWcFthl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/UaTBvXLuPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/5aryz1w4qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/JVZGdaIK3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/udeTYDExgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/zmzBPS9soZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/rMbVTlw7Me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/nDtvxEF4Jc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/aEMHX0dWQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/GeE0QkDZSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/7RmbnkG49e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/aL5hxxyOJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/UccViBtxNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/pWBGt9gghW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/opD3wlHNIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/GVeBDJ43bQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/4EHHgAwTs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/Qx60DNMXwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/Owk2lzJKp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/5DDRry0JvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/QXCawwmeAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/cy3XlitxWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/fI0wgjsplz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/bqxtH0wTFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/zYpzakbKWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/vUF3S6NrU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/7LHsx5GxY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/LIijOJkfDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/Ncd28AEF6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/QtthLs5CyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/Mv0JgK6AcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is good for nothing unless you know the value of it by experience.  P.T Barnum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/m40eGUNrQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/LhhXDtWUIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/KsF6Qi2DXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/sZC5taZAqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/moAEsk8HXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/BvTqD59oFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/2YwOQUXc0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/AP9an5cF0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/Wyq6tKkKEy  http://t.co/0YrFOm2nCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/zb5RlNg82M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the J. Geils Band  http://t.co/1JNzOeUN21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/QR9ClCrfRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/rB3SVXX8FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/tNymX1n8xf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>