<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who moves a mountain begins by carrying away small stones. -Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is predestined: The obstacles of your past can become the gateways that lead to new beginnings. -Ralph Blum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Every Morning https://t.co/sDxTH60aYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luck affects everything. Let your hook always be cast; in the stream where you least expect it there will be a fish. -Ovid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust yourself. You know more than you think you do." -Benjamin Spock

#quotes #motivational… https://t.co/6dIakt3A2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never face facts; if you do you'll never get up in the morning. -Marlo Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody grows old merely by living a number of years. We grow old by deserting our ideals. -Samuel Ullman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up. -Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness Must Be Tricked https://t.co/hT5Hhhirx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minute a man ceases to grow, no matter what his years, that minute he begins to be old. -William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is nothing more than a few simple disciplines, practiced every day... -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder Quotes https://t.co/9OP4NMJqS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A successful person is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks that others throw at him or her." -David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is like rowing upstream: not to advance is to drop back. -Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Too Shall Pass Away https://t.co/PuUp9gWNsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Opportunities multiply as they are seized." -Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every achiever I have ever met says, 'My life turned around when I began to believe in me.' -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Quotes https://t.co/K7aosBI2Sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get right down to the root of the meaning of the word 'succeed', you find it simply means to follow through. -F.W. Nichol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Can Accomplish What You Want https://t.co/MhjKRASukI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your heart soar as high as it will. Refuse to be average. -A.W. Tozer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some days when I think I'm going to die from an overdose of satisfaction. -Salvador Dali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of discretion is worth a pound of wit. -American Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Have A Friend https://t.co/DVStVjSbXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better is not something you wish, it is something you become. -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever observe to whom the accidents happen? Chance favors only the prepared mind. -Louis Pasteur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the depth of winter, I finally learned that within me there lay an invincible summer. -Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are progressing or retrograding all the while; there is no such thing as staying stationary in this life. -JF Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience Quotes https://t.co/KZ9xGMCiGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is impossible for a man to learn what he thinks he already knows. -Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure doesn't mean you are a failure, it just means you haven't succeeded yet. -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who views the world at fifty the same as he did at twenty has wasted thirty year of his life. -Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to jump off cliffs and build your wings on the way down. -Ray Bradbury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflection Quotes https://t.co/c8REvNOHjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wicked people are always surprised to find ability in those that are good. -Marquis De Vauvenargues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better. -Samuel Beckett

#quotes… https://t.co/s2W5BhzF0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all the thirty-six alternatives, running away is best. -Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singleness of purpose is one of the chief essentials for success in life, no matter what may be one's aim. -Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who is shipwrecked the second time cannot lay the blame on Neptune. -English Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Paine Quotes https://t.co/G4vcUHIlnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better. -Samuel Beckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow hopes we have learned something from yesterday. -John Wayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to win, you must expect to win.  -Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Goals are dreams with deadlines." -Diana Schart Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one ever yet was the poorer in the long run for having once in a lifetime, let out all the length of all the reins. -Cholmondeley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Good Success Quotes https://t.co/c7hIbpsU8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest thing to give away is kindness; it always comes back to you. -English proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never remember feeling tired by work, though idleness exhausts me completely. -Sherlock Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes no more effort to expect the best than to fear the worst. It's healthier, more productive, &amp; a lot more fun. -Hambert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things." - Albert… https://t.co/T1udMVUiCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Through seeking and blundering we learn. -Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laziness Grows on People https://t.co/P22JeGA8rX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failures do what is tension relieving, while winners do what is goal achieving. -Dennis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of us die with much of our beautiful music still in us, un-sung, un-played. -Grant Bright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always gotten.  -Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless a man has been kicked around a little, you can't really depend upon him to amount to anything. -William Feather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difficult Things To Do https://t.co/eZRJWnTt0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My reputation grows with every failure. -George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the best books first, or you may not have a chance to read them at all. -Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help people become more motivated by guiding them to the source of their own power. -Paul G. Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a fine thing to have ability, but the ability to discover ability in others is the true test. -Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Travel Quotes to Motivate Your Next Adventure https://t.co/ZkKeqwKxWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Words are nothing but words; power lies in deeds. Be a person of action." -Konyate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indecision and delays are the parents of failure. -George Canning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When thought becomes excessively painful, action is the finest remedy. -Salman Rushdie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life must be lived and curiosity kept alive. One must never, for whatever reason, turn his back on life.  -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Procrastination Quotes https://t.co/EywNluNwlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Act boldly and unseen forces will come to your aid. -Dorothea Brande]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You play the way you practice. -Pop Warner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait for your ship to come in, and feel angry and cheated when it doesn't. Get going with… https://t.co/PrC2etVEw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realize that if you have time to whine &amp; complain about something then you have the time to do something about it. -A. D'Angelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are lifting the world upward and onward are those who encourage more than criticize. -Elizabeth Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Quotes https://t.co/444Es69pWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong beliefs win strong men, and then make them stronger. -Walter Bagehot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you can do, or believe you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it. -Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each of us needs time for mental self-renewal -Whitt N. Schultz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your net worth to the world is usually determined by what remains after your bad habits are subtracted from your good ones. -Ben Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Name - Poem https://t.co/TvUBnot0fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will. -Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to success is to focus our conscious mind on things we desire, not things we fear.… https://t.co/JnZ1YwrtaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait for your ship to come in, and feel angry and cheated when it doesn't. Get going with something small. -Irene Kassorla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the courage to live. Anyone can die. -Robert Cody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me life is a challenge. And it will be a challenge if I live to be a hundred or if I get to be a trillionaire. -Beah Richards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost Blue Monkey Found on EBay - Very Touching https://t.co/dIH3AduH4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is to be measured not by wealth, power, or fame, but by the ratio between what a man is and what he might be. -H.G. Wells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only true happiness comes from squandering ourselves for a purpose. -John Mason Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confidence comes not from always being right but from not fearing to be wrong. -Peter Mcintyre #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is curious that physical courage should be so common in the world, and moral courage so rare. -Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to make a contribution, you begin to die.  -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poem: The Purpose of Life https://t.co/fl8CPYm0jz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the course opposite to custom and you will almost always do well. -Jean Jacques Rousseau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take your life in your own hands and what happens? A terrible thing: no one is to blame." -Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Stain - Poem https://t.co/a9vFCGyAKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is the good fortune that comes from aspiration, desperation, perspiration and inspiration. -Evan Esar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gent who wakes up and finds himself a success hasn't been asleep. -Wilson Mizner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was a man and they called him mad; the more he gave the more he had. -Bunyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True luck consists not in holding the best cards at the table; luckiest he who knows just when to rise and go home. -John Hay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being defeated is often only a temporary condition. Giving up is what makes it permanent..." -Marilyn vos Savant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have got two reasons for success and I'm standing on both of them. -Betty Grable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success Is Hanging On https://t.co/wlvgZ7p60p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>