<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Engineer: Staff Analyst/Developer sought by DISH Network, LLC in Denver, CO. Lead a team of dvlprs who build &amp; maintain web-based applics; dsgn &amp; architect UI, UX, &amp; data mgmt solutions; manage, prioritize, plan, &amp; assign projects to jr.… https://t.co/gKldZxuqYp https://t.co/VMSHIi2FEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Database Administrator Nashville, Tennessee APPLICATION DEADLINE IS SATURDAY, JUNE 9, 2018 AT 11:59PM Dynamic IT team on the leading edge of technology has a need for an experienced SQL Database Administrator.  Do you thrive in a… https://t.co/gBWgCHbYDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physical Design Engineer #AND7EF: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: Physical Design Engineer (Requisition #AND7EF) Responsible for implementing complete chip design from netlist to tapeout.   Apple is an Equal Opportunity… https://t.co/fwmAnsiKY4 https://t.co/duYwNvFYRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer: Barnmaster Supply LLC seeks a Civil Engineer in Ontario, CA. Responsible for design of manufactured panelized buildings &amp; associated structural calculations. Position requires Master’s degree in Engineering w/ minimum 1 year experience. … https://t.co/uVGVLDP5xb https://t.co/LNUW7eOb2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In concession, Trump will help China's ZTE 'get back into business': WASHINGTON/BEIJING (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump pledged on Sunday to help ZTE Corp "get back into business, fast" after a U.S. ban crippled the Chinese technology company,… https://t.co/e9pmg0rXtD https://t.co/BDqccV51zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL/ASP.NET Software Developer: At Experian, we are the trusted power behind data and the leading global information services company, providing a new sphere of insights with Experian’s vehicle, consumer, online and credit data to ignite a more unified… https://t.co/pcYlTUpcHA https://t.co/rwSwjPne0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Marketing Manager: Digital Marketing Manager Applause – the world leader in Crowdsourced application testing is looking to add a dynamic Digital Marketing expert to our growing marketing team. This person will play an integral role in executing… https://t.co/K3oY2OgPyC https://t.co/TZnftOG0hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FI-CO: SAP FI-CO Primary Skills CPA,SAP FI-CO,AC210,AC212,SAP certification,CMA Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking SAP FI-CO for location Southeast U.S. for one of our Top client . Job Description: Required… https://t.co/h9myu81ChY https://t.co/BCWpl5MnhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Fieldglass iXp – Junior Software Developer: SAP Fieldglass iXp – Junior Software Developer Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/QmKy29yYt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Reports and Analytics Developer, MADOC: Regional Reports and Analytics Developer, MADOC – – Careers Home – Featured Job Areas – Advanced Practitioner Jobs – Correct Care Recovery Solutions – Dentist Jobs – Healthcare Practitioner Jobs – Mental… https://t.co/QJSFVZMwQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst Product Engineer – Online Services: Overview Esri needs your help to build an amazing cloud-oriented web GIS platform. If you’re an energetic, detail-oriented software engineer who’s passionate about online services and has a knack for… https://t.co/sjeGXxCZYB https://t.co/fdZKgriZh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Development Operations Engineer: EMS Software is looking for a Senior Development Operations Engineer who will aid us in the ongoing transformation of our product offering from an on-premise solution to one having a hybrid offering with a pure… https://t.co/Khc5hmSFto https://t.co/s5rBFvZXhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Mobility Engineer: PaRaBaL / ISEC7 is looking to recruit highly motivated individuals to join a team of Enterprise Mobility Engineers that provides premier consultative engineering services to its clients, primarily centered on mobile device… https://t.co/11DRPPXhbH https://t.co/8rDnDoWSLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: li { margin: -10px 0px 10pt; padding: 0px; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); line-height: normal; font-family: Verdana; font-size: 12px; } p { margin: 0px 0px 0pt; padding: 0px; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); line-height: normal; font-family:… https://t.co/j5vtFEXzSs https://t.co/JrmidG18n4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Cloud &amp; Security Architect: Principal Cloud &amp; Security Architect Ever wanted to be part of a tech-startup from the ground up? A new ADVENTURE where you’re among the first 100 employees at a FULLY funded startup developing NEW, never before… https://t.co/e27oPBSIms https://t.co/7oI7EyGYWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weapon System Operator (WSO) 4: At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our work preserves freedom… https://t.co/enJVla0Miy https://t.co/iyTgek9py7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Analyst: Job Description ****WE ARE UNABLE TO PROVIDE SPONSORSHIP NOW OR IN THE FUTURE FOR THIS ROLE**** The qualified candidate will be responsible for the implementation of authentication strategies in vendor portal and Blaze business… https://t.co/PBvfH8nxRI https://t.co/MLX8HcEEvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted 12/01/2016 If you are a Senior iOS Developer with experience, please read on! We are a series B start-up based out of a beautiful office in downtown San Francisco, our company is… https://t.co/wtfX8uGsMd https://t.co/B3k8zjcr00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analog Design Engineer – High Speed: Job ID 22341BR Job Posting Title Analog Design Engineer – High Speed Job Description As a global semiconductor company operating in 35 countries, Texas Instruments (TI) is first and foremost a reflection of its… https://t.co/dOd5xOqqxn https://t.co/obR1pfgcO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Administrator: Req ID 97811BR Business Title Senior Database Administrator Group MCIS Location USA DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA Washington Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities Database… https://t.co/AVKp6vEiOy https://t.co/9x3k1V1WR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Good experience in HTML, XML, JSON. Strong… https://t.co/qkx0dn5mVC https://t.co/S4PZK36ZLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Engineer/Developer: C# Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime Position FT Benefits(Medical + Dental + Vision + Paid leaves+ Relocation Assistance+ Relocation Assistance(Flight Tickets&amp; Goods Transportation) Job Description: Should have a Bachelors degree in… https://t.co/ByqOv5jV1Q https://t.co/t3TGy8VPyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: We are looking for a Database Administrator for a perm/direct hire role in Westminster, CO. Location: Thornton/Westminster, CO Type: Direct Hire Benefits: Excellent Retirement and Health Benefits Job Description: – A little of… https://t.co/lRp4DvIaAt https://t.co/oNPDVqT4hM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Our client is looking for experienced Project Manager which oversee Client facing cross-functional teams responsible for delivering defined project outcomes on time and within quality specifications. The Project Manager plans, organizes,… https://t.co/Jp7yCekrDn https://t.co/l4xhDddTTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Lead: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.       We are seeking a… https://t.co/UG7daYsK1n https://t.co/Hun2Sg0L7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Signal Processing Engineer: Description: The Advanced Solutions Group of Leidos Corporation currently has an opening for a Mid-Level Signal Processing Engineer. Job Description: Leidos’ Advanced Solutions Group is looking for a skilled Signal… https://t.co/I1QYV5PSqL https://t.co/tLD5mGgjGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   We are seeking a talented Software… https://t.co/lPdsrTGq7J https://t.co/uzCrKm0rm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer: Description:  Leidos has an opening for Cyber Security Engineer within our Defense and Intelligence Business at our Fort Belvoir, Virginia office.   JOB SUMMARY: Responsible for maintaining the integrity and security of… https://t.co/NGOiQ2VpoQ https://t.co/cqjY4rLuQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Curtain Wall: Welcome to Pervenio Search where you will find careers that offer the right fit for you. Pervenio provides recruitment solutions for leading companies throughout North America. Our opportunities give you the ability… https://t.co/N9y8XiRotA https://t.co/zLrwQ0Kojx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Melrose): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/fsBtB8CSTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – EDS Guardium Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/zfQ42nmVuI https://t.co/vudA0GeQkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Designer – Waveserver: We believe in the power of people. We are a network strategy and technology company that is motivated by making a difference in people’s lives – their productivity, their creativity, their health and comfort. That’s why… https://t.co/5Y51a5VaRo https://t.co/tnqzFTJqJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Engineer II: 109302BR Sr Systems Engineer II CO – Aurora 109302BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems that make the world a… https://t.co/rJbpC8xOSR https://t.co/9D3TErQcVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electromechanical Systems Test Engineer 2:   Job Description – Electromechanical Systems Test Engineer 2 (18002310) Electromechanical Systems Test Engineer 2 Requisition ID : 18002310 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required… https://t.co/kQZvzXYMmL https://t.co/SN3Jy5D3jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Finance: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at https://t.co/EiOaTQ1rko.… https://t.co/YKKJYIYnBT https://t.co/PsgSk1FO3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D&amp;AT-MDM Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/68pyupvbhi https://t.co/j57UfLKxeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FrontEnd Developer — Javascript/React/Node: Front End Developer with JavaScript/React/Node Join our Consumer Experience team, which has full responsibility for the CARFAX online presence, as a Front End developer!  At CARFAX, we create websites for our… https://t.co/TADFHFY4hv https://t.co/yDg4XgRWfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity &amp; Privacy – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us… https://t.co/M31bSjdf2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer (JAVA Back End): Does the idea of building intelligent frameworks using modern technologies to support a clear and defined mission a?  If so, working as a Software Developer on the Data Technologies team may be the perfect role for… https://t.co/mRdEBHp1K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Sec Analyst Principal Job: Date: Mar 30, 2018 Location:Raleigh, NC, US Company: SAIC Cyber Sec Analyst Principal (Job Number:424226) Description: o JOB DESCRIPTION: SAIC has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst Principal is located in… https://t.co/6bHl5UT9Op]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Manager: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Manager, Technology, AMS in Kansas City, MO and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to provide technology-enabled business solutions to… https://t.co/DvR7sKJqY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – Software Test: Manager – Software Test sought by Dish Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Lead testers assigned to automation testing for STB satellite receivers &amp; applications; test planning, resource management, &amp; system architecture development… https://t.co/knZiimqnu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Analyst #20189002: Mygo Consulting Job ID – 20189002 Mygo Consulting Inc has openings for the position SAP Analyst with Master’s degree in Computer Science/Information Systems, Engineering (any),Technology or related to involve in various deployment… https://t.co/bRl7z4EIAP https://t.co/rlhszwxwAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Director: Assistant Director University Counseling Services Oklahoma State University Contingent Upon Available Funding In the absence of the Director of University Counseling Services, this individual performs the administrative duties… https://t.co/KRhevcLtx7 https://t.co/n8wjH3ccSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Engineer: QualitrolTech Inc. seeks Sr. Integration Engineer. Duties are to design and develop integration software codes and packages based on web Methods Integration Server &amp; related software platforms. Education Requirements:… https://t.co/ET42tByHm2 https://t.co/5EA1hDns7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: TS/SCI Cleared Network Admin -Washington D.C -IAT II (Sec+CE) Tier 1 &amp; 2 Roles open. Preferred Experience: -Basic Network troubleshooting experience -Knowledge of BGP &amp; OSPF Protocols -Experience troubleshooting LAN &amp; WAN… https://t.co/IgX32BfF94 https://t.co/NZ8x6HR9gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Environmental Project Manager: A national Environmental firm is expanding its business in the Southwest and is seeking a mid- to senior level Environmental Project Manager/Client Manager to assist in growing and developing the greater Phoenix area.… https://t.co/5oehjE2R6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports the usage of business applications,… https://t.co/QrHKxxQwb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Center (NOC) Technician: The NOC Team is the heart of our Support Operations division and an entry-level technical role. This is a fast paced role that requires a shift in focus multiple times per hour and prioritization of work on the… https://t.co/EExwhak1f0 https://t.co/AP8sPTTzM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. drone program taps Alphabet, passes over Amazon, China's DJI: WASHINGTON/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - The U.S. Transportation Department's 10 winning drone pilot projects aimed at spurring the use of unmanned aerial vehicles in a wide variety of fields… https://t.co/uXzhGR8F6X https://t.co/597mUBT6rR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Treeline Interactive is searching for an Android Developer who possesses a passion for pushing mobile technologies to the limits and will work with our team of talented engineers to design and build the next generation of our mobile… https://t.co/BNQBJUxJmf https://t.co/o1NeT6C3hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst: Job ID: 247944 Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst , Missouri Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Senior Budget Planning Support Analyst City, State:  MO Location:  MOSTL Virtual – MO Department:  … https://t.co/nnQu0YJklj https://t.co/APVhx2pcGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Revenue Analyst: Job ID: 245911 Net Revenue Analyst Warren, Michigan Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Net Revenue Analyst – Physician Net Revenue City, State:  Warren, MI Location:  Corporate Svcs Bulding – 34028 Department:  … https://t.co/OvhKQUkpfL https://t.co/24mZBGrojb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Healthcare Economics Analyst: Job ID: 250713 Lead Healthcare Economics Analyst Austin, Texas Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Lead Financial Analyst City, State:  Austin, TX Location:  TXAUS 4515 Quarry Lake Department:   Managed Care… https://t.co/onz7mfiwlt https://t.co/nKscVo8org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mechanical Engineer – Los Angeles, California: Excellence Leaves a Lasting Impression Bring Your Vision to shape a better world. At Arup, our innovative spirit and determination enables us to express our ingenuity in unique ways developing many of… https://t.co/YK2rfWRGvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/ISJKTCWhgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/r4JJubrhFQ https://t.co/Aca2KvW07J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROJECT MANAGER @ Amazon – Tempe, AZ:   Position Summary Responsible for those client facilities and personnel under his / her supervision to ensure that the Company is providing professional and quality service and to ensure compliance with all safety,… https://t.co/dxPCvCbsbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Manager: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a(n) Cyber Security Manager within… https://t.co/qStPrmW0gi https://t.co/hGrKyrhLO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer in Broomfield, CO. Minimum Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or closely related, plus 2 years experience as Software Engineer are required. recblid r9bk1jxwvomsjuljsr1yl5k5z43h46 https://t.co/KKLEVrchhO https://t.co/4U5FMPABZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design &amp; develop core components for trade capture, booking, position management &amp; PnL calculations, notification to the Back Office booking system &amp; related systems,… https://t.co/PHsvFQg7w3 https://t.co/M7Cwope2A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Principal- Basis: SAP PRINCIPAL – Basis sought by Freudenberg IT LP in Morrisville, NC. Report to Director of SAP Application Services &amp; serve as trusted advisor to our customers, SAP Basis &amp; d/base admins. Act as primary customer contact for… https://t.co/hEzh9MktTw https://t.co/lwRyHmb2yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: HIROTEC AMERICA is the world’s leading comprehensive engineering company; providing state of the art body shop tooling, engineering services and products to automotive manufactures across the world. Currently, we are seeking to expand… https://t.co/eKzdvmWBNx https://t.co/gY6G1jR0Mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Data Analyst: Join Joomag, one of the fastest growing digital publishing companies out there with over 500,000 publishers on board. The Marketing Data Analyst will use audience data to track campaign success, map user experiences, develop… https://t.co/6X5LdLS624 https://t.co/7uvelU7Win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Date: May 20, 2018 Location: Jersey City, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co Apply now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Apply Now EmailStart Please wait… New York Life Insurance Company… https://t.co/F5iAYCiMY8 https://t.co/qwhN9eyQTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead System Data Architect Digital and Mobile Product Development: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind – making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere.… https://t.co/ULuhk0aPeI https://t.co/H0NIY9Ne9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Developer: Requisition ID 2018-42028 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description GDIT is seeking a proactive, creative, team playing Website Developer to provide… https://t.co/Rk4D9Xgp4n https://t.co/LJm5q3kXyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Software Configuration Analyst: The Specialist Software Configuration Analyst will be working in Business Partner Technology as a part of the BPT SCM Admin team providing support for corporate shared service applications which includes Assets… https://t.co/wVbW5KT6NZ https://t.co/N2Iprp22N0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China start-up readies capacity for 150,000 electric cars per year: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Future Mobility Corporation (FMC), the Chinese parent company behind electric car start-up Byton, has placed an order for a paint shop capable of handling 150,000… https://t.co/7hwkLYbI6g https://t.co/Bh484eHm3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Control Engineer: ENGINEERING: Quality Control Engineer: Plan restoration operations. Estimate costs, effects of method changes. Implement quality control objective to resolve problems in restoration techniques. Develop methods, cost analysis… https://t.co/IdpCfIekrW https://t.co/YA5AqjYI6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Location: San Jose, California, US Area of Interest Project or Program Management Job Type Professional Technology Interest *None Job Id 1216550 New What You'll Do Global Tactical Systems and Tools (GTST) needs a Project Manager who can… https://t.co/0zQeOHm19c https://t.co/1HKOYOC5g8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Assurance Engineer – Aurora, CO:   Job Description – Mission Assurance Engineer – Aurora, CO (17025260) Mission Assurance Engineer – Aurora, CO Requisition ID : 17025260 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/b4pNh606ZI https://t.co/gDUsVeIdm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive – Legal Solutions: Account Executive – Legal Solutions ID 2017-8550 Category Sales Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities Summary: The TLS Account Executive (AE) role consists of prospecting legal and corporate clients and driving… https://t.co/j5kSgeFVcz https://t.co/pgobhxIFLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Who we are: Conversable is a funded software startup working on a SaaS platform for building enterprise-class chat/voice bots. Our founding team has started and sold several companies, have worked at companies like Zynga, Yahoo, Demand… https://t.co/DNmRB1I4uf https://t.co/7QBdVIugbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Engineer: ENGINEERING/TECH Sage Intacct, Inc. is seeking a qualified applicant for the position of Sr. Quality Assurance Engineer to design, develop, validate, and execute software test plans and test cases according to the… https://t.co/MB7t8dsyDU https://t.co/Pak9WQe7Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Access Information And Referral Specialist: Access Information And Referral Specialist Oakland Community Health Network Access Information and Referral Specialist Hourly Rate of pay: $17.51 (Hourly) General Summary of Position: The Access Information and… https://t.co/kjwuc5m16L https://t.co/9P6Zd15rVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0518MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies; Manager, Site Reliability (6597.1170) Oversee a team of… https://t.co/WXgkDM0Phm https://t.co/oU73D1nXKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Research Scientist: Samsung Semiconductor Inc. has the following jobs in San Jose, CA: Sr. SW Development Engineer [Req #8EJ1416] Code applications with Java and Android SDK- code and troubleshoot the “core” frameworks; Staff Engineer… https://t.co/BDh7Qzc3uG https://t.co/1z8iL4w2ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newscast/Technical Director: Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the largest and most diversified television… https://t.co/C3jkPG2mUg https://t.co/ytGOn82be7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network-Based Computer Intrusion Analyst ,Princ.: Requisition ID 2018-36558 # of Openings 5 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Network Based Computer Intrusion Analyst… https://t.co/vrf4m7U14C https://t.co/6hOWzMCBBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Software Engineer (Provide tech. consulting &amp; development of app. in Java, J2EE, Spring &amp; Microservices. Analyze the business requirements &amp;… https://t.co/mO2tI05akQ https://t.co/79H3qnbQzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineering Manager #1816034: Senior Software Engineering Manager Needed by AT&amp;T Services, Inc. in Bothell, WA to design and deliver server to server software deployment systems using shell scripts and middleware features from Weblogic.… https://t.co/Lznkg750ya https://t.co/SCbSHQvefV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist, IT Architecture: Nationwide Insurance. Columbus, OH. Specialist, IT Architecture Provide application systems &amp; project architecture support throughout the enterprise. Define application system architecture, application design, database… https://t.co/b3ECXZhpkT https://t.co/Wn3XqHYKeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotics Engineer: Robotics Engineer (Murrieta, CA) Draft, analyze &amp; assemble automation systems for FANUC industrial robot equipment. Develop real-time robotic software programs &amp; vision-guided robot applications. Master’s in Mechanical or Electrical… https://t.co/lZqKbOpXHN https://t.co/HBzJ7G4OAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Firmware Engineer: Marvell Semiconductor, Inc. at Santa Clara, CA seeks candidates for the following position (multiple positions available for each title): Digital IC Design Engineer (Job Code E303)- Provide RTL implementation and verification of… https://t.co/1uAK0xxF7D https://t.co/WlJwjhYydU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRI-COR INDUSTRIES HIRING EVENT: TRI-COR INDUSTRIES HIRING EVENT June 11th and 13th 4:30 – 7:30 pm 1035 Eastgate Drive, Suite 2, O’Fallon, IL 62269   Hiring for: AWS Architects, System &amp; Network Engineers, System &amp; Database Administrators, Functional… https://t.co/VrNf44056G https://t.co/vr4sNFs9Uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Office: Ekman Associates, Inc. is a Southern California based company focused on the following services: Management Consulting, Professional Staffing Solutions, Executive Recruiting and Managed Services. Summary: The Project Manager will… https://t.co/gmc0HfvuMZ https://t.co/aFcKI73Vlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager Microgrid and Distributed Generation: Eaton’s Electrical Engineering Services &amp; Systems division has an opening for a Senior Microgrid and Distributed Generation Project Manager.’ The position will be based out of an Eaton… https://t.co/9pyS9nBJ5F https://t.co/tHOoAK5aFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, IT – Project Portfolio Management Services: Job Title: Senior Manager, IT – Project Portfolio Management Services Location: Loveland, CO, West United States, USA Company: Nutrien Ltd. Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Chemical,… https://t.co/wq7xse0s0n https://t.co/54WLUY249y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Construction: Construction Professionals, are you ready to take your career to another level with an organization that will have your best interest in mind? Since its inception, Timothy Jon &amp; Associates has matched top talent in the… https://t.co/F7hhaGfZ3y https://t.co/H7pXSSCeuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Intern: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5359 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted.… https://t.co/NVmixri0Hl https://t.co/RzrNuJ3XPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer: Java Senior Developer Ref No.: 18-23230 Location: Alpharetta, Georgia Job Title: Java Senior Developer Onsite Job Location: Alpharetta, GA Job Type: Full-time only Description: Extensive technical experience and development… https://t.co/ZXFicVbXBx https://t.co/UDmj2z6Q9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist Ref No.: 18-23690 Location: Loveland, Colorado Job title: Data Scientist Location: Loveland, CO Duration: 12 months Minimum of 5 years of experience in data science Master’s or PhD Degree in Information Technology, Computer… https://t.co/2zvEPjbyJs https://t.co/aB7D6DOFf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROJECT MANAGER I: Job Description PROJECT MANAGER I (*******X) Building a career at Granite may be the most valuable thing you could do… Are you interested in the opportunity to work for an industry-leading company that will give you the experience and… https://t.co/Jb3PlqIlJO https://t.co/aRs5H5YCxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – Associate (Application Support): Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Associate (Application Support) Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Legal Department:… https://t.co/SnE2IqhXVV https://t.co/JGro9GFod2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer @ Cox Automotive Corporate Services, LLC (Mission, KS) – Dsgn, dvlp, test, implmnt &amp; maintain core integ softw tech &amp; sys integs. Reqts: Master’s deg (or foreign equiv) in CS, Engg (any), IT, IS or rel +… https://t.co/vBqhE4uBAX https://t.co/5dY5nQoUkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPIC/EHR Support Supervisor: Are you a Healthcare IT professional who excels at leading teams? Do you enjoy mentoring and developing IT Staff at various levels of knowledge and experience? If you answered yes, then we invite you to apply for our EPIC/EHR… https://t.co/dNl9zeAeVU https://t.co/2DKSYkiRiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphic Designer #SA-0721: Graphic Designer position in Redwood City, CA.   recblid o9fohpu0ql663inkawkuxmaced8dbh https://t.co/cTunD5urSu https://t.co/rUZpmnDl3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist| urbandale IA| 1 year | positions – 1: We are looking for a talented Data Scientist with skills in Data Analytics, Visualization and Machine Learning. This role will be with a highly talented technical solutions team for a Fortune 100… https://t.co/tj15UwO6WN https://t.co/FgOonypSuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Analyst III – Business Intelligence Analy: CLIENT REFERENCE CODE: ****** JOB SCOPE Supports the data and business analysis needs of Network Operations. Utilizes understanding of both business process and advanced technical capabilities… https://t.co/ePQqGRG1ec]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>