<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard honesty tip: Don't let anyone else tell you how many lights you see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take full responsibility for your crew's mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard mental health tip: When you lie down to sleep, instead of thinking about your failures, think about your successes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: Elect leaders the way you would hire crew members. Seek calm, control, and familiarity with how to operate the ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Humility without confidence is sheepishness. Confidence without humility is arrogance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Gain a reputation for completing missions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard game design tip: Add an element of mystery to your holodeck program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Certain crew members are like walking encyclopedias. Remember to ask for their input.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Peace begins with the choice to reject your own anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't be afraid to use imperative verbs. They're called orders for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: If reality gets altered, leaving you alone with your crush, it doesn't necessarily mean it's time to make your move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard science tip: The universal translator is not the end of linguistics. The replicator is not the end of chemistry. Keep going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Study history. The answers are there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Have an opinion on one side of an issue. Stay out of the neutral zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Hone your inner bullshit detector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard sanity tip: If there are four lights, say there are four lights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The crew needs to see you calm. If you're frustrated, complain to a confidante in private, then make a decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's okay if your second in command has a different management style, as long as you both agree on the goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your superiors are just as fallible as you are. It's okay to talk back to them. Just do it respectfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Get your own damn work done. Others will follow suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Fight for what you know is right. Only arrogant bullies think resistance is futile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard social tip: You're not really a third wheel if one of the others is a hologram. http://t.co/ide12MV4eD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you're on red alert every day, then red alert means nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your first impulse will often be wrong, but you have to start somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't let a crew member's age blind you to their skill level, in either direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you build up enough reputation, people will listen to any drivel you say. They'll even repeat it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Some of your decisions are going to be mistakes. You have to make them anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Defend your crew members, even against each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard multiversal tip: Be careful; not even a Jedi or a Time Lord can withstand Vogon poetry. So say we all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: The enemy of my enemy is sometimes a dangerous sociopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard emergency tip: When all else fails, route main power through the main deflector dish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: Don't fall in love with holograms, even if your friends do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If your crew is afraid to talk to you, they won't always give you the information you need. Be approachable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you make a mistake, apologize right away. Embrace humility over defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Exercise makes you smarter. Don't just sit there thinking.

Get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Statements should not sound like questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Your sense of morality is the guiding light that people under your command will follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you have the misfortune to acquire enemies, face them head on. They're just as afraid as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Standard procedures are just suggestions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Good crew members love what they do. Get off their backs and let them enjoy their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't scoff at anything. You don't know as much as you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard grief tip: There is no wrong way to deal with loss. Just be with someone who understands. http://t.co/mPfRK9BT6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Improve your vocabulary by reading books. Words can be your most powerful tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard education tip: The important things will never be on your exams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The appearance of your enterprise is important to your crew, and it intimidates your opponents. Make it look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Finish what you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard responsibility tip: Don't leave known, wide-scale problems behind for the next generation to solve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When crew members are unsuccessful, urge them to try again. Encouragement and persistence may be all they need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Bathrooms are unseemly. Keep them out of sight and don't talk about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep a log of your journey. You will understand better by writing it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There is always a non-obvious third option. When caught between a rock and a hard place, find a jackhammer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Conducting an experiment with an unknown outcome is time well spent, even if the result disappoints you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it so the crew has real time monitoring of your enterprise's critical systems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Forgive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Obedience never lasts long when it's based solely on punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If a crew member needs to become more responsible, give them more responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard drama tip: If it weren't done in the nick of time, it wouldn't be called saving the day. 

Now go finish your taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Use the metric system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: There's no need to solve hard problems alone. Admit when you need help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be realistic about your project timelines. Romulus wasn't built in a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Regulations do not cover every situation. Sometimes you have to decide for yourself what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Not all Klingons are violent. Don't be racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Pick your battles. Let some things go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Recognize when you're being hypocritical. Don't wait for others to tell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you've recently turned into a monster, go take a vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be on the same side as the crew, not against them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Calm the hell down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If specific implementation details are important, then include them when giving the order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Yes, the uniforms are tight, but please, eyes up here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Expecting people to work long hours is short-sighted, counter-productive, and potentially dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Break a complex, urgent problem into subcomponents, one for each of your lieutenants to solve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Maintain a slight air of mystery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Add to the group energy of the room, or leave. Don't be bored. Don't be boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Experiment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Know who you really are and what really matters to you. Then let the crew know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Everyone's a critic, but some criticisms are more correct than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard writing tip: Getting your point across is more important than following archaic rules. It's okay to boldly split infinitives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard rationality tip: There is no such thing as a ghost or a devil. It's just an alien. It's always an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take some alone time. The crew will be fine without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Malfunctioning systems must be fixed right away. There is no excuse for delaying repairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Once all their basic needs are taken care of, crew members are motivated by the meaningfulness of their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep group meetings short. Take your time with one-on-ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The universe is a ridiculous place, but do try to be dignified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Engage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The best creative solutions should come from your crew, not from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Empower others to command when you are unfit. You never know when your mind will be taken over by an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard relaxation tip: Re-read good books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard devops tip: When in doubt, launch a probe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Results are more important than protocol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Most conflict arises out of confusion. Clarify quickly before weapons power up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Remember what you liked to play with as a child. Identify the larger, grown-up versions of those toys at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard theology tip: Unproven gods are hypotheses waiting to be tested. Proven gods are aliens with better technology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: When communication is breaking down, try to speak the other person's language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In an emergency, don't be afraid to let the crew see you in your pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard espionage tip: Stay in character, whatever it takes. http://t.co/AXGA4sSosF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Adopt the latest technologies right away, even if they're in beta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When a crew member's behavior changes significantly, inquire and investigate. It could be important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Succeeding at the very last second is still succeeding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Withhold advice on matters you do not understand.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>