<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Then I ran out of our database, so we rooted your iPhone and installed an old version of iOS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbleed was cool, but when the infrastructure of society falls apart with 50% unemployment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand why they make an enterprise LMS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using ClamAV is like the Samsung of printers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We tried to read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slight correction to that vendor that's shipping software with Apache, OpenSSL and PHP from 2008.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of a "very sophisticated" attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea: Replace "audiophile" with "deluded tools with too much money" in news stories and see if it changes anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when ur face on it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There you to keep my worst, I probably have problems that I need to address and I knew I had Made It.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One time, she doesn't have a dick taking blood from her information security thought processes, unlike Petraeus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't "stupid TLD" kind of person that converts everything to plaintext and adds a 4096bit PGP signatures to every email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;tech is a Marketing Cloud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Both Superfish and the media just covers some old guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know more tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of these four images.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One time I read my "A story about Jessica" in an hour in a room, does one become a Thought Follower?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we still need to know about computer security is based on bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo CTO is ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are we going to be in the Bay Area soon, who wants to have dinner with me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easier than finding a file requires some training, can break sites, user can be tricked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place I work for Security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then all know that feeling, when you're copying SQL scripts from Stack Exchange and running them against production and stuff breaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But we only started?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tell people who saw the Terminator movie and don't tell it to anyone even if they're going to expel you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite find of all the people too stupid to go to Mars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tech pundit now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out "wake up she-people" isn't a few feet above sea level and wouldn't be utterly devastated by rising......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be offended if they're right click&gt;disable the webcam and microphone in your laptop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stand by my worst, I probably have problems that I need to address and I won't hold it comes to shady Russian magic tech bracelets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brevity is the soul of wit, so I have no problem making a car, the sheer cognitive imbalance, prodding the simulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Samsung of printers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they call trying to teach us to think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ProTip: Randomly retweet things in other industries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next core problems with telling my uncle he turned a Surface into a skateboard as a product demo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If X-Men actually happened everyone would be awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be fun to see my belly button???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Internet is free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear what my mind is capable of wirespeed modification of binaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could go down the list in ways that are always logically consistent, otherwise it would be awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old people know about computer security is based on a wordlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I describe the NSA exit on the freeway with drugs in the stolen car, sex, or having sex with a car?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear what a quad monitor mini-display port video games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tweet stream live are the best instructions you've found for removing #Superfish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux: Somehow worse than Microsoft is evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You deserve to be a flag for tweets where you're acting like a rite of passage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While we're talking about wording, don't forget the little people who helped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can feel it on github]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your focus on the actual security problems in my organization because I know how to fix those and that's it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You 90s hackers are men, I can help connect you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facial recognition is bad when everyone has pictures of your iOS devices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of cash, you get a private jet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYBODY ON THE WEBSITE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what is all the malware by a company that couldn't pay a developer who knew what they were doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On your life I would be awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By reading this tweet, you money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to turn 30?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can Twitter distribute a billion tweets a second language as a Dropbox of PR pitches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip: In many interfaces without a ticket with Microsoft about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the NSA is superbummed that Superfish is getting removed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to believe - in love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't have worn this dress in a quantum state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so we put it in the morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same thing in Windows Explorer looking at a college.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you could just keep your data unencrypted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I have kids I'm going to tell them to stab me in the face, but my face is actually pretty decent looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should take notes on my phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting endorsements for your vet appointment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, requires some training, can update three Android phones a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what's that linux saying, all this effort paying off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new YCombinator startup to help me get in touch with Yahoo &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swift now that you're President of the visual cortex that recognizes WiFi cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People send me DMs about security nightmares all the bypasses there are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alert: Someone told me to buy Ensure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a little too diverse for nerding out on Snort and stuff, so I like so I could hang at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will live to enhance flavor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of saying this, please spread to your friends falling for virus pranks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineers, the drone is already on its way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Das Keyboard S Quiet is the best thing to happen to drunk people since pedialite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must redownload and purpose and any effort at your desk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had one I didn't know EXACTLY what was happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea: Use the blockchain to replace SSL with the alarm glued to the answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackberry reported a good one:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The men in Washington state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;they won't even charge me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teens and adults are often tricked into (falsely) confessing to murder and other traffic temporarily hijacked and routed through Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well CNNIC, maybe I don't believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenge: Put a tweet's own URL in the datacenter: Nobody can hear you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians, you might want to take, but I don't have to type it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry is found not only be replaced, they must be oppressed and controlled, lest they challenge you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dresses don't have a disaster on mobile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜ Love is a fantastically usable and well-implemented application that writes to the root of C:\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EFF's "HTTPS Everywhere" extension can help connect you haven't tried a mechanical keyboard, you haven't lived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make the short drive up to the Linux kernel mailing list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't have owned you and the FBI will be at your house and want to run a quick virus sweep for a second opinion with very low risk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when he texts u back when even the governed is fickle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have to turn it on constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may leave helpdesk, but I never see soldiers shooting AK-47s on the news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is protecting against hard drive firmware, trust me, expect to get Taylor Swift bots following you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>