<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/cydco6IX16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/iLkPJGJOHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/rreIgIsgwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/Y8j4gRcx0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/zlMqJv4vGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/JbanZoKLJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/zApzAEF09q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/XFwoOXSMqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/LpCQ3mCw3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ETWjxocxCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/qJAU5sQ0zs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/z3udN9xRsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/VaMbB6m3k9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/Y8j4gRcx0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/XFwoOXSMqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/sSQYDRSwVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/mIYJj2gQEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/AnkIbV4qRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/ncdbJvvoZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/cPd23EQDpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/ikBeIK9Edl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/z38TLv3lER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/5BTZJ5WZxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/8WNFNIQjyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/tCoXJzTHU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/TQhwIfszf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SEEzjoAQFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/vaPHPr0Sl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/WJyLvIMmUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/yL9GXBXbE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/xohDDQJPzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/OfbsaSYuH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/mcbA8CVMoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/9wKpSTkHCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/XYnc7QH1KI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/zegZaBhKYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/ek14RARO0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/XD6nNCVwq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/lfiBPb9EWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/IWldf65SWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/BTuF8cD0DS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/IfgNppP7vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/1qASVU7lCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/7cxiDH0Cs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/4q75g1OsmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/NW9FQP3icg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/z5hNfvrB7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/EbMgLXzodC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/2XuclvD62v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/T0p0gtLpOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/AZ1DJflXKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/GSUfUWJ5S3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/wciZeBYpvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/xJJ5f4PFmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/gcmQnPe70T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/as3KYc0TsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/XFwoOXSMqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/NeZO4EMqMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>