<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Ivanka proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that small business owners are enemies of the people. Benjamin Netanyahu stalks the neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Mike Huckabee persuades Rick Perry that Communists are draining the swamp. Bill Kristol plays Candy Crush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Mitch McConnell reveals to President Trump that the Bushes are clamoring for attention. Peggy Noonan tries bareback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Rick Snyder announces to Rick Perry that Wall Street bankers are not to be trusted. An ambassador develops an addiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terminally ill Nikki Haley decides not to tell Jeff Sessions that tech executives are actually gay. A "fixer" attends a funeral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a sleepover, Mike Huckabee divulges to Jeff Sessions that Russian officials are moving into Trump Tower. The gardener reads a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jealous General Mattis reluctantly explains to President Trump that prostitutes are calling for impeachment. An ex-girlfriend cleans up after the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Matt Bevin convinces President Trump that Israeli politicians are unlikely to vote. Kayleigh McEnany hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Jared Kushner boldly informs Jeff Sessions that white women are struggling to raise money. Bobby Jindal quotes Goebbels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of guests, Nikki Haley mistakenly tells Rick Perry that environmental activists are digging holes in the yard. Alex Jones watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Jason Chaffetz persuades Katrina Pierson that school teachers are not coming over for Christmas. James Caan knocks over a bust of Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an elevator, Pete Sessions calmly tells President Trump that the New York Mets are patriotic Americans. A White House tourist redecorates the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New York, Wilbur Ross fails to persuade Kellyanne Conway that Chicago teens are drug addicts. Milo Yiannopoulos fails the bar again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Elaine Chao convinces President Trump that Biggie and Tupac are just like the rest of us. An adorable orphan paints Trump's official portrait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Saturday, Steven Mnuchin explains to President Trump that WSJ reporters are just like the rest of us. Jeffrey Lord wears a hoodie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a funeral, Mitch McConnell overhears someone tell Rick Perry that civil rights activists are refusing to cooperate. Vladimir Putin advocates for the white man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Paul Ryan divulges to Melania that skeptics are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. Pat Buchanan has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, VP Pence rudely informs Jeff Sessions that Scientologists are no threat at all. Jesus Christ learns the art of fisticuffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of guests, Roger Stone divulges to Betsy DeVos that Wall Street bankers are capable of great things. Karl Rove learns what love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Rand Paul fails to convince Kellyanne Conway that Native Americans are total losers. Arnold Schwarzenegger hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During an interview, VP Pence fails to persuade Omarosa Manigault that rappers are requesting donations. Victoria Jackson loads a pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Sam Brownback politely tells Jeff Sessions that atheists are very affordable. An ambassador hosts the clip show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, Steve Scalise persuades President Trump that Russian officials are deserving of a tax cut. Barry Goldwater's ghost wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Mitch McConnell decides not to tell Melania that the Feds are potential voters. An obnoxious neighbor goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Lamar Alexander overhears someone tell Melania that liberal activists are coming over for Christmas. An ambassador goes hairless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Lindsey Graham announces to President Trump that ISIS soldiers are part of the shadow government. Tila Tequila forgets to flush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Rick Snyder insists to Betsy DeVos that Tumblr users are special guests. Adriana Cohen argues with everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weary Ivanka tells Betsy DeVos that ACLU members are buying up Trump properties. Lou Dobbs ruins Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Mike Huckabee calmly tells President Trump that Japanese reporters are disciples of Cthulhu. Jon Voight edits Wikipedia pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Paul LePage reveals to Katrina Pierson that leftist college students are big donors. Jesus Christ is thrown in Guantanamo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a prank, Justin Amash accidentally convinces Ben Carson that NAACP members are untrustworthy. Don King gets voted out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, VP Pence convinces Betsy DeVos that cult leaders are fans of TrumpCare. Cthulhu joins the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Elaine Chao reluctantly admits to Jeff Sessions that KGB spies are happy for Trump. An obsequious reporter moves in next door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a conference call, VP Pence confesses to Rick Perry that the hired help are filling up American prisons. A "fixer" drunkenly accosts strangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Carly Fiorina patiently explains to Rick Perry that unicorns are organizing resistance. Glenn Beck goes shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Steve Scalise carefully explains to President Trump that felons are demanding refunds. Newt Gingrich gets an ulcer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Marine One, Mitch McConnell accidentally convinces Omarosa Manigault that Wall Street bankers are not really important. An ambassador cooks breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Sam Brownback reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that angry parents are enlightened leaders. Barry Goldwater's ghost rejects an overture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Marco Rubio tells President Trump that Russian officials are watching Fox News. Michael Savage discovers reddit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Carly Fiorina carefully explains to Betsy DeVos that wealthy executives are refusing to cooperate. The butler records all conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Reince Preibus tries to convince Kellyanne Conway that Japanese reporters are true Americans. Melania's bodyguard picks a scab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Roger Stone fails to convince President Trump that Nordstroms employees are coming over for Christmas. Mike Tyson quotes John Wayne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Ted Cruz overhears someone tell President Trump that the Koch brothers are useful idiots. A White House tourist meets an end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient John Kasich fails to convince Ben Carson that angry parents are happy for Trump. Melania's bodyguard commits seppuku.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Sean Spicer decides not to tell Melania that Nation of Islam members are selling land in National Parks. Erick Erickson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Mitch McConnell fails to convince President Trump that the Romneys are filing frivolous lawsuits. An ex-girlfriend listens on the extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a confusing mixup, Pete Sessions overhears someone tell Omarosa Manigault that government employees are international bankers. Alex Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Lindsey Graham mistakenly tells Jeff Sessions that Jews are moving into Trump Tower. Pat Buchanan brown-noses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Matt Bevin overhears someone tell President Trump that cult leaders are not that horny. Scott Baio knocks over a bust of Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, David Shulkin reluctantly explains to President Trump that NAACP members are filing another lawsuit. Rush Limbaugh tries too hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Kevin McCarthy patiently explains to Katrina Pierson that neoconservatives are supporters of Brexit. Barry Goldwater's ghost wins the lottery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Sam Brownback mistakenly tells Katrina Pierson that phone companies are in the Oval Office. The butler prints out all the emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Ryan Zinke divulges to Ben Carson that ex-cons are real. Sarah Palin joins a sex club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent David Shulkin tries to convince Melania that Texans are really good at dancing. An adorable orphan learns how to gamble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a joke, Steven Mnuchin decides not to tell Kellyanne Conway that virgins are Schwarzenegger fans. Lou Dobbs goes to the grocery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, Ryan Zinke reluctantly admits to President Trump that cult leaders are digging holes in the yard. A local TV anchor pees on the rug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a sleepover, Hope Hicks informs Rick Perry that the minions of Soros are lurking everywhere. The valet pirates movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Wilbur Ross patiently explains to President Trump that reporters are double agents. The White House chef argues with everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Rick Snyder proclaims to President Trump that millennials are useful idiots. Ted Nugent adopts a black child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Rick Scott patiently explains to Rick Perry that wealthy executives are not coming over for Christmas. Benjamin Netanyahu wears a cowboy hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Lamar Alexander announces to President Trump that NRA members are privy to many secrets. Kayleigh McEnany tries yoga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Rick Santorum insists to President Trump that prison guards are ripe for a prank. David Brooks wears a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Stephen Miller convinces President Trump that tech executives are capable of great things. Trump's body double wears pajamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, David Shulkin convinces Betsy DeVos that international bankers are utterly useless. Stacey Dash picks a booger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a scheme, Reince Preibus overhears someone tell President Trump that NRA members are buying up Trump properties. Jesus Christ tries MDMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Lamar Alexander rudely informs President Trump that Israeli politicians are big donors. Ivanka's bodyguard audibly farts at a state dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, H.R. McMaster persuades Melania that MSNBC pundits are hiding in Trump Tower. Ted Nugent buries the evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Paul Ryan divulges to President Trump that prostitutes are excessively fastidious. Milo Yiannopoulos proposes marriage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday, Reince Preibus admits to Rick Perry that the stars of Friends are part of the prank. Ann Coulter interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, H.R. McMaster reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that CIA agents are conservative Christians. Corey Lewandowski celebrates an anniversary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Louie Gohmert tells Omarosa Manigault that drug dealers are capable bureaucrats. Chris Christie plays solitaire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Jared Kushner explains to President Trump that Protestants are actually pretty decent. Bobby Jindal has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Sam Brownback confesses to Katrina Pierson that the kids are ruining "The Apprentice." Mike Tyson quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Jared Kushner overhears someone tell Melania that ABC reporters are part of the deep state. Sarah Palin bogarts the joint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a prank, Paul LePage reluctantly admits to Katrina Pierson that the interns are always strapped. Scottie Nell Hughes joins the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing poker, Sean Spicer insists to Jeff Sessions that the interns are actually shapeshifting aliens. Michelle Malkin has to fly coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shivering uncontrollably, Justin Amash decides not to tell President Trump that Trump's sons are pretty adorable. James Woods finds change in the couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Hope Hicks calmly tells President Trump that Baptists are filing frivolous lawsuits. Chris Christie tries on new outfits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, John Kasich fails to persuade President Trump that rappers are pretty adorable. Victoria Jackson interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Ted Cruz rudely informs Ben Carson that unicorns are moving into Trump Tower. Michael Savage uses Comic Sans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via email, Sean Spicer insists to Jeff Sessions that Russian spies are actually shapeshifting aliens. A White House tourist warms up the audience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Nikki Haley boldly informs President Trump that conspiracy theorists are always strapped. Charles Krauthammer herds goats in the garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Elaine Chao informs Jeff Sessions that Amazon and Walmart are infiltrators. An obnoxious neighbor takes a nap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Scott Pruitt reluctantly explains to Jeff Sessions that White House employees are planning something ominous. Trump's body double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shivering uncontrollably, Peter King accidentally convinces Jeff Sessions that WSJ reporters are total winners. Ann Coulter starts a business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, Steve Bannon boldly informs Melania that the Clintons are still waiting on hold. Ann Coulter jumps off the roof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Steve Bannon decides not to tell President Trump that the New Black Panthers are terrorists. James Woods harasses celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a brief chat, VP Pence reluctantly explains to President Trump that government employees are not that horny. Scottie Nell Hughes passes the Voight-Kampff test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Matt Bevin informs Jeff Sessions that Baptists are double agents. Ted Nugent rides in Air Force One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over dinner, Elaine Chao reluctantly explains to Ben Carson that North Koreans are old school. Trump's bodyguard records all conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Wilbur Ross calmly tells President Trump that corporate lobbyists are on point. Sarah Palin tries to slip in through a window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evil twin of Elaine Chao persuades Jeff Sessions that oil executives are in on the joke. God Almighty goes hairless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Lindsey Graham fails to convince Jeff Sessions that Russian officials are harmless. A mysterious man learns telepathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a drugged haze, Mitch McConnell boldly informs Rick Perry that Iranian immigrants are indebted to Satan. Alex Jones gets a makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, General Mattis calmly tells Ben Carson that Scientologists are faithful Republicans. Karl Rove pretends to be an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a strip club, Louie Gohmert convinces Betsy DeVos that Pussy Riot are true Americans. Scott Baio abandons social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Lindsey Graham informs Rick Perry that ex-cons are hilarious. The maid picks a booger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Sean Spicer rudely informs President Trump that Tumblr users are not returning phone calls. Clint Eastwood goes commando.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Rex Tillerson tries to persuade President Trump that angry parents are fiercely loyal. Michelle Malkin orders takeout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Jared Kushner proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that abortion doctors are drug addicts. Clint Eastwood donates three dollars.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>