<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Officer Risk Management Department: Information Security Officer Risk Management Department Job Duties: Provide quality customer service and work toward the generation, promotion and maintenance of a quality work environment for the… https://t.co/pSpIpvdVPD https://t.co/CFKUbP6X45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: NEW YORK LOCAL CANDIDATES ONLY NGKF is seeking a senior MicroStrategy Developer/Architect. The ideal candidate will have a minimum of 5 years of experience designing and developing business intelligence solutions using… https://t.co/anmyUaNA5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Vampyr' Review: A Game Whose Messiness Doesn't Weaken Its Bite: The game manages to mechanize something that role-playing games have broadly bungled: ulterior motives. https://t.co/LoO4HCpGu9 https://t.co/hRsxJvSru1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Networking, Work From Home: New York City, NY Full-time $100k – $175k Posted Today If you are a pre-sales engineer / solution architect with a networking background, please read on! You have worked with networking and wireless networking… https://t.co/aBbg3wZmmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network / Systems Administrator: Are you a self motivated Network/Systems Engineer looking for a new and exciting opportunity? We are looking for a Network Administrator to maintain a reliable, secure and efficient data communications network. The ideal… https://t.co/S0tXyyU9Kd https://t.co/uVpPHNLz7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk Calms Down, and More From Tesla's Shareholder Meeting: At the automaker’s annual shareholder meeting, the CEO struck a conciliatory note while providing updates on Model 3 production, Autopilot, Tesla's Supercharger network, veganism, and more. https://t.co/olzwpsWRcH https://t.co/IlEKMh8Ihj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/vi79QOiYZ7 https://t.co/qQq8nvMgRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batch Software Engineers: BATCH SOFTWARE ENGINEERS *We are unable to sponsor as this is a permanent full time role* RESPONSIBILITIES * Design, develop, deploy and support batch systems. * Architect systems that can handle billions of events per day. *… https://t.co/fEoAcV9j8k https://t.co/H22st3ma5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elections Don’t Work at All. You Can Blame the Math: San Francisco still doesn’t have a new mayor. But that’s democracy for you. https://t.co/fdGHzFAAPA https://t.co/2mEwPzUH2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Support agency in Hawaii as Cisco Network Engineer doing the following: * Perform configuration of Cisco Routers/Switches * Work with local team to support network infrastructure * Administration/engineering of cisco firewalls Required… https://t.co/mvbgRX3yvD https://t.co/BrLT0k9kBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer in Test (C++, Java, Python): Tableau Software is hiring now! Check out this great Senior Software Engineer in Test (C++, Java, Python) role. Sign Up Login Back to view jobs We’re growing fast! Check out the latest jobs we have… https://t.co/tLbOcWLvV3 https://t.co/iJD3O4h2Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dawn of Mobile Convenience Stores—and (Maybe) Free Car Rides: Startups like Cargo, which allow you to buy convenience-store items from ride-hailing drivers, point to a future where your commute doesn’t cost a cent—because you, friend, are the product. https://t.co/XTiMPH9Mfl https://t.co/yy1x0hyxrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Developer: Hadoop Developer Ref No.: 18-24177 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Role name Hadoop Developer Role Description As a Data Engineer, you will work closely with our data scientists implementing complex data projects with a focus on… https://t.co/Ke5HQjq1ba https://t.co/AEtSXjIWdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Android Developer: Prestigious Technologies Firm is currently seeking a Lead Android Developer. Candidate will be responsible for leading development and implementation of innovative mobile applications for Android devices. RESPONSIBILITIES: Develop… https://t.co/7tgV0ZMAqA https://t.co/oVDJ6WSvjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physics Face-off: The Momentum Principle vs. Newton's 2nd Law: Which method is better? It’s complicated. https://t.co/Y07MiuSEHp https://t.co/quyJX9n3wI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humans Tracked Iceland's Glaciers For Ages. Now, Tech Does: Citizen scientists have served as glacier trackers in Iceland—and witnesses to the ravages of climate change—for generations. Will they continue? https://t.co/XZbTX7tzJF https://t.co/oHG8GMlfnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer The Technical Support Engineer is a critical role withing the TGW Lifetime Services (LTS) team, providing highly technical customer service and support, focusing on the TGW Software solutions. This… https://t.co/dVNldRPwtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel Analyst Support Manager, Sigint or Allsource:   Job Description – Intel Analyst Support Manager, Sigint or Allsource (18005632) Intel Analyst Support Manager, Sigint or Allsource Requisition ID : 18005632 Location : United States-Virginia-Fort… https://t.co/R18QRZiQqP https://t.co/nvZYPTS5LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk and the Unnerving Influence of Twitter's Power Users: Twitter has increasingly become a place where a small number of elite users commandeer huge followings—and they don't always use their power for good. https://t.co/aVFFMT6jGu https://t.co/VNwOKLLrs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Statistical Programmer: Xencor Inc. is an innovative biotechnology company located in the Los Angeles area (near Pasadena) and in San Diego. We have an excellent opportunity for an experienced Quality Assurance Senior Associate up to a Senior… https://t.co/1u93XUrU4e https://t.co/GpZm5fNoZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/C# Developer: .NET/C# Developer ================= Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description We are seeking a .NET/C# developer with… https://t.co/INp5YHzfvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps candidates with API: DevOps candidates with API RTP, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 05/31/18, Posted Date – 05/31/18 Primary SkillsDevOps,redhatTax TermsC2COverview We are actively seeking a talented DevOps with RedHat API to work… https://t.co/pgIvlakv8q https://t.co/Rd678VtKX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Materials Cost Analyst (2 openings): Materials Cost Analyst(2 openings)SMS InfoComm Corp.Grapevine, TX Control &amp; improve the procurement material cost processes &amp; procedures. Analyze cost &amp; prepare report for Purchasing Department. Conduct data &amp; cost… https://t.co/6UJaywRi07 https://t.co/6jknBedHf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software EngineerPhoton Infotech, Inc.Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Software Engineer (Provide tech. consulting &amp; development of app. in Java, J2EE, Spring &amp; Microservices. Analyze the business requirements &amp;… https://t.co/uqWI26gnm3 https://t.co/543pAFfrDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – General: UST an IT Corp., Aliso Viejo (Orange County), CA. has an opening for a Systems Analyst-General (Job No 0001A): Will collect; review, analyze &amp; recommend technology &amp; tools; Use independent judgment &amp; discretion to analyze… https://t.co/AXa7kky11j https://t.co/Ejius500Ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response Consultant: COMPANY BACKGROUND: Our clientis a security advisory firm specializing in Data Breach Response and Risk Management. With a highly-successful track record of delivering mission critical cybersecurity solutions, they are… https://t.co/Viy79nDdRd https://t.co/vF0snpJqDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valve Squashes Decade-Old Steam Security Bug, and More Security News This Week: A Ticketfly hack, the Kaspersky ban stays, and more security news this week. https://t.co/4slnmUzDAD https://t.co/BHLk6Xx6NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position Title Project Manager – Information Technology Services: Number of Openings 1 Closing Date Open Until Filled Type of Search Staff Who May This position is open to all qualified applicants. Position Number ****** Campus St. Paul Department/Unit… https://t.co/7DhcY76Y39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Payments / Payouts: Description At YapStone, we approach payments with the same startup mentality that we had when we launched our first payment solution in 1999. We are now focused on combining our entrepreneurial spirit with… https://t.co/nBdyRhaswq https://t.co/ku39xCivH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-level Network Security Engineer: Jobs – InfoGroupNorthWest – ************ – ******************** – – SERVICES – PEOPLE SOLUTIONS – Contract Resources – Direct Hire Services – HR Outsource – PROJECT SOLUTIONS – Software Development – Systems… https://t.co/aWWe5bXdTO https://t.co/H2GFN3rSzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Report Developer: Job ID: EMO-******* Description: Located in one of the following locations – Austin, Houston, Richardson or San Antonio, TX this position is responsible utilizing .NET and SQL Server for creating reports, insights and… https://t.co/BJerLWmxVR https://t.co/9dQayhb8za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Norfolk, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/KAyy6efc8C https://t.co/Tn1N5s8Hfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWDC 2018: The Best Part About Apple's Keynote Is What Wasn't There: Taking a pause to work on stability is exactly the right move for iOS 12 and macOS Mojave. https://t.co/KsK2Tsbsoy https://t.co/Y3eUtH1pey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Lead: Software Quality Assurance (SQA) Lead: Prvd. Test mgmt. for mult. deliverables &amp; drive dev. &amp; execution of QA &amp; QC delivery prc. Function as single POC between governance &amp; testing teams. Must possess exp. in coordinating… https://t.co/QUqWtt2Ep3 https://t.co/crAsWjc5Ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst: Tesla, Inc. has the following positions available at its Palo Alto corporate headquarters and the Tesla campuses in Fremont and San Mateo. PALO ALTO POSITIONS Engineering Firmware Engineer. GG-031191. Approx. 15% travel… https://t.co/GOs4lEJuqV https://t.co/Ix2HhqE6Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: Puyallup Tribe Of IndiansJob AnnouncementOpens: May 29, 2018 Closes: July 11, 2018Job Title: It Support Technician Department: Information TechnologiesReports To: It Support Manager Hours: Full-time 40 Hours/weekSalary: Depends On… https://t.co/MjBiDLTBJs https://t.co/K4BEBywNgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Wars News: That Big 'Solo' Cameo Was a Last-Minute Decision: Yes, that thing everyone is talking about almost didn't happen. https://t.co/NdC821pum2 https://t.co/iWa8HuEoC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PeopleSoft Developer – Data Conversion: Leads and performs conversion development and unit testing for the IPPS-A project. Participates in development, integration and deployment of solutions. Provides data models from business systems planning… https://t.co/Q2aP9zSM8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems Administrator 3/4 (HIRT SOMP):   Job Description – Cyber Systems Administrator 3/4 (HIRT SOMP) (18003331) Cyber Systems Administrator 3/4 (HIRT SOMP) Requisition ID : 18003331 Location : United States-Virginia-Arlington US Citizenship… https://t.co/fjLSp6tb3y https://t.co/9bLFcWEvbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Train Engineer:   Job Description – Release Train Engineer (00001OPX) Job Description Release Train Engineer – 00001OPX  Are you looking to make a difference in a patient’s life? At AmerisourceBergen, you will find an innovative culture that is… https://t.co/kshtG0W4V6 https://t.co/ek9zFQzMB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer I: Senior Software Engineer I Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture – History –… https://t.co/F0xANNEEDa https://t.co/lcNWMJSixD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst III or IV: Job ID: 35640 Business Systems Analyst III or IV (Database Administration) Location: FL Pensacola – GPO Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Job Description Employee Perks Why You Will Love Being Part… https://t.co/mmGxmsacj3 https://t.co/HrssuXrLcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Software Developer: – iOS Software Developer Company Amrock Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Who We Are We’re Amrock, the nation’s largest FinTech provider of title insurance, valuations and closing services. We’re a preferred provider to nine of the top… https://t.co/VAFJOwtWy6 https://t.co/oHMAseVlM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Scientists Turned This Taxidermy Bird Into a Robot: Spoiler: It’s a sage grouse sexbot. https://t.co/G2AOdQMoq9 https://t.co/fey9sO3zEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Android Developer: A Cupertino Silicon Valley technology startup, with an ownership group track record of success (previous startup was sold to a tech giant), is looking for a Android Developer to assist in the development of their media… https://t.co/6q9j0MnOgU https://t.co/XytILkAQ4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: The Global Technology Services organization is seeking a Senior Network Engineer to design, prototype, configure, and evaluate multiple network topologies in support of product design verification and the infrastructure life… https://t.co/OlaNpk9435 https://t.co/XSbbRctsh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questioning Truth, Reality, and the Role of Scientific Progress: In an era when untestable ideas such as the multiverse hold sway, Michela Massimi defends science from those who think it hopelessly unmoored from physical reality. https://t.co/BNnK7iUr6r https://t.co/okKjvfEtOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides integrated services to the… https://t.co/kuYz1CXS6l https://t.co/BcsROzkFIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Rental Cars Fade Away, Avis Will Try Anything to Survive: The 72-year-old company is ready to try just about anything, from bikes to robots, to stick around. https://t.co/ZW2QRfMQgg https://t.co/qeyRxQVMrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Real-time Control / Power Systems: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As… https://t.co/7nKpoHNx5u https://t.co/GLOZ47DVlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4Chan Is Turning 15—And Remains the Internet's Teenager: The chaotic message board is the soul of the internet, the deep source of its sights and sounds—for worse and, occasionally, for better. https://t.co/bf5ivyr6Hc https://t.co/0WxXqinCpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer: Tack Mobile has an opening for an experienced iOS developer to join our team. We’re a mobile design and development firm based in Denver, focused on developing and designing solutions for mobile and connected hardware devices.… https://t.co/MrIdW9Wgcd https://t.co/f4RK52t1O0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How San Quentin Inmates Built JOLT, a Search Engine for Prison: After learning to code from nonprofit The Last Mile, four inmates built JOLT, a search engine to help further their studies. https://t.co/vkS9dTYXsr https://t.co/gUptN4ZUOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack/UI Developer (Java): Job TitleFull Stack/UI Developer (Java) – ID:31472 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsUI programming using Java jQuery, bootstrap and CSS NEED MORE Resumes LocationPlano, TX Date Posted04/11/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE… https://t.co/Jf0YQjt7cn https://t.co/MBBLbGkNlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Support Analyst (Salesforce): Description At YapStone, we approach payments with the same startup mentality that we had when we launched our first payment solution in 1999. We are now focused on combining our entrepreneurial spirit with our immense… https://t.co/7Mg25hQNBU https://t.co/vSKDzKZnTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WINTEL Systems Administrator: WINTEL Systems Administrator will report directly to the L2 Operations Leader and will provide central accountability for all Infrastructure Server Services which are the activities associated with the operations support,… https://t.co/TnSjfbrA1Z https://t.co/QHFTdj2f7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: Description Join the Information Technology Services team with The Space Telescope Science Institute (STScI) as we continue to expand the frontiers of space astronomy. STScI is located on the Johns Hopkins University Campus in Baltimore, MD.… https://t.co/ED5oz69iqW https://t.co/bleZ4d8IYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Workers #15923433: Field Worker (Watermelon Harvest and Pumpkin Harvest) Rancho Nuevo Harvesting, Inc., is seeking 80 temporary Field Workers (Watermelon Harvest and Pumpkin Harvest) to perform labor in fields located in Riverside County, CA.… https://t.co/yLan7000PE https://t.co/vIuGyi5AxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canceling 'Roseanne' Wasn't About Conviction, It Was About Capital: ABC acted swiftly yesterday, but it may not be making the grand gesture of civility many seem to think it has. https://t.co/gGzfZjshP9 https://t.co/Om82GL3YuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level CRM Developer: Celedon Partners is looking for a talented and experienced Jr/Mid-Level CRM Developer with a passion for making a direct difference and eagerness to accelerate their career in a small and growing consulting company. This is an… https://t.co/Z9NcYONMBR https://t.co/Hwf65soFGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director CRM: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the world? If you’re… https://t.co/w5VLDAzKMl https://t.co/NeOkgNqEIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Integrated Product Team Lead: Req ID : 430273BR Job Code/Title : E1953:Project Engineer Sr Job Description : The TUHP PSI engineering team has an immediate opening for a highly motivated technical lead with 5+ years in the role of developing and… https://t.co/Cq7YV2xkQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Description Project Manager Project Manager (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are most well-known for adding beauty and structure to communities… https://t.co/fAGddChwS8 https://t.co/sIRqpEpfIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've Never Seen Waves Like This Before: Photographer Rachael Talibart spends months waiting for the perfect shot. https://t.co/ukYntN0leA https://t.co/JTlPEofT0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer in Test: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is our global vision and the… https://t.co/MC6zSs9uNX https://t.co/HpWQmw0PBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TECHNICAL APPLICATIONS SPECIALIST – US: POSITION SUMMARY The Technical Applications Specialist receives complaints and inquiries from customers and partners for all Luminex supported products. The Technical Applications Specialist will document all… https://t.co/lwSMPog566 https://t.co/ZJgfFvMgPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Store Support Associate Livonia, MI: Store Support Associate Livonia, MI Business Stores – Sears Hourly Job Description The Store Support Associate is responsible for providing a great Member experience, contributing to the overall financial performance… https://t.co/US2ftQiITk https://t.co/0cQ6WYcBCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Softbank Pours $2.25 Billion Into GM's Self-Driving Car Biz: It’s the biggest deal yet in a nascent but booming industry, and confirms the automaker’s status as one of the leading players. https://t.co/kZWV8cKioI https://t.co/MaGwzDbodj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23andMe Is Suing Ancestry Over Some Pretty Ancient IP: And the outcome of the case could reshape the genetic genealogy testing industry. https://t.co/lw1z2m0peP https://t.co/CY8QhtktlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Tesla, Inc. has the following positions available at its Palo Alto corporate headquarters and the Tesla campuses in Fremont and San Mateo. PALO ALTO POSITIONS Engineering Firmware Engineer. GG-031191. Approx. 15% travel required… https://t.co/a7CoO9dFg2 https://t.co/CsqwGOZjjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer RF Microwave Design 5:   Job Description – Engineer RF Microwave Design 5 (17017714) Engineer RF Microwave Design 5 Requisition ID : 17017714 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/20FRwMbGRU https://t.co/egjCc57Eer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer: Senior Programmer Location: Quantico, VA Job Code: 2296 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S.… https://t.co/69Gk1KkC3G https://t.co/dykQGHNVA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services: Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA or Mountain View, CA The Twilio platform enables companies to integrate communications directly into their applications via… https://t.co/9Pt1wywdTL https://t.co/AfUWhAZ80a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IDS Analyst IV/Network Security: Req ID 95048BR Business Title IDS Analyst IV/Network Security Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Arlington Clearance Level Needed Top Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a… https://t.co/6GRQuQLCPy https://t.co/93m2NaGAgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Architect – Healthcare/Educational projects URGENT!: Dallas, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Principal Architect with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive base salary open depending on… https://t.co/sxbPRE1DTJ https://t.co/rYWiHwS8jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Junior: Software Engineer – Junior Jobs in Huntington Beach at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services –… https://t.co/gd21Jnh1T1 https://t.co/ZcZThJzAZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change Made Zombie Ants Even More Cunning: The parasitic fungus that drives ants to sabotage their own colonies has adapted to zombify their quarry better in different climates. https://t.co/5LBa0xaiAn https://t.co/8vU9zZ4ZJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Channel Solutions Specialist #A3Y2NQ: Technology: Apple Inc. has multiple openings for the following in Austin, TX: Channel Solutions Specialist (Req# A3Y2NQ) Assist with Apple’s Authorized Service Channels via Apple Authorized Service Providers (AASPs)… https://t.co/vRPmyg5Syu https://t.co/3OuDsWDSjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Get a Robot to (One Day) Do Your Chores: If we are going to have home assistants that set our tables and fold our clothes, we’re going to have to train them in simulations first. https://t.co/bRWdYWCSXX https://t.co/efitcdPg1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Ghetto Gastro’s ‘Black Power Kitchen’ of Tomorrow: Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram are redefining the underground culinary world, and young chefs are eliminating gatekeepers while they cater to poor communities and celebs alike. Exhibit A:… https://t.co/VjV0JlFJUQ https://t.co/TSntkQIXun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Trunomi [*********************** is looking for a full-stack developer to help build out our product portfolio. A full stack developer is a master of breadth and quick learning and ideally has experience and expertise all across the… https://t.co/8sIwpqluL4 https://t.co/MCI6JXYQkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Engineer: Nuvi aggregates hundreds of millions of pieces of social content that are created every day via Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, and just about every internet publishing outlet on the web. We help the worlds leading brands and… https://t.co/znjyj31crQ https://t.co/OVXjLxup74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Is Giving Scientists Its Data to Fight Misinformation: For the first time, researchers will be able to access Facebook's data and publish their findings without pre-approval from the company. https://t.co/QIzfcqhOGY https://t.co/aY7u3j9Ifb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R48295 Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA has multiple positions available for a Senior Software Engineer. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp;… https://t.co/kuQnbSTmdY https://t.co/2hSsXs7Aui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Applications Engineer / Applications Engineer: ENGINEER Sr. Applications Engineer/ Applications Engineer Job site: San Jose, CA. Send resume to: Monolithic Power Systems, Inc. 79 Great Oaks Blvd., San Jose, CA 95119recblid… https://t.co/8eLpsANNoy https://t.co/APj8BKESFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Reporting: NTSP Holding Company, LLC. seeks Master’s + 2 yrs exp./ equiv.: Director of Reporting (NTSP): CMS Healthcare, Medical Payer Insurance, Tableau, SPSS, Minitab, BI Tools. Mail resume with job ID to HR: 1701 River Run, Suite 902, Fort… https://t.co/Pne3z27Nf5 https://t.co/8i4cmNXJFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's Nothing Noble about Science’s Nobel Prize Gender Gap: Opinion: Given the dearth of women receiving the top science prizes, it's time for the Nobel Committee to revamp how it awards great work. https://t.co/lXe34oNWNY https://t.co/UQ1DvtqDob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Statistical Programmer: Senior Statistical Programmer, MS degree in Science, Computer Science, Pharmacy or related &amp; 1 year experience : Create migrated datasets &amp; specifications from raw data using Macros &amp; CRF. Develop Generalize utility macros… https://t.co/qyphUWC0oN https://t.co/5Oycv1O3QS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How WIRED Lost $100,000 in Bitcoin: We mined roughly 13 bitcoins and then ripped up our private key. We were stupid—but not alone. https://t.co/jWcKyXgVAB https://t.co/R2FpM7vJXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe DNA Can’t Answer All Our Questions About Heredity: Carl Zimmer's new book _She Has Her Mother’s Laugh_ is a book about the question genetics was invented to answer—and perhaps can't. https://t.co/7V0CqrHLO9 https://t.co/TJX8U82eq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cruise-on-Cruise Crash Reveals the Hardest Thing About Self-Driving Tech: Humans are wild beasts, and they're not getting off the road anytime soon. https://t.co/pGz1ET7cIR https://t.co/UiKknfQDOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the Koala Genome Save the Species From Deforestation and Chlamydia?: Understanding the animal's genes could help combat shrinking habitats and an epidemic of chlamydia. https://t.co/yHoJEUYD9v https://t.co/qONsqaEqDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Engineer #CA1217WX: Product Engineer 2 sought by Skyworks Solutions, Inc., Irvine, CA: Bring Skyworks GSM/EDGE &amp; CDMA/WCDMA PA, DRx, &amp; FEM products into manufacturing.  recblid vw2amssaz0rqp5abls1qrhkwe9ncv7 https://t.co/eOmoVIpEZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Atlanta, GA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! We are currently seeking a Project Manager to join our team. This individual must have experience in all phases of the… https://t.co/A6Vv9XVuka https://t.co/P6U1LARMvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Rise Sr. Superintendent Concrete or Steel Frame (180-200k): San Diego, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Founded in 2000, we are a self-performing owner/builder with the passion to create and manage luxury high rise apartment communities and… https://t.co/xYplIHmZrM https://t.co/wIZuypwxbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence Analyst – Mid:   Job Description – Intelligence Analyst – Mid (18003646) Intelligence Analyst – Mid Requisition ID : 18003646 Location : United States-Virginia-Chantilly US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/rWFhUsjPPS https://t.co/EUv3Ssq7XQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtualization Engineer (EHub): Req ID 98474BR Business Title Virtualization Engineer (EHub) Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Stafford Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities   ManTech is seeking a… https://t.co/NwORZFZABq https://t.co/WIfj4o909B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Program Manager: Req ID : 438630BR Job Code/Title : L3044:Program Management Asc Mgr Job Description : The candidate will serve as one of the deputy program managers within the USS Franchise 1 programs. This position will be located in San Diego,… https://t.co/GPcwaV30p0 https://t.co/4EPfBZNWco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New University Rules Encourage Scientists to Avoid Air Travel: For some researchers it’s a personal choice; other academic departments have to pay carbon offset fees. https://t.co/qMEbzXBaq5 https://t.co/flhBVLbwy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Technical Support Interface #2435404: Engineering Technical Support Interface Bechtel National, Inc. in Richland, WA seeks an Engineering Technical Support Interface to act as technical assistant to a project technical director and manager on… https://t.co/keZIIynbzh https://t.co/j0pKBFBTvr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>