<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Engineer: A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/LMWNyczHXz Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following position (multiple positions available for each title): Business Intelligence Engineer, Job Code AZ0136: support… https://t.co/OnQoJ9OV3H https://t.co/jELwcXCOi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/amvv82IuOI https://t.co/TxNnwYkFUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/ywdx4i94Uj https://t.co/PHTkJZ0Bss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: This Big Data Architect position is a Remote Opportunity for the right candidate. The candidate will lead the data lake and data integration architecture for the Magellan data lake (on-prem and Cloud) and be responsible for leading… https://t.co/do3E5pq6Bk https://t.co/2TlSf4lQwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site Reliability Software Engineer: HEALTH[at]SCALE is a rapidly growing healthcare machine intelligence startup founded by machine learning and clinical faculty with strong ties to MIT, Stanford, Harvard and U-Michigan. Our goal is to transform… https://t.co/nmnKkfIyfc https://t.co/6BwWkjKylm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer / Data Scientist: The Application Engineer / Data Scientist will work with business owners to drive strategic and tactical initiatives. The candidate is expected to have Data Analytical experience collecting robust production data… https://t.co/vif49GJ1BG https://t.co/IBH5PjIRko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/Ugr8vA4UYM https://t.co/oMhQLvELNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/8CFKE6dWMq https://t.co/wxhlB2OOFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: The Architecture team is very different from many other consulting practiceswe focus on outcomes and customer success rather than racking up billable hours. As a member of our Solutions Architecture team, youll play a critical role… https://t.co/RsQfUCNBQY https://t.co/J2YPPvXVUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Software Developer – AMAZON ALEXA – alexabostonjobs@amazon.com: Job Description DESCRIPTION Java/Python Software Development Engineer – Amazon Alexa – Cambridge, MA.. Candidates with or without Machine Learning experience are invited to… https://t.co/4WOchSIEZw https://t.co/o26rNoWn20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with adaptable skills in Object Oriented Programming (Remote): Do you enjoy reading and applying new concepts to constantly improve the quality of your code? Do you value collaborative teams, honest communication, and a teaching culture?… https://t.co/UWIF8NNOK9 https://t.co/6BDarmLEH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Location US-NJ-Somerset | DE | US-NJ-Somerset # Positions 1 Experience (Years) 3 Category Engineering Position Description/Company Info Legrand has a great opportunity for a Software Engineer to work in multiple… https://t.co/Yms0m3ixvk https://t.co/DmHsvOLUAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Developer: C++/Python Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one Scripting language… https://t.co/Q50bh8ANjo https://t.co/gdMhVGjKWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Startup/Python/HIPAA Compliant: San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! Based in San Francisco we are a digital healthcare startup that is looking… https://t.co/yqKFHDJh90 https://t.co/tGzNFSgDn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/eBmZsFHDpm https://t.co/DjllHu5XqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom completes move to U.S. from Singapore: (Reuters) - Broadcom Inc said on Wednesday it had completed its move back to the United States from Singapore, weeks after President Donald Trump blocked its $117 billion offer to buy Qualcomm Inc on… https://t.co/sEbKq3sLLM https://t.co/VGC9V7Dh7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/IZC0Ev864t https://t.co/J7PW0sfW5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIns 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.       We are seeking talented Software… https://t.co/Ek5n6UIolY https://t.co/rdjxIWmjvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer: Python Programmer Location: Hillsboro, OR Position: Contract/Full Time Experience: Any Graduate Job Description: 1-2 Yrs of Scripting experience in Python Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python (or) Perl Programming Able to develop Test… https://t.co/zT4iRZ8J5s https://t.co/cL94nFx4ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/YQ6sPlnmcA https://t.co/pT1lHoJIYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Windows (C, C++, Python): Req ID : 375321BR Job Code/Title : E2555:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/BhepTdcuWm https://t.co/zbzPCVebdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/unnu2zyAty https://t.co/XsZ2iJfzTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows and Linux System Administration Lead: Description:The Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Windows and Linux System Administration Lead at Ft. Meade, MD. JOB SUMMARY: The Senior Windows and Linux System… https://t.co/LATL7tTcou https://t.co/i0M7wkgoW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python and MVC] = TOP School or Tech Company!: ABOUT OUR CLIENT Candidates should be from Top School or Top Cloud Technology Leader! Our client is transforming the private funds industry, one of the largest and best-performing… https://t.co/zWEGKDfLN6 https://t.co/e8VfBjjnXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Technical Officer – https://t.co/rCWhgwLmlo: ********** is looking for a hands-on Chief Technical Officer to manage a team of developers and data scientists. ********** is a leading online service provider to lawyers and consumers. Our servers… https://t.co/EcHbID3SCi https://t.co/2I21Zj4CYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/sKOzgh0jYT https://t.co/1gWTFMyDJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – Automation Engineer: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US QA Automation Engineerfor Medical Devices Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/xNALPQKKlM https://t.co/f59xXxsdgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest blockbuster… https://t.co/yggWItn9DI https://t.co/uoxD0BBsEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/YPUkz35y98 https://t.co/Ak7jQMs6Ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D Technical Director/Digital Artist: We are looking for a talented, driven, digital visual effect artist and technical director to help us build the worlds first true holographic ecosystem. If you are an experienced, vfx/game artist who has both… https://t.co/SJWkzvfMug https://t.co/A6pecE1vij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Insights Analyst (Data Scientist): Our Client is hiring a Sr. Data Insights Analyst (Data Scientist) to lead the direction of their Data Engineering and Data Modeling initiatives while blending traditional statistical and multi-functional… https://t.co/C5wwgUT7vc https://t.co/EKnDRzWmFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Engineer, Systems Design- Ansible/Python/Openstack: Job Description: Description The System Design Engineers role is to design, validate and deploy technical solutions to maintain, enhance, and evolve the T-Mobile Network and Systems. Specific tasks… https://t.co/NcpaMbJvHa https://t.co/HTTgmhUSWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nuage Software Lead Engineer: Nokia is a global leader in the technologies that connect people and things. With state-of-the-art software, hardware and services for any type of network, Nokia is uniquely positioned to help communication service… https://t.co/3axfSJov26 https://t.co/bLcI08AJbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python: A well-known prominent automobile manufacturing company is looking to add a Software QA Engineer to their R&amp;D team. In this role, youll be responsible for extending and customizing their existing Python automation framework. You… https://t.co/Cvi8Uibby1 https://t.co/oS8nCDCW40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/y3d1qHj72Q https://t.co/lQaQmHe95t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/NXCdSw6o5E https://t.co/dN1dvJo26N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer (C /C++ /Python): Req ID : 403146BR Job Code/Title : E2551:Cyber Intel Analyst Asc Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are impossible? If you… https://t.co/f0M7E9KNMW https://t.co/1f6NLynG79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In self-driving cars, human drivers and standards come up short: experts: (Reuters) - Autonomous cars should be required to meet standards on their ability to detect potential hazards and better ways are needed to keep their human drivers ready to assume… https://t.co/JM1uRO5z3L https://t.co/pGLXfOg6Mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation Engineer: Covestic is looking for a Sr. Test Automation Engineer who has experience building automated test suites in Python. This position is within a product organization focused on releasing new versions of an enterprise scale… https://t.co/llpYuH9dw1 https://t.co/DHZ63FXMMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Architect- Containers and Private Cloud: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/nIj0ddqczk https://t.co/y7iiFrM6BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Windows (C, C++, Python): Req ID : 375321BR Job Code/Title : E2555:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/u1VwRvtNWL https://t.co/xElFaFl6aA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Support: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/nfEI3WBkzw https://t.co/p7B6cNCqdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Developer TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/lfU81Bzgtt https://t.co/S8OvPbPW6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/eaBKKGpvcN https://t.co/GkIGknMOCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Architect: Description:Join a fast growing, solutions driven, dynamic organization and take your experience to the next level! Leidos has an immediate opportunity for a Systems Engineer to provide engineering support to the Airspace… https://t.co/C8MfBcWt9j https://t.co/f2imIxrniM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Python Engineer – Validate Health: Interested in being part of a small founding team, so you can see your direct impact on improving the healthcare industry? Validate Health is an early stage healthcare analytics company on a mission to… https://t.co/7U2TfH6vLJ https://t.co/fRQGeT8qAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/94mmKQX1ff https://t.co/pE7pFrmP5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Linux / Platform Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/9deK9KDdko https://t.co/gUwJeDc17x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/m6i2jiaEYf https://t.co/bdnDjtwyfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/F7Nz769GDA https://t.co/PgkXW4L373]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer [Java and SQL]: ABOUT THE ROLE Our client is the leading independent data-driven software platform built to monetize and manage premium video inventory with the greatest speed, control, and transparency, wherever and however audiences… https://t.co/9ju5rxb5rJ https://t.co/0gnRwlDa97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer : 18-00744 Ref No.: 18-00744 Location: Lindon, Utah Primary Skills : Java, SQL, Python, C#, PHP Duration : 12 Months (Possible Extension) Contract : Only W2 Responsibilities : Responsible for E2E Business Process… https://t.co/eLgnOvZRSq https://t.co/4lrOCwKNGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA TODAY Network Storytelling Developer- Mclean, VA: Career Portals Job Search Login / Register We are now hiring Req #4109 USA TODAY Network Storytelling Developer- Mclean, VA Development &amp; Engineering Salary FT Monday, March 5, 2018 Gannett, owner of… https://t.co/s8kUu7S5Tt https://t.co/zGSlNnKs5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II, Cloud Solutions: Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! F5 is looking for a software engineer with strong systems knowledge who wants to learn the… https://t.co/np2HqhnULF https://t.co/qr6YjzuMwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Windows (C, C++, Python): Req ID : 375321BR Job Code/Title : E2555:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/6DWPKa1gyU https://t.co/Vmc8thtQMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/7imFHWoazk https://t.co/Hr4VR9c6Nq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/MOTkbZkbBQ https://t.co/jZ8lMb11PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Adminstrator/DevOps Engineer: Description: Leidos is seeking a DevOps engineer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for the CEGS system, a real-time operational SIGINT processor. The CEGS applications run under a virtualized… https://t.co/jfJBDhkocu https://t.co/Fhp0e4aOcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr DevOps Engineer: Qualifications: Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science or related field is required, advanced degree preferred. At least 7-10 years of relevant work experience in a senior technical position responsible for managing… https://t.co/bofa8R6M71 https://t.co/ogSsBxs1KN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Top Skills: Python programming experience Web Services development experience Oracle database – PL/SQL COMMENTS: * Story behind need: New need for the PPNR automation project, regulatory compliance. Would be working on multiple… https://t.co/HGm4eZCGpP https://t.co/zD5OlBoneT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/4CciuwKQ5I https://t.co/5fDif2nxm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OTC crypto market flourishes, powered by Skype: NEW YORK/LONDON (Reuters) - Trading firms are negotiating buying, selling and lending digital currencies like bitcoin and ether over Skype, catering to big investors looking to avoid rocking already… https://t.co/pBPIScnnUW https://t.co/fgzbHAyqbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/ueMRKLSEgm https://t.co/u6b7MhXrjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Strong… https://t.co/xFWLgE1G2R https://t.co/r1jm5BPt77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/pPRpGfgzfn https://t.co/2ac1Vjg9XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Middle Tier Java Developer – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/iBg1Z4Uxtd https://t.co/kVkynFYLE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/VGmGYySVCg https://t.co/aJjFg2yj1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/QfIBJ7N7xh https://t.co/WX5UJvuJ9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/Hn4VAm4QwK https://t.co/kKj4DOwBuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator – NMS: Description:The successful candidate will serve as a member of the Network Operations team responsible for ensuring the continued operation and improvement of the United States Antarctic Programs (USAP) network… https://t.co/BjSKs6Mwhm https://t.co/4zO3kod00y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: This Big Data Architect position is a Remote Opportunity for the right candidate. The candidate will lead the data lake and data integration architecture for the Magellan data lake (on-prem and Cloud) and be responsible for leading… https://t.co/B7WjV4GWTr https://t.co/Yo3bsA94Ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Engineer: Client Reference Code: 215331JOB SUMMARY This Senior Engineer position will be responsible for leading the overall System Integration Testing for Video Services, test execution, automation, planning and logistics, and reporting.… https://t.co/Ne6r08mIkS https://t.co/vhkKYeb8JF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Engineer System Design TIP: Job Description: T-Mobile USA is a leading provider of digital Global System for Mobile Communications/ General Packet Radio Service (GSM/GPRS) wireless voice and data technology standards. Senior Engineer, Systems Design… https://t.co/hKNcs8YJ2B https://t.co/EKdCY6uYIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/Deh0SG2DAj https://t.co/URwN4N01pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Data Science and Analytics: Job Title: Manager/Specialist, .Manager Data Science and Analytics Duration- 4+ Months Location: Arlington, VA Main duties and responsibilities: **Perform technical data audit identifying entity models, current pain… https://t.co/xby5XhKRZu https://t.co/SjvAmzY4jX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: UI/ UX Design Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design, Optimize, and add features to an existing HTML/JavaScript user interface Debug and fix all issues related to new features added Demonstrate progress to the… https://t.co/YtHPRFCnHH https://t.co/IeTRSvw3bR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Linux: Job Description Radiance Technologies is an employee-owned company with benefits unmatched by most companies in the Gulf Coast area. Employee ownership, generous 401K and profit sharing, health/dental/ life/vision… https://t.co/X0nGWmX4fJ https://t.co/eGY2SEbIZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer San diego, California – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Python,Jenkins,Chef,BITBUCKET,Ruby,PowerShell,Terraform, Agile,Delfix, IBM Websphere CommerceTax… https://t.co/nRVvyc9732 https://t.co/DNjoJvhBhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/JLMlMHkFsd https://t.co/YIk22lRsbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/5g5pezFX8d https://t.co/Y49fwQTU5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior NLP Data Scientist: Are you looking to apply your Senior-Level NLP Data Science skills to a fast-growing startup specializing in the area of automated user interaction? We are looking for someone to join our team and help take us to the next level… https://t.co/p7GuCLtq3B https://t.co/8vA7BrLpBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer – Newport News, VA: Web Application Developer Newport News, Virginia Full Time Position The developer will work on several different Automotive diagnostic and configuration tools, as well as a web database application. Job… https://t.co/NdYUVyC0AX https://t.co/9XJnmyp3iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/gkWO68G18z https://t.co/H33hE0sLFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer – High Assurance Software Protection: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can… https://t.co/IXu8fDrRbd https://t.co/GN5PxecmnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Armour says 150 million MyFitnessPal accounts breached: (Reuters) - Under Armour Inc said on Thursday that data from some 150 million MyFitnessPal diet and fitness app accounts was compromised in February, in one of the biggest hacks in history,… https://t.co/RjfZbGQYpy https://t.co/0wrt6pvfGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: It is a really exciting time to be at Extra Space Storage! Extra Space Storage got its start in 1977. Between now and then, we’ve come a long way. Today we are a New York Stock Exchange-traded company leading the self-storage… https://t.co/lLWoZj3iqx https://t.co/lrAMA6XVVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Analyst | AWS Cloud Formation (YAML, JSON, PowerShell, Python): Production Support Analyst | AWS Cloud Formation (YAML, JSON, PowerShell, Python) Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has… https://t.co/VMVJkhqCva https://t.co/ZIiqXYtQsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 3: Job Description The individual in this role will support the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions (GSMS) group in the development of advanced concepts and technologies, carrying out analysis tasks… https://t.co/shOAVfLMXR https://t.co/4cYMOzv10N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center – Sr Systems Software Engineer: NVIDIA’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI —… https://t.co/oe4arGRrQW https://t.co/wvL9IcyRak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – .NET/Python: Position Purpose: Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs… https://t.co/KR9J1J4Drq https://t.co/FV0vXV97yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineer – C/Python, Herndon VA: Req ID : 423985BR Job Code/Title : E2553:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/LxLqH4Sm0n https://t.co/R8hDotcHBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Phantom is the leading Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage company… https://t.co/OaOQUPuoKo https://t.co/AZ9TI0l08U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Strong… https://t.co/1p9M2BTzHA https://t.co/UGZIruv6Hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/3PZCUySKjb https://t.co/TEPpzMSZjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Intelligence Analyst (TS/SCI): Title: Senior Intelligence Analyst (TS/SCI) Location: Quantico, VA The Company: FireEye is the intelligence-led security company. Working as a seamless, scalable extension of customer security operations, FireEye… https://t.co/k4VkQtauBk https://t.co/0vzYY6mYnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer, Principal: Req ID 91987BR Business Title CNO Developer, Principal Group MCIS Location USA COLORADO Aurora Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is looking for a Principal CNO Developer to join… https://t.co/tG3OEQQ7TI https://t.co/fS4RWc2z7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/CSnCjthPjX https://t.co/4W5lQw8obu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer | Catbird Security Skip to main content Tap to expand menus – Contact Us – Careers – ************ – Catbird Private Cloud Security – Product – Catbird Overview – Why Virtualization Security? – Catbird Insight –… https://t.co/eXwJAiDawE https://t.co/3PwwHPR9jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking an Application Security Engineer. Candidate will work with developers to diagnose, document, and remediate application security vulnerabilities. Candidate will also be… https://t.co/bqwc3biZlG https://t.co/awdQSmDXh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Technical: Resonon, Inc. (***************) seeks a full-time software engineer with proficiency in Python and C++. Work will be devoted to software for our hyperspectral imagers. Experience with camera interfacing, machine learning,… https://t.co/rsUY2HOWdN https://t.co/fqYZbfDgP3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>