<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @srinivasancj: Eight Trends That Will Define The Digital Assistant Wars In 2018 https://t.co/eFzpirU0QF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dialogflow: API.AI is now Dialogflow! Learn more about our new name – and two new features – here: https://t.co/nlteV1vvm8 https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChatbotNews: Are you set for #Chatbots? https://t.co/XbcmCDXP1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_mystorycom: #Content or #design: Which comes first to developing a new project?https://t.co/WvQCAoUCdI #contentmarketing #designthinki…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @turboai: The Age of Voice https://t.co/ez0nmntbZ6 #bots #chatbots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @admiraldotai: 5 Common Misconceptions About #Chatbots https://t.co/FRHixfjetS https://t.co/ZFiL5hOB3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattPRD: My chatbots guide has been read 500,000+ times. Every major brand is defining their @Messenger strategy right now.

https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @turboai: How important is it to have live agent hand-off for a customer service chat bot https://t.co/TMK1GKlj8H #bots #chatbots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Goldman-Sachs-Chef Lloyd Blankfein: Ein klarer Merkel-Sympathisant https://t.co/ghX8c1BJtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Green Finance – Banken im Umbruch: „Es geht nicht nur ums Gewissen“ https://t.co/TefOx3uUyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Paydirekt: Mit viel Geld gegen den Konkurrenten Paypal https://t.co/k2EVNllCIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Auch das noch: Paris Hilton wirbt für einen ICO https://t.co/ADrIp8QXZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Trump Sides With Democrats on Interim Debt-Limit Fix, Harvey Aid https://t.co/taca3I1zGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Fußball: FIFA: Ermittlungen wegen Nazi-Ausfällen deutscher Fans https://t.co/SUMQkahqS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj What to expect from the Steve Jobs Theater at the new iPhone reveal https://t.co/H9cc2ohJS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj This tiny modular home is 325 square feet of IoT heaven https://t.co/3AZYFr8jFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Schumer and Pelosi say Democrats will support Harvey aid with 3-month debt limit raise https://t.co/2rd9D6bo9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Please, please stop sharing spaghetti plots of hurricane models https://t.co/crOMNg5Vep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Allianz-Tochter: Pimco Total Return bekommt wieder frisches Geld https://t.co/Th6vPBTh9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Leaked document: EU Presidency calls for massive internet filtering - EDRi https://t.co/oH5L5jfPbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Air Berlin vor der Übernahme: Berliner Spedition buhlt um Pleite-Airline https://t.co/zhbut5Fy7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Sucht Paydirekt eine Finanzspritze in dreistelliger Millionenhöhe? https://t.co/LXkcItqTY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Activists want to fight sex trafficking by changing a key Internet law https://t.co/U33axgXEG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Leipziger Schule: Maler Arno Rink ist tot https://t.co/Z743OSisaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Irma Has Florida Bracing for Atlantic's Strongest Storm Yet https://t.co/qNVNRMJnCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Whatsapp Business: Facebook will mit seinem Messenger jetzt Geld verdienen https://t.co/JF1nsCUXX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Live: Global stocks follow Wall Street lower as investors duck for cover https://t.co/9HEurO2npi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Radar reveals two moons orbiting asteroid Florence https://t.co/lTEm4hQNYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj President Trump winds down DACA https://t.co/b7OVuV1oUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj PARTEI-Aktion gegen die AfD: So geht digitaler Wahlkampf! https://t.co/ZjQEsCRcVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Array of Threats Stir Up Markets https://t.co/RXX2gmP3Q8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Katastrophenalarm: Stärkster je gemessener Sturm kommt auf Karibik zu https://t.co/q0gSugqnZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Ostdeutschland: Bundesregierung warnt vor Radikalisierung https://t.co/89OIWiCH3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Samsung Galaxy Note 8 review https://t.co/TLWnYtB7IG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj This is the new Nissan Leaf https://t.co/dW9xu8N5Dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Irma Has Florida Bracing for Atlantic's Most Powerful Storm Yet https://t.co/qNVNRMJnCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Hurrikan „Irma“: „Wir sollten das sehr ernst nehmen“ https://t.co/hcJM2T2YZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj From Apple to Y Combinator—tech sector denounces new “Dreamers” plan https://t.co/oDXj5I2blL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj We need to stop pretending that the autonomous car is imminent https://t.co/9woGdtH2po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Here are all the areas in Hurricane Irma's path and when the storm could arrive https://t.co/5S7QnZIYIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj PARTEI-Aktion gegen die AfD: So geht digitaler Wahlkampf! https://t.co/ZjQEsD8NN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Microsoft: Feds Must “Go Through Us” to Deport Dreamers https://t.co/7IFeUdTrUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Demon-Haunted World https://t.co/5y7kkufozd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Frankfurter Terrassengespräch zur Mediabranche: „Wir brauchen Wegweiser durch den Dschungel“ https://t.co/jD4w8DaKft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Trump Administration Ends DACA Program for Immigrants https://t.co/fYKEdCyJt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Senate Democrats fight FCC plan to lower America’s broadband standards https://t.co/QLqFY0uEYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Trump ends ‘Dreamers’ immigration programme https://t.co/3znaSj0DQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Man fired for sending private messages at work is vindicated in court https://t.co/JdwzbUo8W5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj How Recep Tayyip Erdogan seduces Turkish migrants in Europe https://t.co/rz6kWhuVjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Die Hypno Cam verpasst Euch ein Make-Over bei Instagram und Snapchat https://t.co/vZ5yuJAMY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Streit um Toshibas Chipsparte: Western Digital will sich als Käufer zurückziehen https://t.co/3WQ9oGy1mF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj PARTEI-Aktion gegen die AfD: So geht digitaler Wahlkampf! https://t.co/ZjQEsCRcVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Video: USS Ford’s “digital” catapult, (not quite) ready for duty https://t.co/MbHIqE6Qo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Apple’s Next iPhone Is Already Facing a Stronger Field From Samsung, LG, and Sony https://t.co/7izFDSzTMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj At Burning Man while your startup burns https://t.co/QPz63SK9e0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Already, Destiny 2 understands its fate, its purpose, its desti... you know https://t.co/rrow3caWiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Corbyn orders his MPs not to vote for EU withdrawal bill https://t.co/X1VI4dRDXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Sphero R2-D2 review https://t.co/l99JBOOg0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj South Korea looks to choke North with oil embargo https://t.co/MmHcLs1RaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj DHL will jetzt alle Pakete zustellen: Paketweiterleitungs-Flatrate für alle Paketdienste https://t.co/cdHMO55Sup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj mr-mig/every-programmer-should-know https://t.co/9mbmIiOv66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Fliegendes Auto: Das Hundert-Millionen-Dollar-Taxi https://t.co/yUGDP55nTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj The Ends of the World is page-turner about mass extinction https://t.co/3SLIMvOEyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Google Drive has become a popular alternative to The Pirate Bay https://t.co/V2fmzvxLEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj MORGAN STANLEY: There is a 10% chance that Brexit won't actually happen https://t.co/5Q5fgkMjs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Norbert Lammert: Norbert Lammert warnt vor Scheitern der Demokratie https://t.co/cruN0eF61f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj „Die Briefkästen sind leer – das ist die Chance für postalisches Marketing“ https://t.co/GYOkN01zl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Lauter Arschlöcher? Warum es in Erfolgsteams menschlicher zugeht https://t.co/I4bOQFyHki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj TV-Debatte: Großer Kampf der Kleinen https://t.co/IAAOqFG58x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Basketball: Basketball-EM: Schröder setzt gegen Italien auf Defense https://t.co/dTtLZFy26G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Magna’s new MAX4 self-driving platform offers autonomy up to Level 4 https://t.co/UUVxUmnGe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Kritik an Merkels Aussagen: Rente mit 70 laut Ökonom ein Muss https://t.co/M1knJU4pKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Zehn Thesen zur Zukunft des Internets, Frau Merkel! https://t.co/tLMYrOqi3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Theresa May rules out delaying Brexit after negotiations hit deadlock over divorce bill https://t.co/xW7QMwCZHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Nordkorea-Krise: Südkorea hebt Größenbegrenzung für Raketen auf https://t.co/n1A6MxQ37I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj U.S. Urges Strong U.N. Response as North Korea Prepares New Launch https://t.co/npTuSnhqcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj The smart kitchen revolution is a slow one https://t.co/IsiN4CgmM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj EU-Austritt: Großbritannien will Brexit-Verhandlungen beschleunigen https://t.co/EWFS1BxTcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj The Ends of the World is page-turner about mass extinction https://t.co/3SLIMvOEyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Neuer Viral-Hit von Lidl parodiert „La La Land“ https://t.co/oq8igBQBPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Erstmals mehr Smartphones in Deutschland als PCs https://t.co/j3GtKjBecM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Germany’s TV debate was a missed opportunity https://t.co/6Q1HLmTyAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj President Trump is expected to announce plans to end DACA on Tuesday https://t.co/sFD8Z2RlEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj U.S. Urges Strong U.N. Response on North Korea https://t.co/npTuSnhqcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Taxify arrives in London to provide a cheaper, more driver-friendly alternative to Uber https://t.co/cHfYNZzOdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Haley Says North Korea Asking for War, Demands New Sanctions https://t.co/vOc727K1Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Google shows off ARCore, its answer to Apple’s ARKit https://t.co/8gD6IO8eZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Run your own OAuth2 server https://t.co/ixywVs17C6?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj China’s Central Bank Is Banning Initial Coin Offerings https://t.co/WnZyfcLDBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj In a continued appeal to Trump, Tim Cook says 250 Apple employees are Dreamers https://t.co/nFIo7CqKZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj South Korea fired missiles into the sea as it simulated an attack on North Korea's nuclear test site https://t.co/McCkfBLfk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Nach Atomtest: Südkorea simuliert Angriff auf Nordkoreas Atomzentrum https://t.co/cwbNFaAbBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Facebook code makes for 16% of the average site… and that’s a problem https://t.co/0cnIUX77w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Novartis CEO Joseph Jimenez Is Stepping Down https://t.co/hOZQPB2KwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Zehn Thesen zur Zukunft des Internets, Frau Merkel! https://t.co/tLMYrOqi3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Trump opens door to attack on North Korea https://t.co/77JJTuLVuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj ASUS’ first mixed reality headset has plenty of pleasant surprises https://t.co/cWYAMjpnDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Microsoft’s ‘mixed reality’ headsets are a bit of a mixed bag https://t.co/RHdA3HcWIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Mattis warns of 'massive,' 'overwhelming' military response to North Korea after meeting with Trump https://t.co/PTP2sXifBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinivasancj Diese Digitalunternehmer haben an Parteien gespendet https://t.co/ezXjySttzg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>