<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a gig? Deliver with Uber Eats!: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you… https://t.co/K6CQlYXh4X https://t.co/IXjVWGRlSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: Software Engineer – .NET Software Engineer – .NET Company Quicken Loans Inc. Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are We’re America’s largest mortgage lender, closing loans in all 50 states. J.D Power ranked Quicken… https://t.co/QKxJu4b6Ga https://t.co/PP4cFrbSA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net, C# Developer: SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER HIGHLIGHTS LOCATIONS: Chandler, AZ JOB TYPE: Contract-to-hire SALARY: BOE JOB SUMMARY GTN is looking for a Senior .NET resource to develop and maintain new or improved software products, procedures and… https://t.co/2ZQ11Hv17d https://t.co/GttQVvHnAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliver with Uber – Flexible Gig: Delivering with Uber is an easy way to earn money in your spare time. You sign up, deliver whenever it works for you, and get paid every week. Why deliver with Uber? * Flexibility: With Uber, you’re the boss—you choose… https://t.co/HdODJiqDdk https://t.co/yo3y6PvQUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONTRACT AWS .NET Developers: AWS .NET CONTRACT DEVELOPERS Sundial Software is currently recruiting for 2 positions that are 6-9 month contracts for our client located in Madison WI. CRUCIAL SKILLS: AWS .NET ENTITY FRAMEWORK MICROSERVICES POSITION… https://t.co/tCyzWmnntt https://t.co/xqKI7dLcf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Full Stack Engineer: Logicea is currently seeking a Senior .NET Engineer with experience in full stack development to join our fast-paced and exciting team environment. Candidates should be self-starters, comfortable working as part of a… https://t.co/X8iyUcxMIt https://t.co/vGYagfPmA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign Trade Data Analyst: Foreign Trade Data Analyst Career Home View All Jobs Locations Join Our Talent Community Search jobs by keyword Search jobs by location Career Home View All Jobs Locations Join Our Talent Community Sign inSign in Career… https://t.co/wmqT7uUPeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/.NET Dev: Sr. Java/.NET Developer Responsibilities * Troubleshooting software application issues. Issues to be resolved require a broad range of troubleshooting skills related to: software functionality, Application Server setup, database… https://t.co/kQeqa5WOqB https://t.co/hi8oteiDBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: You may not have heard of irth Solutions before, but its likely that your home and safety has been protected with its industry-leading services. Every oil &amp; gas company and utility has distributed facilities and workers. Our… https://t.co/NRPHS625jU https://t.co/eWUKoyysf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-18928 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested for, send me updated resume along with best time to contact. Position : Sr. .Net… https://t.co/e5ognmlVF7 https://t.co/8wMGcNr8r9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/bbNkBPkpgq https://t.co/odRQPtVhbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-01185 Location: Pasadena, California Position Type: Contract Start Date: 05/15/2018 Job Responsibilities: The Senior Software Engineer will contribute to design sessions, perform coding and code reviews, unit… https://t.co/bGGWKHMaQz https://t.co/iSPN2Cajz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Cyber Security Engineer: What We Do: The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement. The SEI works closely with defense… https://t.co/4P7Azsq8id https://t.co/778ahUeL6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior https://t.co/eqMhHxVxYr Web Application Development Lead: Job Description Aon is looking for a Senior ********* Web Application Development Lead As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by delivering… https://t.co/4YeCeyXPxD https://t.co/yDBcohogwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.NET Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us C#/.NET Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 18319Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Raleigh, NC… https://t.co/V8MM1fQObx https://t.co/bbBrbX9XJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RA42: Computer Infrastructure Development: Pending for Closing (C++/Linux/OpenCL/TCP IP): This position is primarily responsible for researching, designing, and developing computer software systems, software system GUI, Design software system structure,… https://t.co/78bMgI6V1K https://t.co/4KRtNdAC8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .NET Front-End Developer: Job Description Microsoft .NET Front-End Developer (17455) The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located midway between Baltimore and… https://t.co/o5iPHoYG7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer Must have Active Secret Clearance: A data analytics company is seeking a Jr. – Mid Level JavaScript Developer with an active Secret Clearance to join their team. Responsibilities: * Developing custom Analytics applications and… https://t.co/8Ebn9IgaUo https://t.co/okvYNexMmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zqguck7KPp Developer: If youre an expert in ******, C#/.NET, SQL Server our client located in Northern Durham County, will be interested in speaking with you! Our client is looking to bring on a ****** Developer. This engineer will be highly… https://t.co/gr0Fwatieq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (.NET): Eligo Energy is a rapidly growing energy supplier headquartered in Downtown Chicago. Eligo offers competitive energy supply and related services to commercial and residential customers and is looking for self-motivated .NET… https://t.co/hdWTBMnP6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Engineer: The Project Engineer is responsible for all on-site project administration. In this role, the Project Engineer will report to and receive support from the Project Manager in that daily project administration. The Project… https://t.co/2Apj3UAUl5 https://t.co/7AkUyWOGPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. .NET Developer: Description HI’s Client is looking to add multiple Jr. Level .NET Developers on site at HP for a long term project. Will develop and maintain software for emerging technologies and platforms. Requirements * Good understanding of C#… https://t.co/3IxWYcGHK3 https://t.co/s4B69P5zQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design &amp; implement Oracle database environments to ensure the highest level of performance &amp; availability. Administer all relevant databases, including Oracle, MS SQL… https://t.co/PoT4DFm8ZC https://t.co/KB3lnlrYrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer – CA, TX (USA): * Role : Senior .NET Developer * Start Date: Immediate * Duration: 1 Years+ * Experience – 10+ Years Ideal candidate should have worked on Skills Required: MVC, Web API, Kendo UI, Telerik , Message Queues, Windows… https://t.co/qkjZTDQ4Wl https://t.co/Rz8laOCZ6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Technical Consultant: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |C# .NET Technical Consultant Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site,… https://t.co/FXumhuJ7wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer: COMPUTER: Impetus Technologies, Inc multi-pos avail for Computer Managers &amp; Software Developers pertaining to Big Data. All pos must be willing to travel to various unanticipated jobsites w/in the US. Mail to 720 University Ave., #130, Los… https://t.co/U3VpEt8pCV https://t.co/duhllHG4qd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer: SymSoft Solutions is a Digital Experience and Web Development company based in Sacramento. We specialize in designing engaging Digital Experiences and then bringing them to life by implementing enterprise scale Web… https://t.co/UmrWGGJtgD https://t.co/tKCKHNMffk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zqguck7KPp Developer: Analyze and develop specifications for the enhancement, maintenance and problem solving for the most complex applications or operating system (s). Provide in-depth consulting to IT management and staff at the highest… https://t.co/Xi36TnzZTp https://t.co/5A2jbgFd8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10298 Job Location United States Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and product development team. We design and… https://t.co/zfH4etq7mR https://t.co/g7zg9Q5Rpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Web Developer (AngularJS, MVC): ************* [******************************************************* is a Dallas-based startup with a focus on the best technology, fast innovation, excellent culture and service that shows we care. As… https://t.co/GLd1JbqkiX https://t.co/vh4h2Qspwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Angular JS: .Net Angular JS Ref No.: 18-21254 Location: NYC, New York Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as .Net Angular JS with the client based in New York… https://t.co/NA3gNRbuJP https://t.co/uzSagEwZ6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Software Engineer: RDM is looking for a Senior .NET Software Engineer to facilitate ongoing maintenance and development of our SaaS application platform along with other application development. Our platform supports the fastest growing area… https://t.co/asbTpVGL3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.Net / JavaScript): You will work on an Agile software development team as an engineer, while creating user stories and development tasks. You will be building large scale web/database applications, innovating and creating functional… https://t.co/36kWjIMydE https://t.co/wvBlDrtmTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/.NET Dev: Sr. Java/.NET Developer Responsibilities * Troubleshooting software application issues. Issues to be resolved require a broad range of troubleshooting skills related to: software functionality, Application Server setup, database… https://t.co/vAEmJO3eWe https://t.co/YCSGhhiXU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer with Oracle background: SUMMARY AllStaff Solutions is an established IT and Healthcare Services firm and we love what we do! It makes our day when we are able to help talented individuals find their next career move and our clients find… https://t.co/7Ps77F53pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Technical Systems Analyst: About the position This position manages the team responsible for Onboarding and ongoing maintenance of file exchanges between Group Insurance customers and the internal administration systems. The Customer Data… https://t.co/cxPtlICiZt https://t.co/eTlpOt78gW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst Product Support: Location US-FL-Lakeland Posted Date 1 month ago(4/19/2018 1:53 PM) Job ID 23499 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Headquartered in the Central Florida city of Lakeland, Summit… https://t.co/zGQJFhK0Vn https://t.co/tMANHtQtjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.net Database Programming Analyst, Reporting Team: Requisition ID ******* Job Locations US-CT-Stamford Job Family Performance, Reward and Talent Posting Description Database Programming Analyst, McLagan Reporting Team Aon is looking for a Database… https://t.co/FhUS4aibwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride ourselves in… https://t.co/gJjHUtbN7M https://t.co/1eW5Kd0490]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Report Developer (.Net, SQL): Job ID: EMO-******* Description: Located in one of the following locations – Austin, Houston, Richardson or San Antonio, TX this position is responsible utilizing .NET and SQL Server for creating reports, insights… https://t.co/EbQ08OScIC https://t.co/eAhCZVML8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zqguck7KPp Developer: If youre an expert in ******, C#/.NET, SQL Server our client located in Northern Durham County, will be interested in speaking with you! Our client is looking to bring on a ****** Developer. This engineer will be highly… https://t.co/gHeTJ65o22 https://t.co/OvbG0B9LGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Date Posted: 26/Apr/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: Software Engineer- C# .Net Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market… https://t.co/PTtTMNEDpw https://t.co/kHwcgKgYze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer: SENIOR LEVEL The .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER will help set the standard of a .NET practices corporately. The engineering department is constantly working to improve on processes, quality and techniques, with the goal of… https://t.co/jbfTIlZs17 https://t.co/3FbZR07VDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net/Angular Developer: Senior .Net/Angular Developer About the Job Duration: 1 year contract Location: Atlanta, Georgia Pay rate: Hourly Job ID: 53404 Overview Accountable for the design, development, and unit testing of .NET applications,… https://t.co/B9L2J4nFvr https://t.co/dmsZvUFKVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a .NET Developer to analyze, evaluate and develop new and existing web/database applications; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/qREXIznn9S https://t.co/VVEtWjU6rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer I: Job Title Hardware Engineer I Discretionary Business Title FPGA Engineer I Location WESTMINSTER, CO – Westminster, CO 80021 US (Primary) Security Clearance Ability to obtain a government security clearance Relocation Offered No Job… https://t.co/ehJIfyLzbF https://t.co/1Dm9bRpVWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn unit aims to raise $4.3 billion in biggest China IPO since 2015: TAIPEI/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Foxconn Industrial Internet , a subsidiary of the world's largest contract manufacturer Foxconn , said it plans to raise 27.1 billion yuan ($4.26… https://t.co/24IRD3cZg8 https://t.co/TacxbUMFmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Solution Developer-New York, Boston, Hartford, Philly): About the role The Solutions Development team designs, deploys and tests solutions such as web services, applications and enterprise portals to meet client needs. This team works closely with… https://t.co/vYqN6OLKgd https://t.co/J3CBxyarZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook face-off: EU gets little news from Zuckerberg: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg sailed through a grilling from EU lawmakers about the social network's data policies as lengthy questions left the 34-year-old American little time… https://t.co/flPBuzaWVp https://t.co/jaEevGbzAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Company Overview At Freedom National, we believe that working in insurance doesn’t have to be boring. In our friendly, casual office environment, we work together toward the common goals of offering quality auto insurance at an affordable… https://t.co/pfaeJ5qPpO https://t.co/6wzB5fqt6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Engineer: Adobe Systems Incorporated is accepting resumes for the following positions in San Jose, CA: Software Engineer (Ref.# SJSE106): Work closely with engineering teams and product management to deliver great compelling features for the Adobe… https://t.co/ExCndEaSzp https://t.co/Ln1NTm8KHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Mid .Net Developer: Senior/Mid .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-19584 Location: Chicago, Illinois Job Description:- Minimum 6 years of experience in .Net MVC 4/5/6 Minimum 3 years of experience with Web API and WCF Design &amp; Management Demonstrate… https://t.co/kdQlEbRG6r https://t.co/UXpSjxQkeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .NET Full Stack Developer: Senior Full Stack .NET Developer ARC Healthcare Technologies Why ARC Healthcare Technologies? Founded in 1982 as Advanced Research Company, we have proven to be an industry leader in the area of inventory management… https://t.co/nIfaKPtufB https://t.co/zTAs2OEham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager for Marketing Solutions: The Marketing Solutions division at Credo seeks a Project Manager. This marketing and communications professional relentlessly focuses on what is best for our customers, has initiative, is a lifelong learner,… https://t.co/72jG58K6q6 https://t.co/M5qmcpK2SZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C# .NET: SpringCM delivers an innovative document management and workflow platform that powers the leading contract lifecycle management (CLM) application. SpringCM empowers companies to become more productive by reducing the time… https://t.co/MiVFwHp4tC https://t.co/IuSp3Bjl2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .NET Developer: Req ID: 16586    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our… https://t.co/2ERygkPOAt https://t.co/8WdZaTQ04y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: About the role As a Software Engineer, you will have the opportunity to be part of digital transformation while being surrounded by people who are passionate about building modern applications that leverage the industrys leading… https://t.co/gohdZ8o1LG https://t.co/lvqu5PlCO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net/SQL Server Developer: Job title : .Net/SQL Server Developer Location : Chicago, Downtown, Illinois Duration: Full Time Position Mode of interview: Phone + In person/ Video conference Job Description : * Analyst with technical expertise in .NET… https://t.co/aKGOorNg60 https://t.co/96VGSxQo6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Riverbed Technology is hiring in Sunnyvale, CA: Member of Technical Staff (Software Engineer) (#D163): Drive the definition, design, development, and delivery of new networking features Member of Technical Staff (Software Engineer)… https://t.co/V2dKYL38rj https://t.co/17H9nnKXxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Vice President, Senior Engineer: COMPUTER: DB GLOBAL TECHNOLOGY INC. seeks an Assistant Vice President, Senior Engineer in Cary, NC to provide full coverage of database related tasks and issues for application team. Requires a Master’s Degree… https://t.co/OYLY80YC1b https://t.co/6a77uBTojc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Programmer – Angular/AngularJS – (US Citizen only): We have an immediate need for an experience .NET Programmer to join the team of our client, located in Lansing MI. This is a Contract role and the manager is looking to hire someone… https://t.co/fG3Cpmvcb1 https://t.co/PBqml6rwDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Software Engineer III Location Simi Valley, CA Employment type Regular – Full Time ID 125 Apply Now Who We Are Based in California, AeroVironment (AVAV) is a global leader in unmanned aircraft systems, tactical missile systems and… https://t.co/PPp8SdMxY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab to partner with Maybank for mobile wallet in Malaysia: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Ride-hailing firm Grab will partner with Malayan Banking Bhd (Maybank), Malaysia's biggest bank, to drive the usage and adoption of its GrabPay mobile wallet, the companies… https://t.co/m9Z9eUdjSs https://t.co/RWhb8yy6YA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer: You are a Hardware Engineer with a strong background with Cisco routers and switches. You also have EMC equipment and storage solutions, linux/unix System administration experience, and you are familiar with VMware. You must have an… https://t.co/4dO3pKzN4O https://t.co/nocrPxjdQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Systems Engineer: Why choose between doing meaningful work and having a fulfilling life? At MITRE, you can have both. That’s because MITRE people are committed to tackling our nation’s toughest challenges—and we’re committed to the… https://t.co/MxBp91DGzP https://t.co/1FJdlrBwRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET WPF developer: C# .NET WPF developer Ref No.: 18-19700 Location: Chicago, IL, Illinois Job Title: C# .NET WPF developer Location: US-IL-Chicago Rate: Duration:[Invalid Variable] # of Positions:1 Overview: Build, maintain and test windows… https://t.co/apz6Yo7SkR https://t.co/Hc7o6bosTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/ASP.NET Developer: CRI Advantage is looking for .Net developer to work in a team environment to help build/maintain their current Unemployment Insurance system. Part of the role includes reviewing current architecture and refactor code to meet current… https://t.co/zJrE8hZbcS https://t.co/C3D0SJ8vxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Resiliency Engineer: What We Do The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement. The SEI works closely with defense… https://t.co/OsXo5RgspI https://t.co/M36hkISR9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer with Operations Support: Req ID: 17410    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market… https://t.co/2n6m1UQ6rz https://t.co/jhvJULjKfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead/Architect .NET (Local to Texas OR Illinois): Lead/Architect .NET (Local to Texas OR Illinois) – DKMRBH Inc. – Chicago, IL – 05-04-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer –… https://t.co/OFmhdY7Cmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio Visual Crontrol System Programmer: AVS Installations is seeking an Audio Visual Control System Programmer. This role will include a wide range of programming solutions to support sales and installations of integrated Video Conferencing, Audio… https://t.co/LSWE9mjCrE https://t.co/dzOaJjFjzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Laurel, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/oQWy67sRGJ https://t.co/TmRiHs78EB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-19052 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Position : .NET Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Charlotte/NYC/Jersey City Description: 10 years proven IT experirence performing hands-on software… https://t.co/LkbKpttuBt https://t.co/naQPgVZzWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-19596 Location: Pennington, New Jersey Job Description – Dotnet Developer with Multi-Threading, SQL , WCF Strong written and verbal communication skills . – Good grasp of Design patterns supporting scalability,… https://t.co/SpUKiMWkKC https://t.co/uXQA4Pl2Qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW: Our client located is looking for an ******* Developer with C# experience to support and develop portfolio solutions. The right candidate will be responsible for global proprietary solutions… https://t.co/U6gngqC1qj https://t.co/BCYDG9ACxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .Net Developer: Description HI’s client is adding multiple Full Stack .Net Developers to its Operationsteam supporting integrations and access management of two merging organizations. The role will integrate datafrom one environmentinto… https://t.co/ufYQKuQdrT https://t.co/gcNn87ntvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Position Description As an Associate Software Engineer at Scientific Games you will work on the frontlines of a game development team. You will implement, debug, modify and generally support in-game features, development and… https://t.co/Z2HkI9LrpQ https://t.co/z1cZO8H9Jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer / Architect: Custom Application Developer: Do the Work You Love, Every Day Tired of maintaining old apps based on legacy technologies? Join a team that develops custom apps for smart clients using new (and emerging) technologies. Magenic… https://t.co/dD1m7aVEC1 https://t.co/HJjbltl6tG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Financial Analyst – Programmer – Accounting: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-MD-Owings Mills Posting Description Aon is looking for a Financial Analyst with Programming and Project Management Skills As part of the financial operations group… https://t.co/woyoYB0Zp4 https://t.co/XPvSPKmX1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-20296 Location: Redmond, Washington Job description: – Excellent knowledge of .NET, C, C++ and/or C#, JavaScript – Development experience in building products and application – Good knowledge of Java Security –… https://t.co/WIuPNEUgmD https://t.co/iqimC72y0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Web Developer: The Web Development Team is a growing group working within a progressive IT environment that encourages innovation and creative thinking. This is an outstanding opportunity for a highly skilled full stack .NET WEB DEVELOPER to… https://t.co/U7yUAClN8B https://t.co/Ymqm2Y6AvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence(BI): Business Intelligence(BI) Ref No.: 18-21707 Location: Redmond, Washington Business Intelligence(BI) Redmond, WA 12 Months contract Job Description: – Must have 5+ years of experience in business intelligence and data analytics… https://t.co/pMDITZY78W https://t.co/HndW0RuonS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Description HI’s client is adding ************ Developers to its Network Inventory Applications team in Broomfield. The roles will help develop network inventory and ticketing applications as well as overall telecom inventory and… https://t.co/F6aa0Qlhwr https://t.co/ih70tMfkJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure .Net Developer: Azure .Net Developer in Peoria, Illinois, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To… https://t.co/ztfP1NPLtK https://t.co/w5GzmtQlk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (C#, .NET, JavaScript): At TherapyNotes, our software developers work in a collaborative, team environment to develop the best behavioral health EMR software in the industry. We’re expanding our team and looking for developers who love… https://t.co/sLXtSPKJt4 https://t.co/GxCiQIinBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with angular: .Net Developer with angular Ref No.:18-08455 Location: Centennial, CO Position Type:Contract Start Date: 05/08/2018 Position: .Net Developer with angular Location: Centennial, CO Duration: 8 months – 8+ Experience in Dot Net.… https://t.co/SyQP1wQ6S9 https://t.co/bC0SvqlXTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Careers | American Institutes for Research |.NET Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/0AF4kIsemq https://t.co/rXG6LrJUGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica files for bankruptcy in U.S. following Facebook debacle: (Reuters) - Cambridge Analytica, the political consultancy at the center of Facebook Inc's privacy scandal, filed for Chapter 7 bankruptcy in the United States late on Thursday. https://t.co/KrUQBxrlko https://t.co/djtWe0KBwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead/ Senior .NET Developer: Project Description Current business process in automated in Customer’s system where users have access to a dedicated "investment call" functionality and able to view assets and discussion items that are associated with the… https://t.co/GXm91blD3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer .NET Dveloper: ABOUT GUNTNER: Guntner U.S. LLC is part of Güntner Group, a global leader in heat transfer technology for Industrial and Commercial Refrigeration, process cooling and HVAC application. Guntner U.S. first opened its doors… https://t.co/HvX7gn6C8B https://t.co/WPaDIb3fv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer Bellevue, Washington Job Duties: Design, develop and implement new tools for interactive game development. Analyze requirements and user needs for media pipeline tools, core engine editor tools, and backend infrastructure. Design and… https://t.co/4nyNtQddMP https://t.co/ii1bxSfsn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – .Net: Job Title: Senior Developer – .Net Requisition Number: 23442 Position Type: Full Time City: Brentwood Campus: Corporate OH State/Province: Tennessee Job Description: The Senior Developer – .NET is responsible for the overall… https://t.co/gnVdFxMKB5 https://t.co/LexL7dCls5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayPal in talks to buy Sweden's iZettle in $2.2 billion deal: WSJ: (Reuters) - PayPal Holdings Inc is in advanced talks to buy iZettle AB in a deal that could value the Swedish fintech at around $2.2 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday,… https://t.co/nDAGzXaX7b https://t.co/050Vnm3U9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer (C#/.NET 4): The candidates should be mid-level with between 5-10 years of experience. These are hands-on CORE JAVA developer positions. Candidates need experience with front end C#.NET4+, WPF, Back End Java Spring, Messaging, and… https://t.co/hVC88WZfNi https://t.co/tQUWYjPxks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Intel's Mobileye gets self-driving tech deal for 8 million cars: JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Mobileye, Intel Corp's Israel-based autonomous driving unit, has signed a contract to supply eight million cars at a European automaker with its… https://t.co/00cYHqT6ap https://t.co/KZMUlxUN8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .net Developer: Microsoft .net Developer Ref No.: 18-20706 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- Microsoft .net Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 Role – Candidate should have 5+ years of IT experience – Minimum 2+… https://t.co/Ff3u8giyKB https://t.co/q3oCaIH0OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Services Analyst I: GENERAL PURPOSE: The Technical Services Analyst I is responsible for project assignments, remediation of problems of a moderate scope with minimal instruction from project or department leadership. Areas of focus include… https://t.co/RAWGMV1HRm https://t.co/hau6KgXTaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Chandler, AZ: Software Engineer Chandler, AZ Full Time Position Job Description: This position will develop and maintain the Responsive Retail Sensor (RRS) Management Console user interface. The RRS Management Console is a web… https://t.co/P1rWfzIivq https://t.co/JpJeeELPMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/QdDY74hZCc https://t.co/KRsX9957RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / Azure Architect for Mobile Apps: OVERVIEW We are looking for a hands-on software architect with solid C#/.NET experience to oversee and drive application design across mobile platforms and cloud-based server-side components. The position involves… https://t.co/aVFrPprRqB https://t.co/vcY68rtsQX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>