<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCVancouver: Have a memoir or essay you'd like to share? The @CBC 2018 Nonfiction prize is open for submissions. ✍️✍️
https://t.co/j2S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resto chill. https://t.co/45TC48MenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @barstoolsports: We found the best athlete at the Olympics https://t.co/km1ndhJAnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BannockHammock: I was the only native kid in my advanced math class. First test came along and I got 105% on it (I got the bonus q righ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road trip. https://t.co/n8az8lxCYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome job by all of them. Incredible to see McMorris competing at this level. https://t.co/QoYipl9FSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific spot. | Good Odds | Toyota https://t.co/dDcUjkd4z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to go up to strangers in the gym who are warming up with really light weights and shout, “You got it! Come on! All you,man — ALL YOU!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Nearly thousands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta Thousand of podcasts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnificent Concupiscence is the name of my new band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AKA "Tiger" Williams... https://t.co/8hUPtwXc5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This happens a lot -- cark my words... https://t.co/wSkpLRxkTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benfowlkesMMA My son got seasick on a camel in India. Not exactly a smooth ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s getting better at finding good hiding spots... https://t.co/O0DqtTr4Fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I watched #TheBigSick. Thought it was a sweet story. Could watch Holly Hunter all day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody side-to-sides out of a war zone and shuffles into K-Pop quite like @JeffSempleGN. https://t.co/kbc2n7kpiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberta, We Need to Talk  via @TheTyee https://t.co/P05TpjZ1Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thread. https://t.co/V4UtnN6FNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattdpearce: The Los Angeles Times' new owner, Patrick Soon-Shiong, just sent his first letter to our newsroom: https://t.co/KwD5J92e4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeHudema: BAM! France decrees all new rooftops must be covered in plants or #solar panels: https://t.co/3UdvOYrI24 Why are we talking…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three months without booze tomorrow. Everything is fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benfowlkesMMA Give me 12 beers beforehand and I’m in...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really admire people who can sing, dance and act. Probably because I can do none of these things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s hoping Dawna downs a glass of BC red tonight. https://t.co/paWBqefzlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d be pro-pipeline if it carried wine and led straight into my mouth. #ableg #BCwines #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuzyPatrick @BACTouring Well, it was great while it lasted. Had to leave the show at intermission to go get baby — but the first act was terrific. #babysteps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about Vancouver arts for more than a decade — and always tried my best to shine a light on local stuff. Arts coverage is disappearing, and so are the spaces — so #SaveTheRio, yo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the spirit... https://t.co/x984W4Kklm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m with @SuzyPatrick @BACTouring’s Motown the Musical. It’s our first night out together in 13 months. #babyfree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how you end a newscast... https://t.co/bJYojXPbCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GlobalNational’s @DFriesenGlobal ends tonight’s newscast with a crunch. #Doritos #ladychips https://t.co/SH7hWKEr8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a photo of my son eating ice cream. https://t.co/LYxySUcD1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be Chan's 23rd Olympics. https://t.co/1EpOYTOtSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess it'll be easier to find parking in the summer. | Pay parking coming to Spanish Banks  https://t.co/Ufs19XETqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First I quit drinking, then Alberta bans BC wine. Tough times for BCLD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But seriously -- how awesome was that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not a Space X launch -- it's a Tide ad. #TideAd #SpaceX #spacexlaunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah she did. | Girl Scout sells 300 boxes of cookies outside a California marijuana dispensary https://t.co/F4uEODAjaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanelpratap I think the Tide campaign was better. Let's fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oof. https://t.co/25uUwlmcjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice. https://t.co/9gKyFay999]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently Justin Timberlake did not unite America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @smonkyou: TLDR: the dude who gets the cash was cool with the spot https://t.co/J7UFdULuqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet burn. https://t.co/hoxqfoNoyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TROOPER ALERT: Since starting daycare on January 8th, Dylan has had two colds, a brutal cough, an ear infection and pink eye (in both eyes). Still cute though! https://t.co/iyPElqB06b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edgarseeya I'm gonna have to side with me on this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing Tide could've done better is have Timberlake say, "Nope -- it's a Tide ad!" at the end of his set. #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tide spent $60,000,000,000,000 on this #SuperBowl campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lighten up, ya old bag. https://t.co/B4q30nuT7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it makes you feel better, I heard Justin Timberlake isn't good at Scrabble. #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far worst play of the game goes to the team that conceptualized that @Dodge ad. #superbowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Built to serve? GTFO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, so good. https://t.co/RZ96iMkgjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant Tide ad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling plays. #SuperBowl https://t.co/EQKSPvQNpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific tale. | The search for Jackie Wallace https://t.co/ixNqKsoGVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SuzyPatrick: Beautiful Vancouver ❤️ https://t.co/tNdwTxDOuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix’s Dirty Money Trump episode is an excellent look at Trump the con artist. Worth a watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d be pissed, too. https://t.co/txWyoIYHzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_macdonald It’s not too late for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emailed my dad a story, got this back. Gotta love him  —- even at 82, always an editor...

“Pretty good; had never heard of this.

“Almost stopped reading right away with the disclosure that contemporary journalists "raised their glasses  into the air ..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan does not approve this message. https://t.co/u4taZUdlRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brutal story, well told. | I’m the Wife of a Former N.F.L. Player. Football Destroyed His Mind. https://t.co/gT5uSnDd6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the sheriffs should have moved a lot slower when that dad tried to attack Larry Nassar. At least let him land a few hard shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiking isn't for everybody.

https://t.co/5q4SjVreED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful. | Field of Vision - Concussion Protocol https://t.co/bpgkqwdMRR via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlastairMcA30: For an assignment, I asked some of my terminal paediatric palliative care patients what they had enjoyed in life, and wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many gems in David Sedaris’ Theft by Finding... https://t.co/RYiuNvjXJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AMCMBChiefs: Our letter to the @globeandmail editor regarding the headline about #TinaFontaine. https://t.co/bz5kgv6r9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VY8FYdqWEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thoughtful piece. | My Woody Allen Problem https://t.co/ATPwcPx1gA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Tips:

1) Stay off the Internet

-30-

#writingtips #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At my first Canucks game in ages. Not drinking and ordered a vegan tofu thing. I’ve become everything I hated in the 90s. (@SuzyPatrick) https://t.co/TllACjDOL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanLazaruk I got that today, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roeper dope. https://t.co/C9NNlxP5xV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a big Scott Baio fan but I'd totally watch Charles Is Charged. | Nicole Eggert Details Alleged Scott Baio Sexual Abuse...

https://t.co/KxHwlSOxRA via @variety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tylerjhard Not unheard of — still terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine-year-old son appears with chess set.

SON: “Do you want to play chess?”

ME: “Sure.”

SON: “Great. I’ll go easy on you.”

I laugh. Son proceeds to destroy me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re wondering if parenting is hard, today my son asked me if olden-day pirates preferred tea or coffee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool story, bro. https://t.co/pRMXZP8CPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajchavar: National Geographic investigated Deputy Director of Photography Patrick Witty for sexual misconduct. He left, quietly, but wo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFLinHalifax You’re being deliberately obtuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to name a sports franchise after a disaster that killed 2000 people? https://t.co/ag9Zve3x5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St-St-Studio. Downtown #Vancouver on a ☔️ Sunday night. #Photography #Neon #exploreBC #Photo https://t.co/wSYpTabtE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me leaving the house every day. https://t.co/lS2ArJgt0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flematic @Spartacus_Gym I worked out there in the 90s. Guessing it looks the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dust1551 Thx — will look for it today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to be more positive on and offline so, instead of posting another lazy #IKEA joke, I'm reposting this story on teenaged explorer Jade Hameister. #girlpower https://t.co/5ZxNmdZLtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crap: I forgot about the #ConanHaiti thingy last night. Assuming they'll post entire show at some point....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the trailer. https://t.co/87r4I6lX0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people should be talking about this badass teenaged girl who has now successfully skied to both poles. Not only that, she served up a succulent side of sass to her haters when she completed her latest expedition.

https://t.co/IXtSpzKzne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope they throw the perpetrators ... in the can. https://t.co/IloUjbFJ6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This show is brilliant. https://t.co/bwcx1jZbwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They might want to wait until the case gets ... cold. https://t.co/V0pbBA50kF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two words: Comrade Detective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked down to the #beach while my son was in karate. #Longexposure of downtown #vancouver from Kitsilano. #photography #ExploreBC #photooftheday https://t.co/r94Ab9xHW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a verry simple thing. https://t.co/iUhcUv342U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you talk to me today I will tell you that I’m sick because whining about it somehow makes me feel a little better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine having to look yourself in the mirror after writing this line. https://t.co/RSk8W8u8Ov]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>