<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth Hopefully we'll be lucky with this one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandlecreed was thinking about this the other day, assume it will be like creating another PSN account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cookie_Vonster: Because downtime is my enemy https://t.co/CqE82tzrGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NightInTheWoods: hey!
one week ago we released a game.
people seem to like it.
check it out! https://t.co/B21dKr28EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny__Lawrence Looks awesome!!! My hair refuses to do anything ever..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainfarrell @Nibellion Oh my! Haven't been this hyped for a release in years!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGreatEight6: HAPPY ZELDA WEEK!! @ZeldaOfficialJP @Nintendo @azwah https://t.co/HsGnqY4IYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatsMyChad haha hella casual that's for sure ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would also consider Senior Account Manager level applicants, RTs welcome! :D @weareamplify https://t.co/2tpckHQeFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're currently looking for an Account Director, with experience in events management, tech/gaming - if this sounds like you send me a DM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenkerwin I have no idea, I was too excited by the fact I won to notice the score :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behold, this is the face of someone who has truly milked a virtual udder #NintendoSwitch https://t.co/cYH04tFeyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandlecreed Exactly, everything else is just a perk :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I played the #NintendoSwitch and milked a virtual cow - here's what I thought about it: https://t.co/NJaMRSmsjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nibellion: Mood https://t.co/D5lDAk2A59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shiroth: Just keep swimming, just keep swimming https://t.co/Otd8RW9zss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seven5three Aaah!! So exciting!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, I keep replaying it while editing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't sure at first, but am now in love with the new #AttackOnTitan OP https://t.co/9KnCpGJbW9 #ShingekiNoKyojin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to dust off the Vita, get out that Remote Play and dive under the duvet playing #Persona5 in bed - oooh yes :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seven5three Nice! I would be so worried that I'd ruin my PS4 controller :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatsMyChad Have you seen Pewdiepie's recent video? He made $100 on his latest vid... Geniune ad revenue YT crisis going down atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving #Persona5 so far but there's some dodgy Japanese name pronunciations going down..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greghill Loving your display pic! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's more ways YouTube are making it harder for smaller channels to get anywhere. Butts: https://t.co/dhUkXJT0OZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scully1888 Mmmmm I miss them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ghost__Arcade Haha that's what I'm trying to overcome at the moment! Going from sounding uber posh and weird to natural Japanese conversation. So hard :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ghost__Arcade Haha I haven't heard him.. but now I want to..! What's your latest with Japanese then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ghost__Arcade Yeah I'm having a blip too. So hard to find time and motivation around work, YouTube and, you know, life. Thought a new book would inspire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth My decision was literally based on judging a game by its cover art :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feeling when a game arrives you totally forgot you pre-ordered (alongside the latest Japanese study motivation!) #YokaiWatch2 https://t.co/dUmvlpAxT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Just_Ge0 @beldeth I mean, if you mean the PEGI submission was the best part of it ever then.. YOU'RE WELCOME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Just_Ge0 @beldeth Nonary Games - nice! I helped out on VLR in my RSG days, fond memories :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beldeth Wooop!! Going to buy a lifetime supply for dark chocolate digestive biscuits and monster munch to support the gaming weekend..!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeneticJen Which is everyone's dream, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised the weekend after next is a Bank Holiday sandwich. SO ready to play #Persona5 all day every day. https://t.co/Xt2NR37thc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toadsanime Ah yeah Amsterdam is great (and cheap), went a few years back but would be up for a weekender again :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter friends, any suggestions on cheap but adventurous holiday destinations? I have absolutely nothing booked 0.0"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casually chilling with my noble steed #BreathoftheWild #NintendoSwitch https://t.co/8vTZzYpjID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyBee Have an amazing time!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatsMyChad It was alright tbf. @RyanAPage &amp; I saw it at the weekend. Worth a watch in any case :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soodenim @Cookie_Vonster @katosman Panic mode.. ENGAGE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just back from seeing #BeautyAndTheBeast - was sooo good!! :D Emma Watson is amazing as ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DurkinAround Ah nice! Thanks very much (Assume that means you bought it?!) :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisisLukeOwen: To add to these incredibly true words.

Websites: please, please please - don't ask people to work for free. Our words…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Savantcore @weareamplify Sent a DM over :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you recreate the #NintendoSwitch advert in Honest Burger  @dmseto @TalesOfMrE &amp; @RyanAPage https://t.co/hEqG9oP5jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bearskopff Cheers for the RT :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big ups the @Rebellion's Jason &amp; Chris Kingsley for their placement in the 100 Most Influential list : https://t.co/AhsVPMJaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Just_Ge0 Thanks for RTing buddy :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in London and fancy a brand new jobbie? @weareamplify are looking for a Receptionist + a Brand Editor. Give me a shout if interested!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @floofyfluff: Arctic friends! ᵔᴥᵔ https://t.co/0E2hROlJtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NintendoMemo: Nintendo Company Book 2017 is finally here and beautiful as usual. #任天堂 #Switch /via @masa_fujifuji @Fleece_sliver @meide…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundays are made for casually sunbathing in flower pots, totally pretending you're not stuck,… https://t.co/W7dSRkovvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a cheeky #BokuNoHeroAcademia binge in prep for S2 - SO good!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanAPage @MaxxLDN @GhostInShell Nahh thats Ouran High School Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging with my crew #BreathoftheWild #NintendoSwitch https://t.co/IO3X5JsNDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wait is nearly over until we join the band of Phantom Thieves - time to get #Persona5 HYPEEE https://t.co/I9mrzHgaLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InvisableEwok P4 is just so fantastic, if P5 is anywhere near as great I'll be happy :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth Ja classic! :D @RyanAPage has one too so we can look like lame bag twins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So hyped for #Persona5! Gearing up to sweet-talk some shadows into joining my crew https://t.co/5vesFzImLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorsShelf loved it but the hard mode would drive me insane! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @perlapell: Hey Young Girls, finish your sentences no matter what look someone is giving you while you speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth Welcome to the crew! https://t.co/MeLvhpFPJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Yokai_Watch_UK: FLASH COMP! #WIN a #Nintendo 2DS &amp; #Yo-kai Watch Game! Closes 31.03 @3pm. RT&amp;FLW #Freebie #Prize #Giveaway #Competition…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has cute chickies &lt;3 https://t.co/BOfTGx0Eo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is how we roll https://t.co/8gCyPUYbsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ninjayetti haha I was wondering the same thing this morning :P not enough hours in the day to play all of the games I want to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The__Goomba: This is how I'm gonna introduce myself from now on.
#myheroacademia https://t.co/oP4LpX4rHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mattophobia definition of a true man :D hope you've had a good one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@floofyfluff so cute!! I love them all :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorsShelf Haha HYPE! Look forward to hearing your thoughts on it when you grab a copy :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth Bold words! But I feel like they're justified.. :P Next week couldn't come soon enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to the Persona 4 OST to get hype for #Persona5 - not long to go now guys!! :D https://t.co/RR1tDs95W7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahwww this Mumei Nendoroid is cute!!! Love the clothing details #KabaneriOfTheIronFortress https://t.co/MYD71Ve1Q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're into #anime and #ASilentVoice is airing near you - make sure you go check it out! Beautiful &amp; emotional : https://t.co/cS9e98O76t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_monster Uck, yeah, good shout then. Looking forward to playing it properly though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_monster PC... Think I'm going to refund it and buy PS4 version instead :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_monster Randomly fixed itself, but had 4 crashes like that in a row..? :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone had the 'Server is unreachable' error on #NierAutomata ? Can't even load up the bloody game or send an error report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theFrankieVu Just seen your news! Congrats buddy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seven5three Ahw thank you :D Have a good weekend!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not every day that an #anime gets a full UK cinema release - here's my thoughts on #ASilentVoice https://t.co/QhrVjqLZEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, no suprise here #Persona4Golden https://t.co/3p4dwHPm94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaand copyright slammed. Classic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ASilentVoice (or #KoeNoKatachi ) may look rather beautiful, but is worth watching? Here's my thoughts! https://t.co/a2gpmlDGCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For once it looks like there's more promising anime than poop coming out next season - get hype!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have internet! It's been a week, but @RyanAPage survived with the help of our #TwinPeaks boxset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethamari so cute!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaHollinrake Your photos are making @RyanAPage &amp; I miss Japan so much! Hope you're having a good one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorsShelf Except if you're Taylor, who didn't like LTTP ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to stick a review score number on #ZeldaBreathoftheWild to know it's an absolute masterpiece! https://t.co/Jem8F7WDg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davescook @RPG_Angel Don't even go there, I completely broke down during the Zelda concert a few years back. No idea why :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RPG_Angel @davescook jelllyy!! Was so good last time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shiroth @RyanAPage ohhh there was tears!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight I finally did my first #twitchstream , playing #GitarooMan (semi-secretly!) Proud that I finally got over the nerves to go on air~ https://t.co/FR7uv1siqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainfarrell Ah thanks dude! Hope you enjoy it :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday I posted this review of #Kamiko - a gem of a Nintendo Switch eShop game and only £4.49! https://t.co/LrNhz0Bie8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorsShelf So goooood!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuffFromJordan Oo where did you pick it up from?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>