<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["The only way to find true happiness is to risk being completely cut open." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our generation has had no Great War, no Great Depression. Our war is spiritual. Our depression is our lives." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters fan art. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/Yjjo0c4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It boils down to the fact that we're all jackals feeding off each other." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quit your job. Prove you're alive. If you don't claim your humanity you will become a statistic. You have been warned." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody looks a little crazy if you're looking close enough. And if you can't look that close, then you don't really love them." -Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["'If Marilyn Monroe were alive right now, what would she be doing?'... Tyler says, 'Clawing at the lid of her coffin'" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They should let some people into the library by prescription only." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel lethal, on the verge of frenzy. I think my mask of sanity is about to slip." - Bret Easton Ellis, American Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some stories, you use up. Others use you up." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how much you think you love somebody, you'll step back when the pool of their blood edges up too close." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The trick to forgetting the big picture is to look at everything close-up." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/u11A0eml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your birth is a mistake you'll spend your whole life trying to correct." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how careful you are, there's going to be the sense you missed something." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every word you read of this useless fine print is another second off your life. Don't you have other things to do?" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: @methadrone13 The story about his friend the luggage thrower is almost as bad as "Guts".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must watch for any Palahniuk fan. These stories are brilliant. Skip to the 18 min mark if you don't speak Spanish.   https://t.co/FMHDQKNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In America, if your addiction isn't always new and improved, you're a failure." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's only after you've lost everything that you're free to do anything." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember: the time you feel lonely is the time you most need to be by yourself. Life's cruelest irony." - Douglas Coupland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Until you find something to fight for, you settle for something to fight against." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You grow up to become living proof of your parents' limitations. Their less-than masterpiece." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Chuck Palahniuk's poem from 5th grade! http://t.co/M8LLLGFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're watching daytime television, this is your new demographic. You're a drunk. Or a cripple. Or an idiot." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pygmy art. #OperationHavoc #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/yN2nlXzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find what you're afraid of most and go live there." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's pathetic how we can't live with the things we can't understand. How we need everything labeled and explained and deconstructed." Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're meant to be worn smooth by conflict and pain of every kind. To be polished." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you're thinking, a million other folks are thinking. All of you is a cooperative effort." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We went sailing one time, and he wore a speedo, and any smart woman should know that means bisexual at least." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can go to hell for having low self-esteem, that's why I'm here." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You feel that? That's what church should feel like." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Losing all hope was freedom." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, today's weather is nervous disgust with tentative apprehension." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am Jack's broken heart... #FightClub http://t.co/MoZ6pFVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As we grow older I always think, 'Why didn't I do more when I was younger? Why didn't I risk more?'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People can't conceive of a virtue in someone else that they can't conceive in themselves." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We start off with high hopes, then we bottle it. Basically, we live a short disappointing life; then we die." - Irvine Welsh, Trainspotting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is frantic, panicked and slightly rushed." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/0GzxzZ1UCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My normal ability to feel compassion had been eradicated, the victim of a slow, purposeful erasure." - Bret Easton Ellis, American Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most times, it's just a lot easier not to let the world know what's wrong." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All the effort in the world won't matter if you're not inspired." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 51st Birthday Chuck Palahniuk! "We'll never be as young as we are tonight."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody's all the way dead yet, but lets just say the clock is ticking." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first day you meet someone special, you can count on them one day being dead and in the ground." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think America is just so in love with conflict."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now is the autumn of our ennui." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find joy in everything you choose to do. Every job, relationship, home... It's your responsibility to love it, or change it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Masochism is a valuable job skill." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Insanity is sort of in the eye of the beholder."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are God's middle children, with no special place in history and no special attention." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We love drama. We love conflict. We need a devil or we'll create one." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/AHnvalth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lower you fall, the higher you'll fly." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From famous artists to building contractors, we all want to leave our signature. Our lasting effect. Your life after death." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You could stab a knife right through my heart and you'd be too late." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more people die, the more things stay the same." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: The next three books are written. Here are their titles, summaries and release years. Enjoy. http://t.co/drBXFY8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's so thin she's either dying or rich." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're still the eight year old sitting in school, sitting in church, believing everything you're told." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone smiles with that invisible gun to their head." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We never see others. Instead we see only aspects of ourselves that fall over them. Shadows. Projections. Our associations." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find what you love and let it kill you." - Charles Bukowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The road to hell is paved with publicity stunts." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The future you have, tomorrow, won't be the same future you had, yesterday." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just don't want to die without any scars." #FightClub http://t.co/KXk8DXYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I say deliver me from clear skin and perfect teeth, I say you have to give up! I say evolve, and let the chips fall where they may!" - F.C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Give me lust baby. Give me malice. Give me detached existentialist ennui. Give me rampant intellectualism as a coping mechanism." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More and more, it feels like I'm doing a really bad impersonation of myself." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you died right now, how would you feel about your life?" - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing of me is original. I am the combined effort of everyone I've ever known." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lullaby #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/dNbqe7nI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're always haunted by the idea you're wasting your life." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At least this one looks like love... if you squint." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you don't share your problems, you resent hearing the problems of other people." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is increasing turmoil with a possible physical and emotional breakdown." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Real smarts begin when you quit quoting other people." - Pygmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop the excessive shopping and masturbation. Quit your job. Start a fight. Prove you're alive." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It can only take a moment to waste the rest of your life." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the living are haunted by the dead, then the dead are haunted by their own mistakes." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We come from a generation of people who need their TV or stereo playing all the time. These soundaholics, these quietophobics." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're not drunk and half naked by this point, you're not paying attention." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reject the basic assumptions of civilization, especially the importance of material possessions." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People need a monster they can believe in. A true and horrible enemy. A demon to define themselves against." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can only hold a smile for so long, after that it's just teeth." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Today is the sort of day where the sun only comes up to humiliate you." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harold_smith: Another cover down, this time it's Tell All #ChuckPalahniuk @chuckpalahniuk @methadrone13 @CodeOfConduct http://t.co/K ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choke art #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/MfocE5OR7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we don't know who to hate, we hate ourselves." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hysteria is impossible without an audience. Panicking by yourself is the same as laughing alone in an empty room. You feel really silly."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To some of us, the nights are too long. To some, the days." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["History is nothing except monsters or victims. Or witnesses." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is evil something you are, or something you do?" - Bret Easton Ellis, American Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Turns out @BretEastonEllis celebrated a birthday yesterday. AMERICAN PSYCHO turned 22. Read this retrospective - htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One can't help but picture the lackluster VIP lounge in Heaven, a kind of nonalcoholic ice-cream social." - Damned]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>