<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fully Driverless Waymo Taxis Are Due Out This Year, Alarming Critics https://t.co/28C2BsDgm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo Plans New Version of Switch Next Year https://t.co/EegtyiR8NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lockheed Martin Unveils Plans For Huge Reusable Moon Lander For Astronauts https://t.co/Rffid85TLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Set To 'Eliminate' Cervical Cancer By 2028 https://t.co/LIzMRzDwYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honda Will Use GM's Self-Driving Technology, Invest $750 Million In Cruise Startup https://t.co/0M7u67BRN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toys R Us Cancels Bankruptcy Auction, Plans To Revive Brand https://t.co/gLl9NFOzB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Autonomous Farm Wants To Produce Food Without Human Workers https://t.co/IYu6UmaGPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Yorkers Sue Trump and FEMA To Stop Presidential Alert https://t.co/9KBNBEIwmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG Announces V40 ThinQ With Five Cameras, 6.4-iInch OLED Screen https://t.co/mfbgn4oy1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Is Embracing Android As the Mobile Version of Windows https://t.co/R1HLQORPKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo President: Our Future Is As an 'Entertainment' Company https://t.co/aX3E9CF78t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's Intra App Encrypts DNS Queries To Help Users Bypass Online Censorship https://t.co/zT5szrRqsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychedelic Mushrooms Are Closer To Medicinal Use https://t.co/VA8MsME3gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain Scans Can Detect Who Has Better Skills, Research Says https://t.co/JPxG9gS3l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dell Latitude 7285 combines an immersive display w/ long battery life &amp; optional keyboard to keep you productive on the go. Learn more! https://t.co/XJZZwzreRM https://t.co/FPIm3nVYK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verizon is Offering Buyout Packages To as Many as 44,000 Management Employees, Potentially Eliminating More Than a Fourth of Its Workforce https://t.co/SJfVlxRm2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leon Lederman, 96, Explorer and Explainer of the Subatomic World, Dies https://t.co/mJXBHHa55A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Is Eliminating Bonuses, Stock Awards to Help Pay for Raises https://t.co/STuhMzUIFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Access System Hacking Is No. 1 Patient Safety Risk https://t.co/pTRXirMEDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cities Will Sue FCC To Stop $2 Billion Giveaway To Wireless Carriers https://t.co/c9N7NvUTp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wi-Fi Now Has Version Numbers, and Wi-Fi 6 Comes Out Next Year https://t.co/5Ab3vOewYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entire Broadband Industry Sues California To Stop Net Neutrality Law https://t.co/fIryBsSoxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Now Has the Best Device Lineup in the Industry https://t.co/zpmS9vCwTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Gates-Backed Social Recommendation App Likewise Now Available for iOS and Android https://t.co/ahFPYjDnTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coders Programming Themselves Out of a Job https://t.co/OkGdYSLFkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cellphones Across the US Will Receive a 'Presidential Alert' at 2:18 pm Eastern Today https://t.co/Bhn1mdfE8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Finds 'No Evidence' Hackers Accessed Connected Apps https://t.co/0tVsEgcpNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Announces New Fire TV Stick Featuring 4K Support, and All-New Alexa Voice Remote https://t.co/DjxpWgTNGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobel Prize in Chemistry Awarded to Trio of Evolutionary Scientists https://t.co/7ialgnH0m1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Industry and Tech Groups Unite To Fight Encryption-Busting Bill https://t.co/MbnBxt8BIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovery of 'Goblin' Solar System Object Bolsters the Case For Planet Nine https://t.co/aSVX4D0gSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Study Finds Incredibly High Carbon Pollution Costs -- Especially For the US and India https://t.co/kSqAbQxM4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of US Uber Drivers Make Less Than $10 An Hour After Vehicle Expenses, Study Says https://t.co/0HAdSuVw2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise of Netflix Competitors Has Pushed Consumers Back Toward Piracy https://t.co/iSIXsH5scA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Announces App Mirroring To Let You Use Any Android App On Windows 10 https://t.co/WtgdYfnpCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's First Urban Development Raises Data Concerns https://t.co/USDpZmgjmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AmigaOS 3.1.4 For Classic Amigas Released https://t.co/b2GkrLf3Eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Star Wars: The Last Jedi' Negative Buzz Amplified By Russian Trolls, Study Finds https://t.co/ZGXmAn4bQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla Produced Over 80,000 Cars In Third Quarter, Beating Estimates https://t.co/XhQE249jU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 10 October 2018 Update Is Now Available; Features 'Your Phone' Android Messaging App, Dark Theme For File Explorer, and Other Tweaks https://t.co/LtanA7kdwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Apple Laptops Shipped With Intel Chips In 'Manufacturing Mode' https://t.co/F83qIt5Zvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Unveils Surface Laptop 2 and Surface Pro 6 https://t.co/2FBKeK8yPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government of Canada's Plan To Improve Cybersecurity? Be Less Attractive https://t.co/42mhpf5KL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DARPA Is Researching Quantized Inertia, a Theory Many Think Is Pseudoscience https://t.co/AfkTNhPtX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Slashdot: Why Does Almost Nothing Come With a Proper Printed Manual Anymore? https://t.co/AwEIvdtDOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SuperSU, a Popular Root App For Android, Disappears From Google Play Store https://t.co/pAZSa3Jl1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Solar-Powered, 'Low Tech' Website Goes Offline When It's Cloudy https://t.co/8A40QGM24x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix Eats Up 15% of All Internet Downstream Traffic Worldwide, Study Finds https://t.co/1mF9bSMRVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Governor Jerry Brown Signs a Bill That Bans Bots From Pretending To be Real People https://t.co/grPu4HfgDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers Are Selling Facebook Credentials on the Dark Web For $3 https://t.co/vn3VJFX9pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet Archive Says It Has Restored 9 Million Broken Wikipedia Links By Directing Them To Archived Versions in Wayback Machine https://t.co/RlL4EMRNCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Will Raise Its Minimum Wage To $15 For All 350,000 US Workers https://t.co/7jdIVXg4ih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Apple Engineers Unveil a Next-Generation Sensor For Self-Driving Cars https://t.co/Oiynnflr9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US Government Is Using Road Signs Showing Drivers How Fast They're Going To Capture License Plate Data https://t.co/tGDRqUGyTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physics Nobel Won By Laser Wizardry -- Laureates Include First Woman in 55 Years https://t.co/SBOnqiZkok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half the World Is Now Middle Class Or Wealthier, Says Brookings Institution https://t.co/LE54opKr4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Story of Starlite, the 'Blast Proof' Material https://t.co/pGGCrb2Lrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seattle Police Department Is Offering An Anti-Swatting Service https://t.co/DZT6FDhmex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Computer Has Written A 'Novel' Narrating Its Own Cross-Country Road Trip https://t.co/NTNBs5ygDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Students Say Steve Wozniak's $13,200 Coding Bootcamp Is 'Broken' and Sometimes Links To Wikipedia https://t.co/SNCupTrOTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Puts World's Biggest Solar Power Project On Hold https://t.co/BNcKDjd1oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some iPhone XS, XS Max Devices Are Experiencing Charging Issues https://t.co/7vpwZPg4CO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of Internet, Social Media and Digital Devices Plateaus In US, Pew Research Center Finds https://t.co/87fO3WLPnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GeoCities Japan Is Finally Shutting Down https://t.co/NVaLQD6YKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vigilante Engineer Stops Waymo From Patenting Key Lidar Technology https://t.co/8baG3IG1pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn more about the Dell Latitude 7285. The only 2-in-1 with the ability to transition between four modes: laptop, tent, slate and tablet! https://t.co/0ITEuO6BsI https://t.co/6Yv2ppAq9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Gets Into Game Streaming With Project Stream and Assassin's Creed Odyssey in Chrome https://t.co/aErTMOCvj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VideoLAN Announces Dav1d, a New Libre and Open Source AV1 Decoder https://t.co/d0tNJiamU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Watch Apps Instantly Went 64-bit Thanks To Obscure Bitcode Option https://t.co/ufWeSMg2TH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is Equipping K-8 Classrooms With Robot Sets To Boost Tech Diversity https://t.co/zW32gJ6pJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Updates Chrome Web Store Review Process and Sets New Extension Code Requirements https://t.co/ATyUcdWSvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Now, at Least, the World Isn't Making Enough Batteries https://t.co/O3wIiitEfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cafe in Providence, Rhode Island Serves Free Coffee To Students Who Provide Personal Data; Participants May Receive Info From Cafe's Corporate Sponsors https://t.co/FkF8IMPEdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of the Internet and Smartphones is No Longer on the Rise in America https://t.co/rkRpWV8cEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a Workshop Last Week, a CERN Scientist Said 'Physics Was Invented and Built by Men -- Not By Invitation'; CERN Has Suspended the Scientist https://t.co/hECWBWOyNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP Unveils Spectre Folio, a Convertible Laptop 'Made of Leather' https://t.co/2y9oUwa3IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Travelers Refusing Digital Search Now Face $5000 Customs Fine https://t.co/5Fr9ATQJ36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Forced Suspect To Unlock His iPhone X Through Face ID https://t.co/r1Pnm9L0xR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix is Developing a Slate of Specials That Will Let Viewers Choose the Next Storyline in a TV Episode or Movie, Report Says https://t.co/m121Ldxan6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Open Source Resistance Takes Shape as Tech Giants Race To Map the World https://t.co/gX5UnfojRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James P Allison and Tasuku Honjo Win Nobel Prize For Medicine https://t.co/4fg9CC3Bu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Prepares a Major Weakening of Mercury Emissions Rules https://t.co/pJXFsuwRDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Has a New Law: No More All-Male Boards https://t.co/EX2WyzpIgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gov. Jerry Brown Signs Bill To Restore Net Neutrality in California https://t.co/9Anwr2iPTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudflare Launches a Low-Cost Domain Registrar, Which Will Also Offer Free Privacy To Customers https://t.co/PjUWzZWd2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physicists Investigate Why Matter and Antimatter Are Not Mirror Images https://t.co/HnghxIJD5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Solves Mystery Surrounding 15-Year-Old Fruitfly Mac Malware Which Was Used By a Man To Watch Victims Via their Webcams, and Listen in On Conversations https://t.co/uNnkVEWiCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wikimedia Endowment Gets New $1 Million Backing From Amazon https://t.co/f77hvupEiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ubuntu Linux 18.10 Cosmic Cuttlefish Beta Now Available For Desktop, Cloud and Server Versions https://t.co/zrB1Xpmpzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Kernel Finally Nearing Support For The Apple Magic Trackpad 2, Thanks To a Google Employee https://t.co/UEPueW2ElS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MX Player, a Video App Used By More Than 175 Million Users, Debuts OTT Service. Android Enthusiasts Express Concern. https://t.co/fe6DBrsp5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System76's Much-Anticipated Open Source 'Thelio' Linux Computer Will Be Available To Pre-Order Starting Next Month, But Shipping Date and Specs Remain Unclear https://t.co/6ZGO7DkdLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York's Free LinkNYC Internet Kiosks Are Now Used By 5 Million Users, Who Have Participated in 1 Billion Sessions and Make 500,000 Phone Calls a Month https://t.co/WSSjVbSNHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Spray-On Coating Can Make Buildings, Cars, and Even Spaceships Cooler https://t.co/cfPXNpvv1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Berners-Lee Announces Solid, an Open Source Project Which Would Aim To Decentralize the Web https://t.co/9PZpL13OG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric S. Raymond Identifies A Common Programming Trap:  'Shtoopid' Problems https://t.co/OGdIeohFkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Microsoft Rewrote Its C# Compiler in C# and Made It Open Source https://t.co/KDdlgPYUJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Will Happen When Killer Robots Get Hijacked? https://t.co/ULapW6ebHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 Years Ago, Influenza Killed 50 Million People. Could It Happen Again? https://t.co/y0pLOkelzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Best Open Source Developer Software of 2018' Chosen By InfoWorld https://t.co/W4hHj31wJV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>