<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Take a deep breath, count to ten, and tackle each task one step at a time." - Linda Shalaway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to believe in yourself." - Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't find fault, find a remedy." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want your life to be more rewarding, you have to change the way you think." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your goals are the road maps that guide you and show you what is possible for your life." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell everyone what you want to do and someone will want  to help you do it." -  W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A ship is safe in harbour, but that's not what ships are for." - William Shedd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A superior man is modest in his speech, but exceeds in his actions." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A friend is someone with whom you dare to be yourself." - Frank Crane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love oneself is the beginning of a lifelong romance." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep in mind that neither success nor failure is ever final." - Roger W. Babson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Attitudes are more important than facts." - Dr. Karl Menninger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you'll not settle for anything less than your best, you will be amazed at what you can accomplish in your lives." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People rarely succeed unless they have fun in what they are doing." - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's always too soon to quit." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hide not your talents, they for use were made. What's a sun-dial in the shade." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door." - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed." - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am the greatest, I said that even before I knew I was." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ambition has one heel nailed in well, though she stretch her fingers to touch the heavens." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Light tomorrow with today." - Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're off to Great Places! Today is your day! Your mountain is waiting, So... get on your way!" - Dr Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you learn from defeat, you haven't really lost." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not length of life, but depth of life." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a window of opportunity appears, don't pull down the shade." - Tom Peters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is through cooperation, rather than conflict, that your greatest successes will be derived." - Ralph Charell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never ignore a gut feeling, but never believe that it's enough." - Robert Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ability to honestly and quietly reflect on one's life is one of the most powerful tools for personal growth." - Richard Carlson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your assumptions are your windows on the world.  Scrub them off every once in a while, or the light won't come in." - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Plans are only good intentions unless they immediately degenerate into hard work." - Peter Drucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nature gave us one tongue and two ears so we could hear twice as much as we speak." - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Persistent questioning and healthy inquisitiveness are the first requisite for acquiring learning of any kind." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man of ability and the desire to accomplish something can do anything." - Donald Kircher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know where I'm going and I know the truth, and I don't have to be what you want me to be. I'm free to be what I want." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Making good decisions is a crucial skill at every level." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we do not plant knowledge when young, it will give us no shade when we are old." - Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We make our own fortunes and call them fate." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the midst of movement and chaos, keep stillness inside of you." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty is being the best possible version of yourself.
Audrey Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the truth sets you free, it tends to make you miserable. -
Richard Rohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Either you run the day or the day runs you." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Action speaks louder than words but not nearly as often." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It always seems impossible until it's done." - Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A river cuts through rock, not because of its power, but because of its persistence." - Jim Watkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Excellence is more fun than mediocrity." - Leonard Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you can do, or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power, and magic in it." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is not the destination; it's a way to travel." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is a rough road that leads to the heights of greatness." - Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We need men who can dream of things that never were." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every choice you make has an end result." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you would thoroughly know anything, teach it to others." - Tryon Edwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything comes to him who hustles while he waits." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do what you love, love what you do, and deliver more than you promise." - Harvey Mackay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is nothing so useless as doing efficiently that which should not be done at all." - Peter  Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make the most of the best and the least of the worst." - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Try not to be a man of success, but a man of value." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't be afraid to go out on a limb. That's where the fruit is." - H. Jackson Browne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It doesn't matter who you are, where you come from. The ability to triumph begins with you. Always." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fresh activity is the only means of overcoming adversity." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." - Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All great achievements require time." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you come to a fork in the road, take it." - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["... without darkness, nothing comes to birth, as without light, nothing flowers." - May Sarton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To desire is to obtain; to aspire is to achieve." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can always redeem the man who aspires and strives." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The price of greatness is responsibility." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's always room at the top." - Daniel Webster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The important thing is not to stop questioning. Curiosity has its own reason for existing." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you do the common things in life in an uncommon way, you will command the attention of the world." - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Learning to live in the present moment is part of the path to joy." - Sarah Ban Breathnach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you rest, you rust." - Helen Hayes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tact is the art of making a point without making an enemy." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Believe and act as if it were impossible to fail." - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world hates change, yet it is the only thing that has brought progress." - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is how high you bounce when you hit bottom." - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better." - Samuel Beckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When a goal matters enough to a person, that person will find a way to accomplish what at first seemed impossible." - Nido Qubein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one has ever learned fully to know themselves." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have nothing to declare except my genius." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The mind's job is to validate what it thinks." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All of us do not have equal talent, but all of us should have an equal opportunity to develop our talents." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever your goal, you can get there if you're willing to work." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Self-trust is the first secret of success." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Leap and the net will appear." - Julia Cameron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you think you are too small to be effective, you have never been in the dark with a mosquito." - Betty Reese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Joy is what happens to us when we allow ourselves to recognise how good things really are." -Marianne Williamson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we did all the things we are capable of doing, we would literally astound ourselves." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot teach a man anything; you can only help him find it within himself." - Galileo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Faith is taking the first step even when you don't see the whole staircase." - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You make the decisions to fulfill, to whatever extent, the potential life that exists within you." - Hans Decoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change your thinking, change your life." - Ernest Holmes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are judged by what we finish, not by what we start." - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing great was ever achieved without enthusiasm." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>