<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I need someone who won't give up on me, no matter how hard I try to push them away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles can still happen no matter what it is. You just need to put your faith in your heart and keep believing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, what you want isn't always what you get, but in the end what you get is so much better than what you wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful woman is the one who's proud and comfortable being just herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save the tears in your relationships for someone who will be there to wipe them away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life can be unfair at times, but that isn't a reason to give up. God never said it would always be easy, but it will be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want you. Is that too much to ask?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what our circumstance, we always have something to be thankful for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PiscesTweet: I'm an extremely loyal person... until you aren't. #Pisces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't predict what the future holds, but I'll fight forever to keep you close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are talking about you just because their lives are too boring. Don't respond. Keep living your life, and keep smiling about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel warm and trust each other even when you are apart, it means that you love each other from the heart, not the body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gave us two gifts; one is choice, second is chance, the choice of a good life and the chance to make it the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the most ugliest of people can have the most pure and wonderful of hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the most beautiful of people can have the most ugliest of hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't love you cause you're perfect... I love you cause you're perfect for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be your first love, first kiss, first sight, or first date but I just want to be your last everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need a lot of friends, I just need a few who would be there when I needed them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your voice for kindness, your ears for compassion, your hands for charity, your mind for truth, and your heart for love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All a girl wants is to feel beautiful, be loved, and to be treated with respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing in someone is good, believing in yourself is great, believing in God is everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I expected the least, you entered into my life. When I expected the most, you left from my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to relationships, remaining faithful is never an option but a priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships are about give and give, not give and take. You'll know you're with the right person when they give as much as you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great woman is the one who still loves you more than anything even when you have nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great man is the one who still wants you more than anything even when he has everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone really loves you. they'll never hurt you. And if they do, you'll see that in their eyes... They are hurting too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you respond to your circumstances and the thoughts you choose to believe will shape the rest of your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't really know what love is until you meet that only girl. The one who makes you smile and completes your world .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you know you don't need a man to make everything in your life complete is the same moment that God says "It's time to meet him".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need perfect people in my life, I just want to be around people that love me and people that can make me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love someone is to understand each other, to laugh together, to smile with your heart, and to trust one another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD... I just want to say thank you! Nothing else...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might not get to see you as often as I'd like, but deep in my heart I know that it's true. No matter what happens, I will always love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter who hurt you, or broke you down, what matters is who made you smile again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In love, it is better to know and be disappointed, than to not know and always wonder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm perfect in my imperfections, happy in my pain, strong in my weaknesses, and beautiful in my own way cause I'm me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's better to be kind than to be right. We do not always need an intelligent mind that speaks, just a patient heart that listens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will learn that the best experiences are sometimes made by mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too precious to waste your time thinking about someone who doesn't treat you right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is strange, sometimes it's a reason to live life, but sometimes it becomes a reason to leave life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say a picture tells a thousand words. But when I see yours, I only see three: I Love You.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of people pretend to be happy because smiling has always been easier than explaining to people why you're sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is saving you someone special, and when the time is right, God will put them in your path.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just knowing isn't enough. You need to understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love cannot be explained by words, it must be felt by heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born to make mistakes, not to fake perfection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who really loves you is not someone who sees you everyday, but someone who looks for you everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a girl asks you question, it's better to just give her the truth, chances are she's asking you because she already knows the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We come to love not by finding a perfect person, but by learning to see an imperfect person perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best feelings in the world is knowing your presence and absence both mean something to someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be the sun that shines your day and you'll be the moon that lights up my night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to take an unfamiliar path. Sometimes they're the ones that take you to the best places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may think something is too great to let go, but maybe something greater can only happen if you let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man is afraid of something. That is how you know he is in love with you when he is afraid of losing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience is not the ability to wait, but the ability to keep a good attitude while waiting. God has the solution, don't worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More than anything else, I believe it's our decisions, not the conditions of our lives, that determine our destiny." -Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to let you know I'm still gonna fight for you. I'm not gonna give up on us as easily as you did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get the most out of this life, do more for others than you do for yourself, and do everything to glorify God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your smile is gorgeous, wear it more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never cry for someone who hurts you, just smile and say "Thanks for giving me a chance to find someone better than you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love isn't about always being together. It's about loving each other even more each day no matter how much time you spend apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cry over someone who wouldn't cry over you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's harder to let go of someone you like, but it's a better feeling finding someone new who will care just as much as you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he rejects you, at least you tried.
It's better than wasting precious time wondering what could've been, because then, it'll be too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is filled with smiles, happiness, tears, and pain. You know the best part about it? God is with you every step of the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't have a better tomorrow if you're always thinking about yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, someone has to make us cry, just to make us realize that we deserve someone better that can make us smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When God made you, He must have been thinking about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that makes me wish I were born as a male is... I had the right to fight for the one I really love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like a garden. Sometimes you have to bury your feelings, water them with tears, and then wait to see where they grow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She loves him more then he would ever know, he loves her more than he would ever show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, a pretty face does not mean a pretty heart. Go for the girl that makes you feel complete, not the one that's easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had to count the reasons why I love you and why I'm so in love with you, I'd have count forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You shouldn't give up. Fight for yourself and who you are. You've got to go through the worst times in life to get the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't promise when you're happy. Don't reply when you're angry. And don't decide when you're sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single day you should wake up and commit yourself to becoming a better person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life isn't perfect, but every second with you is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when people turn their backs against you, God is always there with his arms open for you no matter what the situation is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He isn't perfect. I'm not perfect. Our feelings and lives aren't perfect, but we love each other and that's all that really matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman can be with any man in the world she wants to be with, but yet, she chooses you. Please don't take her for granted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must give to receive and accept failure sometimes to achieve, love to be loved and try to forgive even if you can't forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have any requirements to love someone. If I love you, I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are moments in life when you miss someone so much that you just want to pick them from your dreams and hug them for real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this life we cannot always do great things. But we can do small things with great love. -Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be so desperate to find love. Instead, u should save the best part of u for the RIGHT person who deserves you, at the right time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best relationship is when you can completely act yourself and they can still love you for who you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, all I want to do is to be with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith is like Wi-Fi. It's invisible but it has the ability to connect you to what you need, and that is God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very few people have perfect vision, the ability to look through the flaws and see only the best in a person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a difference between "like" and "love". If you like a flower, you will pick it, but if you love it, you will water it everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men are the ones who are given strength by God to protect women. So if you hurt a woman you are not a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl is happiest when she knows that you make her your everything in front of everyone, every time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is the MOST powerful of ANY emotion and the only one of which you have absolutely NO control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be your first love, first kiss, first sight, or first date, but I just want to be your last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those times you say I love you too much, but you still gotta say it because it's true. That's when you're in love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't stop thinking about you, but other times I wonder why I even waste my time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may never understand why God does things that cause you heartache, but you can be sure that God is not making any mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the one who makes you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worry is a total waste of time. It doesn't change anything. All it does is steal your joy for the present.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>