<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This clickbait headline has everything (the strategy is asking for things btw) https://t.co/T6NIKZmm7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The concept of 'Most Advanced Yet Acceptable' explains a lot of product success and user preferences https://t.co/erXTzt0Ube https://t.co/VV9Ni2RL8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of the cashless city: 'There is this real danger of exclusion' https://t.co/zNbgDyhUZZ https://t.co/fZjQHkBGA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divyangsanepara Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hrtnde Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjcrees It all comes together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is just getting too complex... https://t.co/9ntROu0woz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so much today, obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London’s New Way to Count Tube Riders? Tracking Their Phones https://t.co/YYifdJWEfJ https://t.co/kRLrhAUfm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinBelam This place in the city https://t.co/tYBcxfaVcQ sells only London-brewed beer but max measure is 2/3s pint. Conflicted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too much vitamin C... why vitamin pills don't work, and may be bad for you https://t.co/YIe5b5a5jY https://t.co/5NB3AxtFle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iterating through my new book design. Here's v0.2 of pre-launch book cover and title https://t.co/ktgLKodjos https://t.co/oiJCq9QBOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Is in Talks With Hollywood for Early Access to Movies on iTunes https://t.co/hiSAApBvEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1001tweetsapp Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrickBidzDotCom Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevincyu Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@focusatwill Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daleitch Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilldrunkbyko Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McBrideMagic Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glitovine Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srinufx Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble Has Pards actually just succeeded in the managerial equivalent of getting Christmas off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottsantens Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the best stuff I've read this year https://t.co/pyhFW9EbRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of articles out there talking about 'the end of work'/basic incomes etc. This is particularly good https://t.co/0G096aAmr7 https://t.co/KSpmfDUdTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thefootbalr Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fordengroup Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You need to spend time on the future even when there are more important things to do in the present" https://t.co/VIMDPFORaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical Candor — The Surprising Secret to Being a Good Boss https://t.co/rSGlFgSGW4 https://t.co/Wm7PSpfHWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PromotionOffice Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s more likely that what you think will happen in the next five years will actually happen in the next three." https://t.co/u3fCci4Lxq https://t.co/S7lGXVU3o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Tweet from @ishmatt has been withheld in: Argentina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurationSuite Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurelnatale Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Worldstartupmap Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Blog Posts Are Boring: 9 Tips for Making Your Writing More Interesting https://t.co/LbnkUL1lq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emoji_ben Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Sometimes magic is just someone spending more time on something than anyone else might reasonably expect.” https://t.co/xBk3ZMb4wO https://t.co/Rlrl2A0Lzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexa and Google Home Record What You Say. But What Happens to That Data? https://t.co/56pgZTorZs https://t.co/kkaE5oMowj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASAPATHEIST Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@databoxHQ Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkForster87 Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble @lukeaaronmoore @petedonaldson Just don't let Speller get too lairy on his Baileys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeaaronmoore @FootballRamble @petedonaldson Have a good one chaps, gutted to miss it this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quttera Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickdesign_me Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@milkandeggscom Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only 43 per cent of those rough sleeping in the capital in 2014–2015 were British citizens" https://t.co/8SVan8Y5g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make a Bot That Isn't Racist https://t.co/WuqLQhWk4h https://t.co/Q4FadVQJBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Custom cookbooks from online recipes make total sense. It's like a printed version of your bookmarks... https://t.co/9rMIiTDgi5 https://t.co/CM0byuRMjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gvre Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @worrydream: In honor of the death of Hans Rosling (too soon), watch his video on eradicating global poverty. https://t.co/J4BKdNiKtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you should design at 1x resolution https://t.co/HbaRi5HKxX https://t.co/8dOapcWal3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWarcos Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amelia_Womack Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great honest post on the realities of time management. It boils down to saying no/doing less https://t.co/KcsuAUiI8L https://t.co/V4VothXyHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is last chance for 25% pre-launch discount on Designing Ecommerce Websites https://t.co/ktgLKodjos #uxdesign https://t.co/qzcxfpOItC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amelia_Womack: After years of it being on the cards, our student loans have now been privatised ☹️#studentloans https://t.co/5RS35mUOhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["China increasingly drives global supply and demand, while the West settles for Nobel prizes." https://t.co/Ft5tbrObwg https://t.co/b6KWswwpxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phanosd Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a bunch of snowflakes &gt; Russia demands apology from Fox News for Bill O'Reilly calling Putin a 'killer' https://t.co/U3Z6eVxwkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @danbarker: Every time @realDonaldTrump mentions the NYT their share price jumps. Was on a strong downward trend until he was elected. h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lazy Thinking: Modularity Always Works https://t.co/oUAbrP9pBQ https://t.co/tnyaDfv7Fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tunelland Hi, there's no new date for this one at the moment. You can follow here to see when it's scheduled again https://t.co/cfMJE8lmUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TALK72Podcast Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanBeeson Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know when making an analytics dashboard https://t.co/57rVtiC2oW #ux https://t.co/3xGjzMyfDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final cover is ready for my new book. Out in a few days time... https://t.co/ktgLKodjos #ecommerce #ux https://t.co/hlaHGb8YVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More good stuff from @johnharris1969 on the realities of politicians being able to make jobs https://t.co/6WyvColtKe https://t.co/bHS2ilsnz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkGoulston Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@panzopan Theresa would be proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilippeAuclair: Imagine if the swing had been towards UKIP. I think we'd heard a bit more about this, as about other similar results t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are individuals capable of processing all the information they once relied on institutions to process for them?" https://t.co/1FqFj9acUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lrntto: The Learnetto Podcast Episode 006 - How to be a data-driven UX designer with @ishmatt - https://t.co/FzHmlU5U7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the future of "badges worn by employees to record their movements, interactions and speaking patterns” https://t.co/NsoJqyPCQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraftMetropolis Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Milo Yiannopoulos became famous by violating the terms and conditions of a social media site’s user agreement. https://t.co/P…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words of my MP voting against yesterday. Great point on most Londoners being immigrants in some form. https://t.co/4bTrRIS9X8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanshale Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Law_and_policy: MPs voting against what they believe to be national interest are a greater danger to representative democracy than anyt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCDanielS: Fellow MEP in the European Parliament as Nigel Farage speaks. "He's lying to you" the sign says. https://t.co/W8YLibFWZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_may Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@i_bm Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two great pods, get on them https://t.co/JqnSC3Xyaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joffley 'Disappearing photos and videos' is a catchy name...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Muir: THIS IS ALL OF US RIGHT NOW. ALL OF US. SCREAMING INTO A FUCKING WELL: https://t.co/CzXxkIDywg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarolineLucas: Well I didn't know we were quite *that* powerful. (This is ridiculous): https://t.co/7u5v9xrlwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gt: If nutrition labels were designed to visualize ingredients like this, we would make better choices—as would the manufacturers. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf? https://t.co/SWJzEM3czU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrianleslie: This is chillingly well argued https://t.co/aBrxLncz3t https://t.co/lqFDPMFot6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MJowen174: Trump Visit In Full 

Wetherspoons Reception
Jim Davidson Recital
Megabus Motorcade
Meet That Shakespeare Guy
Return (Melani…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's better anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential visitors to USA are gonna have to be careful what they tweet. Trump is a fascist bellend. Oops. https://t.co/60V19pmlQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@festivaluprise Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArancinaUK Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mizzhena Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hulk_Themes Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maiabridi Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to design a great ecommerce website https://t.co/07Ma4gY3rP https://t.co/ASEgitkdaW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>