<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/XsjwLzK3JI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/7oeqmU3bTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/Ee44JOSYy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/rWJID9B4FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/yakJOi3Wed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/1sJIuAuH6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/AqUqIYrBXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/bbPEI4l1Z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/thxlC5LpMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/QME3SmaGzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/AhxDWOHLjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/Xu7480OWOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/trAnrNxOQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/6F2ZbBxWKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/bfnMomSd4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/PM0Eph8Drp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/aYlfD5UwnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/8vDMNn30lP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/nOQEZg5uHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/HJPqg5bQn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/XllfN9uPYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/Yf7Uav9iHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/tudTJKrEv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/4PpNHOD2WI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/slVDq0jmKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/DagFW712jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/D1lVm9O2Wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/HYpHhXp8Ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/9wNc8vYECl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/13fwrXa2KJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/I3zfFd3fV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/NgZ45J2tns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/QyoG3010TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/AhxDWOHLjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/w0PfX3v06X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/CJotrRKYZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/4DjM4Mg6uZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/gpLhzEQWKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/vXfizjLYB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/m7k1BTPIQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/Se6cgbU23w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/S5TsGnykNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/vNVg2Kt9b6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/OjcEuIl9SO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/lmgglO1yvv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>