<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/NRBDFb4Mun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chiffons   http://t.co/x1LDC06axL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/2A29DRn3wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/RqQUMfhU85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/VSMFKnwD64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/zHvdA2JOLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/1IwladebvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/UarKS3ttC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the Cecil B. DeMille of science fiction. - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/jOFNtnkCCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/mzC4wFo0EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/tzjc4EW7h9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/NhT2mwF4ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/HlqJKfIPKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/1LdrbJUDJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/mQNq6g8ZNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/DlR8dLHn26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/rjnGGP3sSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/XQs6o9xVKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/CLfr5bRiGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/LOA8ghAvVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/rZjaNHFWjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/mSxQwKjTSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/054jBgSbsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/0Iu12i8P1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/soprAl39TR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/kL8vQFswGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/6iBSsKYOOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/Dj1efULJwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/OGxXs9TfvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/7pUuiXKZBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/404iI41zs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/6KqicNdGR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/Qb23dgSq37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/brp8S9gx69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/CFWaZzBhQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/t3Y9Ocd6jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/Stbe52WawT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/iAOYh8sRqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/rZjaNHFWjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/CgdLJ0Ufr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/Cj2juPw1be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/0frMYDld3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/FKW0rSVSO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/DdE5WaKuK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/70Wfa0M681]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/tMfDSbFk7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/81dSFSFkga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/gZf0Xtm5l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/mhNUyxYXf2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>