<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter. I should have a recurring "I am worried about Twitter" section.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see why he's in the market for new lawyers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli. You can hear a little of the secret Wu-Tang Clan album in the background, maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t think we know yet." I feel like I know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you might as well get bigger -- or get acquired by someone bigger -- to deal with all the regulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes the entire finance industry more fragile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like it is not the name "hedge fund"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "Hedge funds with more than $16 billion have announced shutdowns so far in 2015."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder is a mess. "The market for food delivery via app is 'overcrowded'"; I guess food delivery is to 2015 what laundry was to 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty average, says The Harvard Crimson, but that's not what I want to talk about. What I want to talk about is this: Yup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Himes just uses "material" and trusts the courts to know what it means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A second would be to say, okay, I get the web of relationships where banks allocate deals to help their issuers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is a big markup! And Leonardos don't Trace; it's not easy to see what the last trade was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing in this column. But some of what I write elsewhere is CEOing advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially since the main argument is that the jury should have gotten to see a deposition that Steve Cohen did with the SEC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, it was run by Martin Shkreli, how do you think its internal e-mails read?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This all seems like good news if you work in the industry, but most people don't, and of course there are skeptics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, business schools aspire to be two-year sleepover parties for future CEOs, and they're right on track.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too big to jail too big to jail too big to jaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The current U.S. approach -- misappropriation, personal benefit, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Necessarily. See footnote 2, though: It does own some RMBS, and so conceivably some writedowns could come out of its pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could phrase that more kindly; the expressive goods retain most of their value even if a genuine compromise is reached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really everyone should try to set expectations low when they start a new job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, Theranos is in a "pause period."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But if banks get better at measuring the value of research, they'll be better able to put a price on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This checking with your broker is called a "locate.") You don't have to actually borrow it to sell it short, and neither does your broker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anything I feel like academia is now more skeptical of activism than it was a decade ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's rich enough. But that attitude is probably why I'm not him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Ackman has spent the last three-plus years arguing that Herbalife is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human condition is that we are mortal beings, and nobody can live forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're short Treasury calls and want to hedge that exposure, you have to buy Treasuries as they go up, and sell as they go down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, here is "IPO Pricing as a Function of your Investment Banks’ Past Mistakes: The Case of Facebook."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Most of them are not current public-company executives, and the ones who are have known Ackman interest already.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(A deal that would preserve its CEO's job? Sure, maybe.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand it is hard to resist thinking of governance in moral terms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But one benefit of this theory is that it excuses the Fed a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he knew he wasn't supposed to insider trade. So why did he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Stuff kicked off as an e-mail newsletter one year ago today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crime that has everyone outraged here, and that has led to record-breaking fines, is not fixing FX rates in chat rooms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will I be more likely to see “Angry” content because I personally stay on Facebook longer when I’m reading stories that make me mad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF YOU WANT TO KEEP IT SECRET, BE SURE TO PUT IT IN ALL CAPS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you actually do the blood tests that you've claimed you can do? And obviously you need to have answers for those questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha no the opposite, millennials get really mad about social-media faux pas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There could be “a lot of contagion effects,” he said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it severely understates what has been done to make sure the crisis doesn’t happen again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I didn’t send flowers,” Mr. Trump says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buchanan seems to think that is a bad motive. But it's a good motive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one but a sociopath would actually borrow a friend's shoes and sell them on eBay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(You don't even have to have worked there to write one!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're keeping the headline anyway because "blood wolframite" doesn't have the same ring to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Fidelity kept money market funds safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their benefit checks won't start arriving in the mail, and the value of their eventual benefits will keep rising as if they hadn't filed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The statute of limitations for bringing securities fraud cases is five years. Do you see the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She may be hampered by the fact that Goldman Sachs has given her more money ($675,000), and she doesn't have to pay it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Deutsche Bank announced the details of "Strategy 2020," its plan to get smaller and safer and more profitable and more boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some dishonesty might be required to grease the wheels of bond commerce. Elsewhere: "Tensions mount in repo market."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, using credit derivatives to hedge credit risk would, one hopes, have the effect of reducing risk-weighted assets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their trade: short both bearish and bullish leveraged ETFs in the same industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why it is consumption. At least consumption of financial "advice," or whatever this is, might trick you into saving money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(For more, read “Three Unicorns to Bet On.”) The parenthetical is a bit jarring, and I suspect Cohan didn't write it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgepearkes (Neither is Matt Yglesias. ) I do think, though, that might be ... good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think literally no person disputes this fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody is worried about Point72 liquidity, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is not a fan: Obviously there are mood-affiliation benefits to demanding that bankers get paid less, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo!? Meanwhile on the Old Internet, should Yahoo sell Yahoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then on went the op risk charge, bringing the banks back to a CET1 ratio that the Fed was comfortable with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weird thing is that this guy teaches in the "Negotiation, Organizations &amp; Markets unit" at HBS. And this is how he negotiates?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't sound like any of them actually bought stock though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a lot of fun of Jefferies's "be nice" memo back in September, but their hearts were more or less in the right place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't get cost reductions from hypothetical computerized trading; you get them from the computerized trading that actually exists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In filings, the 1MDB fund has reported paying more than a billion dollars to Aabar—not specifying a full name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this one of those cases where the media simply doesn't appreciate the realities of the industry that it covers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Camp's bill apparently also would subject publicly traded private equity partnerships to corporate tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like obviously the client is expecting an un-marked-up price, and so thwarting his expectations seems straightforwardly dishonest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still, there are those who would argue that evaporating it, while worse than redistributing it, is still better than not evaporating it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much longer tweets -- you know, like Facebook posts -- are coming soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's the mortage servicing business going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably more interesting than just another data point on how much they overpay their CEOs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh sure, probably; some of them are quoted here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you might as well get bigger -- or get acquired by someone bigger -- to deal with all the regulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway there's the usual claims of pumping (with press releases) and dumping (of stock), but also this: Come on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway here is an SMBC cartoon on the subject.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Let's just start with the name: "leveraged conversion."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two weird things going on here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volatility is high, or it is low. If asset prices are low and volatility is high, that seems bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never really got it, but this article about him is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, to hear the Fed describe it, banks are in a weirdly lucrative place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So here's Starboard's letter to Yahoo: Ouch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, trading banks struggle to consistently outperform the other two business types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Con: If you grind the banks down to nothing then you don't have banks any more, and didn't you want banks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except Citadel, Citadel is great, they're expanding into lots of market-making businesses that banks are leaving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[), American Apparel (that name! ), and RadioShack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like Yahoo's corporate mission statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weatherford sent him a draft of a standard consultancy agreement but: I don't know, who's to blame here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how to 
make the Volcker Rule worse
.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the one hand, a lot of politicians are going to shout at you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[— so they just piled up, leaning against a wall or stacked on the floor, former employees said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: 

Technically the SEC's conflict minerals rule does not apply to diamonds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the underlying activity is legislative in nature, it is protected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The buddy seems not to be, at least not yet, though give it time.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>