<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/MPqKd5ISdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/f4PWAdyvy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/y4aL30HyRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/dssreWyVbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/pI43wZanmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/qsHyXQgwaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/lsBRgZNjvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/BBtlBOpLkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/u1CZNFp3N0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/Eaxt1sY8PZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/UGzBZGxtVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/10gUsB4MXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/J2P56zAzIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/YtFU1K6dHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/jFqtkBALb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/awIRisRd9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/dZmp3VkLaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/NPCZDFDZXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/hIktn79IkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/mw3CnOZTnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/PiQ9MRcIbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/QANKxlA0HG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/wamh3u4sdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/2MuWUvKBJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/y9DM5LmHFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/OPH02qE2Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/jWetOcZEAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/dtmv8EKij0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/qcJZAC6dzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/xD8wLo5BDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/D8y3rMc4tY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/VMi2NEjcEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/5CSoX0mJKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/CEkEBnKTYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/7577DjEW6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/0KbJJrFuQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/yGZ20kutwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/OLtzOzZX6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/hj8vyPkLlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/2XA2ltD5W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/k8kXtmiwDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/m4eFMMNgHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/2SbhClTUce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Q6thWir5Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/eo2QTVXxUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/hrDYtyRyG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/dQPMYKMcIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/O7TWlgP8UT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/B8n9XC6cHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/LIDsi3IoEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/jJXTdGDect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/HxA2mE7TRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>