<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/bHkPzTUHsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/pMpzq6gEl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/238ivt9DuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/1BVhvTefL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/KF3vi8Wose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/6ujPWvSTag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/7kh5bVIWnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/WlNOGKlDJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/oQIdzo3lu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/wcGjRhlbtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/x9QnOsP0w6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/3qlyEGDIgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/ya8JJ7Ac9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/r1dmkSEfEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/8cwbYeqqBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/kzEiZRpAcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/aR1619SJa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/BSQuFMPAWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/sfec1OvSeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/rAn3pCY9kV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/rkkV8zEiiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/WOIEaf4hx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/4AyafmePli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/CuBsZ6V13E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/BmmvzGymEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/pY7d0vG0gW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/RZOkaNfYJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/almqL2S0c4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/jyOhyN77xI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/Ro0FR2oi52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/m2D0aklu4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/XZuaTKEtBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/EyM4jZMrDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/RjCHBOfry1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/1wVmteIWOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/2cv1hMRBpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/tOd4EaUceH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/YW6036irr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/6HY4qb9ZXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/sjrQE1kRBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/nA7liqM3CI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/awb5pLILaB  http://t.co/o9P16zbNBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/IHcUUV3PUa]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>