<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/TA05TlEiDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/A7Gj2lkjgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/KxnOeaOqiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/2KS1K9ogcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/bonl3Tr1Jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/5A5khrdopT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/dE7ONzX4dY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/Ylqa6Eww7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/EVrriWoEFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/t28OOeL3F9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/zBanLO8FfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/pKpXIerpIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/8kPF9PpkN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/l2kZuKc0oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/Wgf0gyoT12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/MLGE2ggmWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/MQjiRySDM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/Oy0AdYiXhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/t4R7Wj3mod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/phzneNWs2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/afeBAby0VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/GgUYnj7kJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/1lMoZbY3yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/334300g2Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/GIucMtYL9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/xNQdzMRnhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/KN8InJP9rZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/AsYCEWjs9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/GyzqXUwylo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/LIcGIYCoIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/ainXtBeTjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/rtKOauGaSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/gqxrQx1qxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/9pAdKWhcym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/M9HHeOjynj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/FwnYgIXWgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/NEGjd4Vv5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/0ZxMVhhXlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/Xi5LG5qOy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/xpl924p0P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/pxX7l2PnwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/MSczI9wutD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/M8K8jofDBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/0cGOFeupER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/svGSZPvHfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Cool Glow in the Dark Toilet Roll http://t.co/2GY0ESk1Re]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>