<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of your life is the quality of your relationships.  -Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudden resolutions, like the sudden rise of mercury in a barometer, indicate little else than the variability of the weather. -David Hare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody really cares if you're miserable, so you might as well be happy. -Cynthia Nelms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's got badly, goes badly. -Irish proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect Quotes https://t.co/Fkf5XPbnpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can stand tall without standing on someone. You can be a victor without having victims. -Harriet Woods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U have 2 put in many, many, many tiny efforts that nobody sees or appreciates b4 U achieve anything worthwhile. -Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you walk down the fairway of life you must smell the roses, for you only get to play one round. -Ben Hogan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to leave the world a little better than I found it, and that's my goal in life. -Armand Hammer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who is afraid of a thing gives it power over him. -Moorish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may doubt what you say, but they will believe what you do. -Lewis Cass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes the hammer of persistence to drive the nail of success. -John Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticism Quotes https://t.co/QNx7F2kEjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is wise to keep in mind that no success or failure is necessarily final. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get action. Seize the moment. Man was never intended to become an oyster. -Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything you vividly imagine, ardently desire, sincerely believe &amp; enthusiastically act upon must come to reality. -Paul Meyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man can only receive what he sees himself receiving. -Florence Scovel Shinn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've exhausted all possibilities, remember this: you haven't! -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discontented Poem https://t.co/DTfzEILyvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What great things would you attempt if you knew you could not fail? -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibilitizing is overcoming while you're undergoing. -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you limit your actions in life to things that nobody can find fault with, you will not do much. -Charles Dodgson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To find out what one is fitted to do, and to secure an opportunity to do it, is the key to happiness. -John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The highest reward for man's toil is not what he gets for it, but what he becomes by it. -John Ruskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Originality and the feeling of one's own dignity are achieved only through work and struggle. -Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware of dissipating your powers; strive constantly to concentrate them. -Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage Poem https://t.co/aB3Arv3Lpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy are those who dream dreams and are ready to pay the price to make them come true. -L.J. Cardinal Suenens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing of worthy or weight can be achieved with half a mind, with a faint heart, and with a lame endeavor. -Isaac Barrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should carefully observe which way his heart draws him, and then choose that way with… https://t.co/xOWOLr9tQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength is a matter of the made-up mind. -John Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for opportunity. You can't wait for it to knock on the door. You might not be home. -Jinger Heath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You create your opportunities by asking for them. -Patty Hansen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude is a quality similar to electricity: it must be produced and discharged and used up in order to exist at all. -Faulkner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I Must Do Is All That Concerns Me https://t.co/oILCqsViR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is more to life than just existing and having a pleasant time. -Johann Friedrich Von Schiller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was when I found out I could make mistakes that I knew I was on to something. -Ornette Coleman #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't program yourself, life will program you! -Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Talk happiness. The world is sad enough without your woe." -Orison S. Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should carefully observe which way his heart draws him, and then choose that way with all his strength. -Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we could learn to like ourselves, even a little, maybe our cruelties and angers might melt away. -John Steinbeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Tack https://t.co/b2oTVg5ZPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you are afraid to do is a clear indicator of the next thing you need to do. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it. -George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to achieve excellence, you can get there today. As of this second, quit doing less-than-excellent work. -Thomas Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never be the person you can be if pressure, tension and discipline are taken out of… https://t.co/CMP67Yoqus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worry does not empty tomorrow of its sorrow; it empties today of its strength. -Corrie Ten Boom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The golden rule for every business man is this: Put yourself in your customer's place.  -Orison Swett Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The basis of accomplishment is in never quitting. -Mengzi Meng-tse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is by attempting to reach the top in a single leap that so much misery is produced in the world. -William Cobbett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempest-Tossed Souls https://t.co/za7lowiovJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immense power is acquired by assuring yourself in your secret reveries that you were born to control affairs. -Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From success you get a lot of things, but not that great inside thing that love brings you. -Samuel Goldwyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep in mind that the true measure of an individual is how he treats a person who can do him absolutely no good. -E Friedman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't grow unless we take risks. Any successful company is riddled with failures. -James E. Burke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We know nothing about motivation. All we can do is write books about it." -Peter F Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though ambition in itself is a vice, it often is also the parent of virtue. -Edgar Quinet #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Better or the Good https://t.co/MogTdOvjh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be humble, you're not that great. -Golda Meir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use what talents you possess; the woods would be very silent if no birds sang there except those that sang best. -Henry van Dyke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No thoroughly occupied man was ever yet very miserable. -Letitia Elizabeth Landon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is with trifles and when he is off guard that a man best reveals his character. -Arthur Schopenhauer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A nail is driven out by another nail; habit is overcome by habit." -Desiderius Erasmus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If hard work were such a wonderful thing, surely the rich would have kept it all to themselves. -Lane Kirkland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Efficiency is doing things right; effectiveness is doing the right things." -Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cast of Characters https://t.co/1eFs1GQ0EM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God uses suffering as a whetstone, to make men sharp with." -Henry Ward Beecher #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To design the future effectively, you must first let go of your past. -Charles J. Givens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seize the day. -Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Act boldly and unseen forces will come to your aid. -Dorothea Brande]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick battles big enough to matter, but small enough to win. -Jonathan Kozol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man has in himself a continent of undiscovered character. Happy is he who acts as the Columbus to his own soul. -Sir J. Stephen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Your Life Like You Climb A Mountain https://t.co/HHBjQrQCIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget mistakes. Forget failure. Forget everything except what you're going to do now &amp; do it. Today is your lucky day. -Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goals are the fuel in the furnace of achievement. -Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep your fears to yourself, but share your inspiration with others." -Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather see the wonders of the world abroad, than, living dully sluggardized @ home, wear out thy youth w/ shapeless idleness. -Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, but when the eraser wears out ahead of the pencil, you're overdoing it. -Josh Jenkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day, you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. -Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The man who does not read good books has no advantage over the man who cannot read them." -Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read, If You Want To Be Interesting https://t.co/tDDHglQma4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't the strength to impose your own terms upon life, you must accept the terms it offers you. -T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those whose work and pleasures are one are fortune's favorite children. -Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person without a sense of humor is like a wagon without springs. It's jolted by every pebble on the road. -Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps. -Confucius #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every job is a self-portrait of the person who did it. Autograph your work with excellence. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never miss the water till the well runs dry. -English Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron-Will Determination https://t.co/ggfqn7Rhjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't have confidence, you'll always find a way not to win. -Carl Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain. -Rita Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion is the medium between knowledge and ignorance. -Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've found luck is quite predictable. If u want more luck, take more chances. B more active. Show up more often. -Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We consume our tomorrows fretting about our yesterdays. -Persius #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There can be no friendship without confidence, and no confidence without integrity.  -Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a man could have half of his wishes, he would double his troubles. -Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope is the companion of power, and mother of success; for who so hopes strongly has within him the gift of miracles. -S Smiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slander is like a hornet; if you cannot kill it dead the first blow, better not strike at it. -Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as bravery; only degrees of fear. -John Wainwright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enthusiasm is the greatest asset in the world. It beats money, power and influence. -Henry Chester]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>