<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ecommerce in Slovenia and Croatia compared - Ecommerce News #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/KOopqAh0YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Survey says: Political polarization isn't the internet's fault - Engadget #internet #web https://t.co/nrVPqvjSHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Here's How You Make Customer Service Your Secret Weapon #entrepreneur https://t.co/qsxGxo8nPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju RIT team heads to national cybersecurity competition - Rochester Business Journal #competition https://t.co/t9us7halVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people dream of great accomplishments, while others stay awake and do them" via Danielle Luedtke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social storms Digiday Awards with adidas campaign #socialcommerce https://t.co/YXOOhG2mFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Anything Living On Saturn's Moon Enceladus Might Belch Methane #technology #geek https://t.co/Z1OPTS69Mb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Is Being Accused of Publishing Child Pornography - Fortune #facebook #internet https://t.co/bBuTvwsheJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline is the bridge between goals and accomplishment. Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju New S$21m mail sorting facility boosts Singapore's e-commerce scene - Channel .. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/pJX6xglZML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Internet Companies Urge FCC to Save Net Neutrality Rules - Variety #internet #web https://t.co/wrrzyyk1vE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How the Seasons Affect Your Direct Mail Campaigns #entrepreneur https://t.co/xp1W9iQM68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social Commerce Is Primed to Go Mainstream (Survey) - Adweek #socialcommerce https://t.co/Om7lGrosgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Jam the Trump Brand - The Intercept #branding #brands https://t.co/I56XNy1uWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song.- Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Lingo That'll Save Your Next Cocktail Party, From 'Rovables' to 'Manthrea.. #technology #geek https://t.co/SD6DnOqXse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This 25-year-old left a $120000-a-year job to become a Facebook video star .. #facebook #internet https://t.co/Cxjk5jnR2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A meeting is an event at which the minutes are kept and the hours are lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Op-Ed: SWOT analysis of the Nigerian e-commerce sector - TechCabal #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/Po13G92jel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The evolution of the Internet - https://t.co/QeRzGLXpWI #internet #web https://t.co/CVwNHa5VvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Which is Better: an IRA or a 401K? #entrepreneur https://t.co/I5mXYXYudw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How the promise of social commerce is being fulfilled by chatbots - Businessins.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/KKKxXe6HZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju These Are Teens' Favorite Brands of 2017 - Fortune #branding #brands https://t.co/hjCoq2Sog8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Alanis Morissette isn't buying her ex-business manager's embezzlement explanat.. #manager #leader https://t.co/G9gwMOPWSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the right people on the bus and in the right seat. Jim Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Math's $1,000,000 Question Isn't Just for Mathematicians Anymore #technology #geek https://t.co/zkfYdaID1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Accused San Bernardino Shooter's Facebook Fawning Disguised Homicidal Rage .. #facebook #internet https://t.co/aNBqDNe75P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail. Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Cross-border e-commerce facilitator raises $16 million - Business Insider #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/PF9ociKQmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 17 million people have no reason to join the internet because it's dominated by .. #internet #web https://t.co/FKvApAPxTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Make Better Business Decisions by Seeing Where the World Is Going #entrepreneur https://t.co/0zi4sXsy0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Twitter now lets brands make their own 'custom hearts' for Periscope ... - Te.. #branding #brands https://t.co/kZB3pXuddz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never invest in anything that eats or needs repairing. Billy Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #349 #socialcommerce https://t.co/oZ0ga9Qg4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The 'Most Dangerous' Volcano Can Be a Tricky Thing to Pin Down #technology #geek https://t.co/05CIFf85r2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Need More Alternatives to Facebook - MIT Technology Review #facebook #internet https://t.co/XQiGFgvSZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to manage somebody, manage yourself. Do that well and you'll be ready to stop managing. And start leading." via Mark Gonzales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju International Chamber of Commerce pushes for ecommerce agenda at WTO - Economi.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/PxMIGIVjew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Connecticut lawmakers push to protect Internet privacy - CT Post #internet #web https://t.co/wEilA41uZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Tips for Maximizing Software-as-a-Service Growth #entrepreneur https://t.co/Q3pg9Z5iW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tencent becomes China's first $100 billion brand: WPP survey - CNBC #branding #brands https://t.co/SAM9fejlYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Richard Simmons Signs New Business Deal, Manager Says Return to the Spotlight .. #manager #leader https://t.co/OJwiJV41Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only true wisdom is knowing that you know nothing." Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Free Nuggs. Pls RT #technology #geek https://t.co/QmiZljAUFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Properties Dominate Social Networking Worldwide - Newsweek #facebook #internet https://t.co/3oFXhKuPte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Best Dividend Stock in E-Commerce - Motley Fool #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/B4U75SGArc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Bill would legalize internet gambling in Michigan, but only inside casinos - Cra.. #internet #web https://t.co/QoeNDAW4V8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What You Can Learn About Business From a Mango Vendor in Fiji #entrepreneur https://t.co/IPFHMdS2MB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Rice Business Plan Competition announces 2017 winners - Houston Business Journal #competition https://t.co/VT5B5cHCa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Nuclear War? Nah. Massive Fires Haunt the Dystopian Future #technology #geek https://t.co/xsOCtrfBaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Relative of man shot dead on West Side: 'Facebook killed him' - Chicago Tri.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/WZNVkiTPvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, therefore, is not an act but a habit - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju When a Small Ecommerce Business Should Consider a Consultant - Entrepreneur #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/lJBCSOIy0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Mass. GOP senators file Internet privacy bill - The Boston Globe #internet #web https://t.co/TN9mNn5NHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 2 Entrepreneurs Describe Their Worst Business Moments -- and How They Overcame Them #entrepreneur https://t.co/EM6m2FU9jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What are the top 100 brands in US? - Jackson Clarion Ledger #branding #brands https://t.co/7uAP1K6Rpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age is an issue of mind over matter. If you don’t mind, it doesn’t matter.- Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The New Smurfs Movie Finally Solves the Smurfette Problem #technology #geek https://t.co/0AgdzpEJ80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook resource helps spot misleading news - Fayetteville Observer #facebook #internet https://t.co/gQLa9enori]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to manage somebody, manage yourself. Do that well and you'll be ready to stop managing. And start leading." via Mark Gonzales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju ECommerce is Dead. Long Live iCommerce! - Customer Think #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/f8s13jTFex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Secret to Free Music Is Internet Radio - Gizmodo #internet #web https://t.co/KwHtkahaoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Affiliate Marketing Model: A Blueprint for Success in the Gig Economy #entrepreneur https://t.co/ZuF5l37kZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Coach's latest executive shuffle shows ambitions to acquire more brands - CNBC #branding #brands https://t.co/UZ5x33hVmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Opportunities don't happen, you create them." via Chris Grosser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju TV Isn't Dead So Long Live YouTube TV #socialcommerce https://t.co/tqSsRURjqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Sorry, But if You're Married, Browsing Tinder Totally Makes You a Snake #technology #geek https://t.co/XIpmxIre9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the things worth doing in the world had been declared impossible before they were done. Louis D. Brandeis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How I Came Up With a Million-Dollar Ecommerce Idea in 20 Minutes - Entrepreneur #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/FsO1FxfP97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju For Internet Privacy, VPNs Are an Imperfect Shield - New York Times #internet #web https://t.co/QLZqTo3pts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Simple Ways to Make Sure Your Direct Mail Campaign Is Opened #entrepreneur https://t.co/6pTDGZVBOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social Commerce Not a Hit—Except When It Is - eMarketer #socialcommerce https://t.co/n8zeHo6IPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Amazon's fashion brands are growing rapidly — but it'll take awhile to catch .. #branding #brands https://t.co/TQaHEq7bgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Police ID man killed at Winston-Salem business; manager injured - Winston-Sale.. #manager #leader https://t.co/Js703vd9OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will. Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Search for the Universe's Missing Antimatter Remains Annoyingly Nebulous #technology #geek https://t.co/c7AkFo5gaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's Midwest Move Bursts Tech's Bicoastal Bubble - WIRED #facebook #internet https://t.co/k4QI1dDigf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work." Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ralph Lauren calls ecommerce audible, bets on Salesforce - ZDNet #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/jxZps4J73D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Socialize the Internet - Jacobin magazine #internet #web https://t.co/nrYFDgD8Cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Creating Space for Introverts to Flex Their Superpower #entrepreneur https://t.co/WlH2orlNjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Cramer Remix: This biotech player could get pounded by some fierce competition - C.. #competition https://t.co/QMVAQg5tN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Here's the message brands are sending Fox and customers - https://t.co/spvyEo4OmS #branding #brands https://t.co/8pOfWawsi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She should go far. The sooner she starts, the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju You Could Soon Print Out Simple Electronics With Your Deskjet #technology #geek https://t.co/BcyM0YIPlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Partners With Craiglist's Founder to Fight Fake News - Fortune #facebook #internet https://t.co/UhyiyQbjbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to cheer yourself up is to try to cheer somebody else up.- Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trump Signs Bill Letting Internet Service Providers Sell User Browsing Data - CB.. #internet #web https://t.co/nUggaZl1BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Pay Attention to Your Own Guidance System #entrepreneur https://t.co/jmqseVwMLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why China Is Leading Us To The Future Of Commerce - Forbes #socialcommerce https://t.co/5Z285xXb17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju UA students win top prize at business competition - Tuscaloosa News #competition https://t.co/ZkrTGGzmSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Panera Bread's Takeover Alternative Is To Become The Next Dunkin' Brands - Fo.. #branding #brands https://t.co/tTpICpJ2FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An idea can turn to dust or magic, depending on the talent that rubs against it.- Bill Bernbach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju WE ARE SOCIAL'S MONDAY MASHUP #348 #socialcommerce https://t.co/Kn2RAks125]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Russian Hackers Have Used the Same Backdoor for Two Decades #technology #geek https://t.co/Lh8LYkkz7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They slipped into the gene pool when the lifeguard wasn't looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How e-commerce companies make you spend more - https://t.co/1H7remS5Wp #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/MjlfbJxIsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Schumer urges Trump to veto anti-privacy internet bill - New York Post #internet #web https://t.co/gj3FSGKzy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 Ways to Get Your Small Business Booming in New International Markets #entrepreneur https://t.co/7qMlRozdIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 Reasons Brands Could Be the Next Victims of Fake News - Adweek #branding #brands https://t.co/CoVzTqeS8s]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>