<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darhassett: @e_mcguire @MiriamOCal @rte @NewstalkFM  Please listen to this from about 2.30 minutes onwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@e_mcguire @James_Proclaims @stiofandunne BOOM!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arusbridger: Full news story on last night's British Press Awards with Guardian named Newspaper of the Year http://t.co/GmZURFqIH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish secondary level students ‘mediocre’ in problem solving http://t.co/UTr0GHE9ml via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From time to time our journalism may be so challenging that it offends or shocks; that is a sign of strength, not weakness" #RTE #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Garda Commissioner didn't just decide to go off on a world cruise,"Niall Collins FF.  Think he was feeling enough heat at home. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We know how important it is to be first,  but it's even more important to be right" John Mulholland Editor @ The Observer former @DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refreshing to hear positive and innovative thoughts on the challenges faced by aspiring journalists.Thank you @jnmulholland #DCU #DataNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Snowden leaks is the most complicated story the Guardian has ever told " #DCU #MAJ #futureofjournalism #data]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Glenn Greenwald's power as a journalist is that he's an outsider - he probably has no friends" - John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ #NewJournalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Glenn Greenwald is an activist,  he is not an objective journalist" claims John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ #Journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Snowden wouldn't have considered the Guardian if there was a paywall" claims John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ #Journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Openness brings accountability and trust" - John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ #Journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @russellcrowe: I know Ireland is a sovereign nation. You can imply I don't love Ireland but it won't stick, love the place, love the peo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" Live journalism enriches reflective journalism" - John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Data journalism is critical to the future of journalism" John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Desktops are becoming increasingly less important for the journalism industry" John Mulholland #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not just about journalism - digital disruption is happening everywhere" John Mulholland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stiofandunne: John Mulholland reckons newsprint is no longer mourned by journos in UK and US. I'm not so sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amazing moment Spanish journalist is reunited with his son after being held hostage in Syria http://t.co/Tl8vVj78io via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @damiantambini: Published today: a guide to media subsidies #polis14 http://t.co/n3pKLdxZPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanstray: "If you're doing investigative journalism, don't build a market, build a network." - @lyramckee #polis14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denmahon Amazing! Brian Cox, Ardal O' Hanlon and the bog. In my element :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denmahon Outside Mullingar and going to see The Weir. Let's hope I don't want to melt like ice #WestEnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_hartnett Plan! #parknearthepolitician]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_hartnett Seems like a worthy ethical issue for tomorrow's exam?! Blue screen must be acting up! #insideinfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't keep up with all the news today! #6.1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Proclaims I'll stop while I'm ahead!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mobile users are not replacing one platform with another; they're consuming more news than they did in the past" #silverlining #dcu #maj #♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IanDempsey: PHOTO OF THE DAY: (@IrishTimes) Brilliant http://t.co/Q7cclJp6oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @newschambers: Health Minister: Will make my views known about Garda whistleblowers at tomorrow's Cabinet meeting. #ntfm http://t.co/n6J…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking on air after last night's @WomenOnAirIE event. Great speakers, great message and great signs for the future #herecomethegirls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting and somewhat comforting nuggets '10 writers on the tips that did no good' http://t.co/ynhrsbGjQP @LibertiesPress @stingingfly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @e_mcguire: "Bolshy, not bossy." @PriorClaire @WomenOnAirIE #womenonair #hellyeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOnAirIE: Just say YES #confidence #conviction thank you @DearbhailDibs and @PriorClaire #inspirational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_hartnett #Livingthedream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_hartnett You're hilarious Hartnett! Vincent is a fan of the wild look himself! #Leinster2004 #UpWestmeath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Saying 'no' to contributing on air is saying 'yes' to the status quo" Dearbhail McDonald #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lack of women on air is symptomatic to lack of public female representation in Ireland," Dearbhail McDonald #womenonair #journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcbrienmary  Dearbhail McDonald's 10 commandments of female contributors - all over it! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thou shalt not say no to any opportunity of going on air," Dearbhail McDonald #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The difference between men and women on air is conviction and confidence, " Dearbhail McDonald #womenonair #journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Champion your stories, " Dearbhail McDonald #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to be a great broadcast contributor? Leading advice from leading media women #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post will give away its web content to subscribers of other newspapers #onlinejournalism http://t.co/f1cUyyUbAn via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProperChurch: Take off time! #ParisBound http://t.co/6bv7limAes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'd love to hear more of your thoughts on journalism. Come to Dublin to launch your book! @KirstyWark @e_mcguire @darhassett @Hibernia1989]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @e_mcguire: @ClaireMc_C @KirstyWark Great idea! Aspiring journos in Dublin would love to talk to you! #MAJ #DCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyWark will be on @johnmurrayshow at 9am! Amazing!! Wonder if she'd pop by DCU for a chat with some buddy young journos? #MAJ #DCU #BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to getting some top television tips from guest speaker @BBCDublin_Shane in class tomorrow. #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nialler9: First names for @ForbiddenFFest 2014:  include Flaming Lips and Flying Lotus in 3D —&gt; 

http://t.co/vkn0WWBDTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Academic researchers are obsessed with new media, while journalists are having a collective nervous breakdown," BBC Radio 4 #DCU #MAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darhassett Not officially.  Just helped to make noise  @alan_hartnett #dontmesswiththemidlands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Proclaims @e_mcguire News never sleeps ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Womens_eNews Ireland near top of EU-wide survey on abuse against women | Irish Examiner: http://t.co/6uVTgUMNAW via @irishexaminer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarmelMahon hahaha! Thanks Mahon! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The picture the IRFU didn’t want you to see http://t.co/0ZmeS8iKIu via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GAA at its best: Donegal team stop their bus to help man turn his turf http://t.co/3Vtn6CQofv via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful RTÉ doc on building Titanic Belfast #RMS #HarlandandWolff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Womens_eNews Lucy Li – aged 11– makes history by qualifying for the U.S. Women’s Open http://t.co/pTbSOcZnOn via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeFinneganShow @IrishFarmerette Really enjoyed your 'Would you marry a farmer?' item. Real women, real lives, real stories #greatradio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd rather have a Snow Fall builder than a Snow Fall" – World's greatest newsroom still grappling with digital #NYT http://t.co/sIWDrVg0ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thetimes: A new journalism bursary in honour of Richard Beeston, who died of cancer aged 50, is now open http://t.co/YGVZ7YknOA http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robynkonichiwa: So hype! Röyksopp &amp; Robyn - Do It Again (Moullinex Remix) on @hypem http://t.co/XnDqa3eH2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sineadgleeson: Two of our best female poets in conversation at @AbbeyTheatre on June 15th: Eavan Boland and Paula Meehan. http://t.co/y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RTE and Sky reveal GAA schedules ahead of opening weekend of live coverage http://t.co/tqKLcZ4y4I via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ursula Halligan: I've watched female colleagues disappear because of challenges facing women in the media http://t.co/aQ4L8zRiOm #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childcare and focus on appearance challenge women in the media, seminar told http://t.co/BSRijLdFcL via @Independent_ie #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOnAirIE: Full house today at #WomenonAir conference in Dublin Castle"Without you it is only half the story" http://t.co/cuAM78pG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @orla_barry: RT : "Can you imagine a female George Hook" @UnaMullally. We need women with strong opinions #womenonair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't use the word 'just' it's an apology. Speak up and find your own voice - Una Ni Raifeartaigh @WomenOnAir #Experts #Women #Journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcbrienmary @WomenOnAirIE Well spotted Mc Brien!  Inconspicuous as always :) You're missing another great one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomenOnAir Women on top at Women on Air conference #DublinCastle #Experts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistleblower Maurice McCabe back on Garda PULSE system after 18 months http://t.co/6SI5HcxX2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DearbhailDibs: 80,000 to walk from Darkness Into Light http://t.co/nbKMHHz6UQ #amrunning #dil14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big weekend ahead for ladies GAA - Sport - GAA - Articles - Westmeath Examiner http://t.co/VG9jbkqV9s via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off The Ball remember the deaths of Senna and Ratzenberger http://t.co/3zQ1Rjkt8K via @Newstalkfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@e_mcguire thesis is my Everest.  On route to the convent #maynotreturn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@e_mcguire twittering away at hash dot hyphen underscore hash dot :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking very well @DunneEileen, loving the revamp. Enjoyed last night's @TheGodSlot, great season! :) http://t.co/WFxTITh27E via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MagsGarganIC: Happy retirement to Gerry McArdle, producer of RTE's @TheGodSlot which finishes it's current season on Friday, Apr 25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Womens_eNews Jill Meagher’s husband speaks about male violence against women and the ‘monster myth’ http://t.co/9l60zynZAB via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Examiner newspaper group to shed up to 60 jobs http://t.co/rISF3vLszD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NYMag: Six independent bookstores that are thriving — and how they do it: http://t.co/9c0L6ZGlRh http://t.co/ZKoRBF716F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Guardian and Washington Post win Pulitzer prize for NSA revelations:  http://t.co/WnoPRxcGTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darhassett DM :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 Signs Made By People Who Don't Know How To Use Quotation Marks. http://t.co/B9omDHKzK7 via @itspulptastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevin 'struggling to get his head around' vicious attack. Great photos @davidconachy http://t.co/BKVLSMTsMI via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Waters Interview: "I've been put on trial over my beliefs" http://t.co/3dAzawZG4f via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veronica Guerin told phone conversations about paedophile priest were taped http://t.co/8VQIU0FvPk via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shakespeare: an oldie but a goodie :) http://t.co/AzEDSWg5Q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MH370: Chinese patrol ship detects pulse signal

http://t.co/Wpt7zMzn70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGodSlot The 25th is marked. Sounds like another wonderful show. Going out on top, well done you. #TheGerrySlot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whistleblower John Wilson was the first uniformed guard to wear a beard. Even more of a legend #thelatelateshow #RTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan policeman shoots two foreign journalists, one killed http://t.co/lqNkngo6fJ via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ucdagfood: Front cover @Independent_ie's Going-To-College guide features @CavanInstitute graduate &amp; incoming @ucdagfood student http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @catherine_mayer: A beauty pageant as a vehicle for change?! #RoseofTralee http://t.co/qMRYBtOqp3 via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Fionnan Sheahan and Jason O'Brien take the Ice Bucket Challenge - Independent.ie http://t.co/bGrqSJQntq via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average wage beyond our graduates - Independent.ie http://t.co/s25O9sSkqw via @Independent_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'd expect €21k, with the hope of doubling it' - Independent.ie http://t.co/AvDuCMU3Y8 via @Independent_ie]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>