<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gonna have to perservere no matter how hard it is, your destination might just be a short mile away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People never appreciate what they have... Until they lose it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASSUME --- Making an ASS out of U &amp; ME. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends say he's the idiot for letting go, but I think I'm the idiot for holding on .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate when all the blame gets put on you just because you're the older sibling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have controll of my heart and by a single word, you can tear me apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She wakes up early to get ready &amp; put on her make-up to feel pretty, but all he does is wipe it off &amp; tells her she's beautiful without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that millions of people can believe in you, and yet none of it matters if you don't believe in yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The need to impress almost always overpowers the need to express.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love...It s complicated, but not as complicated as me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best cure in this world is the power of your smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dream of a better tomorrow... where chickens can cross roads and not have their motives questioned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That amazing moment when you listen to a song and it completely moves your soul....it's priceless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you wear glasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we kiss...I forget about everything and everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere in the world tonight, someone's falling in love for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being with all the girls in the world doesn't make you a man. But making one girl feel like she's the world... that does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was one of those days where everything I did reminded me of you and every song I heard somehow related to you. I hate days like today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the hardest thing and the right thing are the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you decide you wanna act right and grow up, don t assume I ll take you back because of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to be unique, and different, and shine in your own way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single  Taken  Wondering how to get started]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about the worst part of your life is that you get to see the true colors of everyone you cared for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, by the way, you're everything that I want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sad when you miss someone and you don't even know how to tell them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lazy moment when you don't feel like brushing your teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What lies before, and what lie behind us, are tiny matters compared to what lies within us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I look at my hand I remember the day you held it and didn't want to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are days when you need someone who just wants to be your sunshine and not the air you breathe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss you, but I'm trying not to care. I love you, but I'm trying not to show. I want you, but what can I do when you're not even mine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not compare what you are best at, compare what you are worst at, and win it. Then only you are a true winner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile and a kind word cost nothing, but can mean so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can walk away and say that we don't need this, but something in your eyes says we can beat this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's about taking chances and you'll never know if you're right until you try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only get jealous because I love you, and I don't want anyone else to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather you give me the straight answer, than to let me take a hint out of your indirect reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I lie awake at night, and I ask, 'Where have I gone wrong' Then a voice says to me, 'This is going to take more than one night.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don t think too much. You ll create a problem that wasn t even there in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technically, I m single. Emotionally, I m taken because in my heart, I ll always be yours, even if you don t know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The part that sucks about love is that you do get to choose who you love, but you don't get to choose who loves you back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you put a ;) after anything it makes it sound dirty. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the reason I want to wake up in the morning. &lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't die of a broken heart, you only sometimes wish you did...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake laughters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong now, because things will get better. It might be stormy now, but it can't rain forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes two people have to fall apart just to realize how much they need to fall back together again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth? I tried as hard as I could. I took as much as I could take. I put up with all I could, but it wasn t enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who don t respect other people s relationships, deserve to be disrespected back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe this is wishful thinking, Probably mindless dreaming, If we loved again I swear I'd love you right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the world you may be but one, but to one you might be the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you wait so long for something that when it finally arrives you no longer need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I was comforting my best friend last night... and I realize... I should really be listening to my own advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope once in a while you think about me, so I dont feel so pathetic for thinking about you all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear boy, Our silly conversations mean more to me than you'll ever know. Sincerely, I'm in love with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being notorious in school has it's advantages. At least the teachers will remember you after you graduate. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes strength to remember, it takes another kind of strength to forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only think you're immune to feelings. The most unlikely person could reduce you to tears, laughter, or spontaneous declarations of love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing the person you love, love someone else is like being shot. After you're wounded, every breath hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say the first step is admitting you have a problem, so here it goes...I have an addiction... You.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never loved you anyways... I never did and I never will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesnt make the world go round, love is what makes the ride worth while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only so much a heart can take before it starts to break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss you like a retard misses the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is out there; it s just not easy to find. If it was, it wouldn t be worth it when you finally find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real loss is only possible when you love something more than you love yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ability to live is the rarest gift. No matter how life disappoints you, overcome it. Because you are given an option to survive. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't force myself to have a space in your life, because if you know my worth, you'll create one for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you wish, it's like you're throwing something in the air, and it or not come back down. It's in your hands, then it's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the only thing I can't get enough of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The saddest thing in life is when you meet that special someone and know it will never be, and that sooner or later you ll have to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There s a story behind every person. There s a reason why they are the way they are. Think about that before you judge someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m cute enough to make you look twice, sweet enough but not too nice, I m a little crazy but not too wild; just enough to make you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not drunk, I'm just intoxicated by you. s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling lonely is better than feeling hurt, lied to, ignored, and taken for granted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I hate growing up. I miss being a kid, I miss my childhood and I want it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and you aren t together anymore because God has something better in store for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on my way to believing again...that love does exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who sits in the car when it rains, picks a raindrop, and cheers for it to beat all the other ones to the bottom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And she painted on a smile and learned how to pretend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you walked out of my life, you took all of the color with you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cherish your present before it's too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward feeling when you realize you're chewing on a borrowed pen..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wanna know what I think about when i m with someone else? That I wish it was you I m hanging out with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking that you've heard a message or a vibration, but there is actually nothing. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dreadful feeling when you're stuck alone at home, and no one's free to go out. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always smile in the morning...it makes people wonder what you did last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fall for a bad boy; fall for the unpredictable one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't forget someone you used to love, you just accepted the fact that you were not meant to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She can't live without you. She wont even try. She can't stop thinking about you and she doesn't know why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women fall in love by what they hear. Men fall in love by what they see. That s why most women wear makeup and most men lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thosefriendsthat make you laugh when you're down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without that little voice in your head, you wouldn't be able to read this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People think I m so innocent...if only they knew what really goes through my head..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I m nobody s second option, you either CHOOSE ME or you lose me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in second chances, I just don t think everyone deserves them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best relationships are those where you don't need to be actually with each other but you want to be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more difficult than knowing you're perfect for each other, but that you may never be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minute you decided that I wasn t worth the truth was the minute you decided to break my heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather go after someone than just sit back and regret it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect the person who gives you honesty, because most will just tell you what they think you want to hear.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>