<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/95tDP5beot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/hkT22LBjvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/wKoDKNezlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/I4a64wHbpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/gpBFxqRTKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/sbyVwhQjzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/eG4SojTU2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/rJfcFaXOmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/74IRc8FMUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/Hs7PARhgQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/5x76jtSNPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/xLnAoms5UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/aHnmfhQP3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/xOjRZWEKwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/eVUSrqS2m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/KnEVbRUIWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/LiiVEwmCc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/usV9ZQbkF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/XL3tmpwuVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is good for nothing unless you know the value of it by experience.  P.T Barnum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/EUGoqK2tde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really hard to maintain a one on one relationship if the other person is not going to allow me to be with other people.  Axl Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/VnHWkzjq3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/QaHmiNxZRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/h1JHRSEcUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/26litadjeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/7Rvc67DyBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/M2mbVv5MO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/DXgZG2MBPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/DnSXNsVWva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/wbQCe6MUQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/CnKL97WkFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/XKuV8R62KF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/GDhvdDLaQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/KHQxUdDVDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/nQHbbGminU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/Omt6lpkaMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/cOnqauLd0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/xUdk5hRrFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/M7dmHwJOGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/37syoaI2Nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/qzTZwfjnKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/Bqih4QRx98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/fiSM9RLvPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Most Popular Cat Breeds in the U.S.  http://t.co/ANZFMwfYKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/rB52G8IqfI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>