<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Hispanic Heritage Month at the Naval Observatory: On Wednesday evening at the Naval Observatory, Vic... http://t.co/XQwOx93d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Economic Data: More than the usual amount of economic statistics were released this morning. As a whole,... http://t.co/hk9HKP9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empowering Women and Girls in the United States and Abroad: This week, we took two major steps in empowering wom... http://t.co/UDXxcMXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join a Live Video Chat on Combatting Human Trafficking: Yesterday, President Obama spoke at the Clinton Global I... http://t.co/qvhEw5ZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration Teams Up to Bring Jobs Back to America: Yesterday, the U.S. Departments of Commerce and Labor ann... http://t.co/GVBEGJbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Drives America: 

Click here to see the photo gallery. 

See the full size gallery
For the third yea... http://t.co/gTfRnLs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Addresses the United Nations: 

    President Barack Obama addresses the United Nations Gen... http://t.co/HBkKDMrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune In: President Obama Addresses the United Nations General Assembly: President Obama will address the General... http://t.co/Bxwh6EUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, We The People!: A year ago, the White House launched We the People, a new platform that allows a... http://t.co/jl5gO5AA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Behind the Scenes in August 2012: The White House Photo Office just released the latest set of be... http://t.co/KsgauFIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch First Lady Michelle Obama at the Congressional Black Caucus Foundation Dinner: Tonight, First Lady Michell... http://t.co/8IOHFMp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Must Act to Create Jobs and Grow the Economy: 
President Obama describes how the House ... http://t.co/6h7zur97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: The Dignity and Freedom That Every Person Deserves: 
Here's a quick glimpse at what happened thi... http://t.co/aYSt05kS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Space Shuttle Endeavour Takes Its Final Flight: 

Click here to see the photo gallery. 

Ear... http://t.co/1bqdN2Xj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Olympic Visitors at the White House Through the Years: 

Click here to see the photo gallery. 

... http://t.co/emlFqiCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Emancipation Proclamation is 150 Years Old: 

    President Barack Obama views the Emancipation Proclam... http://t.co/glUP9AAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chimney Rock Becomes Our Newest National Monument: Today, President Obama designated spectacular Chimney Rock in... http://t.co/TyOt8heK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National POW/MIA Recognition Day: You Are Not Forgotten: 

    A POW-MIA flag flies over the White House, S... http://t.co/GkMuQpt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Secretary Clinton in Africa: 

    Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton hugs a camper w... http://t.co/ZuiZZ9sc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the Next Generation of LGBT Leaders: On Wednesday, the Vice President and Dr. Biden hosted an “End o... http://t.co/8nrYyWkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 09/21/12 or "The Dignity and Freedom That Every Person Deserves": This week, the President, Vice... http://t.co/d9hDg3gS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marking One Year Since the Repeal of Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell: Earlier today, I had the opportunity to meet with a ... http://t.co/fCmMrLCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Decision to Move Forward: Paralympian Lt. Snyder Meets with The First Lady: Brad Snyder’s story is a remarka... http://t.co/zMgh2jcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: The End of Don't Ask, Don't Tell:  
On this day in 2011, “Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell” was finally ... http://t.co/nyx5dDgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashley-Care: Gaining Peace of Mind by Getting Coverage Through a Parent’s Health Plan: Ed. note: This is cross-p... http://t.co/MsFwNORW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets with Aung San Suu Kyi: 

    President Barack Obama meets with Burmese Opposition Lea... http://t.co/eKpOaExp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration's Efforts to Promote Travel and Tourism Are Working: 
The Obama Administration's number one prio... http://t.co/aFGQN7Rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the 2011 WNBA Champions: 

    President Barack Obama welcomes Coach Cheryl Reeve and the WNBA ... http://t.co/DC3eSbYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're Invited: Join the White House Fall Garden Tour: 
This fall, the White House will once again open its gar... http://t.co/bDPq6PC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes Video: Team USA at the White House: 
	On Friday, more than 400 Olympians and Paralympians were... http://t.co/DE26VgBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Business Google Hangout on Wednesday, Sept. 19: 
	Ed. note: This was originally published on the NASA Admi... http://t.co/F8A7HOLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Preparedness Month: Does Your Family Have a Plan?: 
	Ed. note: This was originally published on FEMA.go... http://t.co/T2Z4hlnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18th Anniversary of the Violence Against Women Act: 
	On September 13, 1994, President Bill Clinton signed the V... http://t.co/bOhNT8ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patent Reform: Celebrating the One Year Anniversary of the America Invents Act: 
	On September 16, 2011, Preside... http://t.co/qARDR7UJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Government, Open Data, Open Source: 

	Thomas Jefferson once ... http://t.co/vIzPKkQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Gets Update on Storm Relief at FEMA: 

    President Barack Obama receives a briefing about... http://t.co/Jg0ZxyfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Recovering and Rebuilding After the Storm: In this week’s address, President Obama thanks the br... http://t.co/9A9r8RLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: “What’s Brightest in America”: Here's the week in review of the federal response to Hurricane Sa... http://t.co/HYfTPG6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Help the Survivors of Hurricane Sandy Clean-up: .toggle-text{
border-radius: 3px;
width: 100%;
background... http://t.co/hwFPH0FC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in October: While more work remains to be done, today’s employment report provides furt... http://t.co/RMnhf6Yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 11/02/12 or "What’s Brightest in America": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everythi... http://t.co/IN0cSYmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Tours Storm Damage in New Jersey: 

    President Barack Obama and New Jersey Gov. Chris Ch... http://t.co/gW45zgf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama in New Jersey: "We Are Here for You": 

    President Barack Obama and New Jersey Gov. Chri... http://t.co/mzKFPhkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Help the Survivors of Hurricane Sandy: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks during his visi... http://t.co/bsAugVKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update on Hurricane Sandy: 

    President Barack Obama receives an update from officials via video telecon... http://t.co/Tobxk049]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Urges Caution for Those in the Path of Hurricane Sandy: 

President Barack Obama delivers a st... http://t.co/vyLnGFn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses Hurricane Sandy: 

    President Barack Obama receives an update on the ongoing res... http://t.co/K9xrochs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Protecting the American People with New Wall Street Reforms: In this week’s address, President O... http://t.co/9fHBpP3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: "The Difference One Person Can Make": 
Watch the West Wing Week here.
Here’s a quick glimpse at ... http://t.co/3J2NTNII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.7 Million Records Released: In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in hi... http://t.co/vlbIhYiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring Hurricane Sandy: 

    President Barack Obama receives an update on the ongoing response to Hurr... http://t.co/sHIEewsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance Estimate of GDP for the Third Quarter of 2012: Today’s report shows that the economy posted its thirteen... http://t.co/t4aTTQNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 10/26/12 or "The Difference One Person Can Make": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to e... http://t.co/57It9BBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Jill Biden and HHS Secretary Kathleen Sebelius Host Breast Cancer Awareness Month Call: 

    Dr. Jil... http://t.co/vicQkDXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden and Dr. Jill Biden Commemorate Breast Cancer Awareness Month: 

    Vice President Joe... http://t.co/qQKbLbRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Hosts Visiting Young African Leaders: Earlier this week, Special Assistant to the President and Seni... http://t.co/0eAfejyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Chance to Attend the Lighting of the National Christmas Tree: 

    The National Christmas Tree is ill... http://t.co/DtQOB0SI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United Nations Day: 

    President Barack Obama addresses the United Nations General Assembly (UNGA) at th... http://t.co/91hCroH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Date Set for Entry-Into-Force of the U.S.-Panama Trade Promotion Agreement: Editor's note: This is a cross post ... http://t.co/9G0BXruN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Should Join the President to Help Responsible Homeowners: President Obama urges Congres... http://t.co/PVu6xdsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fall Social in the #WHGarden: As part of the 2012 White House Fall Garden Tours, we invited 50 of our follower... http://t.co/P8qGqumw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Purple for Spirit Day: Spirit Day -- the celebration created by a young Canadian woman named Brittany McMi... http://t.co/fgoV5Vz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upgrading the White House Homepage: This morning I'm pleased to announce something you may have already noticed:... http://t.co/kii2PrDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 10/19/12 or "The Power of We": This week, the President reflected on the state of the auto indus... http://t.co/3hBL2N7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up with the Curator: The Presidential Seal: There's no doubt you have seen the official Seal of the Pre... http://t.co/Q7juMd9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating National Wildlife Refuge Week: More than a century ago, President Theodore Roosevelt set aside a tin... http://t.co/0f98Q45m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog Action Day: “The Power of We”: Following last year’s contribution for Blog Action Day (that addressed the d... http://t.co/6zq3Uttv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Fall #WHGarden Tour Photos: Starting today, the White House once again opened its gardens and grounds to vi... http://t.co/IwWxGxsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: One Million American Jobs Saved and a Stronger American Auto Industry: President Obama talks abo... http://t.co/hhksWxsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: “Our Journey Is Never Hopeless, Our Work Is Never Done”: 
Watch the West Wing Week here.
Here’s ... http://t.co/pvMfQYY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: #My2k, Tweet it!: 
Watch the West Wing Week here.
Here’s a quick glimpse at what happened this w... http://t.co/nHNOA8nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email from David Plouffe: "We Have to Keep It Up": Senior Advisor to the President David Plouffe just sent the m... http://t.co/pBTPFJL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 11/30/12 or "#My2k, Tweet it!": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's h... http://t.co/Plarypt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: World AIDS Day 2012: Last year, on World AIDS Day, President Obama announced ambitious... http://t.co/Zoo3jn89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Goes to Costco: 
Today, Vice President Joe Biden visited a newly opened Costco in Washingto... http://t.co/GgtVn8Ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limiting Tax Deductions: The Reality of the Math: In his Budget, the President proposes to raise $1.56 trillion ... http://t.co/mwW5ORvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Front Door for Immigrant Entrepreneurs: Yesterday marked the launch of Entrepreneur Pathways, an online re... http://t.co/L5ygzHCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What $2,000 Means to Middle Class Families: Yesterday, President Obama called on Americans to speak out in favor... http://t.co/BQJsooQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Their Story Again: 

    Dr. Jill Biden speaks at the Ceremonial Groundbreaking of The Education Center ... http://t.co/xM7YwXGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joy to All: First Lady Michelle Obama Previews the 2012 White House Holiday Decor: 

    First Lady Michell... http://t.co/NtImffPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Hours on Extending Middle Class Tax Cuts: #My2K with Brian Deese: If Congress doesn't act by the end of t... http://t.co/VcBU8h9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving Towards an AIDS-free Generation: 

    A red ribbon is displayed on the North Portico of the White Hou... http://t.co/RDDwx46x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#My2k: What $2,000 Means to Americans: If Congress fails to act before the end of the year, every American famil... http://t.co/45jBjiR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Wants You to Speak Out on Passing the Middle Class Tax Cuts: Surrounded by Americans who had wri... http://t.co/NQX9jllM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama: "This Debate is Too Important for Washington to Get it Wrong": President Obama just sent the me... http://t.co/IWa61PAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Round-up: Certainty for America’s Small Businesses: 

    President Barack Obama talks with partic... http://t.co/dSV60foU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Welcomes Mexico President-Elect Enrique Peña Nieto: 

    President Barack Obama meets with... http://t.co/8OJxHdjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving Tuesday: America has a tradition of generosity. Today, we celebrate Giving Tuesday, a new nationwide effo... http://t.co/1lETdVPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partnerships for Homeland Security: In response to the devastation of Hurricane Sandy, the Federal, state, and l... http://t.co/wH0kMUkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting with Human Rights Defenders in Cambodia: During the East Asia Summit in Phnom Penh on November 20, Presi... http://t.co/oKne4kjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Announces Judges for Equal Futures App Challenge: 
(Picture drawn by Abigail Dabu, Age 14)
“…I would... http://t.co/kXx7POLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting Human Trafficking in Cambodia: On each leg of his trip to Southeast Asia this week, President Obama rai... http://t.co/UwrnXJ5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasing Taxes on Middle-Class Families Will Hurt Consumer Spending: Today, as we move into the holiday shoppi... http://t.co/2xG7v5ip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Today: Summer 2013 White House Internship Program Application: Medical school student, volunteer firefighte... http://t.co/SOHkw6ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Receives the 2012 White House Christmas Tree: 

    The official White House Chri... http://t.co/bBKCjre1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Wishing the American People a Happy Thanksgiving: During this holiday season, President Obama gi... http://t.co/CITdvN7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 11/22/12 or "Hello Burma!": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's happe... http://t.co/n1jGBTG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Pardons Cobbler, the National Thanksgiving Turkey: 
Watch the video
Today, President Obama pardo... http://t.co/2ykgqKU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Thanksgiving with the Presidents: 

Click here to see the photo gallery. 

See the full-siz... http://t.co/2YrlbMig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Vice President Joe Biden Tours Hurricane Sandy Damage in New Jersey: 

Click here to see the pho... http://t.co/ivTCodo9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>