<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/cPXokSgxGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/6BJ9Fx76yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/zOWdAdMqwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/IXrlAwFe0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/eQn0HdF5cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/6DxT9TEj9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/fqYf1WLiHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/01t1zaP6u6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/ECRatI1A6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/1JC8kROSFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/1CfiBdCBjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/wQQJLJ2kJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6YHsJV2ATA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/MDvgvVc11i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/IKJFw9lFDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/NefzNW2IPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/FyXUGcP86P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/itYp0JHDls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/0YXtLSHGR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/RUNoD5q66I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't tell how much spirit a team has until it starts losing. - Rocky Colavito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the fascinating history of the Twilight Zone TV series! http://t.co/hSN54jr43S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/BT4nPrpHK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/fZgRkMRCo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/aQR40ESyWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/97QMkm0UdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/j8Eo8Q2izu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/iWfO2gNjyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/tpYiFvGUqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/MoqKLs3Xo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/rC5M6uXkrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/dxWyacsgSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/wRE3TY2K4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/DnShCNPtAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/QNf7S2hiQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/rtEr6o2BYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/hPRvFE3nF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/ZTivar3tdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/GJvMvK1sJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/rXuf0pga4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/f0ru7rIYgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/MtLZb2EgV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/o2Oc847db7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/lmYaEOygvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/OdQJIS9gEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/H5z2MWyroV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. - Marcia Wieder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/eS7g3E5MKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/1TbmS9XFmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/XsbFvossuV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>