<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/uIaOtuKSwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/mAdo70RsB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/xKFzJnRp3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/oqaMBpILVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/NP91G31VFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/FUA5aq1BDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/idcxYsvf6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/ZXHcxpfRmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/46Mh1AMFqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop earning when you do what you love. - Asha Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/MY5Gb2O1dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/qiL9CjiFG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/TGKLaxZuMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/fxR4wR0Vfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/vaoHg12SOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/uh5aYrKuHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/HHkHwRUevs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/xjiaWHvU8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/d188VkfKJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/If5yPwIb12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/QYIevkb2J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/UFxWpklng5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/3HepCkbDD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/ZEFDQc16aG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/xUenyrmN8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/DksiD3lv7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/m6dCEo5CC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/SvRuI8rQP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/EE1IgTcNRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/t32c4Sy1ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/hWOYKHhILe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/Zp87OwgI5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/rvZPWCdoOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/If5yPwIb12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/3HepCkbDD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/XJpwytTU4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/ox9XkIyC8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/a1FfYsJTWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/RWcKAFRgKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/OvYuVloXQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/86vpr7Sbwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/fKSTF37I1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/lElPSejIRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/vBizpYCIhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/cILTFE1YDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/uhkzx9gF9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/ZEFDQc16aG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/kZ0JwNtz9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/9NqYV4iHPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/tdaIDKtXol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/NHJ6PSdQRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/OxypK8Pjfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/vaoHg12SOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/UIDKIt2aAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/OTe9KxbqBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction films are not about science. They are about disaster, which is one of the oldest subjects of art. - Susan Sontag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/LLPZ0SX2iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>