<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/nQHbbGminU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/a1YCg96ndU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/ql79rNJrv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/Xivdvw15Vu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/9CIz37nojR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/h1JHRSEcUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/idtRLEfPcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/ZRSx9hDA5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/IRLUzRNKJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/1lpHfme5NL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/Paf42laUAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/NIkVi59DiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/6SNE1BlUKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/2p9DPL8E7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/9lpdyejpYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/8vDMNn30lP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/RiODFSVTZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/jYVrWl1s9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/AgnXyHywoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/jBL3nAl1fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/6N2gfHFUUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/FTCO8lUINT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/vzDgbg2gVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/KtwILg08CC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/s0KJRTSIbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/HYpHhXp8Ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/PTNeTrzv2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/IRDacMaWHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/4ngyFWBtF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/F3ITYDkIB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/yToOvC0fXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/90a5YLRPSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/iKComwcSaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/lXrSi3FszX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/R05SmyWjKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/onTiUscXwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/3Wj9fg1HMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/VTJ9xgz625]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/QpLk6I8u5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/nSPkJ3HNcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/LmV0Nz7zpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/HSBwPiyHSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/0HOybpo4ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/BAvuSZmyZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/NrGhAiD1iZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>