<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumjodwyer Blocked and reported]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was the Louis van gaal of songs #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange necks #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KTTunstall: Oh my God. Harry’s chin crease like ACTUAL labia. This is some real life @AphexTwin shit. https://t.co/QSMFhNbjih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Corbyn is conflicted #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM TRAPPED IN A GLASS EUROVISION OF EMOTION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's cos they remind me of timberlake who, let us not forget, is scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are several male acts tonight who look like they think they're woke but are a bit Aziz ansari #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I too love beyond the bones #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big mood #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eurovision isn't moribund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caesar is super interesting #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is woody Allen and we should kill him #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyrically this is a big fuck you to Ukraine #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their sweat is 40% beard oil #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a Viking lad and I'm okay #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Czech Taron Egerton is creepy like Matt Damon #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peak France #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to be prescriptive but if you sound like Del Amitri please don't dress like pirates forming a Killers covers band #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aileen_mcgibbon It would certainly be distracting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like The Script singing something written by olly plimsoles #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the love child of hucknall and that detective no one likes in Sherlock #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be more songs where a huge bearded unit stared supportively at whoever's singing #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This song
Is not
About Brexit 
About Brexit
About brexiiiiiiit
#Eurovision2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is the windows media player dress lady coming back? #Eurovison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That answers the question "what if junior senior but fundamentally unlike able ?" #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is stripped back, she didn't even get off a stool for the key change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Death to come to claim his granddaughter #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine #eurovision https://t.co/Mb80oeIumj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think it's an exaggeration to say that the Netherlands song is the worst thing that has ever happened #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Pattinson https://t.co/VmUUuN3lOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JimMFelton: https://t.co/aLunakX56R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dawkins does Twitter searches on his own name https://t.co/pyPA8ugA5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimCMackintosh Hah, not you. Go finish your Chris millar poem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is really good for finding out that writing heroes are tedious middle aged men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo Why couldn't davie Cameron, the pie, simply not have taken this attitude to Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jowrotethis: SHOUTING ANGRILY ON THE INTERNET WORKS. https://t.co/LAFB7n4b5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I too am from the Netherlands #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CiaranCRN: https://t.co/OYY0lpZK9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving I also write about someone who is definitely not me but is also obviously you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProudieYT: If Mark Lawrenson was a meal deal https://t.co/abL7ofyNFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @dadwroteaporno halloween special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealKav_P: Most terrifying AirBnb review ever https://t.co/JEj8KlbEUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeenageScream_: Just when you think your afternoon activity can’t get any more 90s ... a Scott Minto Premier League 95 Sticker Collecti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josherick3 OH FLOWER OF SCOTLAND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the most patriotic i've ever felt https://t.co/tHf81AfloO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords he's probably just watched the nolan films and thought 'oh yeah, bane is corbyn']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords to be fair that does happen in batman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryGiles totally up for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryGiles mixing bots and human poets and asking the audience to figure out which is which?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seriously though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[idea for a poetry show https://t.co/Yff06lCgkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonnyGabriel: Ignore the headline for a moment, this article is a good look about how football can impact on our anxieties and our ment…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TrashTaylor: Hey guys, I’m looking to speak to performers who have been to @edfringe more than once for a piece I’m doing about mental…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving i wouldn't trust that shop, it's claiming that irn bru extra is in a new can when that's clearly sprite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're enjoying these episodes of #DoctorWhoOnTwitch might I recommend Paul Cornell and Christopher Jones' comic 'The Heralds of Destruction'?
https://t.co/nYYuZvKzNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate you're so coy jim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sex is great and all but have you ever got to the one page of a Grant Morrison comic where it all suddenly makes sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaywhittapoet: Delighted to have my poem "A home front" included in the latest @lies_dreaming podcast, in fine company with @CWilsonPoe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobbiePye: They're selling Tennents in Murcia as a craft beer in a hipster bar https://t.co/kwz83VGD50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MHarrison90 @sebpatrick That's normally the big end of episode oh fuck moment certainly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate No, more boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByLeavesWeLive: The Slaminals of Farthing Wood - as funny and original as it is difficult to explain what it is in a tweet. On Fri July…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick @MHarrison90 yeah, i meant that bit. Mark, did you mean that bit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick @MHarrison90 and this was back in the pre 2018 times of pre -Chibnallian secrecy. impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebrainofchris infinity war doesn't have bernard cribbins, and is thus inferior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords i genuinely believe RTD could turn that into heart breaking television]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MHarrison90 was it a surprise at the time? I can't remember]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords it is a joyous smashing together of at least three different toysets...but i would like just a teensy bit more dynamism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[essentially i want brooklyn 99 but set in space and with admin instead of jokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also I want Shadow proclamation fan fiction, but only if it depicts them as mind-numbingly dull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching Doctor Who on i-player and holy shit i'd forgotten how turned up to 11 The Stolen Earth is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick Ah, I remember positing a Dalek-as-allegory for the rise of the right and a DoG commentator saying they thought this was extremely silly as UKIP weren't that bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robleane Who would win at subbuteo - Doc Ock or R2D2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK @ryanjjvance I suppose I would slowly applaud the reality of a 50 ft Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robleane I expect an article expanding on this by Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK this does seem sarcastic tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lloydpoetrock coping mechanism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in hindsight, maybe whoever cancelled Arrested Development after three series had a point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @atruedrwhofan: Me every day: https://t.co/xW0ZVdUMd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @snake_friend: I'm:

⚪gay

⚪straight

🔘escaping to the ONE place that hasn’t been corrupted by capitalism... SPACE https://t.co/M8U4XVpc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomwfootball: Just made my favourite pre-World Cup discovery (courtesy of The Observer’s tournament preview): the four officials who si…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Churchill: if we cut funding to the arts, what are we fighting for?
aide: so you'll send money and food to India then?
Churchill: ahaha fuck no https://t.co/1qlDXWhLJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Oldfirmfacts1: https://t.co/bPUbSFH0S6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: Join @poetryasfuck at @ByLeavesWeLive for The Slaminals of Farthing Wood 

https://t.co/l0cf9GWlMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @periwinklewine: Buy it in a carton, serve it the coconut it came out of. A logical trajectory #servingsuggestion https://t.co/ZZuRzzZt9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate well in ron's case it's because he's a midnight garage creeper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK well it'd certainly get an audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thekitze: Love that ancient wisdom https://t.co/CCrcFXKkyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aljwhite: It appears @MarinaHyde has delivered one of the single most devastating responses to a tweet in journalistic history https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seneska I don't think they mean grant Morrison either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seneska But why is it on bbcnews?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seneska I genuinely am having trouble processing this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryanbroems: Found the official flag for the straight pride parade https://t.co/y7IbWFVKnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Probably made my coffee too string]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Fuck, I'm actually having to breathe slowly to get past this bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving I almost started trying to analyse this but my brain hurt so I've stopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Oh wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving I can't even. Too many questions]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>