<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["No great man ever complains of want of opportunity." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All men who have achieved great things have been great dreamers." - Orison Swett Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At first dreams seem impossible, then improbable, then inevitable." - Christopher Reeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude. Don't complain." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Self-praise is for losers. Be a winner. Stand for something. Always have class, and be humble." - John Madden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Enjoy your achievements as well as your plans." - Max Ehrmann]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who would travel happily must travel light." - Antoine de Saint-Exupery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Snowflakes are one of nature's most fragile things, but just look at what they can do when they stick together." - Vesta Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more original a discovery, the more obvious it seems afterward." - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The harder you work, the harder it is to surrender." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can never cross the ocean unless you have the courage to lose sight of the shore." - Christopher Columbus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Progress is impossible without change and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything." - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth is the ability to fully experience life." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quality is never an accident. It is always the result of intelligent effort." - John Ruskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is defeat? Nothing but education; nothing but the first step to something better." - Wendell Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is impossible." - Susan B. Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are today where your thoughts have brought you; you will be tomorrow where your thoughts take you." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't depend on your eyes when your imagination is out of focus." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop worrying about the potholes in the road and enjoy the journey." - Babs Hoffman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our greatest glory is not in never falling but in rising every time we fall." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A man is literally what he thinks." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A danger foreseen is half avoided." - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Finding a way to live the simple life today is man's most complicated task." - Henry A. Courtney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yesterday is but today's memory, tomorrow is today's dream." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone needs to be valued. Everyone has the potential to give something back." - Diana Princess of Wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things do not happen. Things are made to happen." - John F Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we think determines what happens to us, so if we want to change our lives, we need to stretch our minds." -Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a hard battle." - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being challenged in life is inevitable, being defeated is optional." - Roger Crawford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not everything that can be counted counts, and not everything that counts can be counted." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot perform in a manner inconsistent with the way you see yourself." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No pressure, no diamonds." - Mary Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our chief want is someone who will inspire us to be what we know we could be." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't limit yourself. Many people limit themselves to what they think they can do." - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to achieve widespread impact and lasting value, be bold." - Howard Schultz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How did it get so late so soon?" - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you wish to know the mind of a man, listen to his words." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never stand begging for that which you have the power to earn." - Miguel de Cervantes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Know yourself and you will win all battles."  - Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no such thing in anyone's life as an unimportant day." - Alexander Woollcott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field." - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As soon as you trust yourself, you will know how to live." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To conquer fear is the beginning of wisdom." - Bertrand Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Striving for excellence motivates you; striving for perfection is demoralizing." - Harriet Braiker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you believe with feeling becomes your reality." - Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Management is doing things right; leadership is doing the right things." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not enough to be busy. So are the ants. The question is: What are we busy about?" - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only he who can see the invisible can do the impossible." - Frank L. Gaines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you would be wealthy, think of saving as well as getting." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be like a postage stamp, stick to one thing until you get there." - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyday, give yourself a good mental shampoo." - Dr. Sara Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Live out of your imagination, not your history." - Stephen Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life's Tragedy is that we get old too soon and wise too late." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If at first you don't succeed, try, try, again. Then quit. There's no use being a damn fool about it." - W.C.Fields.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you are working on something exciting that you really care about, you don't have to be pushed. The vision pulls you." - Steve Jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who enjoys doing and enjoys what he has done is happy." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They may forget what you said, but they will never forget how you made them feel." - Carl W. Buechner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Opportunities multiply as they are seized." - Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human mind treats a new idea the same way the body treats a strange protein; it rejects it." - P. B. Medawar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination." - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is not courageous enough to take risks will accomplish nothing in life." - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["High achievement always takes place in the framework of high expectation." - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one thing that makes a dream impossible to achieve: the fear of failure." - Paulo Coelho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is real magic in enthusiasm. It spells the difference between mediocrity and accomplishment." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doing your best is more important than being your best." - Shannon Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes it is not enough to do our best; we must do what is required." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Freedom is not worth having if it does not include the freedom to make mistakes." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can give you a six-word formula for success: "Think things through - then follow through." - Edward Rickenbacker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["View life as a continuous learning experience." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do." - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A ship is safe in harbour, but that's not what ships are for." - William Shedd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we can no longer change a situation, we are challenged to change ourselves." - Viktor Frankl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Believe that life is worth living and your belief will help create the fact." - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Minds are like parachutes. They only function when they are open." - James Dewar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Better to do something imperfectly than to do nothing flawlessly." - Dr. Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get your ideas on paper and study them. Do not let them go to waste!" - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you hear a voice within you say "you cannot paint," then by all means paint, and that voice will be silenced." - Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even if you're on the right track, you'll get run over if you just sit there." - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our attitude towards others determines their attitude towards us." - Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is inward and not outward; and so it does not depend on what we have, but on what we are." - Henry Van Dyke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectionism doesn’t make you feel perfect. It makes you feel inadequate. - Maria Shriver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is a waste of time if you use the experience wisely." - Auguste Rodin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the life of your dreams." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What would life be if we had no courage to attempt anything?" - Vincent van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great minds have purposes; others have wishes." - Washington Irving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All glory comes from daring to begin." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take a deep breath, count to ten, and tackle each task one step at a time." - Linda Shalaway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to believe in yourself." - Sun Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't find fault, find a remedy." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want your life to be more rewarding, you have to change the way you think." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your goals are the road maps that guide you and show you what is possible for your life." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell everyone what you want to do and someone will want  to help you do it." -  W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A ship is safe in harbour, but that's not what ships are for." - William Shedd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A superior man is modest in his speech, but exceeds in his actions." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A friend is someone with whom you dare to be yourself." - Frank Crane]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>