<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Her: What is your favorite color Him: Beautiful Her: That's not a color Him: Yes it is. It's the color of your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's love, sometimes it's hate; but either way it's you that's in my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep tabs on backstage action from the 2013 MTV Movie Awards with All Access Live! http://t.co/oEmhGTkJOx - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish I could just go back to the past and laugh at myself then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a mistake and I want to do everything I can to fix it... but I can't do anything if you don't give me a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you but I hate you. You drive me crazy. But yet for some reason; I still call you my baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most peaceful things is, having the one you love fall asleep in your arms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2Yes you re in his bed, but are you in his heart where it matters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment of regret when you are brought back to reality after hours of onlining. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want you to know something, but I can't get the words out, so I'll just let the first 3 words of this sentence explain it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't our hearts have brains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With every step taken, you're closer to the top of the mountain. With every step untaken, you're one step further. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people say they love me, but I don't need someone to say it, I need someone to show it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If aliens are looking for intelligent life Why the heck are you scared!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall in love with someone who deserves your heart, not someone who plays with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is not to forget but to forgive. Not to see but to understand. Not to hear but to listen. Not to let go but to hold on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have that one dumb friend. And if you can't think of a dumb friend...congratulations you're the dumb friend :).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you fall in love you feel like you're in heaven...when your heart is broken, all hell is unleashed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best things in life are worth waiting for, fighting for, believing in, and just never letting go of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder what my life would be like with out you. Then I thank God I only have to wonder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not a photographer. You just have an overpriced camera.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember: love is not in how you know her, love is in how you understand her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dreadful feeling when you're stuck alone at home, and no one's free to go out. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you finally decide on something after a long hesitation, everything will seem much clearer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you walked away from that someone you love...and they DIDN T chase after you...rest assured, you made the right decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not falling in love, I'm falling into pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I forget you when you're always on my mind How can I not love you when you're controlling my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got an attitude that just screams for an adjustment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One tear drop can speak in any language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fight for someone who won't fight for you, cry for someone who won't cry for you, or stay with someone who doesn't appreciate you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, people only rain on your parade because they're jealous of your sun and tired of their shade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I'm over you. Maybe I've moved on. Maybe I like someone else, but maybe, I'm just a really good liar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It s better to let someone walk away from you rather than walk all over you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the truth actually does raise its ugly head, but you can t see it because it s hiding behind lots of pretty little lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I feel for you is more then love...it's beyond words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There comes a time in life when you have to let go of all the pointless drama &amp; the people who create it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when you look into someone's eyes and see everything you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let how you feel make you forget what you deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The annoying moment when you're dying to go out but can't find anyone to go out with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Moving on"...just two words that take about a second to blurt out, but can take forever to achieve...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can t make you love me,want me,or understand me/..all I can do Is hope that someday you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like clouds, when they disappear, it s a brighter day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest things to say are the words that mean the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GUYS: love her, spoil her, wine her, dine her, kiss her, wife her, appreciate her, respect her, make her smile, make her happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you find love, I mean real love, well, you don't give it up without putting up one hell of a fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just promise me that you'll never promise anymore...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seemed better in my imagination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be able to forgive, but I can NEVER forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angry people do stupid things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once I start disliking someone, EVERYTHING they do is irritating to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether life is beautiful or disaster, it depends on how you treat yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't fall for you, you tripped me and just walked away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere in the world tonight, someone's falling in love for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to respect yourself and love others. Don't let anyone push you into something that is not you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I expected; I was disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear mom, Please stop telling me not to play with my food. You spent the first  years of my life pretending it was an airplane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! You have succeeded in hurting a girl who truly loved you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do it because I can, I can because I want to, I want to because you said I couldn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm willing to wait for you, to be you're number one, because I know you're ohh so worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love is electric ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't carry a conversation don't talk to me. I'm not gonna talk to myself while you give one word answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate people who don't hear me out when I need to explain something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old enough to know better, young enough to do it anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart says "Yes" But my mind says "What if...."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who treats his woman like a princess is proof that he has been born &amp; raised in the arms of a queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather argue with you, than kiss someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies, if a girl ever steals your man, there s no better revenge than letting her keep him. REAL MEN can t be stolen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say if u love someone enough they r worth all the pain in the world but if it was really love u wouldn't have to be feeling pain at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when you walked ahead of your friends and realised that no one is following you. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn how to love and how to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who hurt you, teach you the greatest lessons in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only love one person at a time, and right now its me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never afraid to tell you I love you... I was just afraid you wouldn't say it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it that the one who makes me the happiest, is the one who is already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it called a crush? It s because that s what happens to your heart when you find out they don t like you back...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are everything I never knew I wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be lying if I said you stepped out of my dreams and into my life... My dreams were never this wonderful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I lie awake at night, and I ask, 'Where have I gone wrong' Then a voice says to me, 'This is going to take more than one night.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know what we are, but know not what we be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like pi - natural, irrational, and very important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A million stars and a million dreams. He's the only star I see and the only dream I dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You asked me whose life was more important - yours or mine and I answered "mine" ; you walked away angry not knowing that you ARE my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Everybody! Sorry for being away for so long, Emergency at home, but I m back now so tell all your followers ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep blaming her for taking you away from me, when the truth is you could've fought for me, but instead you let me go as if I was nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you spend too long holding on to the one who treats you like an option, you will miss finding someone who treats you like a priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real girl isn't perfect and a perfect girl isn't real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#YIRide Yamaha's 2013 YZ450F. Why do you ride? http://t.co/JXaHcevLZ3 - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear O.J., Thanks for the advice! Sincerely, Casey Anthony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy tips for out of shape tennis players. http://t.co/Cn7bqHNkzO - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't believe the guy who says he loves you; but believe in the guy who shows you that he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love someone, be brave to tell them...otherwise be brave enough to watch them be loved by someone else...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it funny how someone can really make you mad just by yelling "BINGO!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She made one mistake in her life...he said he would never hurt her and always love her,and she believed him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He keeps my feet on the ground and my head in the clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm selfish for wanting you all for myself but I can't help the way I feel about you. I want you and only you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a math equation. In order to gain the most, you have to know how to convert the negatives into positives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm multi-talented, I can talk and piss you off at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when you realize you're wrong in an argument, but you keep arguing anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you know how much you mean to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'd laugh at the stars and we'd share everything, too young to notice and too dumb to care. Love was a story that couldn't compare]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>