<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do I not give a fuck?
Let me show you right now before you give it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: Ilya Kovalchuk announces his retirement at just 30-years-old: http://t.co/CrQZE9gocp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miami round 2 💪 bitches where you at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#workhardplayhard #gettinerdone #teambringit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tryin to be as humble as possible but makin this money feels damn good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid 8 hour corporate orientation at work. Yes please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 where in the basement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws no super castlevania IV is. Get it right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 did you guys get flooded?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome year. Sick new job and got to go to Phoenix again New York again and now back to Miami in the fall 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald quote of the day 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 cool thanks man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 I thought you already were? When I come this week ill bring my CDs for you to copy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 that's actually legit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 what album is that from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 she picked me up earlier 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 I'm working till 5 your moms picking me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 it would be inspirational if you were]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 y'all gonna be at the house tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 nooo like 20 times at the house the other day and go thru your tweets I swear at least 5 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 as in clean up messes or dancing around?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 why is everything inspirational? Stoppp wearinnn it outtttt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HulkHogan longtime fan can I get a retweet brother? Lookin forward to Fan expo in August]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DarrenDreger: Clarkson agrees to leafs. Details being worked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TSNBobMcKenzie: TOR agrees to 5-year, $21M deal with Bozak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: UPDATE: The Bruins have traded Tyler Seguin to Dallas in a seven-player trade that includes Loui Eriksson - http://t.co/CyXbf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 whoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justina_barton over easy lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lookin forward to the future success of Mackinnon, Landeskog, and Duchene for the Avalanche Franchise! Get er done Coach Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 I support your rant, nobody likes soccer on tv including Richard the IV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 @ashleeyywatt123 id go but the NHL draft is on at 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: Respect to all the people in the Canada who support the legend for Canada day. I love the Stu Hart the Maple Leaf Garden…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CMPunk: Has the prick posing as me on Instagram put up the pic of my shoes yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MapleLeafs: The #Leafs will speak with 26 prospects today as the #NHLDraft process continues. #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Maple Leafs and @the_ironsheik same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik amen sheik. What does the legend have planned for this fine Saturday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks smokey smokey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fuckin despise people who don't answer their phone then msg you and say what's up. Worst pet peeve ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald were not going till tomorrow come drink with us tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: A look at the scene in Chicago for the Stanley Cup Parade. http://t.co/ihp0iFrAWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: Thousands expected to attend Blackhawks Stanley Cup parade http://t.co/IBCxc1ITrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 deep stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry up 5pm I'm about to go ham. Payday/wasaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: Michael Jordan Iron Sheik same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's reaching wasaga this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zebras Tremendo Garrotazo doble / Mating Breeding @rogerrdunn  http://t.co/MzZciq9VAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk congrats Punk! Hard earned victory for the Blackhawks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmorra wasssssup? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHI-TOWN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaleyCuoco you ever make appearances in Toronto? Would love to meet you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 blahhhrifjfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 jahovaskians boys blondie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron bastards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 ye I have that effect on ppl listen I was showin the fam the videos and I couldn't find the dancing one 👎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VinceMcMahon: I've always admired the work of the late James Gandolfini, a great heel on television.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron did you put em under the colonels pillow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessRichter111 @ashleeyywatt123 @Kaitlyn_Rooth DEF we can :) it's in 2 days!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald @billiecorrigan what is this lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 don't forget to take the dog out and empty the dishwasher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 that was actually good I saw it like a week ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks shut the hell up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 how was it and what did you do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram fuckin sucks crashing every 2 seconds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: Fuck the #Batfleck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Clooney may finally be dethroned as the worst Batman ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst glad to see redemption island back with a new twist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HacksawJDuggan: 3MB is like The Rockers if they were all Marty Jannetty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billiecorrigan my dirty mind had the same thoughts as @alana_macdonald had to creep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 @NicoleArbour you lucky duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 which]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatTheNESpunk I'm cool with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto bound for Black Sabbath tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 what a random tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasinaysmith I was lookin for you yesterday where do you work at wonderbread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 get me some too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 get the party started I'm comin over tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 I went on leviathan twice yesterday and the second time me and Tyler sat at the front and had our hands up the whole time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leviathan twice today second time at the front, hands held high whole time what a rush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HulkHogan I hope your not wearing a tna shirt when I come meet you at fan expo I want the real hogan I know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasinaysmith you tell em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik I watched OTR yesterday bubba I support your cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: I at the TSN station now talk talk talk about how I'm the legend and how nobody can fuck with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron @NikoKetsilis I'm goin to the concert Friday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work done. Time to fuck this Sunday night in the ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik where you at bubba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate going out then working the next day  👎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ribfest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 tell Rick they just announced at comic con that batman is gonna be in the next man of steel movie first time ever both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VinceMcMahon: I want to personally welcome Ultimate Warrior back to @WWE http://t.co/26Z44YD5PK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game chasing with @Raymondraws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna be a good year for hockey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so change of plans since we did Miami last year we are going to Los Angeles in October instead. Cali here I come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna make it a goal to buy back my whole Super Nintendo library]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet free breakfast from the union. I'm down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsmailMadani what is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katyperry king Bosco http://t.co/CkhJsHjluR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst ready for yet another great season!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>