<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/lDzBsWCi6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/D6NvhQ8OcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/gOsQN9gywQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/ce3hKWDZYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/MNZXEMAHTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/bpARDe0Zfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/uc5c06Qpcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/9C7z9NmIsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/CiARBnl3Zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/vNWHyeygFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/VoffmIsSP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/zdbseP0WPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/RCYBA7esiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/odxWYEfwGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/qDG09ZEYf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/zYeCO9Q4Q8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/DIovALZkg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/UFQxYz2buu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/zNfmBQJC3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/KFOtXkKihd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/g2OYMhbXM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/6dCCub4ho1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/IOeSOTp4DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/Bw3lw8S45Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/rpDxagiiIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/eRspNCkZkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/N92HlvU7ay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/bqwoY9QfnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/zZturWy0iS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/zNfmBQJC3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/I2kSEsyVUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/xYq9RDrMj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/IycvLtwZUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl 1:  I spent my vacation fishing  Girl 2: Then why did you buy a new bathing suit?   Girl 1:  That was my bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/zLqxKe0Bao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/R1RD4fIjsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/GWpev8FUkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/GsmCmqNwTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/ncymGLqMWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/1ESjuSWCv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/3ASbefpTOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/791vd0b4Pb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/z6S2TUhnNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/Stbe52WawT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/x9i1d095rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/hSVcMmlLsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/nERWirsS4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/YVPRQ9LiPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/32AkO3i0uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/WkVaHCy1Gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/kmcjV7EWVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/wIXEAJsyeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/1KOL8IgP0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/kyXoN84mmg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>