<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Like obviously the client is expecting an un-marked-up price, and so thwarting his expectations seems straightforwardly dishonest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then, you know, they keep bidding. They're just giving the company each other's money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere in market structure, here's an open letter from BATS ("Dear industry participant ...") about equity markets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executive pay. I'm basically sympathetic to executive 10b5-1 stock plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here is the story of how Glenview Capital Management made $3.2 billion betting on Obamacare by buying hospital and insurer stocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google 
pays its executive chairman
 well. What would happen if everyone was paid what Gawker writers thought they deserved?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[) Elsewhere in investment banking, Citigroup will be paying traders roughly what they got last year, while bankers will get a little more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Carol Loomis is great, but that seems like a terrible legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(When last we talked about it those numbers were $40 billion and $16 billion, but since then Alibaba has had a rough couple of days.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he electronically reproduced the code there? I don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. I know, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're keeping the headline anyway because "blood wolframite" doesn't have the same ring to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ISDA has received a copy of the Prospectus for Japanese Yen denominated bonds of the Republic of Argentina dated as of January 2005."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba would get those for free. Also it would get the rest of Yahoo for free!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the worst way to communicate this side of, like, voicemail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weirdest part is, why would you want to be a juror on a lengthy tax fraud trial?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[("You can fondle the cube, but it will not respond.")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgepearkes "IEX, he said, can be part of the solution," says the article, but didn't he create the problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you know who is good at market timing? Barack Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if you were long with client money this morning, sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is complaining -- "I don't think there is any good that can come of it," says one long-time muni analyst -- but not from everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, the word "unicorn" has a long history of being used metaphorically for a rare, mysterious and desirable thing. "One was 'home run.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Banks in London Devise Way Around Europe's Bonus Rules." You were expecting a different result?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine yes boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people -- the Federal Trade Commission, Warren Buffett, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "It’s welcome news to hedge funds that have trailed the market almost every year since the global financial crisis."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loan market blacklists. What is a "bank loan"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 
stories of business
. Do other people enjoy reading the Harvard Business Review's blog as much as I do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lowrey: That is, let's say, a controversial claim about corporate law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't spend a lot of time in Silicon Valley but I'm sure that's how it works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Though still not on a total enterprise value basis.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand if you're on the board of directors of the seller, and an investment adviser to the buyer, then all of this is right out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fraud isn't just about saying false words; it's about your counterparty relying on those words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The SEC is too slow
. The statute of limitations for bringing securities fraud cases is five years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umm: Investors trying to sell Chinese shares have found themselves locked out of 72 percent of the market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh fine and this:  After a free historical tour of the Israeli port city Jaffa, Weis had offered to tip his tour guide in bitcoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, business schools aspire to be two-year sleepover parties for future CEOs, and they're right on track.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this week should be a test of the bond market liquidity worries, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bond dealers 
price discriminate
. The SEC is investigating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech triumphalism: thing 2. "We have a mechanical bull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said at the time: Would this press release significantly change a "reasonable investor's" view of Tesla? Obviously not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a strong feeling at the time that Sand Hill Exchange's proposed business model did not fully comply with all relevant regulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private equity is buying a lot of companies from private equity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New York Fed is not short of interesting ideas on bank capital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you could still have all the arguments you'd have about a too-high or too-low price; $15.18 is not magically the just-right price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What will we do when robots take all our jobs?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Here is an even more overwrought account.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ... might have a different view? But here is Gretchen Morgenson's (from a couple of weeks ago sorry).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Among other things, Citadel is a fantastic regulatory success story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is not like the end of the world, or even the end of the bank trust preferred CDO market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, this is the way investigations work. Some good news for health insurers was announced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not a ton of constructive places to go after that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The frequency of the complaints suggest that they're not having much effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. But, as I said yesterday, you can stop: Now there is evidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it keeps happening. Is this one of those cases where the media simply doesn't appreciate the realities of the industry that it covers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unicorns. Honestly the tech industry has only itself to blame for this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And since traders are humans, or at least mammals, this happens sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "It’s welcome news to hedge funds that have trailed the market almost every year since the global financial crisis."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your competitors pay their CEOs 4,000 times what their workers get, how can you justify paying less?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what you say about any misconduct, when you don't care what the misconduct was. It doesn't describe the FX scandal at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it feels a little like cheating to count UBS in this week's tally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's also just sort of a quaint throwback to 100 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike every bank in Europe, though I guess like kind of a lot of them, RBS is 81 percent owned by the UK government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s where to go, that’s a great business.’” “I would love to hire your son,” came a voice from the crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They see this as a risk primarily in open-end mutual funds, not in exchange-traded funds, which strikes me as reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawsuits were brought in 94.9% of takeovers in 2014 versus 39% in 2005.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Disclosure: I used to work at Goldman too.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second point is: What is the right answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or is it just, like, wherever you look hard enough, you can find multiple unrelated cases of insider trading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were also buying fake business plans, since they couldn't dream them all up on their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Disclosure: I am a former Goldman employee, and a former shareholder.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latour’s post-trade surveillance tools did not use the ISOs that Latour sent to the exchanges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can feel it in the building and see in the people that work with him that they’re all proud to be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think reviewing criteria with investors would be good, or at least indicate that you're not defrauding them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have nothing against rich people, some of my best friends are rich people, but why would you join a social network for rich people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly the tech industry has only itself to blame for this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might think that a nuclear powered Nimitz-class supercarrier would not be a pleasure craft, but you would be mostly wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Want" is such a loaded word. Obviously you want to favor your favored investors, that's what "favored" means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm really just catching up; please bear with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you turn Twitter into Facebook, it won't be Twitter, and Twitter is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over any long enough period, the 
best performing growth stock
 will outperform the worst performing value stock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems like a bit of a failure if capital regulation drives banks to do strictly idiotic trades like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Investors are fleeing from a business they see as confidence-based, and therefore prone to unravel at speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One possible solution would be for Congress to pass a law making insider trading illegal, but, you know, don't count on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all horse-trading and politics; the merits of, say, derivatives regulation don't seem to get much attention in Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to think that protecting smart people from doing dumb things would be a low-touch endeavor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A while back it released, like, a YouTube video to the effect of "ooh invest in our hedge fund," and there was a surfer involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But you know what looks awesome in a world of $50 oil? Forwards/futures/puts/whatever struck around $100, that's what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If I can go into a partnership and demand specific terms, that sounds good, except why is that the case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nice novelty is that the Securities and Exchange Commission is basically your accomplice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even worse than investment banking, though, is being in the business of settling massive mortgage lawsuits every five minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can no longer really be surprised to hear that banks might have colluded to manipulate a market in something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who made money selling bonds to the Fed during QE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were a high-frequency trading firm, would you want to be on that list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of America is just allowed to do this. It's fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They’re not able to make a lot of money from exploiting slow investors following macroeconomic news," says one of the authors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those companies can opt out of U.S. exchange corporate governance rules (about things like independent directors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could go to a fair tax. There’s a lot of things you could do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course Puerto Rico isn't a state, but, you know, by analogy, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is, of course, a deep misunderstanding of modern capitalism.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>