<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Administrator: IT Systems Administrator – Redditch, Worcestershire   Salary – 30-40k plus benefits, pension, healthcare   Active Directory, Microsoft 365, Cloud, TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, Windows Server 2003/2008/2012, VMware vSphere/ESXI… https://t.co/YG3dE7BXvY https://t.co/LM5UK3kCJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parts, Materials, and Processes Manager: 02-Oct-2018 Parts, Materials, and Processes Manager Space California 453564BR • Demonstrated experience leading diverse engineering teams focused on Parts, Materials and Processes (PMP) to achieve functional and… https://t.co/i797Q9Vepa https://t.co/Y0W6IicDb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Consultant – SecOps: VIQU are working in partnership with a global organisation to recruit for a Cloud Security Consultant on an initial 6-month contract. As a Cloud Security Consultant, you will be responsible for the architecture,… https://t.co/PGC6D59I9f https://t.co/3UgyEmBgXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NBAer fined for smuggling dog on plane: A former NBA player has been fined for smuggling a dog into Australia in his hand luggage, breaking the country's strict bio-security laws. https://t.co/OJRwBjaX2F https://t.co/DAvIk1Caom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow System Administrator/Developer Lead: ServiceNow Systems Admin/Developer Lead Keys: ITIL, serviceNow, Rest, Soap, JAVAScript, SAAS Cloud. Must be ok with paired programming agile SCUM Application Configuration. Job Qualifications Required: (5+… https://t.co/ki8bWunbeT https://t.co/9m5euMNs5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Coventry, £50K: Business Analyst, Coventry, £50K Our client is the leading provider of banking software within the UK. Knowledge Skills and experience Core skills – Strong analytical and problem solving skills are required, including a… https://t.co/0i4No17trE https://t.co/bgGfhbEoqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Technical Architect: Big Data Platform / Hadoop Technical Architect – Permanent – Bedfordshire – up to £75K An exciting position has arisen for a Technical Architect specialising in Hadoop and Big Data Platforms, with a growing FTSE 100 Company… https://t.co/DD9fcBmeim https://t.co/eknvsgy4vp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer Contract: SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER Position Summary: A Senior Software Engineer will develop, maintain and support new or existing software products while evangelizing and applying the best practices of software development.… https://t.co/ByhLGih1Bt https://t.co/HXWUVZYiCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst: Minimum 6-8 years of experience in the software industry, with at least 4 years of experience in an Analysis andor client facing role. * The ability to translate complex business requirements to deliverable solutions that meet customer… https://t.co/ymGTVlp7qG https://t.co/Vh3wb1CRon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Cornell's family files lawsuit against doctor over singer's death: Chris Cornell's doctor is to blame for the Soundgarden singer's death, his family states in a lawsuit filed Thursday. https://t.co/svMov9NoBH https://t.co/WAP9p08Pjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Development Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be a technical leader on our team that is developing network automation to accelerate service deployment. You will provide leadership in software development and… https://t.co/2kmuM9ouIk https://t.co/tvwQ7G1LhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: IT Support Engineer Full time to £30,000 PA DOE Rochester VR/02286R For this role it is essential that you have previous experience of working for a Managed Services Provider. An opportunity has arisen within our client’s team for an… https://t.co/0l4ea5Fgd0 https://t.co/59PomCB2j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks plans 2,100 new stores next year: Starbucks is planning to open 2,100 new stores globally next year. https://t.co/a9lyA602NY https://t.co/DOMe53cYqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer – C#, Azure: Net Developer – C#, Azure – Social Enterprise London, Kings Cross £ 49,634 – £60,000 Per Annum + Extensive Company Benefits Are you an experienced C#, Azure .Net Developer? We are one of London’s leading housing associations,… https://t.co/mz7H3sgWwl https://t.co/iFObVANlq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #R57999: Software Engineer Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple position available: Perform tech design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of comp apps using existing &amp; emerging tech platforms. Requires… https://t.co/Yu68YmNUGo https://t.co/JOfj22lANp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Manager – MicroServices – Bristol: 100% management – but still hands on with a technical overview * MicroServices, Java, Scala, Kafka, Agile, Scrum * TDD, Continuous Integration / Delivery * Manage 3 teams of developers This is a… https://t.co/xrS9DENXAw https://t.co/QbPEfTGEQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple will stop sharing numbers on how many devices it’s selling: Apple shared its latest quarterly earnings report today, but during its call with investors the company’s CFO Luca Maestri also delivered an unexpected announcement: it won’t be sharing… https://t.co/PiniBpjzZy https://t.co/21luCExBIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee IT Support: Are you looking for a first role in IT? Do you have good communication skills and a solid understanding of IT? This opportunity offers great training, a fun and dynamic work environment and great opportunities for career progression.… https://t.co/P529D7X3Vg https://t.co/CYUmra49pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer – VMWare / O365 – Cheltenham – £27k: IT Support Engineer- O365 – Cheltenham – £27k Role Overview A 2nd Line IT Engineer looking to progress their IT career and joining a rewarding employer with multiple sites in the UK would be… https://t.co/CmliMmc2AQ https://t.co/yZ0wsy0F85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: IOS Developer – Chippenham or Bristol £55,000 – £60,000 Where’s my keys, where’s my phone, where’s my keys, where’s my phone? Remember when Zippy from Britain’s got talent couldn’t find his keys or his phone? Well he’ll won’t be losing his… https://t.co/SgOj8ZTzQh https://t.co/pefAjEmX6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer – Berkshire: Java, Linux Senior roles in Reading From £45K Would you like to work with a global company who are interested in Engineers who are developing and learning new technologies? If so, I am looking for Senior Software Engineer’s… https://t.co/5JmhJEbYZc https://t.co/ZSTsOHK7h8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Developer: Junior Developer Stoke-On-Trent Permanent – £25,000 – £35,000 Do you love technology and are passionate about building your skills? Do you want to learn in a collaborative and interactive environment? UA are working with a thriving… https://t.co/XOsy9fx2qh https://t.co/oqTZhG08YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: My client, a giant in the oil and gas space, are embarking on a journey of digitalisaiton by using advanced technologies (data science, advanced/predictive analytics, machine learning, blockchain) This role will see you join an existing… https://t.co/E4vxZS6wG4 https://t.co/k0xD1defIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to win voters is with joy https://t.co/KkIvsFEHTp https://t.co/8t29JtDDU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.T Operations Technician: Yoh Solutions are currently recruiting for an I.T Support Technician to undertake an initial 3 month contract based in Surrey. Position Description: The IT Technician is responsible to deliver IT services, to support end users… https://t.co/7VHWLG5nii https://t.co/tTVTV0VDI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Delivery Specialist: Elementum SCM, Inc. has multiple positions open in our Mountain View, CA office for the following: Technical Delivery Specialist(s) (Job #78): Analyze eng, buss &amp; data proccng prbs, implmnt &amp; imprv, comp sys &amp; processes for… https://t.co/vAxVXw4NQe https://t.co/6T2qJRLgUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Fujitsu Technology &amp; Business of America, Inc. has 2 openings in the Sunnyvale, CA location for a HW/SW Engineer to dev test tools, automate &amp; accelerate qualification processes &amp; to run qualification test plan to resolve issues.… https://t.co/28GSbM6TSi https://t.co/oOEzg5pibQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NFL teams' different approach to bolstering their rosters for the stretch run https://t.co/eLYfVqiffG https://t.co/hj6UoI3XU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java AWS Solutions Architect – Cardiff – £50,000 + 10% bonus: Java Solutions Architect (AWS) – £50,000 + 10% bonus – Cardiff centre My client is a highly successful financial software business in Cardiff, with a well established Development and… https://t.co/ENLwZCFCsX https://t.co/yr4haNB8D9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Principal Software Engineers – (Backend/Dat-: Senior/Principal Software Engineers (Backend/Data Engineering) We are looking for experienced Senior and Principal software engineers to stabilize, scale, and innovate our core data processing,… https://t.co/zR6xgLi026]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Front End Developer – React Permanent Cardiff Salary: Negotiable, dependant on experience General requirements: • Experience and understanding of large and complex code bases and architectures. • Highly accountable and takes… https://t.co/BqsbBPp84q https://t.co/00knF6yblA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Engineer: Job Description Systems Software Engineer Location: US-MA-Westborough Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Robotics LLC Position Category: Software Development Company/Location (search) : Country (Full Name): : United States Job… https://t.co/s0AbRbCus4 https://t.co/suMWQ89Lti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retailers have a holiday labor problem: It's three weeks to Black Friday, and retailers have a problem. https://t.co/XihibdllfH https://t.co/hOJI1qYQ8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Newark, NJ Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 10/12/2018 Job Description TITLE – Data Analyst LOCATION – Newark, NJ CONTRACT – 5 months Job Description:… https://t.co/QqAaizvEB2 https://t.co/fFOCSoHhdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of DevOps – Bristol – Azure, CI/CD, Agile – To £80,000: Head of DevOps – Bristol – Azure, CI/CD, Agile – To £80,000 + benefits Would you like the opportunity to lead this software company through a significant evolution of it's service delivery… https://t.co/41jNQuVnvb https://t.co/iordVYjiDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10th child dies from adenovirus outbreak: A 10th child has died following an outbreak of adenovirus at a New Jersey rehabilitation facility, state health officials said. https://t.co/NJWml51jWS https://t.co/EjbuKGPuTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Developer: We're currently seeking a Senior Quantitative Software Engineer to join the largest independent investment management firms in the World. You will be joining the ever-growing Fixed Income Systems Team here in London and will work… https://t.co/pXpByS1CU7 https://t.co/cwcpsvMT4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Backend Engineering – Machine Learning: Machine Learning technology startup in Central London are hiring for an additional Python Backend Engineer to join the existing tech team of 10 technologists solving the hard problem of getting computers to… https://t.co/jrnPYyIJPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Developer: We're looking for an experienced Senior JS Developer to join our growing team. As a JavaScript Developer within the Creative Technology team, your focus will be to develop applications and/or frameworks to help automate… https://t.co/xgQY5Crq80 https://t.co/zwuNeLCcgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer – London – AWS – Docker – Linux: My client in Central London is looking for an experienced DevOps Engineer to join their growing team. This is a great opportunity if you're interested in innovative projects and making a difference. You… https://t.co/nWOwGbGh2t https://t.co/LHWCTfnIat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Government Cloud Solutions Architect: Job Description Principal Government Cloud Solutions Architect Location: US-VA-Herndon Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Recruiting Team: North American Teams – AWS Company/Location… https://t.co/65yetWtspw https://t.co/ghSaAytWuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days before the midterms, the President accuses Democrats of plotting to help Central American invaders overrun the nation with cop killers: In the most racially charged national political ad in 30 years, President Donald Trump and the Republican Party… https://t.co/ZYCVwOSAy3 https://t.co/TvtDyqPWCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk IT Support Engineer – Top 3 Hosting Datacentre Brand: Service Desk IT Support Engineer – Top 3 Hosting Datacentre Brand Leeds. LS15 £18,000 – £28,000 DOE + Excellent Benefits + Personal Development ++ Ready to join one of the leading UK… https://t.co/Xe4MjW64LH https://t.co/hUXI6DRtRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python / Django Developer: Role: Senior Python / Django Developer Type: Contract Location: Guildford Length: 3-6 months Rate: £(Apply online only)/day Great opportunity to work with this early stage, well-funded, software company who are… https://t.co/kJ04VlULZ2 https://t.co/N3kezwAWLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stores Operative: Job: Stores Operative Control the movement of stock through the local stores, engineer vehicles and the business in general. Review logistic reports to help control and manage stock aligned to engineers and sites. To control stock with… https://t.co/lLhQ2bkhUJ https://t.co/KACZZHUN5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How politics became a risky business for companies in the era of Trump and King: Land O'Lakes and Purina, the two companies that dumped Iowa Rep. Steve King this week over his incendiary comments, learned what a growing number of corporate interests are… https://t.co/xdQ6KVGB8h https://t.co/wwWcwlEODL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lime recalls some scooters due to fire concerns: Lime, the electric scooter and bike-share startup, has pulled some of its scooters from the streets of Los Angeles, San Diego and Lake Tahoe. That’s because of two hardware challenges the company has… https://t.co/iuXyAY8BzW https://t.co/FDwLoVxTk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: The Company Brewster Pratap are working with an innovative and unique company who provide a unique software product globally. Based in the heart of Sheffield who are looking to expand their team with a Senior Web Developer. They are… https://t.co/KwsCBxCrgV https://t.co/fQsnrc7YaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In cervical cancer surgery, minimally invasive is worse than open, study says: The type of surgery a woman has will affect her ability to survive cervical cancer, new research suggests. Among patients with early-stage cervical cancer, women who undergo… https://t.co/J4dQvxqTCq https://t.co/7LtlM5s9Tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer Cambridge: C++ Developer – Software Engineer – Cambridge – Developer An international semi-conductor software house are looking to hire into their core R&amp;D team based in Cambridge, UK.  My client is a hardware and software company that… https://t.co/Aka8YFOznC https://t.co/P0AxKFK205]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Pre-Sales Job: Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Presales Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Regular Full Time COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP started in 1972 as a team of five colleagues with a desire to do something new.… https://t.co/N78BXyOfDr https://t.co/2EcGN98UAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer (Cyber Security): DevOps Engineer A rapidly growing cyber security company disrupting the software, hardware and mobile security industries are on the lookout for a DevOps engineer to support the expansion of their platform and client… https://t.co/GnMUJ6p3KA https://t.co/Jfa0o3MlC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Systems Admin – Dublin CC: Senior Linux Systems Administrator – Dublin CC This period is one of the most important in my clients entire history. They are currently working to change a part of their business model and get more involved in the… https://t.co/BNwqGobP1O https://t.co/nVsgoZI9V8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Steve King's explanation for his racially charged comments is epically bad: On Tuesday, Ohio Republican Rep. Steve Stivers tweeted this about his colleague Steve King: "Congressman Steve King's recent comments, actions, and retweets are… https://t.co/MSyi8yHDRM https://t.co/TY2XJg4l0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Owner: Technical Product Owner – London – £75,000 I’m working with a Multi-national Facilities management and Real-Estate firm based in Central London who have rapidly expanded the Technology and Digital Function of their business. With… https://t.co/Grgqfn4A3n https://t.co/FByY0YYPiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal AWS Solutions Architect: Job Description Principal AWS Solutions Architect Location: US-CA-San Francisco Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Job Description External job description Amazon Web Services (AWS) is looking for a… https://t.co/Cv7Tz182zT https://t.co/Z8x9QfMkPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: An exciting opportunity has arisen for an experienced Business Analyst to join a recognised and established institution, based in rural Bedfordshire. It relies critically on its IT infrastructure and information systems to support its… https://t.co/0RYVl9MxcY https://t.co/T0qOVh3tq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – US: Role Test Analyst – US Auto req ID 35638BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Utilities Skillset Utilities – Generic , Country USA State / Region / Province California Work Location Rosemead, CA Company ITL USA Job… https://t.co/XjlzJY1LoV https://t.co/9ZhoNeiORV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner: VAC-6640 Job Title: Product Owner Location: Bolton Type: Full-Time Permanent Pay: £30,000 – £40,000 (plus full benefits including pension etc) My client, a leading provider of software solutions is looking to build up their business on the… https://t.co/K7X5wvhgLQ https://t.co/FbIZ3U3zCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megyn Kelly's camp calls out NBCUniversal CEO amid testy exit talks: Megyn Kelly's slow-motion exit from NBC News has turned into an all-out legal battle. https://t.co/xRcdih9aBc https://t.co/QzW9SqkHT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester: The Company A software company specialising in the Financial Services sector, an award winning business with a global client base and elite team. My client is looking for an experienced Software Tester to join their Portsmouth based… https://t.co/mk3D4cWkx2 https://t.co/7A5gBqkJ6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Team Leader: Permanent Position Development Team Leader Up to £50,000 P/A I have an incredible opportunity in Hull to work for a market leading client with offices in the UK, Europe, Asia and North America as a .NET development team lead. The… https://t.co/mcjdC4wkwl https://t.co/g4APCfkndD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer 100% Fully Remote: Our client is a leading creator of software for digital learning. Most recently, they have created 2 pioneering products which have had great success and are used by thousands of people around the world. Due to… https://t.co/JtY5CCDygL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer / Architect: Location: Central Oxford. Salary: 50K + benefits package + flexible hours Are you an experienced Java developer wanting to join a highly motivated, experienced and passionate development team while working and coding on… https://t.co/xfidqibLgg https://t.co/F7hp8OgSKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA’s prolific planet-hunter Kepler has finally earned its retirement: After nine years of service, half a million stars surveyed, and thousands of planets discovered around those stars, NASA's astonishingly successful Kepler space telescope is finally… https://t.co/LFhwt7CGVa https://t.co/42lZxEvxSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Network Support: My client is a non-profit organisation that aids industry leading companies with internet information content. The ideal candidate will have a keen interest in IT and have come from a 1st line environment or support environment with… https://t.co/8JCEP82GR6 https://t.co/8ve1EPUS51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I am the underdog:' How Scott Walker ended up in his toughest race yet: Little about Tony Evers feels like he'd be the one to slay the giant. https://t.co/hJNFQf7fPA https://t.co/xkyYmbOmrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpdesk Engineer – 3rd line Support – Epsom: Helpdesk Engineer – 3rd line Support – Epsom £25k – £35k + bens My client is a reputed Managed Services Provider with an exciting opportunity for a 3rd line Helpdesk Engineer to join its UK headquarters.… https://t.co/SZfIt88oJG https://t.co/CNicEahFeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Line Support Engineer: 3rd Line Support 3rd Line Support General Description: Working with the Head of Information Systems you will be integral to ensuring that the IT infrastrucure is robust and flexible to meet the challenges of the digital… https://t.co/0o0Ovdyoy5 https://t.co/D2FIiNcblu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power utility says its equipment may have sparked the second largest wildfire in California history: A California utility company has acknowledged that its equipment was responsible for starting the second largest wildfire in the state's modern history. https://t.co/tKaWvrN5Eq https://t.co/6lnbRmOXiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Lead Developer | Birmingham Would you like to learn .NET Core and Azure? Avanti Recruitment is currently working with a Logistics and Supply Chain focused software company based in Birmingham. They are looking for a strong C# / .NET… https://t.co/Gnd1v04hvE https://t.co/mdbIDU6jPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Greenfield Site – R&amp;D Project: Data Scientist – Greenfield Site – R&amp;D Projects Data Scientist required by an innovative start-up in Sheffield to help build the machine learning capabilities of their one of a kind product. You will be… https://t.co/th8uWLfBwW https://t.co/t7C59fYYWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer £40-£45k + Flexible Working + Career Progression Our client is a growing IT company based in Segensworth, due to planned growth they are seeking an experienced and personable Software/Web Developer to join their… https://t.co/TkjKWvKxHP https://t.co/MlyFRRktZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austin bar transforms into Moe's Tavern from 'The Simpsons': It's one thing for people to dress up for Halloween, but it's quite another for a bar to get in on the act. https://t.co/L8K4xMYrM4 https://t.co/MGKoD5plOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice Specialist/Engineer Service Operations:   Job Description – Voice Specialist/Engineer Service Operations (27475) Job Description  Voice Specialist/Engineer Service Operations – 27475  Profession : Service Operations  Work Location : Europe-Czech… https://t.co/prVWiOT3py https://t.co/yOGaZM6XtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer – PL/SQL Java: For BNY Mellon Principal Developer – PL/SQL Java job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers –… https://t.co/XgocWzHs1X https://t.co/sSvpvtp4r4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic Account Manager – Gartner for Legal and Compliance Leaders: Strategic Account Manager – Gartner for Legal and Compliance Leaders What makes Gartner a GREAT fit for you? When you join Gartner, you’ll be part of a fast-growing team that helps the… https://t.co/Vn5z30RNvq https://t.co/oJrZIahH2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer, Finance Technology: West Creek 3 (12073), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Employer, were building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard… https://t.co/iDedhTsv7a https://t.co/TdCXjHmrR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veterans slam Trump for border 'stunt': With his decision to deploy more than 5,000 troops to the US-Mexico border, President Donald Trump has ordered more military personnel to the US southwest than he has serving in some of the world's most contentious… https://t.co/QagQoSA1vo https://t.co/3pviGLC31m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress Developer (Progress Openedge 9.5 &amp; 10): Progress Developer The Candidate Essential technical skills are: Progress development experience (Progress Openedge 9.5 &amp; 10), JavaScript &amp; HTML, support and bug fixing, basic DBA skills, delivery of… https://t.co/zLZ6U91IP3 https://t.co/8ZOt06SDW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Product Analyst: Software Product Analyst Overview Sentry Insurance is seeking a Software Product Analyst to join our PolicyCenter team. As a Software Product Analyst, you will leverage your basic knowledge of software development and gain… https://t.co/RPfBH0Mn39 https://t.co/TemAN4bShS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Apple finish 2018 on a high note? We’ll find out Thursday: Will the company satisfy Wall Street with its latest earnings report Thursday? https://t.co/33cP9SKmo5 https://t.co/Z4PvdWjBo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the quarterback who inspires Tom Brady https://t.co/icansWjAj3 https://t.co/f8MLv2NpeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Owner: Senior Product Owner // Cardiff // £50,000 + Additional Benefits I am looking to recruit a Senior Product Owner for a vibrant and innovative Digital organisation based in Cardiff. What you’ll do – Determine project feasibility… https://t.co/mgGsAR5Xuo https://t.co/4JkTo8isHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: A trusted and leading Cloud Consultancy is searching for a talented Support Engineer to join a medium sized team of Support Engineers within a Microsoft environment. This is a fantastic opportunity for a Support Engineer to progress… https://t.co/ZqsFZnl519 https://t.co/J7JcXB8Af2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer: A .Net Developer is required for a small development team who’s currently transitioning to a DevOps environment. This is a great opportunity for an experienced .Net Developer to pick up skills in Continuous Integrations and Automated… https://t.co/rTdAwhxHDk https://t.co/zkvRugxlSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Justice Department investigating Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke: The Justice Department is investigating Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke for possibly using his office for personal gain, following a referral from Interior's inspector general, two… https://t.co/RSoNMR0keX https://t.co/ggG9lIZn9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator / DevOps Engineer – Near Wakefield: Linux System Administrator / DevOps Engineer – Near Wakefield Commutable from Wakefield, Pontefract, Leeds, Huddersfield, Barnsley System Administrator, DevOps, Nix Systems, Linux, MySQL,… https://t.co/myWub3aaiv https://t.co/jjY4tJBkQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer: A Senior Data Engineer is required for a household name in Manchester who have grown massively since 2016 and are widely considered one of the best in their field. The team are recruiting for a Senior Data Engineer to join the… https://t.co/AXFiYHquH9 https://t.co/EPHwu7b6dL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer: American Express Travel Related Services seeks Senior Engineers to serve as a core member of an engineering team to develop digital and automated solutions for our customers. * Develop and design software applications, translating user… https://t.co/pSkBGhM9jt https://t.co/23gwoMYVyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Full Stack .NET developer needed to join a leading technology firm based in Farnborough. As the Full Stack .NET Developer you will be joining their already existing and very talented product delivery team working in an agile,… https://t.co/ez6P4ZRUXz https://t.co/Zsub8lXyk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Technology Development: Director of Technology Development Job Requisition Identification: HRIT00001 Employment Status: Full-time, Exempt – Salary Work Location: 177 Mott Avenue, New York, NY 10012 Job Summary: Oversee the design,… https://t.co/0niZwqFxRY https://t.co/xiIXNKuWyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer – Farnborough https://t.co/11YitoRoNg, C#, MVC, JavaScript, SQL This is a fantastic opportunity for a software developer to join an exceptional client based in Farnborough. You will be working in an agile and… https://t.co/rGmGKPgVGy https://t.co/sGQQyZoq6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultants: CONSULTANTS Slalom’s Irvine office has openings for Organizational Effectiveness Consultants: Conduct organizational studies &amp; evals, design systems &amp; procedures, conduct work simplification, etc. to assist mgmt in operating more efficiently… https://t.co/pSJcspAgX6 https://t.co/SMy1Dc8KfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Penetration Tester: An opportunity with one of the world’s top telecommunication firms has come available in the last week offering several unique benefits. This client is looking to help individuals who have been operating at an intermediate… https://t.co/A5GsU3Cg28 https://t.co/dkQAXVN3K3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: ASIC Design Engineer (REQ#A7394X) Provide innovative solutn’s to improve qual of phys dsgn at chip level: area, timing, pwr, schedule, &amp; process. Hardware… https://t.co/dTuy1iU2H0 https://t.co/dp3JflpFmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GE hit by new investigations from SEC, Justice Department: The SEC and Justice Department are investigating General Electric's power business, adding to the conglomerate's mounting legal headaches. https://t.co/xQjutHnR2r https://t.co/x8DtgyWXq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DELL Boomi SME: DELL Boomi SME – Contract 6 months + – £600/650 Per day – Crewe – Immediate My Client, a consultancy that delivers services to a large government department, are looking for a Dell Boomi Consultant to support the development of all… https://t.co/5RzT0WNS86 https://t.co/qq1wNPTDsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Careers | ec2 Software Solutions Skip to content Toggle navigation – ******************** – ec2 1.************ – ***************** – Numa 1.************ – Our Software – Help Me Choose – BioDose/NMIS – Numa – Patient Reporting –… https://t.co/m2uDoH1vrv https://t.co/Mmq35ZJMdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penetration Tester – Next to no Travel: A UK consultancy based on the south coast is looking for a penetration tester to join them. They do a lot of their work remotely from the office and travel is extremely rare so you’ll be able to get home to your… https://t.co/t5fixFmQFy https://t.co/WCWoAwcsBR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>