<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/JgVcwkxXbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/h05fXOfBXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/n6MGy4Sisx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/nLQh1Mqmhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/Cf1Thc6shr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/qcpbRZozDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/6Zz1ROlTSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/HGRbVHbODv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you thought about researching your ancestry?  Check out this introduction... http://t.co/qPFNyq0ac3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/w3YGXRlTiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/vbOuZUO0TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/9uw40iFnKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/sLr0l79JK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/nVlmvR9Mxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/4wx3nqSihN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/N261CbpPID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/zJXmZs5APs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/RUTQvqedVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/WD5ViyHLS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/cahHYnGrNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/Bvyp4Llw5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/aa4MMuBiUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/vn4dFEbDqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/HNyG4VOtj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/PksQIAWcff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/GV3tOQBr51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/6HY4qb9ZXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/RUTQvqedVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/ehW3r2AXHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/4n3EJSYARL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/j95HZDk5PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/OATSYwkEeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/yUG4QiyedM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/CaRGyzajmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/ctfVNrRGWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/4xLZhrvzw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6DxFWL9zSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/VvoNAMYW1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/iBK2ojZXFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/iCHF6MJkaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6DxFWL9zSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/ezDa7ktc4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/aOeyNLws6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/6WUNRaWneE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/lfcfqq45ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/gTiZDWOlSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/uPMwnwwJ0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/3XY6jbbKY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/CyA4J3K4gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/T0Kbt39UIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/SsaXebcBTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/q9vv33bQqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/uWUV5luUVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/1rNKW4Lils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/CSN4hRiLs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/CQs84Us2gY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/EDscCrheYz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>