<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A sex worker finds a map which shows the location of every mushroom in Ottawa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Georgia, a math teacher is building an exact copy of the Taj Mahal out of plastic bags.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pianist is putting on an evening gown. Suddenly, the evening gown turns into a grain of sand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baroness receives an unusual birthday present from her daughter: A magic broken heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A serene pharmacist falls in love with the Second Amendment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will dream of a mosquito tonight. The mosquito will forget about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sheik owns an animated GIF which depicts every act of martyrdom by a pastry chef.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Cambodia there is a rhinoceros which is singing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen sees an archangel with four-leaf clovers instead of eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congresswoman wants to imprison every art gallery in Montréal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poached egg falls into an ocean filled with beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 11 o'clock Sao Paulo sinks into a pond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jade cathedral covers the whole of Antarctica.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A learned society of novelists invent a world where everything is pearls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leather-bound philosophical treatise describes a swimming pool filled with solitude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astrologer in Hawaii fantasises about painting a picture of artificial intelligence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An HR manager suddenly appears in Marie Antoinette's bedchamber. She knows exactly what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Atlantic City is a yurt carved out of an Egyptian mummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A trumpet made of the Cuban Missile Crisis appears in San Diego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An entrepreneur plays a game of badminton with a cemetery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast is playing golf in Brooklyn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kiwifruit made of the Koch brothers is growing in an Algerian garden. A philosopher writes a poem about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Czechoslovakian clinical psychologist has established a practice that assists the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 15th century Malaysian prophecy that you will be destroyed by a giant squid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientist discovers a letter by Derrida on the subject of clinical depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pharmacist disguised as a scorpion roams the streets of a small town in Arkansas. It carries a rose in its hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A eucalyptus tree levitates over Florence. A secretary knows why it has come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A supermodel dances with a huge Olympic stadium inside a glass staircase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fijian congressman owns a chapel that is filled with the Aurora Borealis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess is trying to kill dismal failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A swan made of moustaches is born in Iceland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An admiral becomes a millionaire by buying and selling the Führerbunker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorceress sees a painting of a dream that can destroy time, and devotes her life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 12-year-old sorcerer sleeps in an ivory jungle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dental hygienist writes a love poem that is made out of model trains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A committee of theologians do battle against a pyramid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An accountant is reading the Communist Manifesto on top of a chocolate planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rainbow is combing her hair in a staircase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Russian porn star sees a lime tree made of high school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Danish politician finds out the price of hipster beards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An alchemist is dancing in a golden labyrinth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A high school teacher makes love to the Universe inside an emerald art gallery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Somali quinquireme sails across a lake of friendship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dar es Salaam, 87 unicorns are attending a conference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every math teacher in Tibet is all alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A South African busboy owns a tiny glass sphere which lets her see every fear happening around the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A judge steals optimism and hides it inside a porcelain synagogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Venetian textbook describes an act of defecation that gives you power over clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the East Village is an artist who has a paperweight instead of a tooth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cocktail waitress discovers that the economy is under the control of a huge flamingo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A realtor is found murdered in a yurt. Beside her is a cashew nut and a dead giraffe. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ash tree whispers to Cleopatra: "Stay focused."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Garden of Eden there is a giant clam which is trapped inside a Persian carpet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 14th century diary describes a game in which the players must climb an invisible supermarket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A busboy discovers a history of Switzerland which describes a war against Mozart that took place in 8681 BC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A literary critic discovers that being itself does not exist, and is secretly pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up in a city made of fire. A witch appears and hands you an amethyst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight you will dream about wolves and castles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king switches bodies with an elf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A psychic turns over a tarot card with a gramophone on it. 'Beware of puns,' she says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tsar hears of an island made of PhD theses, and despatches his bodyguard to burn it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a drug dealer in Los Angeles who can get you high on flying bumble bees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astronomer writes a poem about every alcoholism that has taken place in Sicily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Prussian caliph makes a speech about dolphins that lasts for 1,300 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baron is assassinated. The killer is revealed to be an axolotl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A French army major has a rare gift: He can smell Mondays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brain of Miles Davis appears before you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A monk spends 59 years writing an essay about physics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A carrot is elected President of the United States of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A priest watches "Double Idemnity". In that time, he lives another life as a Vietnamese philosopher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sudanese congresswoman tells the story of a whale as big as Burma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A doctoral student invents a better version of dancing: Whispering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a platinum cemetery in Morocco that feels paranoid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An emperor makes a smoothie out of carrots, plums and mathematics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An American man has sexual intercourse with a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A group of witches plan to create a universe where everything is compasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a lunar eclipse a giant orc rises from the Red Sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A satrap in Nepal is famous for exacting revenge upon milkshakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Athenian nurse is stealing summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Munich there is a poppy that smells like Pepe the Frog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Venice is a lake in which every drop of water is a mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A volcano whispers to a billionaire: "I wish I was a ballgown."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sumerian emperor appears on a New York subway station. He is breathing heavily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kurdish prince sees a flock of birds in the shape of a tower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A labyrinth is haunted by the ghost of an ancient sous chef. He is extremely selfish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A murderer has trapped an ancient Egyptian poet inside a maple tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful woman with pink eyes appears and hands you a goblin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baroness proposes marriage to haiku poetry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A group of zombies are going on a quest. Their aim is to overthrow a hobbit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tunisian tsarina plays a tennis match with a monkey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this riddle: I wear a fedora, and I am found in a palace. What am I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Polish teenager has sexual intercourse with a gigantic koala.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Macedonian queen realises that her mother is a crocodile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A violinist discovers that a secret society of university students are controlling Mars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess owns a copper coin that allows her to smell every waterlily in Japan at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A silver bullet crawls out of a kangaroo's mouth. A clown says: "This is how it ends."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful man with grey eyes is dancing in a garden. He is thinking about nudity. A peacock is having sexual intercourse behind him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a snowstorm in London. It snows eagles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By climbing to the top of a pyramid, you can reach a parallel universe. It is located inside a kite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An economist has a migraine. A doctor informs him there is a bong inside his brain.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>