<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart ive done a couple of teaching positions at schools in van so far. I go to this art store lots so we just got talking haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to the downtown Opus this Saturday from 2-4pm to see me teach; I'm demonstrating my techniques, as in this piece: http://t.co/08DGKebu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self portrait for a promotional poster, for an upcoming show at the Gam Gallery http://t.co/1Y4SIVH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cool to paint a lighthouse from the maritimes :)

https://t.co/k7eYQV6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm I like that 399 number of LIKEs...400 would be way cooler tho :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Xmas break has been full of eating, sleeping, snowboarding and drawing commissions. Now, how do I make this my EVERYDAY.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 cards bundled and ready for sale tomorrow, 11-6, at the Croatian cultural centre!! Come get a pack :) http://t.co/zg9kFz5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These sweet greeting cards will be for sale at the Last Chance Xmas Show @ Croatian Cultural Center this Sunday!! http://t.co/plA6B2l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting the bundling process :) gotta fold and sort 500 of these puppies :) http://t.co/uvXKmHBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got more greeting cards bundled The last batch sold out so fast, contact me for last minute holiday needs! 

http://t.co/dDzXvyE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kauf hey man thanks for following. i like your bio - ambitious man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started and finished two paintings this weekend. I'm tired. Xmas break time :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yea new greeting cards are almost ready from the printers. Already a backorder list :) lemme know if you need some! http://t.co/dDzXvyE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jY74SjqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandymlau no prob bob!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandymlau @CultureCrawl the show is actually a group show at the Gam Gallery on Hastings-Details to be posted on here as i get em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandymlau @CultureCrawl of course! where do u work in the city? my studio is down at powell and dunlevy. new group show in january comin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipSlagter nice advice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipSlagter oh man i dont plan to. got so deep into it so fast, and i just wanna see what happens in 2, 3, 5, 10 more years!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipSlagter sounds awesome - thats fantastic to hear. ive been at it 1.5 years haha! plenty to go :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandymlau hey there - i like the look of your background. and your descriptions. super cool :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great holiday show this weekend, a big success. Thanks everyone! Now time for holiday painting, boarding and relaxing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks everyone for your love and support at my show today - it was a great success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you're around tomorrow, come on by the studio for my holiday show and sale. Get some cards, prints, and tea/snacks! http://t.co/dKixwSmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ARTOF_DARKSIDE thanks for the follow..that tiger is pretty rad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipSlagter philip - i really dig these paintings man. how long you been doing this for? pretty great stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanGalleryRow thanks for the follow! i think you should look at my new city-inspired pieces http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm
im pretty stoked about thm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonjardine thank you for the follow! check out these sweet city pieces i just did: http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got the coolest holiday cards you'll find. You can order em directly from me and they are not expensive :)
http://t.co/dDzXvyE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These greeting cards with my art are goin fast - get em while you can - 9 bundles left :) http://t.co/dDzXvyE8 http://t.co/XEbblqvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished - This piece is tenatively titled "Circumduction" but I'm working on a cool different title related to... http://t.co/yzmRDort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey friends. This is a great shop and a great connection they are doing for the community. If you swing by, you... http://t.co/YCMRnBWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just posted a bunch of new paintings in my site's gallery:
http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i painted a vancouver bike! #art #vancouver more: http://t.co/XWF77qzi http://t.co/ILGqO55U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Snapshot #3 - Powell and Dunlevy http://t.co/NJlDDhCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Snapshot #2 - Homer and Cordova http://t.co/54goabpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Snapshot #1 - Cambie and Pender http://t.co/tdLQ2m3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The funnest part of this painting series is how I'm exaggerating colours, like on these recycle bins http://t.co/BCeF1JXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madalinezanni thanks for following - i love TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonjardine hey thanks for following me - i hope you are able to see some of my works as i post them! i like your photos that i see here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trevororourke thanks for the follow mate - i just finished a sweet painting a couple days ago: http://t.co/eTs4TkW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new piece! i cant wait to paint grafitti and stickers with old nintendo characters etc all over these recycle... http://t.co/2jKl4oc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New painting of an alley dumpster downtown Vancouver. 20" x 24", Ink and acrylic on wood panel http://t.co/smCZdFeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gisele Amantea's large poodle sculpture on Main St is part of a larger project: http://t.co/tbsJnUxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonShawPainting ya friend, so much fun - they are full of colour and character!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all the details about the recent! Golden Brush Live Painting event! On my blog!... http://t.co/0QKsMPdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man I love painting dumpsters! #art #Vancouver http://t.co/brdejvEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandymlau thanks! I'm really pleased with how it turned out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneak peek of newest city painting! its a dumpster! "awesome" photo cred: my iphone..ha http://t.co/pXwCQw1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthabbey thanks buddy! makin these for a sweet show at the end of feb at pendulum gallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you live in vancouver, do you recognize this building i just finished painting? http://t.co/9EJf4QqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@back2thebedroom thanks friend! it keeps me busy after work hours :) im certainly glad you enjoy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Painting!

"Nine-To-Five"
24" x 30" 
Ink and acrylic on wood panel http://t.co/Mxz4rjYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@back2thebedroom if you're curious, this new painting i just did is pretty rad: http://t.co/XWF77qzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@back2thebedroom hey friend thanks for following me and my art!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyingy ooooh nice yes! thats amazing..maybe i should consider something cool with my art and photo blending! intersting :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've recently put a bunch of new art on my fan page-you can see it here: http://t.co/zUngeNIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job friend! I'm moving in a month..just renting tho. Haha promoting me hey!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traceyferris damn girl that's awesome! Where is your
New pad? I think I saw you from the bus a few weeks back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In-progress #3. I think I will cluster these in a cool grid when complete for the next show, at the end of February. http://t.co/rMlGShJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In-progress #2. These are very fun to make because they are quicker and allow for more experimentation of colour etc http://t.co/Asq6j9OJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In - progress. Started a sub-series of little city paintings to accompany the larger works. A very handy 12" x... http://t.co/5g7yJ880]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennnney oh u should meet some of the vancouver attitude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart haha alright thats two votes for yes so far ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an idea of doing large, large scale paintings of pop culture cereal box mascots. Not sure if this idea is amazing, or absolutley absurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyingy damn thats crazy! whats the contest tho? i think im missing part of what youre explaining?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a brief article about me and Jennifer in today's Vancouver 24 newspaper :) http://t.co/oWvH3SIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new painting I'm hoping to finish up in the next couple of days. This is how it looks before highlights... http://t.co/aNLhzYId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm workin on a painting at the gam gallery today. 110 east Hastings, til 5pm or so, come say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we won :) http://t.co/YPYWGIC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[action shot from the art battle last night :) http://t.co/VixalLN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers and thanks to everyone who attended golden brush tonight! Was awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awaiting the winners' announcements. Look at the keen focus! http://t.co/YlqNURHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The event was well attended! Thanks to all for
Joining! http://t.co/OLdqpqhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and Jennifer's set up for tonight's painting competition at the Vancouver urban winery http://t.co/SJtdqQFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come see a great show this Saturday at the Gam Gallery, 110 E. Hastings! I'll be hanging out at the gallery to show you around! We can chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicDarling do you know of any cool art blogs/twitter folk/etc that i can hit up by chance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicDarling hey thanks for the follow! i miss TO. I'd love to go there and do a show with my paintings :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyingy thanks for the follow mate, if you are into cool paintings, thats what i do; i just finished a sweet new one: http://t.co/XWF77qzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrutsGallery ya struts!! see you in may! (reunion weekend)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out this sweet group show that five friends and i are hosting at the gam gallery, opening this friday night! http://t.co/1qZPEaL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a drawing of a bike. http://t.co/XWF77qzi http://t.co/JIp80zDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a drawing of a bike. http://t.co/XWF77qzi http://t.co/YnqKhb1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very pleased with this new piece.

Dyadic
24" x 36"
ink and acrylic on canvas http://t.co/58PWpgqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - Buzz buzz buzz :)

opening one week from today at the Gam Gallery guys! http://t.co/IUMwlgSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pendulum gets my vote as one of the best restaurants in Vancouver: http://t.co/dWwPs7Nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had a meeting for next month's show at the Pendulum Gallery. Wow, its gonna be so fantastic! Amazing space, stoked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted 8 portraits and tell the story about who they are: http://t.co/HlK5VPZL5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My insights into why I find Turkey Vultures such an amazing subject:... http://t.co/HcR8N7wO6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really really stoked for this Friday's reception of our show, City:Life. I'm really excited to see whoever... http://t.co/5ysgnLdKny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm doing the make-it show in April, a great venue for offering reproduction prints like this one! http://t.co/V1XljyKX9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the show at the Pendulum Gallery looks so great, I went today and creeped its onlookers. View work here: http://t.co/MLQ11m7g26 #art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Reasons Why Painting A Dumpster Is So Cool:... http://t.co/nevOO6paKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/wOuF6Q7rzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to see what happens when I animate my drawings, here is a write up about it (and video!)... http://t.co/Yt776b9DgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's blog post focuses on the Sun Tower, the subject of one of my latest paintings: http://t.co/ggV0JbYk8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a step-by-step photo-story of how I created my latest painting, Enumerative. Lots of close up detail photos. http://t.co/n3L4WPGYSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our show at the gallery
Is hung and you can view it! Opening party is march 8 :) http://t.co/9xM1M01wQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is eighth Urban Snapshot piece. Powell and Jackson. The chains and lock are so prevalent in that... http://t.co/k2b1SeOTSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is another from my "Urban Snapshots" mini series. I love the cool wires for the trolley buses in this city.... http://t.co/ujmtAM8Hi7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>