<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Senior Scrum Master: About the position Prudential’s Enabling Solutions team is seeking a Senior Scrum Master leveraging Agile methodologies and thinking across business and technology initiatives. The person… https://t.co/gZVTYvKGew #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II: Job TitleScrum Master II – ID:30847 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsJira, SCrum Master, Agile/SCRUM LocationIrving, TX Date Posted01/24/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global… https://t.co/p8HgCL6G2o #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software QA Engineer: Summary:The Principal Software QA Engineer will be responsible for developing and lead test strategies and automation for NSC’s Software platform and IoT products. This person will… https://t.co/g6xTqFBbJb #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, Apple face EU law on business practices: (Reuters) - Online platforms such as Google , Apple and Amazon face new European Union rules on their commercial practices with smaller businesses that use their services, as… https://t.co/4MmJom6WIF #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ZeVaFBNZaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior EA Modeler/Developer: Supports the development, configuration, testing and deployment and integration of PeopleSoft/OIAM Application Security for the IPPS-A project. Provides support for systems development… https://t.co/FAH757g7AN #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer, Accurate Background: QA Automation Engineer will ensure the delivery of world-class high-quality applications for the various Accurate Background platforms. You will be triaging bug reports,… https://t.co/wQOz8Ullbp #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/83uTLF3EoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer: Test Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python… https://t.co/91d7voGCpP #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IT #hiring Number One IT Job site in the US: ☆ Entrepreneur Magazine Feature 🔵 https://t.co/STP6SjQtvT 🔵 as Most Popular Tech Job Site ☆ https://t.co/A52UPb2wg2 #recruiting #Jobs #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/5OFiksvmLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager/Scrum Master: Do you want to use your superpowers to help save the lives of thousands of homeless pets each month? Can you help us manage workflows and communication on projects to insure… https://t.co/cjLrouEKqa #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom ends bid for Qualcomm after President Trump nixes deal: (Reuters) - Singapore-based Broadcom Ltd withdrew its $117 billion bid to acquire Qualcomm Inc on Wednesday, two days after U.S. President Donald Trump blocked the… https://t.co/jUMe29bAUs #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/nLsBQkaxtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Full Stack PHP Developer: Vynyl delivers high-fidelity software, design, and product solutions for clients across a wide spectrum of industries and needs. Recent projects include applications that: power the #1… https://t.co/nzdfSCNxGN #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ygJKtm7wGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: Web Developer Equus Software, a rapidly growing technology company, needs passionate web developers for the AssignmentPro software product development team in Denver, Colorado. We are looking… https://t.co/BL0yszhmBq #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Application Developer: * Design, Develop, and Test Software applications built with *******, C#, MS SQL SERVER and front end frameworks such as Knockout JS or Angular JS. * Production Support for… https://t.co/j1Wffot1wk #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: We’re seeking a Front End Developer with full stack aspirations who will help us transform the education technology landscape. Our team is building the world’s leading student success software… https://t.co/tuWhEZ6xQz #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest… https://t.co/20eiNtYZ5f #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese investors want relaxed rules for tech IPOs: exchange: SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Most Chinese investors expect regulators to relax rules on initial public offerings (IPOs) by technology companies, and would like to invest in… https://t.co/9psFVE9LED #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ymKPpHoO9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master… https://t.co/viqzLEPw0O #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: Join our Big Data Team and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! KEY… https://t.co/m0QbrUryKc #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: As part of the TPGSI business team, Business Analyst (BA) will elicit and document business and technical requirements in support of TP strategic objective to design a new eligibility and… https://t.co/3flOgEVppS #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: JOB REQUISITION Digital Project Manager LOCATION SAN RAMON JOB DESCRIPTION Robert Half is seeking a contract Digital Project Manager to join the creative team to work on new creative… https://t.co/9crF71tIn2 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IT #hiring Best IT Jobs Posted Daily: The Best jobs are on 👉 https://t.co/STP6SjQtvT 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/bWpYu71qYZ #recruiting #Jobs #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/BeTGFq8sCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Administrator (SW Asset Mgmt): Job TitleServiceNow Administrator (SW Asset Mgmt) – ID:30731 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsServiceNow, SACM (Service Asset and Configuration Management)… https://t.co/ZKqbb1z5FL #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge rejects U.S. demand to exclude AT&amp;T argument in Time Warner merger trial: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - AT&amp;T Inc can cite a voluntary commitment not to withhold content in licensing talks as a key part of its defense when an… https://t.co/ikXvyp7AkA #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/epkbTChX5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chubb Associate – IT Project Manager: Chubb is the worlds largest publicly traded property and casualty insurer. With operations in 54 countries, Chubb provides commercial and personal property and casualty… https://t.co/dWUAQv1zQu #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Software Engineer: eOriginal eOriginal Java Developer – Software Engineer Baltimore, MD 21201 Java Developer – Financial Software Engineer SUMMARY OF POSITION eOriginal is a financial software firm… https://t.co/HjgRYz55zS #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers… https://t.co/NaAN1ZY3S8 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: Scrum master philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 02/28/18, Posted Date – 02/28/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2COverview Required Skills Set: Years of Experience: 5+ years… https://t.co/TIoyEiCLSa #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F-22 Pilot Training Software Engineer, Junior: Are you interested in learning to fly an F-22 while developing and maintaining F-22 Pilot Training Software used to train F-22 fighter pilots? The F-22 Vehicle… https://t.co/buDZB03y3e #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer, Principal: Req ID 91987BR Business Title CNO Developer, Principal Group MCIS Location USA COLORADO Aurora Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is… https://t.co/VbORIWy0H9 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: G20 financial heads to urge crypto-asset monitoring to safeguard financial stability: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - The world's financial leaders will call on international standard-setting bodies on March 20 for stronger… https://t.co/DbEibH9yrU #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/0im24fG9rE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Lead: Job Description Summary: CACI National and Cyber Solutions is looking for an experienced, innovative, and eager Software Engineer to help lead a team of developers employing modern,… https://t.co/wVKH7F1Udq #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Mid-level: Primary Objective: The Software Process Engineer will plan, coordinate, and provide process support for software development, operations, and maintenance activities to all El Segundo… https://t.co/c1cMyLbcAs #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, .NET Developer: Do you have the right stuff? Gullview Technologies is an exciting new and rapidly growing technology company focused on taking on the most vital and challenging business and technical… https://t.co/RhO2rMYWuK #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What Youll Get to Do: In this role, the ideal candidate can analyze user requirements to derive software design and performance requirements. While designing and coding new… https://t.co/CfaVBRbv8j #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Intern: Company Introduction RobustWealth [*************************************************************************************************** is a fast-paced wealth management company that is changing… https://t.co/Pd99WH3Usw #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IT #hiring Seeking IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/STP6SjQtvT 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/qafmjHjNbo #recruiting #Jobs #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/JRhdap0PTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Scrum Master – Engineer: Client Reference Code: 214149 Job Scope: The Technical Scrum Master – Engineer is is responsible solutions architecture, development, configuration management, and deployment… https://t.co/iieahfcsIA #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google brings free WiFi to Mexico, first stop in Latin America: MEXICO CITY (Reuters) - Alphabet's Google said on Tuesday that it will launch a network of free Wi-Fi hotspots across Mexico, part of the search giant's effort to… https://t.co/0shceKD9Eh #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/L4ytO1YjY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: InfosysIVS-Financial Services- Technical Test Lead Automation Testing Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/sEoAfVDENn #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Virginia beach, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 02/22/18, Posted Date – 02/22/18 Primary SkillsJIRA,Agile/Scrum,Agile craft, ConfluenceTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview Responsibilities:… https://t.co/5skShL8GEe #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Agile Coach: AgileTrailblazers is seeking an individual who is passionate about agility in the software delivery process. We are looking for an experienced agilist who has played many roles on agile team as… https://t.co/L3FRysmNol #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Android: As an Android-focused software engineer at Grio youll be focused on building Android applications using the latest SDKs and industry best practices. You will be able to work on a… https://t.co/JWNFRU93Yd #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect: We are a small team of passionate problem solvers working to radically change how ambitious organizations and federal agencies build software. We think differently and have developed… https://t.co/X4vUOWtNak #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple, Google see reputation of corporate brands tumble in survey: (Reuters) - Apple Inc and Alphabet Inc's Google corporate brands dropped in an annual survey while https://t.co/uhPpyoOsfT Inc maintained the top spot for the… https://t.co/3wgylpzMJq #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/7l9Ba83Izy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers… https://t.co/SgKs0gOZmm #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cassandra DBA: We practice Agile/Scrum methodology and we program in a variety of languages such as Python, C/C++, &amp; Java. We are building a large scale and high-performance cloud based networking service platform… https://t.co/Rgyw0T1cbg #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Performance Engineering: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house… https://t.co/r309Qv6wSV #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director – IT Project Management: DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT FULL TIME PERMANENT POSITION – No H1B LOCATION: ATLANTA, GA SALARY: up to $110k/yr DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT SUMMARY This position is… https://t.co/7jxEndVqy2 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared (Req# 00015): JUNIOR JAVA API DEVELOPER (JAVA, REST API, JS) Title: Junior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms:… https://t.co/t9tiHITFf9 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IT #hiring LOOK &gt;&gt; IT Jobs: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/STP6SjQtvT 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/9lOFWVpHwf #recruiting #Jobs #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/l0cx3HHIqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REV – COMPUTER PROGRAMMER ANALYST II: REV – COMPUTER PROGRAMMER ANALYST II – ******** View Profile State of Florida – Home – About Us – Agency – Agency for Health Care Administration – Agency for Persons with… https://t.co/vymjlrj3TU #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple to buy digital magazine service Texture: (Reuters) - Apple Inc will buy the digital service Texture, which gives users access to articles from magazines published by various companies for a monthly subscription fee, the… https://t.co/94Rds8k5Jr #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/t4VnHd1iRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Architect (SAP S/4 HANA – Logistics / Oil Gas) – SAP Innovative Business Solution Job: Date: Mar 4, 2018 Location: Newtown Square, PA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area:… https://t.co/hpFPvwSpAK #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Developer: At Ad Hoc we build government digital services that are fast, efficient, and usable by everyone. Ad Hoc brings small teams of highly skilled professionals from the private sector to build… https://t.co/Q4EQjgvvXx #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Technology Lead US DevOps Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute… https://t.co/amjkZB5eK7 #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Developing great software takes more than just writing code. It takes a cohesive team, passionate about developing elegant products that scale exponentially in an extremely short time-frame. A… https://t.co/yw178NKB0c #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – US IT SOLUTIONS: Duration: 12-24 Months Strong communication skills are important as well as some experience with helping to implement a Scrum environment. Qualifications * 7+ years of experience… https://t.co/z9Z0hINREM #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber re-enters Barcelona with professional driver service: LONDON (Reuters) - Uber is seeking a second chance in Barcelona three years after it was forced to shut down in the face of taxi driver protests by introducing a fully… https://t.co/UQaUU7aolK #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Co4EEm4I94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Remote: SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Full time permanent position US Citizens, Permanent Residence, or TN1 Visas only SALARY: $95k + 10% Bonus LOCATION: Lafayette,CO or Portland OR… https://t.co/wdE2SXUsyf #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Coach: Job TitleScrum Master/Coach – ID:31104 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFirst level Scrum Master certification (CSM, PSM I) LocationPlan0, TX Date Posted02/26/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE… https://t.co/IVGfqLniwO #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Full time permanent position US Citizens, Permanent Residence, or TN1 Visas only SALARY: $95k + 10% Bonus LOCATION: Lafayette,CO or Lake Oswego OR preferred, but… https://t.co/J1aYGYDb4i #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Ruby on Rails Engineer: Looking for a challenging job with opportunity for growth? Do you like to find ways to improve, teach and inspire to achieve goals? Come build a career at The RealReal a successful,… https://t.co/AvKoRFqkJs #scrum #scrummaster #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java Stack Technologies: Transforming the future of healthcare isn’t something we take lightly. It takes teams of the best and the brightest, working together to make an impact. As one of the largest healthcare technology companies in… https://t.co/lUtLWX7X2x https://t.co/YT1hM2p9IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4 – Business Analyst: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center… https://t.co/nZme9bUo4b https://t.co/uGcmve3phK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4 – Business Analyst: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center… https://t.co/Q4wvdQPcNK https://t.co/LLy2EljArE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Consultant – Custom Application Development: Neudesic is currently seeking a Senior DevOps Engineer, who will participate in Requirements Analysis; identify solutions working with Architects, design Applications based on Systems Requirements… https://t.co/ryQMvdfY3c https://t.co/d2oZA5qBEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Software Engineer III Location Simi Valley, CA Employment type Regular – Full Time ID 73 Apply Now Who We Are Based in California, AeroVironment (AVAV) is a global leader in unmanned aircraft systems, tactical missile systems and… https://t.co/rO1Tpayhgh https://t.co/pFEIPAD6Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Lead / Manager: 108094BR Software Project Lead / Manager CA – Goleta 108094BR Job Description:  Candidate will serve as a senior software project lead / manager of software development, software integration, and software testing phases… https://t.co/d8VuZUUzjX https://t.co/InUdZNiE0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Application Security Engineer Ref No.: 18-00501 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/20/2018 Passionate about Application Security with 3 years of experience with any combination… https://t.co/XlPdLiopHZ https://t.co/xwM05lgaed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Scrum Master: Project Manager / Scrum Master Department Technology Services – Corporate Applications Job Description Everest Global Services, a member of Everest Re Group, Ltd, has an opportunity available for a Project Manager/Scrum… https://t.co/1g4dIvITwU https://t.co/OXwjOiNm2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Tester (REMOTE): QA Tester (REMOTE) ================== Req #: ******Location: Remote (Any State), VA USJob Category: Engineering and Technical SupportSecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI serves the U.S.… https://t.co/TdmrzlzJJN https://t.co/IxO0hyiiNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Agile Coach: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/10/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at… https://t.co/NMub77SFUR https://t.co/zHgixM35a5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal SACM Product Owner/Scrum Master: Date: Apr 11, 2018 Location: Southlake, TX, US Company: Sabre Req ID: 35321 Job Family: Information Technology/Software Development Sabre is the global leader in innovative technology that leads the travel… https://t.co/GYTvU68K9q https://t.co/oGnRnFJhl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Supreme Court weighs South Dakota e-commerce sale tax fight: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Supreme Court on Tuesday will consider whether to let states force out-of-state online retailers to collect sales taxes on purchases in a fight potentially… https://t.co/GhgBGLJCry https://t.co/lDqbwY6rv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Scrum Master Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with internationally recognized brands such as… https://t.co/mtBsnnVQQJ https://t.co/d8NuvXSns9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering or of study. 5 years work experience as a Java developer, implementing test data solutions. Minimum 3 years work experience developing solutions in a environment, e.g. AWS. Full… https://t.co/jIBQqBbFGS https://t.co/HJgDmCLBGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Lead – Integration and Technology: Senior Technical Lead – Integration and Technology What makes us Qlik We’re motivated to help people make discoveries in data, share insights, make decisions and act with confidence. Making a… https://t.co/AU5uy7KiIN https://t.co/taSUwDEIQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Developer – Mobile/.NET: PURPOSE AND SCOPE: Participates in all areas of the project lifecycle, including analysis, design, development, implementation, support and enhancement. Contributes to functionality and process design for… https://t.co/DIWv3n9hcp https://t.co/G8jPdrw0t3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Quality &amp; Speech Analytics: Client Reference Code: 216577-2Quality and VOC Team Overview:Want to work on a team focused on transforming Quality and Customer Experience across the enterprise? Join a team that is transforming the way we… https://t.co/xjgkscN2zm https://t.co/ZeloxxI7MK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adv FS- Senior Agile Scrum Master (SAFe)- Sr. Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/NWg1hiAjsL https://t.co/9wT4hOysyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Engineer, IdentityNow (Austin, TX HQ): This position is based at our Austin, TX HQ Sr. UI Engineer – IdentityNow (SaaS Product Team) SailPoint is seeking a Sr. UI Engineer to join our engineering team in designing and implementing our cloud… https://t.co/ZahpN9AUL5 https://t.co/GPn7DSknN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: O3 World is seeking a Full Stack Developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************** You will work with some of the… https://t.co/5HW4b2dZ0M https://t.co/Hi4b1m8cH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Level 1: The web developer is responsible for developing frontend and backend code for a variety of web based applications including business systems, mission systems, and warfighter support systems. Applications are written in a variety… https://t.co/uvtdWEXp99 https://t.co/l4WUWoclly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development, Lead – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 216286 Who We Are: Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed… https://t.co/TuMdPGp7IW https://t.co/sZRDSLgyMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Engineer: Description:JOB DESCRIPTION:   An Identity &amp; Access Management (IdAM) program is seeking a client integration team member in support of a mission critical enterprise system. Roles and Responsibilities:   Apply program IdAM… https://t.co/icQ3avIc8D https://t.co/hqda8DkyzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer, Software – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 215676 Who We Are:Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed… https://t.co/vAmwaHlcRK https://t.co/rJAgTN9wZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Level 2: The web developer is responsible for developing frontend and backend code for a variety of web based applications including business systems, mission systems, and warfighter support systems. Applications are written in a variety… https://t.co/SEQvL3bbe7 https://t.co/lwYRZ6SkdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’ lives. We’ll help you… https://t.co/A8RihiEVsK https://t.co/AcCCluqlj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Beaverton, OR Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/1/2018 Job Description Job Title: Senior Android Developer Duration: 6-12 months Contract… https://t.co/DhXIPsWp0L https://t.co/Y5kT6a8ouo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Mid-level Software Developer in Test About us INVIDI Technologies Corporation develops products and services for addressable television advertising. Our… https://t.co/2YgkDT3804 https://t.co/g3pizVtXyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Outcomes: About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people to advance the… https://t.co/o1amTF6vYW https://t.co/4nQ4kp1K0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: 7900 Westpark Drive (12131), United States of America, Tysons, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One… https://t.co/K84cmfpc9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Team Lead – 15503: Software Engineer Team Lead Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company)Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants… https://t.co/mesh7YJVm4 https://t.co/QSdE1MYt8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems Engineer 5: If you are the sort of person who loves a challenge and likes to be involved in serious organizational and software change — Then what is happening in the Cyber and Intelligence Mission Solutions Division is the place for you.… https://t.co/YZS8PyIxgH https://t.co/g2YNv2m8qC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys EAISAPI Technology Lead Mulesoft Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/V6UmK2o6z3 https://t.co/TBGofwwQ1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java / AWS Developer: Job Description Responsible for creating, extending, and maintaining the connection software platform as new features are expanded to extend our offerings to clients. Heavy emphasis on Java 7 or 8 application/webservices… https://t.co/97FfOWcOXI https://t.co/qltkiCUpnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Ruby on Rails Developer: Experienced Ruby on Rails Developer at Gartner Skip Navigation Menu – Career Opportunities – Why Gartner – Life at Gartner – Campus Search Keyword CategoryCategoryAccount ExecutiveAdministrativeClient… https://t.co/2InAJcQh90 https://t.co/AK9M3D0tIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager II-PMO Services: Job Description Employee Perks Why You Will Love Being Part of the Navy Federal Team: *Competitive compensation with opportunities for annual raises, promotions, and bonus potential *Best-in-Class Benefits! (7% 401k… https://t.co/qxyjJFb5gl https://t.co/22oC8l3Cir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (Job Number:435242) Description: Scrum Master Job Description SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. You will work in a highly collaborative and agile… https://t.co/Pi87DbouZi https://t.co/Jl0hnWS7VD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Engineer: Description: JOB DESCRIPTION:   An Identity &amp; Access Management (IdAM) program is seeking a client integration team member in support of a mission critical enterprise system. Roles and Responsibilities:   Apply program IdAM… https://t.co/FenrqI3LHp https://t.co/LUTjqgMreu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>