<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst who would be the most unlikely Survivor to return as a fav in a future season? #Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst Phillip is the man but Cochran has it this year! #survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 SURVIVOR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @raymondraws heinous attack!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alannamitch tell you the leafs won 5-1 tonight boooooooooom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: Take note Toronto, why cheering for a bad team is oddly therapeutic. http://t.co/JcL8zQ18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws he doesn't talk in the game which is stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws tap tap tap tap tap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald I really like people who can appreciate real music like you. Classical music and film scores are the real deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald listen to Malcolm's journey on YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald I want The Lost World one but they discontinued it and its like a million dollars on Ebay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald that's fucking amazing, I bought the score by John Williams at HMV a couple months ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRock: If you don't do it - someone else will. 

AM training starts now.. 

#NoMoreSleepLetsRoll #JustBringIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws welcome to the dark side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JRsBBQ: “@rogerrdunn: @JRsBBQ http://t.co/lew2YIyj
SO young...@tonyschiavone24 &amp; me. Damn good team. Fun days. @WWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alannamitch walk outside for a bit, that's a workout in itself 😛]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@handley_9 lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to build a rink outside? #Snowday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRock: Training - don't over think it.

Keep it instinctual, intense &amp; dirty. 

#GripColdSteel #PushUrPace http://t.co/EWyzYZqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beareum  http://t.co/kOZywnxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSN_Sports @CraigJButton Go Leafs Go https://t.co/n6pMAsf9Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Btw started listening to your podcast where you discuss your debut. Great stuff, your a legend #Countdowntothemillenium #Jericho #TalkisJericho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retro @IAmJericho 2003ish? https://t.co/Z5MuTG7Omn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapFriendly This is so sad RIP Emery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle You glitched]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @elliottbaron @Raymondraws Niko got me https://t.co/KDJFfQldgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @elliottbaron @Raymondraws Lol that was good not gonna lie 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayesTSN What If he’s pretending and making content for #Overdrive1050 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucianKujaku @Raymondraws @NikoKetsilis No he tries to get inside of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk @GoldenKnights @LDAngeli #GoLeafsGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bhaber44 @theScoreNHL I'm a leaf fan and this made me laugh pretty good, good job lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 I thought it would be good too i haven't seen it but everyone is popping bout how garbage it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReneeYoungWWE do you ever come back to Toronto to visit The Score family?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegamechasers do you watch survivor billy its dope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme nooooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst @sarahcourteisme prob why there wasn't any Canadians on the show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme sickkk 😊 no spoilers I'm watching on like 20 min delay 😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @DanSlott wow is it actually? Damn I gotta keep an eye out for it..the baywatch one comes out tomorrow too 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 DT has some good places too on Spadina! Take care boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregCapullo I'm lovin it Greg, not too sure about early reviews for BvS tho.. Gonna have to watch for myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveaustinBSR I bumped into you a few times over the years at hotels bars etc. always regretted saying hi, always busy you were. Big fan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho Jays Clinched!!! Thought you should know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk My Jays will see you guys in the World Series!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York City here I come!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 damn right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon hoppin on a quick bus from Toronto to New York tomorrow! Cant believe I'm going to my 8th Mania! Hope to see you there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chellatamby91 @rogerrdunn @tripleh ill give it to you tho hunter, you sold me on a shirt of yours. That's one more than Henry will ever get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 @rogerrdunn @tripleh this time it's personal... For the 10th time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 @rogerrdunn @tripleh well you'll prob get your wish cuz it's predictable. Well speaking of predictable it could be Metallica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TripleH I'm tired of your Motörhead music. You should come out with your 2000 theme at Mania that would be sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon hey Steph, big fan of the business can't wait till Mania Sunday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bozie42: Good luck to the Blue Jays as they start their season tonight!!! #dowork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSTOTips I just tried, it didn't seem to correct the problem :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tstotips I also use my IPad 2 if it matters. Thank you for replying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSTOTips I'm on apple. I have a 4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSTOTips hello Iv noticed I'm not getting the conformity bonus for my premium items. Do you know if this is a common issue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HulkHogan long time fan! Can I get a retweet brother?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 that's nice of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 what did you do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks lol nuff said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 jeez lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 upgrade your gigs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 I just missed it cuz my mom was like yo put on wheel of fortune for the first half hour... -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just won a 100$ Tim's card!!!!!! #RollUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 Ian Fleming books. Loooooooook em up yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenWalker7 your a Yankee now. Isn't Timmy's a forbidden sacred beverage there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alana_macdonald sounds exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goin to meet Goldberg for first time today 💪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws your a muppet to Gary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmorra Kaaaaaaaaaaaaaaadri!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws @unkleko do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 good luck son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonJ1606 @raymondraws @chellatamby91 rubbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws @chellatamby91 don't lie I saw you guys running glitter on each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 @raymondraws you both love Gary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasinaysmith it was yesterday! I dealt with one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron @raymondraws @unkleko @nikoketsilis @eddievalentim more like hank scorpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws @elliottbaron @unkleko @nikoketsilis @eddievalentim I don't agree with this. You should all be playing SIMPSONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaron thanks buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsmailMadani thanks buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanessa_orz thank you 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who does laundry on their birthday? This guy does 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 @rogerrdunn @raymondraws yup pretty much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausduh whoa whoa whoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bozie42 fuck those jobbers you guys rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RIP #PaulBearer Another legend lost...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao see ya later Couver get the fuckk outtttta here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: Patrick Marleau completes the sweep! The Sharks move on while the Canucks head home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnMichaels @TheEpilepsyGuy Go Leafs Go!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnMichaels do you have a man-cave with all your wrestling stuff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HacksawJDuggan what would you rather eat for breakfast? Scrambled Cena or Rock over easy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik he has nothing on Cosby. Crosby is a crybaby little bitch sheikie baby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik I hope your watching Leafs Playoff hockey tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Leafs Go!!!! #AlmostTime #Leafs #Playoffhackey @MapleLeafs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerrdunn @Raymondraws @Chellatamby91 fuck you guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerrdunn @Raymondraws @Chellatamby91 lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis Marvel and you win this round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron Man 3 IMAX was legit]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>