<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_DearParents_: Raise your child's awareness of the mass media's efforts to brainwash citizens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A society of sheep must in time beget a government of wolves. ~Bertrand de Jouvenel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who suppress freedom always do so in the name of law and order. ~John V. Lindsay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sin of silence when they should protest makes cowards of men. ~Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything in a revolutionary is wholly absorbed in the single thought and the single passion for revolution. ~Nechaev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Systematic Corruption: bailing out the bondholders even though they hold the paper to our national debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machines were, it may be said, the weapon employed by the capitalists to quell the revolt of specialized labor. ~Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the freedom of speech is taken away then dumb and silent we may be led, like sheep to the slaughter. ~George Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves. ~Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MARTlNLUTHERK: It is time for parents to put away the Disney consumer ethic, in favor of political resistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are right you cannot be too radical; when you are wrong, you cannot be too conservative. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must learn to live together as brothers or perish together as fools. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reasons2BLazy: The less productive you are for your capitalist employer the more revolutionary you will become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Injustice anywhere is a threat to justice everywhere. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RebellingSlave: I will stand up to those who crush the bones of my fellow workers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the white man's brother, not his brother-in-law. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sigymund_Freud: Psychology must be used to make the populace fearless and unafraid of confronting the enemy class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I refuse to accept the view that mankind is so tragically bound to the starless midnight of racism and war. ~ MLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look to a day when people will not be judged by the color of their skin, but by the content of their character. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_RevoIution: I am the spirit of the masses, I am the desire to tear down the psychological barrier erected by the counterrevolutiona…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human salvation lies in the hands of the creatively maladjusted. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is never voluntarily given by the oppressor; it must be demanded by the oppressed. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JFKennedys: Do not empower the fascist business class by voting for the politicians in their pockets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A riot is the language of the unheard. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A right delayed is a right denied. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Che___Guevara_: Third world citizens must demand governments that serve their citizens, instead of serving Wall Street interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who won't die for something is not fit to live. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man can't ride your back unless it's bent. ~Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fred__Nietzsche: Nihilism must direct the masses towards collective action; otherwise it will too be used and exploited by the enemy cl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workers of the world unite; you have nothing to lose but your chains. ~Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rich will do anything for the poor but get off their backs. ~Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2GetFired: Send your boss an accidental text that says 'I think I know who the office snitch is.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If voting changed anything, they'd make it illegal. ~Emma Goldman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No real social change has ever been brought about without a revolution... revolution is thought carried into action. ~Emma Goldman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: The Profit Margin: a measure of how far the corporation can squeeze profits out of the consumer and its employees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can kill a revolutionary but you can never kill the revolution. ~Fred Hampton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can jail a Revolutionary, but you can't jail the Revolution. ~Huey Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spirit of revolution will not die while the hearts of workers continue to beat. ~Ernst Toller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to support a revolution is to make your own. ~Abbie Hoffman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Blacks: a racist term, is it so hard to say African-American you racist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in revolution. ~Mary Harris Jones (Mother Jones)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The job of the writer is to make revolution irresistible. ~Toni Cade Bambara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TextsToMyBoss: Who is more of an idiot, the boss or the people trying to become a boss? They're all fucking morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolution begins with the self, in the self. ~Toni Cade Bambara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have not made the Revolution, the Revolution has made us. ~Georg Buchner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Andy_WarhoI: The world needs artwork which shows how the mass media is nothing more than propaganda beamed at the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever finishes a revolution only halfway, digs his own grave. ~Georg Buchner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A revolution is an act of violence whereby one class shatters the authority of another. ~James MacGregor Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Huey_PNewton: The people are ready to seize power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great revolution in just one single individual will help achieve a change in the destiny of a society. ~Daisaku Ikeda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every revolution has its counterrevolution - that is a sign the revolution is for real. ~C. Wright Mills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All civilization has from time to time become a thin crust over a volcano of revolution. ~Henry Ellis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main object of a revolution is the liberation of man... ~ Jean Genet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoIIstonecraft: The revolutionary girl sees plastic surgery as a method used to destroy the very authenticity of womankind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise yourself to live your life as a revolution and not just a process of evolution. ~Anthony J. D'Angelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love without role, without power plays, is revolution. ~Rita Mae Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WealthyFacts: In a survey of the world's billionaires 72% said world hunger is 'not really a problem'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We used to think that revolutions are the cause of change. It is the other way around: change prepares the ground for revolution. ~Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know the theory and methods of revolution, you must take part in revolution. ~Mao Tse-Tung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RebellingSlave: I will not spend my energy on mindless mass media entertainments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A revolution is not a dinner party, or writing an essay, or painting a picture, or doing embroidery. ~Mao Tse-Tung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seed of revolution is repression. ~Woodrow Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: 20 percent of the population in the developed nations were reported to consume 86 percent of the world's goods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No thieves, no traitors, no interventionists! This time the revolution is for real! ~Fidel Castro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A revolution is not a bed of roses. ~Fidel Castro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Reality Television Shows: False reality, a real reality television show would be a show about families being foreclose…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When dictatorship is a fact, revolution becomes a right. ~ Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot make a revolution with silk gloves. ~ Joseph Stalin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DearDrugAddicts: Drugs make you feel too paranoid to resist the power-structure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time there's a revolution, it comes from somebody reading a book about revolution. ~Mike Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who do not move, do not notice their chains. ~Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dear__Teenagers: Your teachers are neither wise nor brilliant. They're paid by capitalist institutions to mold you into careerist slave…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The working classes in every country only learn to fight in the course of their struggles.~Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The masses are the decisive element, they are the rock on which the final victory of the revolution will be built. ~Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Things_U_Need: Subversive behaviors, they will move your mind away from conformity towards the subversion of capitalist systems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital is an historical necessity, but, so too, its grave digger, the socialist proletariat. ~Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is always the freedom of dissenters.~Rosa Luxemburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to crush the bourgeoisie is to grind them between the millstones of taxation and inflation.~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government is tottering. We must deal it the death blow an any cost. To delay action is the same as death.~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Sarah Palin: a woman who had managed to turn herself into the hero of the ignorant, the simple minded, the self-righte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to destroy the capitalist system is to debauch the currency.~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes - history needs a push.~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticalLetter: Dear Religious Leaders: Stop using religion to brainwash the people in the interests of the ruling class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom in capitalist society always remains about the same as it was in ancient Greek republics: Freedom for slave owners. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascism is capitalism in decay. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Babe__Ruth: The populace must reject all team (corporate) branding as a mere attempt to stamp the populace with mindless logos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can a nation be free if it oppresses other nations? It cannot. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The privileged class can never be overturned peacefully. - Johann Most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YgamblingSucks: Casinos are places where workers give back their hard-earned incomes to the corporate class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who make peaceful revolution impossible will make violent revolution inevitable. -JFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Above all, what socialist, without flushing with shame, maintains he is not a revolutionary? We say: none! ~ Johann Most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shocking__Facts: 3000 Wal-Mart workers are fired every year for as much as complaining to other workers about the low pay and lack of b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free speech is the whole thing, the whole ball game. Free speech is life itself. ~SalmanRushdie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me liberty or give me death. - Patrick Henry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How strangely will the Tools of a Tyrant pervert the plain Meaning of Words! - Samuel Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital is dead labor, which, vampire-like, lives only by sucking living labor, and lives the more, the more labor it sucks. - Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Who2Unfollow: Unfollow verified bloggers, why would you follow idiots who waste their writing skills on products and product reviews?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You show me a capitalist, and I'll show you a bloodsucker. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't separate peace from freedom because no one can be at peace unless he has his freedom. ~Malcolm X]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>