<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/q6DJR6wyy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/ZGSODJcVlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/uFknnghhBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/v31wTfxun9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/zs9VPGfDto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/Xi5LG5qOy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/MlkPSwzo8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 106 miles to Chicago, we've got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes, it's dark &amp; we're wearing sunglasses. Hit it! - Elwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/jmH83HzhHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/ainXtBeTjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/QJC0b182b1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/kJzZhIkoDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/3fX3uZQudG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/PCSTD3aoiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/fnHhP2Q7gD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/dBR3p14nTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/TQAPzf6xDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/u8Z4VwoYhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/xZwJ0FvpA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/taXFOQszKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/M2vZYMfrpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/b28mROCr07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/T5j40N92I5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/06m9zB7ZNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theory is a hunch with a college education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/SLff7RU9GK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/pxX7l2PnwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/xNQdzMRnhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/VisgNcIlcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/O2VDW4ozfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/Hej2gQbe8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/TlYYMgrzfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/7Xj98zuUhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/M8K8jofDBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/l2GQFxcdVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/wU7WAVozrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/5nbyne79rN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/NDen1Auydk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Setup an iPad Speaker System  http://t.co/dl5PmLkViI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/fa6vjdMNHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/FFxaedthve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/pxX7l2PnwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/oKmogADSQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/sZ8arCSVXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/nXaHSXDU1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/UnaJyBw0eD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/Re3hObmAYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/V1r6ki9Dwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>