<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[No one's gonna take my soul away, I'm living like Jim Morrison. Headed towards a fucked up holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you like 'Body Electric' by Lana Del Rey. http://t.co/0PZQoZut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey If I get a little prettier can we have a baby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's the perfect pop star – and fashion icon – for our times. http://t.co/ctq0CrBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know more about jewelry than I do about fashion. I love emeralds &amp; diamonds." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I didn't know it would come to this. But that's what happens when you're on your own and you're alright letting nice things go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is #1 on 'The 50 Most Popular Women on The Web' (According to Google) 2012 with 722 Million results! http://t.co/N68hHGrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for Lana Del Rey at NME Awards 2013 as 'The Hottest Woman in Music'. Lana is currently on the 5th place! — http://t.co/rXGKqqBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think Lana Del Rey's lips are sexy! http://t.co/h5vep09j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got that medicine I need, dope, shoot it up, straight to the heart, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for Lana Del Rey!  — 'Best New Artist' http://t.co/yGUa40V7 + 'Video Of The Year' (National Anthem) http://t.co/t5lovlki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When life becomes very hard, it's necessary for me to just ride, to drive fast." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is the true superstar. She makes her own songs and her own videos. And I think she doesn't need a Grammy to prove it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pray the rosary for your broken mind @TheGRAMMYs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all have bad taste in music @TheGRAMMYs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm strong but I'm lonely like Marilyn Monroe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Ride, I speak of the freedom one can find on the road." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GRAMMYNoms Lana Del Rey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIDE. http://t.co/yR40LjfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time with you, it feels like I'm in summer. I don't know why. Maybe cause you're so cool &amp; keep it down on the real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the best Lana Del Rey's source for Indonesian Team Lana: @LanaDReyINDO ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ADQJERXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're children of a bad revolution, and partying is the only solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I tell the stories exactly as I have lived them. I sing what I have lived. There’s no other recipe." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COME AND TAKE A WALK ON THE WILD SIDE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is mean, and love hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let's go back to where we were before we cared about who we would become. We were young and on fire - we were no one." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this city exist, surely Team Lana would be very happy to stay here. http://t.co/AUAIca02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey Hello? Hello? Ca-can you tweet me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to you @The_LanaDelRey ♥ You're the best Team Lana I ever knew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I sing in an dreamy way, like in a conversation with God." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I’ll miss you forever, like the stars miss the sun in the morning sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose your last words, this is the last time. http://t.co/H3It7DRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It takes getting everything you ever wanted and then losing it to know what true freedom is." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am nostalgic of an era I never knew." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I CAN'T. http://t.co/XfIh2Vk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a Boy Team Lana &amp; I'm proud of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you're living like able to do whatever you wanted to do, you have to expect losing your companions on the way." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Seeing myself on the screen makes me cringe." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You feel like even though you didn't know the person, then all the songs are for them now, that's romantic." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Her vintage 60's charm just might kill you." —Billboard on Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all Team Lana. http://t.co/cmud7DpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[❒ Single ❒ Taken ✔ Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I still remember that day we met in December, oh baby, I will love you till the end of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now my life is sweet like cinnamon. Like a fucking dream Im living in. http://t.co/pDlXDSfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to stay hopeful even though I get scared about why we're even alive at all." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have a personal ambition to live my life honestly and honor the true love that I've had and also the people I've had around me." —Lana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaven is a place on earth with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got scared when I'm listening to Video Games for the first time, cause sound of the bells at the beginning of this song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the reason we exist, everybody knows it. It's a fact. *kiss kiss*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was a singer, not a popular one, who once had dreams of becoming a beautiful poet." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is the Queen of Alternative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[List of songs recorded by Lana Del Rey. http://t.co/Enb6klRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2013's Grammy Nominations will be released December 5th at the Grammy nominations concert in Nashville. #LanaForGrammy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you want @LanaDelRey released a perfume called 'Dark Paradise'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like 'Dark Paradise Perfume' or maybe 'Gods &amp; Monsters Perfume'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Lana should do a fragrance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet me and tell me no one will love me better than you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'll have a vanilla milkshake with a side order of the American dream.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG 10k! Thank you so much #TeamLana! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You fit me better than my favorite sweater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L♥VE. http://t.co/kwj00i9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your love true? I'm under influence, getting hot and chills too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EsztiDelRey: Lana: "Sometimes someone comes to me and says 'Excuse me, you look a lot like Lana Del Rey' and I just reply 'Thank you ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This album is a tribute to living life on the wild side. I'm sort of kidding because I'm not that wild anymore." —Lana on 'Born To Die']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey's 'Born To Die' is the 3rd Biggest Selling Albums of 2012 in the UK! http://t.co/3uYOSc35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDReyINDO: Lana Del Rey's "Born To Die" is currently the 3rd biggest selling album of 2012 so far http://t.co/6t26BQQ8 #LDRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You make me crazy, you make me wild.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when I saw you for the first time, you were laughing, sparkling like a new dime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you still love me when I'm no longer young and beautiful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Once I was lost, but now I am found." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Del Rey. http://t.co/fV6Rk0Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Lana Del Rey! http://t.co/alO9sxE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's nice to love and be loved , but its better to know all you can know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's great. She has been working for a really long time, that's make her a really interesting person." —Lana on Lindsay Lohan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The songs I've written are an homage to true love and a tribute to living life on the wild side." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS! RT @LanaDReyOnline: 'I adore my fans, we have a strong bond when together' - Lana Del Rey http://t.co/zz0RsXmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And when you cry, I'll be right there telling you, you were never anything less than beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, why is british accent so sexy? It makes me have an eargasm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey next single off 'Paradise' is Cola. RT If you're excited for the music video! http://t.co/78E0lwSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#5ThingsIFindAttractive http://t.co/hVSB671m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody told me love was blind. Then I saw your face and you blew my mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe in the person I want to become, I believe in the freedom of the open road." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said to "be cool" but, I'm already coolest. I said to "get real", don't you know who you're dealing with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey is … http://t.co/UAI52S52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Born To Die' has sold over 3 million copies worldwide. So proud of you @LanaDelRey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pussy tastes like pepsi cola.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KylieJenner: "When someone else's happiness is your happiness, that is love." -Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing I'd like to do, is to make a short-film for the entire new record." —Lana Del Rey on 'Paradise']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My approach to religion is like my approach to music. I take what I want and leave the rest." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[❒ Straight ❒ Gay ❒ Lesbian ❒ Bi ✔ Lanasexual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look up to hear myself saying, “Baby, too much I strive, I just ride.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just want to have something to do all the time, and it's easier to do when people think you're great." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lana Del Ray's pepsi soda." I'M CRYING. http://t.co/0oXSmBLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my friends tell me I should move on. I'm lying in the ocean singing your song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think I'm pretty and you like the way I talk, I like your music and you like the way I walk, so I think we're gonna get along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gargoyles, standing, in front of your gate. Trying to tell me to wait, but I can’t wait to see you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana &amp; Barrie. http://t.co/ytdEiCbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man 1: My girlfriend is a doctor.
Man 2: My girlfriend is a model.
Barrie: My girlfriend is Lana Del Rey.
*silence*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't cry myself to sleep like a sucker.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>