<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/MNviaGaDrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/dIrjlR0i1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/VTLalTV9yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/P4aZnvcAEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/Tj2HegQEPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/0SFEmKGudb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/B5upTTUiYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/4ftLiPdAhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/lDUpziHHzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/UI0FtQzKAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/KtqSN2gMjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/M9HHeOjynj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/KXcBhWNUez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in control, you're not going fast enough. - Parnelli Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/b4Dzqkcnv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/0zgVZpLfxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/MNORDXgr48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/coQ3nTVUss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/UDrRorbqzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/RfwytyRWx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/5ApWLR2VHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/T7DcuG1rna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/RevJ3ZHLlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/K2X7EmpjVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/91iZtexZ1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/RTUA252sw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/UdTChzDlY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/ThMJb576k0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/06m9zB7ZNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/7TT29rQW2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/eeCxCtO2TR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/1hy0T30Qit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/r9nC2D7mJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/mTKQXX6o4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/7EsKpQGm8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/eXsPOP5mFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/hjo7lPwSvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/3s6G6nVve2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/WZG1niAv97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/7wrG2iEESp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to being a good manager is keeping the people who hate me away from those who are still undecided. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/MSczI9wutD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/coQ3nTVUss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/IxEYbHuLAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>