<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Intern: IT Intern (12 month Fixed Term Contract) Milton Keynes Snapshot of What We’re Looking For We are seeking two driven, technically orientated IT interns to support the Business Systems team in the delivery of best-in-class ERP business… https://t.co/QhVtPQNare https://t.co/MCRCZph5IZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Full Stack Developer Are you a Software Engineer looking to cross train into Node.js? If the answer is yes, this might just be the perfect opportunity for you! This company has been protecting reputation and revenue of global retail… https://t.co/5OJHoUU9p4 https://t.co/jj2GfaBJuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France considers 'all options' to quell violent protests: The French government is considering "all options" to control protests against rising fuel prices that have turned violent in Paris over the last three weeks, a spokesman said Sunday. https://t.co/AOg8MH4Ejt https://t.co/S6duww7FVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Digital 3/4:   Job Description – Engineer Digital 3/4 (18024719) Engineer Digital 3/4 Requisition ID : 18024719 Location : United States-California-Woodland Hills US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/0sTvXCui7Y https://t.co/If4OfOmSy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MPP Technical Analyst: Location: Missouri Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Analyst Jobs The Specialty Materials and Integration Team is looking for experienced technicians to provide Materials and Process, Research and Development… https://t.co/zUJH1cvoGe https://t.co/5KPtp5dtk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend Magento Developer – JavaScript, HTML, CSS – Bath – DEO: Frontend Magento Developer | JavaScript, HTML, CSS (SASS/LESS), PHP | Bath | Dependent on Experience Experienced Frontend Magento Developers are required to join a new team after opening a… https://t.co/AmQQSxvpHc https://t.co/JbNKCYx8Pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Sr. DevOps Engineer. Candidate will play an integral role in the transformation into an Agile and DevOps environment. Candidate will design and develop enterprise software… https://t.co/NbCJ1i7QE6 https://t.co/ii1HwiKCda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Analyst: Job Description: * Supported by an IT team of 10, you will be first point of contact for all PC activity. * Responsible for solving a range of software, hardware and network problems for employees and clients users# * Purchasing and… https://t.co/1vJI4Dg58I https://t.co/pGZs2Rtmkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: Education – Bachelor’s Degree Skills – Project Management – Linux – TCP/IP – TCP – DNS Job Description At Amazon, we strive to be Earth’s most customer-centric company where people can find and discover anything they want to buy online. We… https://t.co/Wzn23qCuQQ https://t.co/ZHVpbHUczl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – £60k – £80k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex: Senior Java Developer – £60k – £80k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex A Senior Java Developer is required by a leading company based in Burgess Hill, West Sussex. They are currently going through… https://t.co/Gj9gOXIuEe https://t.co/aoBuDVXeJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Site Reliability Engineer: Palo Alto, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted 10/16/2018 We are one of the top Advertising Agencies in the US that specializes specifically in Video. We've been profitable for years and our culture feels very 'startup'… https://t.co/3GWDTSQQJm https://t.co/Mh3kpFliXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineering Manager 2 – TS/SCI:   Job Description – Cyber Software Engineering Manager 2 – TS/SCI (18015282) Cyber Software Engineering Manager 2 – TS/SCI Requisition ID : 18015282 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship… https://t.co/MbYvoDUSih https://t.co/41UUethVIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli police say there's enough evidence to indict Netanyahu in a third corruption case: Israeli police said on Sunday that there is enough evidence to indict Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in a third corruption investigation. https://t.co/XhwbGzPwyB https://t.co/nhJOUCNs49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uLrOTWo3CS MVC Developer – West London: https://t.co/uLrOTWo3CS MVC Developer – West London £30-40,000pa DOE + training + certification Permanent Are you looking for a role where you can work with the latest Microsoft platform technologies?… https://t.co/7Igfim03ei https://t.co/moPTDf2LCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integration and Test Engineer 2/3:   Job Description – Integration and Test Engineer 2/3 (18025653) Integration and Test Engineer 2/3 Requisition ID : 18025653 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position:… https://t.co/eg5uAL8Wgx https://t.co/MPGMnbFGjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – SAP PS: SAP PROJECT MANAGER, The Shard – London, 6 months Project Manager for a dynamic FTSE 250 company based in The Shard. You will support the Projects team in their E2E process mapping and alignment to SAP Project Systems. This role… https://t.co/ygDY0K7XcL https://t.co/Hn7JpStrHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tester – Azure, Power BI – Swansea – up to £450: Tester | Azure, Power BI | Swansea | £400 – £450 per day This growing consultancy is seeking a professional Tester with experience with Microsoft Power BI and Azure to start immediately to start creating… https://t.co/ZoiPsRwWCt https://t.co/LYVQH9sIq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin's Trump returns to 'SNL' with worries about the Mueller investigation: Alec Baldwin's Donald Trump returned to "Saturday Night Live" and he brought his worries over the Mueller investigation with him. https://t.co/UMjh6VwEi3 https://t.co/9VVxPjU95m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer .NET Manchester: I am looking for an experienced Software Engineer with a solid background in C# but with a passion for new tech, for a leading Technology company based in the heart of Manchester City Centre. As a Software Engineer… https://t.co/UcBgqp9K3X https://t.co/vyelY97dq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Test Analyst – rapidly growing company: A software house in Edinburgh are looking for a Junior Test Analyst to come on board. They are a fast-growing company, and were recently mentioned as one of Britain’s fastest growing tech companies! Due to… https://t.co/ue4SBVFFpI https://t.co/rruMQNzQjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America faces a crossroads after Bush's death: The contrast could not be more stark. As big headlines around the world announced the death of George H.W. Bush on Friday, just beneath them were these: https://t.co/om6tVzeJcy https://t.co/vamENJXPbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Analyst: Spalding based – this is a temporary role until 31st October 2019 to provide 2nd line support for all desktops, laptops, printers, mobile devices and telephones that are the responsibility of the Desktop Support Team. This role… https://t.co/wnq57ThvJ3 https://t.co/Pywk1lvNBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds arrested in 3rd weekend of Paris protests: More than 200 people were arrested and dozens were injured in Paris on Saturday after clashes erupted between police and protesters, according to a police spokesman. https://t.co/MGWh9FloPP https://t.co/gVLuvTEi4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epicor 10 Consultant – Competitive Salary + Car Allowance: Epicor Consultant, Finance or Accounting experience – Competitive Salary + Car Allowance + Bonus I am working wih an end user company in the Midlands whp are due to undergo a high profile… https://t.co/Sd7f3wfIAJ https://t.co/uDcSrM6ZRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPOS &amp; IT Deployment Engineer: EPOS/IT Deployment Engineer Location: Nationwide contract Duration: 12 weeks (strong chance of extension) Rate: £100 per day + van + fuel card Job Description We require multiple EPOS engineers for an urgent deployment… https://t.co/WSoyi5o6LH https://t.co/cDNipRffqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Software Engineer Senior Level: PURPOSE OF JOB IMPORTANT: Applicants When filling out your name and other personal information below, DO NOT use any special characters or ALL CAPS. Use only standard letters in the English alphabet. Including… https://t.co/PLECF4LoYA https://t.co/a70xgMQZ2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – PHP, MySQL, JavaScript – Leeds – £35k: Full Stack Developer – PHP, MySQL, JQuery, Laravel – Leeds – up to £35,000 The Role An exciting opportunity has come to light for a Full Stack Developer to join a forward-thinking Digital… https://t.co/4cvSefyQZi https://t.co/lkwtt3KjOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meek Mill on prison reform: 'We are trapped inside of a system': Rapper Meek Mill says he and many other formerly incarcerated people are "trapped inside of a system that's extremely hard for us to get out (of)." https://t.co/skXsJLOnW9 https://t.co/3fNDTHyQYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior IOS Developer (Remote Working): Junior IOS Developer – Norfolk – Remote Working – Salary Negotiable We are working with an expanding Norfolk based software owner. They are seeking applicants for a newly formed native iOS development position.… https://t.co/Erlqn8lLHO https://t.co/PeiZeBmVzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Analyst: The Sales Operations Analyst within of Strategic Resource Planning &amp; Market Optimization will develop and execute on an analytical framework for decision making regarding market segmentation, sales opportunity valuation,… https://t.co/mnsfFTzkF4 https://t.co/hzLxPxiXrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPOS &amp; IT Deployment Engineer: EPOS/IT Deployment Engineer Location: Nationwide contract Duration: 12 weeks (strong chance of extension) Rate: £100 per day + van + fuel card Job Description We require multiple EPOS engineers for an urgent deployment… https://t.co/wuYs368zFW https://t.co/xuWW77m8C5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bush lived his life by this acronym familiar to pilots https://t.co/EMLM36tmbS https://t.co/Z5KpgHJGKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Support Engineer: Senior IT Support Engineer Salary £35,000 – £38,000 DOE Full Times Hours Our client is looking to appoint an experienced and enthusiastic Senior IT Support Engineer to assist the IT Manager. MAIN DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:… https://t.co/u2rwsP62Hq https://t.co/KCAF3G6UXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Chase and Holland are partnering with a leading employee in Lincoln to recruit for a Java Developer. The role is to build software using languages and technologies of the Java and AspNetCore frameworks. You will build applications from… https://t.co/p3zfUcu9Pk https://t.co/fsqngI3BXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Corporate PR: Head of Corporate PR It is the policy of IHS Markit to provide equal employment opportunity (EEO) to all persons regardless of age, color, national origin, citizenship status, physical or mental disability, race, religion, creed,… https://t.co/rUzTvafJCA https://t.co/W8G4NCJOij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPOS &amp; IT Deployment Engineer: EPOS/IT Deployment Engineer Location: Nationwide contract Duration: 12 weeks (strong chance of extension) Rate: £100 per day + van + fuel card Job Description We require multiple EPOS engineers for an urgent deployment… https://t.co/e1Zlrwx6AF https://t.co/H7gFrXr81W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st/2nd Line Support Technician: 1st/2nd Line Support Technician A 1st/2nd Line Support Technician is required by our Healthcare sector client based in Central London (Oxford Circus) on a permanent basis to support in hardware, software and network… https://t.co/DhQxco2NNy https://t.co/4hbDpq2hRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst – Quotit: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Irvine, CA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 11/27/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Responsible for providing business analytical support by… https://t.co/wehq8RMTCL https://t.co/x9WfWYSgV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Javascript Developer (Javascript, ES6, HTML, UI, React, Redux): Javascript Developer (Javascript, ES6, HTML, UI, React, Redux)- London- £400-£500 per day Javascript Developer (Javascript, ES6, HTML, UI, React, Redux)- London- £400-£500 per day Our client… https://t.co/BAQ1V4Gsa3 https://t.co/r4GJRQ3fE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family and the political world react to Bush's death: The 41st President of the United States and patriarch of a political dynasty, George H.W. Bush died on Friday in Houston. He was 94 years old. Friends, family, and fellow politicians are now paying… https://t.co/ypjcRgujoW https://t.co/dzB9YHCk5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer: SunIRef:it Full Stack Software Engineer (Java, JavaScript) – Seattle, WA 98104 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords,… https://t.co/fCY4DTY788 https://t.co/9nK0hMCF2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Team Lead: Service Desk Team Lead My client, A market leader in loyalty and payment solutions urgently require a Service Desk Team Lead to join their team based at their Headquarters based on the South Coast. Please see the full job… https://t.co/xETbGMR9Mi https://t.co/yT92JZOm0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Test Analyst Kingston to £28K: Our client makes smart, efficient and secure systems that transform the lives of workers. Their products provide reassurance, confidence and support. Making their job better. They currently supply and support… https://t.co/op9FX2uk3H https://t.co/oWgG3D6OnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: Net Developer, are you interested in learning React and Redux? Build Restful Services using Web API 2? Work with AWS? Interested in putting your development powers to help the greater good? We are looking for a Full Stack .Net Developer –… https://t.co/UOI1sdmje9 https://t.co/zbBNHe6HhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineer: A Senior QA Engineer is required for my financial industry client based in Guildford. They are looking for someone to join them as soon as possible. Senior QA Engineer – Salary between 40,000 and 60,000 per annum depending on… https://t.co/MUv85nt3uu https://t.co/MbWp47dEqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This DNA tech is helping police solve cold cases: In the summer of 2017, hikers found skeletal remains on the side of a highway outside of Baltimore. https://t.co/BIo9HKTwJN https://t.co/N4kxvTFZue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate IT Support Consultant: FINTEC recruit is seeking a Graduate IT Support Consultant. This is a permanent position based in Cambridge. Salary is £20,000 to £25,000 plus bens eg contributory pension scheme, private healthcare cover, share options.… https://t.co/93NILV7LlC https://t.co/8u5dFikvV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer – Birmingham: Job Description Be part of something exciting! Our client is one of the big five IT and business process firms in the world, and are currently growing their digital team of agile specialists, building and delivering user… https://t.co/RHRfS31Obo https://t.co/NS28NHbSCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The astounding Putin-MBS high five: A video is worth a thousand words: At the G20 summit in Buenos Aires, Russian President Vladimir Putin and Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman can be seen flashing big smiles, laughing and giving each other… https://t.co/IZLrl30J0m https://t.co/hBQv6QPdlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMO Analyst: Plusnet’s Programme Management Group is responsible for end to end programme and project management across the Plusnet project portfolio, providing a consistent approach, control and clear accountability for delivery. The purpose of the PMO… https://t.co/Y33BH3Tj4V https://t.co/5JCYZAVkqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shuttle business Via could add scooters to its lineup: Via, a shuttle-based carpooling service and platform that partners with cities in the U.S. and Europe, could soon add scooters to its business. Via CEO and co-founder Daniel Ramot said onstage at… https://t.co/BVN3pzGiYG https://t.co/u6dKKLSLLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Our client is looking for an Infrastructure Engineer to focus on providing the smooth running of a range IT hardware systems Group. The successful candidate will work as part of a team, managing multiple concurrent tasks with… https://t.co/lVTY2hdjh3 https://t.co/kFXQTuwdGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eCommerce/Digital Marketing Apprentice: Write your own future within this specialist eCommerce stationery business in Stourport. You will be tasked with generating and updating content and uploading information to various eCommerce websites and adding… https://t.co/2nJATqOGAP https://t.co/D8rHMSRNqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge rules against Trump administration in 'sanctuary cities' suit: A federal judge ruled against the Justice Department on Friday in a lawsuit over withholding federal money from so-called sanctuary cities, the latest blow to the Trump administration's… https://t.co/khsXCh2kyQ https://t.co/3kXuiVh936]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Tester,Java,TestNG,Selenium,API,Web Services: Senior Automation Tester,QA Engineer,Java,Junit,API,Web Services You will join this Global powerhouse in online shopping. I am looking for someone with a great eye for detail and competence in… https://t.co/LmV6gFpl3E https://t.co/gMlOSnjXok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Desktop Infrastructure analyst (VDI): We are currently working with a leading business in Bristol, who require some expertise on Virtual Desktop Infrastructures (VDI). The client requires experienced senior technical analysts in a virtual… https://t.co/56HfIfHOmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Data Analyst: Job Description IT Data Analyst Job Responsibilities: The primary functions will be providing necessary help in retrieving, interpreting, and analyzing data. The analyst will also be cleaning up data for upload, creating reports, KPI… https://t.co/J90sIGnhhO https://t.co/3UWuEoi6DT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsunami warning in effect in Alaska after quake: A tsunami warning is in effect for coastal areas of Cook Inlet and southern Kenai Peninsula in Alaska after an earthquake Friday with a preliminary magnitude of 6.7, according to a bulletin from the… https://t.co/rjZz9Dd0UY https://t.co/XenusvP6rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Design Architect (Service Design, Service Architecture): Service Design Architect (Service Architecture, Design, Transition, Delivery) A leading UK FTSE 100 provider of IT Solutions and Services are looking to hire a talented Service Design… https://t.co/ZcIIGHtP4a https://t.co/yrTznd5FOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer – AWS/Docker/Kubernetes: Senior Systems Engineer – AWS/Docker/Kubernetes 6-Month Contract Excellent daily rate Our client has an opportunity based in Dublin for a Senior IT Systems Engineer with good experience with AWS, Docker… https://t.co/wUe8GDk7r7 https://t.co/GZBuagdVZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: SunIRef:it Senior Software Engineer – Milpitas, CA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or… https://t.co/3348IKwqyI https://t.co/b7QM4DjBvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Analyst / Business Analyst: We are currently recruiting for an self motivated Junior Business Analyst, with an excellent understanding of business requirement gathering on behalf of a market leading software implementation company based in London.… https://t.co/ITl9MxWijK https://t.co/AHDN03WAUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Specialist, Enterprise: The Role: Do you value supporting revenue growth and retention? Do you have experience ensuring a positive client experience throughout the entire sales cycle? As an Application Specialist at S &amp; P Global Market… https://t.co/c3y2v8u4d9 https://t.co/8oWjKRI0bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Here at Kalibrate we're on an exciting journey following recent significant investment. As such we're looking to add the best professionals the market has to offer on an international scale. Key to this growth is a Senior Developer… https://t.co/pkn4XPb2l0 https://t.co/d82q8OHSe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia isn't buying Trump's reasons for canceling Putin meeting https://t.co/ov7mpRvMy9 https://t.co/r3rf34wZyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# WPF Developer – London: Bringing a new approach to their industry they are now looking to expand their team, to continue improving and delivering their state-of-the-art Software platform. If you are looking to work in a stunning setting with a growing… https://t.co/tOUImz7fl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Advisor: An IT Support Advisor / First Line Support Officer is required for a growing, forward thinking company in Northampton who truly value their employees and even offer the opportunity to work from home! SALARY: £20,000 – £24,000… https://t.co/0tXuRN1A8V https://t.co/nD0gPU4htt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator: Position Summary The Senior Systems Administrator will provide leadership and positive influence to support the firm’s strategic objectives and goals. Assist in establishing standard operating procedures and mentor others in… https://t.co/oIUHQR251P https://t.co/lQ2MAzlHHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer C# SQL HTML CSS JavaScript Software Developer My fantastic client in Preston is looking for a solid Software Developer to come on board on a permanent basis and join an award winning team. The role is to develop… https://t.co/Csw9Nkb2z5 https://t.co/5CSmYsBhK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have two ages, chronological and biological. Here's why it matters: Reminiscent of a scene from "The Social Network," the whiteboard in researcher and professor Morgan Levine's Yale Medical School office is covered in a series of letters and numbers.… https://t.co/ufHyxA3CYy https://t.co/xuPova0GLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Software Engineer: Position: Software Engineer Location: Broomfield, CO Revolutionizing business through data science and analytics, Alteryx offers an end-to-end analytics platform which empowers data analysts and scientists alike to break… https://t.co/MpP1xQDGkM https://t.co/xKkzzCjcaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, HEDIS/Quality Reporting:   Job Description – Sr Analyst, HEDIS/Quality Reporting (1807112) Job Description  Sr Analyst, HEDIS/Quality Reporting – (1807112) Primary Location : US-MI-Troy-TROY Job : Quality Organization : Health Plans Job… https://t.co/jhSidwdGa1 https://t.co/A47pGRrPn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract eBusiness Developer – Portsmouth: Contract eBusiness Developer is required to join the team and your main responsibilities will be the design, production, modification and maintenance of websites and web application user interfaces. You will… https://t.co/ebnAJFoe56 https://t.co/CLUtdV05iT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Line Support Engineer: An award winning IT support company in Sheffield are searching for their next 2nd Line IT Engineer to join their friendly expanding team. Duties include: • Managing technical requests, prioritising and dealing with them… https://t.co/87AT0zLf5l https://t.co/g4T8o5SLAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. and Trump Org. in spotlight after Cohen plea: Michael Cohen's admission that he lied to Congress about Donald Trump's knowledge of the ongoing effort to build a Trump Tower in Moscow during the 2016 campaign has ensnared the President's… https://t.co/n3IN6acuAD https://t.co/mIlJsPtOU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / SQL Software Developer: C# / SQL Software Developer As one of the Top 75 fastest growing tech companies in the UK and having been voted by users as the Best Recruitment CRM in 2018 (amongst many other awards!), Firefish is a real Scottish… https://t.co/5QKEyN5ooA https://t.co/ifYILOOeLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Service Engineer: Field Service Engineer Reading – Guildford Circa £25,000 + Overtime +Standby + Van This is a fantastic opportunity for you, an experienced Field Service Engineer to join a world class, leading IT Support company, providing IT… https://t.co/jFgOyGZToq https://t.co/a7hEwSiXjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer / Cobol Developer (VME Platform): Senior Developer / Cobol Developer (VME Platform) – Contract – Reading, Berkshire. A leading IT services company is searching for a Senior Developer / Cobol Developer (VME Platform) to join their team in… https://t.co/oDnlnDRuQb https://t.co/gL48bsPF0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undocumented immigrants detained after boat washes ashore in Laguna Beach: Ten people were detained on Thursday after a small panga boat landed in Laguna Beach, California, according to police. https://t.co/lyofMc1zo5 https://t.co/QI1sLzC7ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crusade against open-source abuse: There’s a dark cloud on the horizon. The behavior of cloud infrastructure providers threatens the viability of open source. Thankfully, several leaders have mobilized to propose multiple solutions. https://t.co/82pn1ioF6P https://t.co/cmZVnvbKiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management – Graduate Progamme – January Start: Enjoy communicating? Approachable and articulate? Would you enjoy managing a project? If you are ambitious, analytical and interested in Business and IT and wish to build a successful career in a… https://t.co/Dedk5nFfiW https://t.co/paH9CukNLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineering Technologist: Mechanical Engineering Technologist to assist engineers to develop/test mechanical systems and products for marine vessels for manufacturing company in Sarasota. Requires 3 years experience in job or as Mechanical… https://t.co/gwdLSxGrwC https://t.co/PwJ3yt3oUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan preparing to put US-designed stealth jets on an 'aircraft carrier': Japan is preparing an order for roughly 100 US-designed F-35 stealth fighter jets in a deal that could potentially upend the balance of power in Asia, according to sources familiar… https://t.co/J3F5nUgtRf https://t.co/GJEk6lNsJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developers: Senior Software Developers / Park Ridge, IL: Develop &amp; design of web/mobile components &amp; services to introduce new capabilities &amp; services for online/mobile customers on a highly scalable eCommerce platform. Development &amp;… https://t.co/BiEGvuMrX6 https://t.co/14LQUEURYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PHP Developer: Looking for your next job as a PHP Web Developer in Attleborough South Norfolk, working with a cool, fun and vibrant global business? Then this is the opportunity for you. As a PHP Developer you will work closely with the… https://t.co/VmuhTXWTfY https://t.co/fzAOboOE9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT SUPPORT ENGINEER: Our client, an established ICT solutions provider, is seeking an IT Support Engineer to join their team on a permanent basis. The IT Support Engineer will be responsible for carrying out a variety of technical tasks, acting as a… https://t.co/d6q9StHX3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: ENGINEER Ambarella Corp. has the following openings in Santa Clara, CA: Software Engineer (Job#P2005) to develop infrastructure and tools for Autonomous Driving development. Submit resume to https://tinyurl. com/ydarzjkg Sr. Software… https://t.co/CYEgI2UDxJ https://t.co/bJxC8QU4Xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX/UI Designer – Mobile Apps: Senior UX/UI Designer – Mobile Apps Horsham – West Sussex £50,000 – £60,000 per annum + benefits An experienced UX/UI designer is required for a high-tech software company based in Horsham, West Sussex. Our client is… https://t.co/7VKFZ9IdGU https://t.co/uC4bTmiPiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victim: Destroying my rape kit tells me I don't matter: CNN speaks with a woman in Fayetteville, North Carolina, whose rape kit was destroyed after a detective decided what happened to her wasn't a crime. See more at https://t.co/G7AXmTjF60. https://t.co/MGQiJscw0Q https://t.co/SqY67XeZSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: V. Murphy. Please reference job # below: Solutions Consultant (Palo Alto, CA) Advise company stakeholders on methods to improve efficiency… https://t.co/IOx3DuFmdf https://t.co/SIdGe1Xwuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmers/Developers: IBM Curam Programmers/Developers (7 open Positions) (South Jordan, UT &amp; unanticipated client sites across the US. Must be willing to travel and/or relocate domestically.) Design/Development experience in IBM Curam projects, using… https://t.co/vZH7oQKAcb https://t.co/nfIOjVXMRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: We are looking for a passionate Senior Embedded Software Engineer to join our client's team in Cambridge. The role requires a versatile, driven software engineer who enjoys applying their problem-solving prowess to… https://t.co/80nLta0zj6 https://t.co/riwfoCc6nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Cohen's plea agreement: President Donald Trump's ex-attorney Michael Cohen pleaded guilty Thursday to making false statements to Congress about the Russia investigation. https://t.co/Zko54sWMfP https://t.co/PYBgSslTps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst Programmer/Web Developer: Position Details Position Information DepartmentExtended Campus (DEC) Classification TitleAnalyst Programmer Job TitleAnalyst Programmer/Web Developer Appointment TypeClassified Staff Job LocationCorvallis Position… https://t.co/FXOinXYTXb https://t.co/g9BKbGg5px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock Controller: Stock Controller – Leeds – Salary £20k – £24k, 20 Days Holiday + Bank Holidays, Free Car Parking, Excellent Opportunity to join a successful, growing business. We are currently recruiting on behalf of a very successful, progressive… https://t.co/RzSysZTwzj https://t.co/fFhDT4E1NA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing the latest set of judges for Startup Battlefield Africa 2018: Startup Battlefield Africa is right around the corner. This year it’s in Lagos, Nigeria on December 11. As usual, we have a stellar lineup of panels that will include investors and… https://t.co/aL3xex5X8V https://t.co/1yO0KGsrir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician: A leading firm of chartered surveyors, chartered town planners, property and business consultants are looking for an IT support professional to join their IT Infrastructure within a Windows environment with a mixture of Windows… https://t.co/31v32vNgHO https://t.co/nUkdtijQpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer IV: Job Summary: Job ID: 6586 – FT – Unclassified (salaried) Under minimal direction, participate in an agile team responsible for delivering solutions including acquisition, implementation and integration of locally hosted and SaaS… https://t.co/6rbWY9nBw7 https://t.co/acGVWt9ifW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unilever CEO Paul Polman retires after 10 years: Unilever CEO Paul Polman is retiring at the end of the year after a decade in charge of one of the world's biggest consumer goods businesses. https://t.co/A5ETLpOiE8 https://t.co/P3Tw0oEbKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay Per Click analyst Coventry to £30k: Our client is an amazing success story. From start-up they have become the 3rd largest player in their market and now employ 250 people. They are a genuinely entrepreneurial company where all employees have an… https://t.co/S3XsGZBC6T https://t.co/SI1j3REEA6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>