<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[More Options for Brands on Twitter: The Site Tinkers With Timeline: Twitter is quietly updating to its Timeline ... http://t.co/5AepLvb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs-in-Residence Aid Immigration:  http://t.co/TFwDKCeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup Lessons from David Cohen and the TechStars: Though the TechStars program lasts three months, participant... http://t.co/f73qMyAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: A social Google music ? | Motorola says Ice Cream sandwich devices coming | iPhone 4S caused dip: ... http://t.co/VuIloxIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What iOS 5 Means for Marketers: This past weekend, I took the plunge and upgraded my iPhone and iPad2 to iOS 5. ... http://t.co/pLpSDTRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotlight on Takeover Mobile Ad Formats Fades as M-commerce Takes Center Stage: Mobile e-commerce is becoming mo... http://t.co/1bUVcS9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Oracle buys RightNow | 500,000 Android apps | Square enters Wal-Mart: CRM:

Oracle buys RightNow.

Mob... http://t.co/s7v5apBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excerpt: From Pawnshops to Poverty Inc.:  http://t.co/K8QwZdIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archive: Help an Employee in Financial Crisis:  http://t.co/5p6XFwhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Monday Beats Black Friday: Cyber Monday is over (sort of) and the results are in. It’s a HIT!
According to... http://t.co/vOheixFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Cyber Monday sales surge | CTIA mobile rating system | Google catalogs on Android: Ecommerce:

Big sal... http://t.co/SkQQZ01K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Branson on When Inexperience Is an Advantage: Richard Branson answers reader questions on breaking conve... http://t.co/lGRBguxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Cyber Monday binge | DoJ may approve Google's Admeld purchase | Mobile 3D?: Black Friday/ Cyber Mo... http://t.co/Rm2p3XV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree “It’s amazing what ordinary ppl can do if they set out w/out preconceived notions.” — C. F. Kettering RT @successmagazine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @capricecrane: With the amount of people who hide their identity online you'd think this place is rampant with superheroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Paid Search Offers Bigger Bang for the Buck: Now that more people are using their mobile devices to searc... http://t.co/cHaKGfUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankful for that Online Sale? Or Just Thankful for Your Customer in General?  Send an Email Saying So: Email ma... http://t.co/eQgMZCvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gingrich, Romney Face Criticism on Illegal Immigration Stances: Newt Gingrich and Mitt Romney, leading contender... http://t.co/LmcSpVUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The $600 Million Dollar Marketing Secret: I want to share one final marketing tactic with you in this post. Like... http://t.co/xfxiHpJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. TV Shows Arrive On PS3 PSN In The U.K. But Pricing, Range Of Content Is Still An Issue: British PS3 owners ... http://t.co/7iaFe9W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: Today is Thanksgiving! And So Is Tomorrow!: Yay! Today is Thanksgiving! FEED ME TURKEY!
Ok so I know... http://t.co/qIrIczwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Business Saturday Gets White House Support: In the weeks leading up to Black Friday, it’s mostly the big b... http://t.co/6d1roXH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Yelp More Than Just Restaurant Reviews?: Look I will be the first to admit today is a very slow news day.
Tha... http://t.co/oEuu4a6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create a Job Board on Your Business Website: Selling job postings online can help small businesses increa... http://t.co/ZIezAimC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google+ TV Ad Runs But Will People Get It?: Google ran a TV ad on Thanksgiving during the early NFL game. I miss... http://t.co/JmqxI31a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Is What You Think It Is: Change Is What You Think It IsThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
Happy Thank... http://t.co/q5t6PVQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shatter The Five Barriers To Making The Sale: So let’s touch back on that original question from last post – how... http://t.co/dObHBCNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook: 1 in 10 Ticker Stories Could be Ads: Facebook has found a way to put more ads in front of more people.... http://t.co/x6Wcjzvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Look for an Alternative to the Holiday Hype: I love a bargain, but frankly, it’s only Wednesday and I’... http://t.co/VowFYMLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMandossian Great article from @FastCompany—Work Smart: How To Find Your Sweet Spot: http://t.co/YOXylVbE #opportunities #skills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Happy Thanksgiving? There's An App for That: Thanksgiving is, if nothing else, a celebration of the abundance ... http://t.co/MhVP6WGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To “Make Money” Fast…: Over the next few posts I want to give you some important techniques you can use to e... http://t.co/ulRh6G4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Continues to Slim Down by Dropping More Offerings: Google continues on its year round spring cleaning as ... http://t.co/ZJaEkg2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony Adds Free TV and Movies To Playstation Home | Crackle Goes Live, Ustream To Follow: PS3 owners who are also... http://t.co/CwlceG3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: The case against a Facebook phone | Windows Phone marketplace | Penguin stops e-lending: Mobile Co... http://t.co/niSTpAFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I Learned About Entrepreneurship from Richard Branson: For young entrepreneurs, having a mentor -- even one... http://t.co/LoP38wis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Leads in Social Media Effectiveness for SMB’s: E-mail marketing service provider Constant Contact has p... http://t.co/BArYdCYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Chill Adds Hulu To Social Viewing Line-Up, How Important Is It To Watch TV With Others?: We all remember Sund... http://t.co/NtGf5wCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revenge of Startup Nation: Matt Straz just wrote a short and succinct post on Mediapost's Online Spin, giving 6 ... http://t.co/I0MZXnVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPad Tops Kids’ Holiday Wish List: The electronics department of Santa’s workshop will be putting in extra hours... http://t.co/iPnPKvSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeathaWhadeva: If a telemarketer calls give the phone to your 3 yr old,and tell them its santa clause. &lt;--Brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling Music in the Digital Age:  http://t.co/HgW4gJax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the End of Yahoo’s Iconic Billboard in SF Signal Other Things?: As of December a SF landmark, the neon Yaho... http://t.co/WhWE6Lvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony Considering Internet TV Offering To Rival Cable, But Will Media Companies Take The Bait: They way we consum... http://t.co/REtRYSSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet Marketing Jobs Are Available!: The economy may be bad but the protective bubble around the online space... http://t.co/SxIQDK68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skype Video Chat Now Live on Facebook: A year from now, there will be absolutely no reason to leave the confines... http://t.co/gXRc8lx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Verizon Opt-Out Ads | Google Music | Facebook spam |: Online Ad Market:

Verizon welcomes users to the... http://t.co/OreKTwyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet Summit 2011: Engagement and Data Rule the Day: Tackling the social marketing landscape can be quite cha... http://t.co/kKxCgdaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gmail iOS App Back, Fingers Crossed All Around Mountain View: Two weeks ago Google put out their long awaited Gm... http://t.co/dW9j4j3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree Are You Driving Your Customers Away? Find out: http://t.co/1iqhax5X #customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports is the Ticket at LivingSocial: LivingSocial members consumed 28,742 hot dogs in Q3 while burgers bit the ... http://t.co/6rTxNFVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shfly3424: Now and then it's good to pause in our pursuit of happiness and just be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree Follow these six steps to diffusing customer anger: http://t.co/a6SCd1Ud #success]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating an 'Ecosystem' for Minority Entrepreneurs: To foster entrepreneurship among minorities and in urban cen... http://t.co/RC0chUw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cure for Your PubCon Hangover: There’s no better way to test your resolution than braving a four day confere... http://t.co/SivZsj9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Commerce: Where Do We Go From Here?: Social Commerce is one of those terms you wouldn’t have found in the... http://t.co/6C7DlvXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree The High Cost Of New Hires: http://t.co/LuIDmjGv #employees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Few Employers Use Health-Care Tax Credits: Low exploitation rates for tax breaks intended to encourage small... http://t.co/GWN0SZUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Rules for Pricing Products: Before you put a price tag on a product or service, find out how much customers... http://t.co/ecUqnysM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be Present for Your Business: How to Be Present for Your BusinessThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing

... http://t.co/peXMg32C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media: You Can’t Pretend It’s Not Happening: In a series of posts beginning today, we are excited to have... http://t.co/QgiThfM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree 4 Signs You Are Overworked: http://t.co/1Tzgy0xq #jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tablets Top For Video Viewing As iPad Beats Android | Amazon Kindle Fire Could Disrupt: Tablets are growing in p... http://t.co/qQgfrhuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Teens Twitter but Facebook Still Rules: The Pew Internet & American Life Project found that 16% of online t... http://t.co/8MTkeKwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMandossian 12 Ways to Become a Recognized Expert: http://t.co/xZNJTwfU #experts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: W3C privacy draft | Google Music sneak peak | Disney acquires mommy blog platform: Privacy:

W3C a... http://t.co/podlRb9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree Work Smart: 4 Tips For Startups (via @fastcompany): http://t.co/tD1JevjF #business #startups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Gifting's Momentum Grows: Social gifting service Wrapp has raised $5.5 million in Series A funding led by... http://t.co/Kc8UlmEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Steps to Finding a Business Mentor: Here's how to meet an experienced startup advisor and maximize the rel... http://t.co/QC4chOwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Deere Uses Social Media to Feed the Hungry: Here at Marketing Pilgrim we like to give our readers some expo... http://t.co/TiliSA0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMandossian 
10 Leaders and the Surprising Ways They Stay Productive: http://t.co/OnonAnOw #leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting More Support to Veterans-Turned-Entrepreneurs: Buy Veteran is one of the recent efforts to build awarene... http://t.co/keVea65L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Invitation: Join the Magical Marketing Experience Mastermind Group for 2012 with Andrew Lock 
Check out http://t.co/cNMHcQEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jobs Crisis Among Veterans:  http://t.co/ky20j75Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Vending Machines Intrigued by Google Wallet, But Other Contenders Still Circle: Coca-Cola is piloting a pro... http://t.co/0qO4kb8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Nears Deal With FTC to Clear Way for IPO?: Any time I read Facebook and privacy in the same line I get ... http://t.co/8BeCVbcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Lessons from America's Greatest Military Leaders: Military talents can transfer well to guiding a team throug... http://t.co/lldNt9Mv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain In A Day On Nov. 12 | BBC Documentary Will Use Video Clips Uploaded To YouTube: Life In A Day was a spec... http://t.co/UHXDOMlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid Search Dollars Decline, While Display is On the Rise: Earlier this year, Kantar Media said they were cautio... http://t.co/Ea7hm3N5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid Search Ad Spending Takes Hit in Q3. Fortunately It Doesn't Feel That Way: Spending growth slowed during the... http://t.co/52TyjxsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship Gender Gap Isn't Shrinking: Women still start fewer businesses than men and are less likely to ... http://t.co/RbI2yDHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email Marketers Continue to Merge with Social Media. Unfortunately, Their SMB Customers Want More: In its first ... http://t.co/EJTFG29q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing and Measurement: Still Not So Perfect Together: Marketing executives and those that they badger for in... http://t.co/m5iTGt8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking Up New Business Ideas from Old-World Recipes: How some entrepreneurs are drawing from the distant past t... http://t.co/CCC97uPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Anyone Know What Is Legal and Illegal On YouTube? Does Anyone Even Care Any More?: Believe it or not things... http://t.co/OzMOLIXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Timeline Arrives with a Ticking Clock: Facebook unveiled their new Timeline design back in September bu... http://t.co/TfoiJwFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Minute Tips to Goose Site Speed: As the shopping season heads into the third week of December, online retai... http://t.co/Zzo5hNJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine New Year's Resolutions for Stressed-Out Entrepreneurs: A look at life changes you can make to find more bal... http://t.co/orRKjuVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top News: Timeline goes live | Glam Media eyes IPO | The anti-Groupon: Social Media:

Facebook Timeline goes liv... http://t.co/bIfJV3qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free -- or Almost Free --Tools to Help You Start a Business in 2012: A helpful resource guide to turn your small... http://t.co/RyvgK0uU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate Louis C.K., Love His (Profitable) Digital Content Distribution Honor Box Experiment: It’s OK to hate Louis ... http://t.co/oCR0lS3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grant Cardone on Closing the Sale: Watch the archived online chat with sales pro Grant Cardone, who answered you... http://t.co/F1BoYIQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google+ Upgrades Hangout with Recording and More: Google+’s multi-person, webchat tool, Hangout, just got pushed... http://t.co/BCx4IrBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While You are Waiting for Facebook Mobile Ads: Rumors are intensifying that Facebook is getting ready to step in... http://t.co/931PAnjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Reputation Management Apology….Ever?: Over the past year, companies have:
caused homes to be trashed
tr... http://t.co/AFwzuf0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Branson and the Space Tourism Business: The famed entrepreneur talks about the origins of his Virgin Gal... http://t.co/hKbOiH4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers OK Small-Business Research Programs: Lawmakers moved to extend and expand two key small business resea... http://t.co/nNy5kuSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Recover from a Social Media Blunder: What do Gilbert Gottfried, Kenneth Cole and GoDaddy’s CEO Bob Parson... http://t.co/pGwk8Fw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clickandbefree The One Resolution You Need To Make In 2012: http://t.co/yw19XFNy #business #growth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Advertising's Fight for the Small Business: Increasingly small businesses are focusing more resources on... http://t.co/SLhERNcx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>