<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/1Szbbiz7fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BRMCR6Pgfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/Nf0Tmt2eKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/xHpR5MMPCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/1Ayqb3b3Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/ugVmerJuyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/HbdmzjMUAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/D7zaGtEgxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/snN7SUPZfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/GZORdtnwt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/chid2iacsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/psHBEKhTnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/4bPotrmDyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/9eX3jO7buc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/oxEbkFLKrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/vqSlOidCIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/H0Advx9S6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/dw3bIRCpvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/dleqmKj71q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/Kuv4JQfNdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/ZMaz7Ticaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/liQAJVLBPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/sNOvahQahm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/sdGjE0p7BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/NK8Umc3TUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got Flossie dog, and she is great. She and I are still in love, 14 years. That's a relationship that works. - Drew Barrymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/e3Dz3xaaim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/BlH0kq8jLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/gRRlUmUfOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/EsS0Xv7Ai6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/da3tfW5NMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/ZxVvNVDGZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/EUjoQhsEaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/S0azKaFQiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/VGN3qsUCmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/oQ1zQQfLTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/BIppSeQJBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/6vRjRrZD5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/fv6GlR5149]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/QO54OY9QYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/fQLHcQY009]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/qZXRPd9iNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/15se96itya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/yPDIS32xwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/x8im0XHqz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/aaaxRncL0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/YJIcWYiAMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/BLvMjCmUmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/vN78joEdmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/jML66Qd6kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/Wq3OJSq5G0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/qj0b6WmG5e]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>