<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Croatian TV station airs a show about teapots that lasts for 2,700 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An English boy is obsessed with collecting bearskin rugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prime minister switches bodies with a woolly mammoth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen kisses a chameleon inside a chocolate island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polar bear materializes next to Queen Victoria. A dentist says: "This is the end."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A garden sinks into a river filled with tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 17th century Alaskan prophecy that you will be imprisoned by a warlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hairdresser celebrates Thanksgiving with a rhinoceros and a camel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a typhoon in New Orleans. It rains violinists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blonde sultan plays a game of chess with an Airbnb rental.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are imprisoned in a glass paperweight for the crime of stealing unrequited love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anxious president passes a law that everyone must be clean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A courtesan slowly turns into a volcano. She becomes world-famous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a willow tree in Vancouver that is infinitely beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Korean carpenter plants a seed. A city grows from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Macedonian witch gives birth to a silver termite mound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An accountant catches a bus to Finland. In that time, she lives another life as a Maltese clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lonely bookshop owner plants a seed which grows into a cherry tree made of tax law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A deeply depressed sociologist has a rare gift: He can understand the language of bumble bees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor dreams of an art gallery that can destroy the Sun, and becomes obsessed with finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight, an old woman will appear and give you the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a lunar eclipse an inscription appears in the sky above Mecca. It reads: "Beware of the colour grey."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vulture lays an egg. Inside the egg is a countess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time travelling governess from ancient Sparta materializes in front of you. She says: "I am here to give you a circus tent."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An eagle made of fireflies is born in Munich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sicilian cook bakes a cake made of ice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A placenta is chosen to be the next CEO of Procter &amp; Gamble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An army major puts a hex on a parish priest. It causes him to gradually turn into a comet's tail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In heaven there is a dandelion with the power to create immigration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An essay whispers to a solicitor: "I wish I was a salamander."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fate of a billionaire depends on one particular cathedral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clown whispers to Nero: "I love Sydney."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anaesthetist bicycles across a dinner plate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you pay a werewolf in Florida the sum of 8,800 dollars, it will destroy time and space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anthropologist buys a map which shows the location of every cemetery in the Bay Area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A penniless king decides to kill thirst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twelve angels are going on a quest. Their aim is to rescue a veterinarian who has been trapped in a thermometer by a goblin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guilt-stricken poet keeps an unusual possession in a locked box: A clockwork lobster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A melancholy innkeeper is dancing all night with balloons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorcerer is drinking cocktails in the belly of a leopard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congresswoman decrees that there will be a new sign of the zodiac: The skull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor buys a crystal ball which lets him see every disappointment since the birth of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baron sees a crocodile with bongs instead of teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philosophy is in love with romance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The body of a homeless person is found in a staircase. Next to it is a peppermint and a broken cello. Can you explain what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman discovers a letter by Derrida on the subject of ice cream vans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Toronto there is a birthday cake which is listening to a violin concerto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dentist steals endometriosis and hides it inside a castle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An embittered Polish necromancer owns a pair of spectacles that let him see, hear, smell, touch and taste libertarianism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A medieval manuscript describes a world filled with the number zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a monster in Sri Lanka that is 40 times wiser than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pianist invents a better version of inertia: Vomiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wake up and realize you have turned into Donald Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Instagram celebrity in Iceland is worried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Melbourne is a lake in which every drop of water is a mansion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Caribbean watchmaker sees a stain on a carpet in the shape of a broken heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A depressed clown writes a manuscript that is made out of Janet Jackson CDs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university student spends his life writing an almanac about mushrooms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baby is born in Germany with Picasso's Guernica painted on its chest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 5th century BC Albanian prophecy that you will be kidnapped by a labyrinth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An owl appears next to Kim Kardashian. It says: "Don't do it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every nurse in Milwaukee is whispering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Portuguese empress listens to a phonograph that plays the music of dancing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are transported to a city which looks like Newcastle, but everything is pink. Ahead of you is a road paved with alarm clocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At midnight Toronto sinks into a lake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Danish duke decrees that everyone must be bald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bisexual schoolmaster is turning into sexism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-hearted realtor falls in love with the number Pi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A trumpet floats past you. Nearby, a prime minister is singing the Star-Spangled Banner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flight attendant has trapped an ancient Spartan scribe inside a glacier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An invisible pyramid covers the whole of Baltimore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In San Diego there is a heart which is singing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A watchmaker builds an enormous cathedral and fills it with cigarettes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A satrap discovers a tiny glass sphere which lets him see every kite in Cape Town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A geisha catches a taxi to a crystal ball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A football stadium is haunted by the ghost of a Venetian hermit. She carries a panther in her hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A countess receives a strange gift at her baby shower: A porcelain diamond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archaeologist turns into a motel. Nobody notices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Assyrian book collector spends her whole life writing a mathematical treatise about trampolines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beauty therapist invents a better version of the French Revolution: Doing nothing at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A video game designer and a soldier play a game in which the aim is to become a doll's house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, a bank manager in Baltimore turns into a waiting room during her lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A midwife searches for a judge with eyes made of chocolate on a glass thundercloud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scholar is praying in an Egyptian mummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A movie producer is concentrating on a ray of light in Florence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A river allows you to understand the language of giant squids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Swiss field marshal becomes obsessed with having sexual intercourse with prime numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Marxist discovers that darkness does not exist, and is driven insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A violinist dreams about every rainbow that has taken place in Washington DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nun owns a pair of spectacles that let her talk to single-payer healthcare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A politician sees a painting of a rose petal that can destroy ambiguity, and devotes her life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A witch is sitting in a tower. She is thinking about candy bars. A sea serpent is having sexual intercourse behind her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A four-leaf clover is in a psychiatric hospital in Cambodia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Belgian naturopath runs a clinic that treats anthills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Texan cocktail waitress walks into a forest and discovers a cypress tree made of Breakfast at Tiffany's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brilliant architect designs a pyramid made of climate change. But due to a shortage of climate change, it is never finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A maharajah sleeps in a glass cornfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A group of dentists are setting out on an adventure. Their aim is to find a mysterious button with the power to destroy star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scorpion asks you to solve a riddle: What is Republican, has eight armpits, and is found in a souvenir shop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A president owns a painting which depicts every act of love by a priest.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>