<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer – Full Stack: Client Reference Code: 215393Job ScopeLeads in the planning, design, development, implementation, and execution of innovative application and platform solutions related to security, service delivery, datacenter and… https://t.co/1dqGoSYzvA https://t.co/0ix0DPrdKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China joins HK-U.S. battle for Chinese tech listings: HONG KONG (Reuters) - When Charles Li, chief executive of the Hong Kong Exchange, last year announced plans to help the next wave of Chinese tech giants go public in the city, bankers celebrated. https://t.co/qaKlIWFYGi https://t.co/Ea9K2qj5Or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/ocH3ki976i https://t.co/A4w7Speccq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/orFwVnHEn1 https://t.co/v4gLhSEMED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/Zv4lXimnTO https://t.co/yVMXr5V8EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python &amp; JavaScript]: JOB DESCRIPTION Our clients product team is expanding and seeking top-tier senior engineers (Full Stack and Back End Engineers). Theyre looking for independent thinkers that want to take ownership of parts… https://t.co/TlyXQ9bYk6 https://t.co/hLMVfFP5VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/qf5JqumyDG https://t.co/4rEM21MWLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/CVSr83HVfO https://t.co/tvGmKaRpgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/BM3WFvuuhw https://t.co/ZpeyJmCAkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX: Sr. Python Developer – Houston, TX – Parmesoft Inc. – Houston, TX – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/J1YxmFO3mK https://t.co/qzgzGz6hGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/5ZdnB1zO7o https://t.co/XFbeVYRPKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/yYj9K3r6n7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer III – Commercial Tools – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 215428 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving… https://t.co/CpVS4oTBTg https://t.co/pdgBwTxJZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/rlo9ksaE0J https://t.co/H6sHAgA2Ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/Cloud Engineer: IoT Defense is looking for a strong, motivated engineer looking to make an impact on our 2018 strategies. We are a start-up business looking to build out our development and engineering team to support our products. With the… https://t.co/tkjdkL1zOw https://t.co/bqem9Oxi93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Devops Engineer: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Cloud Devops Engineer Professional Services – Columbia, MD | Fulton, MD | Full Time Job Description About Us: Engineers solving real-world… https://t.co/LfNljAhDfh https://t.co/dWAI6AJQgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Concur iXp Intern- Product Manager Intern: SAP Concur iXp Intern- Product Manager Intern Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/Q0saT3i2mi https://t.co/4Ax5quZHKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Backend): At BitGo, our mission is to make digital currencies usable for business. Since pioneering multi-signature technology in 2013, BitGo has grown to become one of the most well known and reputable brands in the digital asset and… https://t.co/LWMtnzCBmU https://t.co/GRO7oFjF7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/1ryBoGvqvt https://t.co/BjQCu2HSIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description Are you a talented Network Engineer looking for the next step in your career ? Check out PSS! Position Description PSS, Inc. is actively seeking a Senior Network Engineer to join our growing team located inChantilly, VA.… https://t.co/oNNWjOYMHw https://t.co/QGbDB6h91C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/WLjOkBP7J3 https://t.co/gLQIBCHQcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/vZTkbhg7j1 https://t.co/ujcj7CfpOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Algorithm Developer Engineer: We are looking for a brilliant mind to join our team, working on solving very real and important problems. You will take a leadership role in our algorithm team to develop machine learning and behavior… https://t.co/JoCKTNCHNy https://t.co/0mYMd3gNjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adidas to close stores in online push: CEO in Financial Times: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Adidas expects to close down stores in the coming years as part of a shift towards selling more goods online, its chief executive told a newspaper. https://t.co/qMQTRH3T5e https://t.co/XOt8VJOoha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/DncoRLIW4J https://t.co/fWBhJFdb4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tableau Developer: JOB TITLE: Tableau Developer JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: This individual will be responsible for identifying, designing and deploying solutions to help the business drive insights from transactional data to drive… https://t.co/dUte3dyhwF https://t.co/Su3vBhWc9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – Automation Engineer: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US QA Automation Engineerfor Medical Devices Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/E172gXBPvk https://t.co/sofuYxiw1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Blockchain Engineer – JavaScript, Python, A.I: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Blockchain Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in Sunnyvale, CA with recent capital investments we are a fast… https://t.co/ocT8z27t25 https://t.co/bMg4wu7oaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Cybersecurity Engineer Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/1XHLxbM4uc https://t.co/t688wrWMmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/bBRs4SUle6 https://t.co/rZ1MYJBq18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer [Python &amp; JavaScript]: JOB DESCRIPTION Our clients product team is expanding and seeking top-tier senior engineers (Full Stack and Back End Engineers). Theyre looking for independent thinkers that want to take ownership of parts… https://t.co/6bIlKjdPTM https://t.co/tSCaxqygwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Architect (Python/Javascript): Old Mission Capital, a global quantitative proprietary trading firm is currently hiring a Senior Web Architect/Developer to work in our Chicago office. The Senior Web Architect/Developer will be responsible for… https://t.co/N229JgjRlx https://t.co/XPHDsP31a6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/fTbpxhJy7X https://t.co/qSbHW1x010]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: At SwiftStack, were creating a purpose-built object storage system to help companies store, manage, and access the petabytes of data they generate in the course of their business. We are primary contributors to OpenStack Swift, the… https://t.co/xg1IQKWkVX https://t.co/rxhKvFGwb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS – Financial Crimes Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/KMwS70LPHF https://t.co/tzRO127ivK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Software Developer: Prestigious Financials Firm is currently seeking a Web Software Engineer with Python development skills. Candidate will design, develop, deploy, and support batch systems. Candidate will help architect systems, optimize… https://t.co/VKEU38s8gE https://t.co/t1e4MucSR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/m3GxAU2C4X https://t.co/Inv2ypr54I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/t8REHK5XRA https://t.co/ojQ1Z90Ujg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/DMHvA8Rn8p https://t.co/6q9pnomOUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer IV / Python Developer: Required Skills: * BS or MS computer science * 4 years experience in software development * Experience with Python &amp; Java Nice to Have Skills/Not Required: * JavaScript, Django, &amp; Raptical/MySQL database *… https://t.co/Qh7VkwSMjI https://t.co/xDtQQFOJ6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VC++ Developer: VC++ Developer – Asconsoft Inc – Saint Louis, MO – 03-22-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career Toolkit Articles –… https://t.co/29NyAI59ER https://t.co/XRJNoX3xbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-end Developer: We are looking for an experienced Back-end developer to join our team. You will be responsible for supporting and improving functionality of the product. Responsibilities * Participate in the entire application lifecycle, focusing on… https://t.co/w2mZbxqhFr https://t.co/4Fyv2xFK9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Automation Engineer: Senior Network Automation Engineer $140-170K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Wilmington, DE or Omaha, NE* The Senior Network Automation Engineer is self-directed and highly autonomous, detail oriented,… https://t.co/Z4E2f34VQK https://t.co/1z3SBKEWQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer, Back End: The Role: Course Hero is changing education by building a global community of students, the largest digital library of study materials, and innovative machine learning technology to support both learning and teaching.… https://t.co/XErV4Da2Dj https://t.co/Rb1530Ek2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/OKGVv8HZEV https://t.co/8hs2dEioRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/epQI0gLdow https://t.co/k3GxQhC0EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Technology Director: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/kl5sdN0plO https://t.co/KczMimF0mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activist fund says Toshiba chip unit worth as much as $40 billion: TOKYO (Reuters) - A Hong Kong-based activist investment fund said Toshiba Corp's chip unit was worth as much as $40 billion, double the sale price agreed with a Bain-led consortium, as it… https://t.co/Ay7NR3M9FH https://t.co/xr4ZbkQ0ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Middle Tier Java Developer – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/hBOcwEHHB2 https://t.co/SxgzHdPzpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/oApF5GP2qs https://t.co/Lxx9oFkTr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Test: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/3gAYP0o8QZ https://t.co/mJQlWvFgtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Should have Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream * Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python * Should Have… https://t.co/0OWNRTuvZ6 https://t.co/Z5QXx30w4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical SEO Overlord: Description: We’re looking for a world-class SEO genius to join our team. You know who you are: You were around before Panda, Penguin, and even Caffeine. You do on-page with your eyes closed, and reverse engineer backlink profiles… https://t.co/kfyZvRz1F7 https://t.co/rC17RZJN1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/2O8hrkWTO2 https://t.co/JbfjUHzw5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted 01/11/2018 Located in a beautiful office in the Mission District in San Francisco, we are an early staged funded B2C Fin-Tech start up that is combining Artificial Intelligence, Machine… https://t.co/M5S3Yi9wES https://t.co/410Eg3Rrpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Data Engineer: Junior Data Engineer Stonecrop Technologies, a telecom innovator focusing on improving the speed and motions of developing and improving communication networks seeks a savvy Data Engineering Manager to lead our Supply Chain Data &amp;… https://t.co/BR2ymOiYLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Engineer: Description:The Program provides sustainment support for selected legacy exploitation software applications until they can be retired or returned into service.  The legacy software application sustainment is taken over from… https://t.co/tmtEh3Twjg https://t.co/xVR2dZixa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation hardware Engineer: Validation hardware Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Be able to build out and setup of PC client systems (hardware and software) Experience in Software validation and executing test cases Experience… https://t.co/h70ac0jLMQ https://t.co/Qd6wuUZ2MB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/zRMnCCJbOF https://t.co/wnJihh3Kuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Req ID : 410768BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Orion Test &amp; Verification Engineer. This person will be responsible for writing test success criteria, developing test procedures, scripts and… https://t.co/XGid1qI1N3 https://t.co/DDExryBDKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer downtown Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsPython DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD from IT Serve Phone – Skype 5 month project in downtown Chicago. Please… https://t.co/7ZJSIrqyKn https://t.co/38uTcNrH9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS IOT Developer: AWS IOT Developer Indiana, Indiana ID ******* Overview: Our Client is Global leader in IT services, digital and business solutions that partners with its client to simplify, strengthen and transform their businesses. Our Client has… https://t.co/rhbTxqd01S https://t.co/On0R0iVeQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/3uIY0V1bTM https://t.co/6ojzaFIXSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-end Developer: This fast-growing company is adding to their staff. The technology is a scalable platform that has both mobile and web applications. They use some of the most modern and robust technologies in their stack including: Docker, RESTful… https://t.co/l72MFftM7k https://t.co/Pwp2hTB2Cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Hardware Engineer: Senior Hardware Engineer Job Description KCP Global R&amp;D Roswell, GA at Kimberly-Clark Senior Engineer-Hardware Requisition No. ****** We are currently seeking a highly motivated senior engineer to join the Kimberly-Clark… https://t.co/En1LsH8cmm https://t.co/w9ycYMJvfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/PCywwavoKy https://t.co/ZKIqY38TNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Adminstrator/DevOps Engineer: Description: Leidos is seeking a DevOps engineer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for the CEGS system, a real-time operational SIGINT processor. The CEGS applications run under a virtualized… https://t.co/GQnko9ILTQ https://t.co/msVNn4vlzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer (C++/ Python) Hillsboro OR Full Time position Job Responsibilities Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework… https://t.co/unGn5YF4Hr https://t.co/xV9UxP8z9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/3VYFywTjMe https://t.co/QEOo2lGhzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab's Uber deal still has some obstacles to navigate: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Regulatory scrutiny could complicate ride-hailing company Grab's takeover of Uber Technologies' Southeast Asian business, but there is little the authorities can do to stop Uber… https://t.co/WYFdPVGcCX https://t.co/TkQ4ghJi9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/iIBMHniKEv https://t.co/XN4bonBtRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Security Engineer: Position Summary: The Secure Coding Team, of the world renowned CERT division of the Software Engineering Institute, is a pioneer of the identification and development of secure coding and secure software development… https://t.co/8jXqIJgaET https://t.co/TGThAClziD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/xyMfmsBqdv https://t.co/ZXDtZvGWHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: In this exciting role, CW will be part of a fast-paced storage I/O R&amp;D team creating and maintaining tools for running experiments and process data in support of… https://t.co/UP214qFGhN https://t.co/Bbpe0IK2Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Security Engineer: Workiva started with an idea: to make complex collaboration easy. Wdesk is an all in one platform that simplifies complex collaboration while keeping data in sync, thus reducing risk. Thousands of organizations, including over… https://t.co/IxgqTnnY7Y https://t.co/cgD7g4Zo5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Engineer: Workiva started with an idea: to make complex collaboration easy. Wdesk is an all in one platform that simplifies complex collaboration while keeping data in sync, thus reducing risk. Thousands of organizations, including over 70% of… https://t.co/Th0iDVfcwu https://t.co/0Si3x7yLQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Software Engineer IILocation: Salt Lake City, UT The Software Engineer II designs, develops, tests and maintains the NICE inContact software platform. Key responsibilities include all tiers of the NICE inContact technology, including… https://t.co/jNMq9yhhAS https://t.co/hTtMliYF7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Analyst | AWS Cloud Formation (YAML, JSON, PowerShell, Python): Production Support Analyst | AWS Cloud Formation (YAML, JSON, PowerShell, Python) Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has… https://t.co/kr5x6ReGl1 https://t.co/ujDXOPoNiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/yZ8PDfECw9 https://t.co/T6CNPGyD02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Lafayette, Louisiana, United States Position ID: J0318-2009 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals Build a Career that Matters at CGI’s Lafayette Center Position Description: Want to… https://t.co/XmAN3aJohs https://t.co/X5BqudjoFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Should have Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream * Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python * Should Have… https://t.co/H4qF6z7wvZ https://t.co/xwn8wdFdKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Technical Officer – https://t.co/rCWhgwLmlo: ********** is looking for a hands-on Chief Technical Officer to manage a team of developers and data scientists. ********** is a leading online service provider to lawyers and consumers. Our servers… https://t.co/rUfZa3RUf4 https://t.co/ygnNGGYhkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Software Developer: As we build and scale Crystal over the next few years, our product &amp; engineering group is growing along with it. We’re building the largest, most accurate personality platform in the world – it’s a huge project that… https://t.co/v13InbE3yn https://t.co/tHKDR2ik0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: We are looking for a Mid Level Python Developer for a full-time direct-hire role with our client in North Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Operate and develop within enterprise data environment hosted on AWS. Preferred experience/skills:… https://t.co/G6MiU2G5JD https://t.co/vn0wKOiVkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/aoA05jaQDp https://t.co/lBM9xN66vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – Fraud Detection: Are you an experienced Data Analyst looking to join a rapidly growing startup in the exciting space of fraud detection? WHATS THE JOB? As a Data Analyst, you will be using your knowledge of fraud while matching it with… https://t.co/X6wDPFNRJz https://t.co/XkQ5SrGgV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/Sn8Q1HqUdp https://t.co/WvW5oJqYIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x programming Strong Design and Development… https://t.co/DLaqlDa4bv https://t.co/McmT2FO4ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – TS/SCI with polygraph: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment extends beyond the… https://t.co/H91suMJobz https://t.co/538rjhczDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist ($150-180k) – Python and MATLAB: San Francisco, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today Job Title: Financial Controller Job Location: San Francisco, CA Salary: ($150-180k) Based in San Francisco, CA, we are an exciting medical… https://t.co/Wn6G91Yga9 https://t.co/pm1As70EvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer: As the nations leading bottled water company, Nestlé Waters North America is dedicated to providing customers with healthy hydration options. Alongside that, were also committed to developing our people enabling them to make the… https://t.co/UBDurPUFxU https://t.co/TQRykHe7gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Who we are: Arable Labs, Inc. is a venture-backed startup founded by scientists to provide crop monitoring and point precision weather forecasts – a complete approach to crop management. (https://t.co/oIwfiVV0ZW). What we need: We are… https://t.co/gz0olSiPuO https://t.co/gTfSKg9jaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook fined $33 million for failing to aid Brazil graft probe: BRASILIA (Reuters) - A Brazilian judge has ordered that Facebook Inc pay 111.7 million reais ($33.4 million) for failing to cooperate with a corruption investigation, federal prosecutors… https://t.co/76XcXcHrao https://t.co/KzqKwX0Foq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/FyYO9BXPEC https://t.co/X7MfE9fqvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure Cloud Solutions Engineer: At Northwestern Mutual, we believe relationships are built on trust. That our lives and our work matter. These beliefs launched our company nearly 160 years ago. Today, they’re just a few of the reasons why people choose… https://t.co/iAfiVW1adg https://t.co/f2mdAsKTTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software applications. Master’s in Computer… https://t.co/WNb6cFID8i https://t.co/EJo4keMrUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineering: Description: Job Description This position is a Systems Engineer on the Exploitation Services (program), working hand-in-hand with the ACE, Chief Architect (CA), Chief Engineer (CE) and the Program Management Leadership team… https://t.co/TCoviOEP7E https://t.co/2kHgo86GTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users… https://t.co/dBbEbrDjKC https://t.co/oLZZxPMxG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Linux / Platform Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/sQlVeDcDSF https://t.co/BS6JDH6kki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description: The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) is seeking a Software Developer in Aurora, Colorado to support maintenance and development for a real-time operational SIGINT processing system. The applications are implemented in C++… https://t.co/nZu3du4xBx https://t.co/p3i6D2QNY3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>