<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Which quote here is better: number six or seven? http://t.co/6X9ax1AuNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "It is the mark of great people to treat trifles as trifles and important matters as important." - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will receive everything you need when you stop asking for what you do not need - Sri Nisargadatta Maharaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: Some days it takes a lot of courage to be yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Inspirational Quotes http://t.co/UBBUyaiQAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consciousness is much more than the thorn, it is the dagger in the flesh. - Emile Michel Cioran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not about what you can accumulate. I learned to live when I learned to give. - Anne Beiler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: There are no shortcuts to any place worth going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: Something that's of common interest to every man, woman and child on the planet must surely be the notion of 'Peace'. ~ An…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any emotion, if it is sincere, is involuntary. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: When you stand before God, you stand before the creator of the universe, the one who can solve any problem, if you just as…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are my butterfly and I refuse to set you free. - Shannon Hale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only one thing that can heal the heart... Only one... It's love. - Masashi Kishimoto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/eNaXG8uqel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: It is never too late to be what you might have been. -George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's to opening and upward... and to yourself and up with you and up with and up with laughing. - e.e. cummings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: If you do not think about your future, you cannot have one. -John Galsworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Classic Books while you work http://t.co/8EgULgzBlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love, all alike, no season knows, nor clime, nor hours, days, months, which are the rags of time. - John Donne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Great Motivational Quotes here: http://t.co/nLd2ofUQFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[«Everything has been figured out, except how to live.» — Jean-Paul Sartre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which quote here is better: number six or seven? http://t.co/B0oYIbzTsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: Do not judge my story by the chapter you walked in on. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Classic Books while you work http://t.co/YvLRCxjPZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/59d5m1hjm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seventh quote here is a killer... http://t.co/MfeQa8085c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Happiness doesn't result from what we get, but from what we give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: All mankind's inner feelings eventually manifest themselves as an outer reality. ~ Stuart Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this app to Listen to Motivational Books on your Android phone http://t.co/0OQmHGvMPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[browse some motivational quotes here  http://t.co/jZ7FADRplC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened. - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True happiness is when the love that is within us finds expression in external activities. - Mata Amritanandamayi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: If you keep putting off doing what matters most, you will start doing what matters least, a cycle of unfulfillment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's always room for love; You just have to move a few things around. - Anoymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanting to be someone else is a waste of who you are - Kurt Cobain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: The best &amp; most beautiful things in life cannot be seen, not touched, but are felt in the heart. -Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never know the quality of someone else's life, though we seldom resist the temptation to assume and pass judgement. - Tami Hoag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years teach much the days never know. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: "Not to be occupied and not to exist amount to the same thing." -Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: No one has ever become poor by giving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a fine line between love and http://t.co/IuaxsgXFGS frees a soul and in the same breath can sometimes suffocate it. - Cecelia Ahern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Books are the mirrors of the soul. - Virginia Woolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/668jBljItF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "The gem cannot be polished without friction, nor man perfected without trials." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which quote here is better: number six or seven? http://t.co/0HeyEbhgki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which quote here is better: number six or seven? http://t.co/7knWH61bsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: A true friend someone who says nice things behind your back. - Anthony Hall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Stop wishing for something to happen and go make it happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend of mine once defined love as finding someone you can talk to late into the night - James Patterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How satisfying it is to leave a mark on a blank surface. To make a map of my movement - no matter how temporary. - Craig Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: It is never too late. Even if you are going to die tomorrow, keep yourself straight and clear and be a happy human being t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: You must be ever flowing like a stream, so as to stave off stagnancy, which will only leave you feeling dead inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will wear my heart upon my sleeve for daws to peak at. - william shekespear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seventh quote here is a killer... http://t.co/g6cD0FGR9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Everything we hear is an opinion, not a fact. Everything we see is a perspective, not the truth. - Marcus Aurelius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: Courage is the first of human qualities because it is the quality which guarantees the others. -Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: The best way to predict the future is to create it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the life of your dreams. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness. The word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of health for both mind and body is: http://t.co/U6eFWk4c8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I trust that everything happens for a reason, even if  http://t.co/zTU3XoSRVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: At the end of the day, it is what it is. - Unk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: A true friend sees the good in everything, and brings out the best in the worst of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When one tugs at a single thing in nature http://t.co/P4S5qHvj33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Act as if what you do makes a difference http://t.co/V46WVK7Dc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's http://t.co/hm0fmTqMCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: Please don't block these doors... http://t.co/Kt8VHrJMas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: If you wish others to understand you, show them your true self, drop the pretence &amp; show them the unguarded view of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you can, with what you have, where you are http://t.co/1P4i4DYeJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday is not ours to recover, but... http://t.co/FFz0RTer5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Being powerful is like being a lady. If you have to tell people you are, you aren't. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not defined by the family into which we are born, but the one we choose and create. We are not born, we become.  -Tori Spelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: Nobody grows old merely by living a number of years. We grow old by deserting our ideals. -Samuel Ullman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You often meet your fate on the road you take to avoid it. -Goldie Hawn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not how you start out, it's where you end up. -Dee Dee M. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Eventually all things fall into place. Until then, laugh at the confusion, live for the moments, and know everything happen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "Everything comes to him who hustles while he waits." - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About Learners, Doers and Teachers: http://t.co/CWDS9DE3c4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action is the antidote to despair  http://t.co/kBaXUfGQHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a succesion of lessons which must be lived to be understood. -Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that is necessary for evil to succeed is: http://t.co/b3Ihm6bWeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Love this. http://t.co/BWEQh9KL0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And life is what we make it... http://t.co/Sm06tp0Jma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people die with their music still in them. Why is this so? Too often it is because they are always getting ready to live...  -Oliver We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn’t the problems along the way that make us... http://t.co/8hy7KZrUsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m a great believer in luck… http://t.co/DzJvYOIfqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Through all of living have much joy and laughter, life is to be enjoyed, not just endured. - Gordon B. Hinckley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: The seed of love is within every act of kindness, a seed that will grow in the heart of the recipient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: God has a blessing with your name on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what they are called, the spaces between seconds? but I think of you always in those intervals. - Salvador Plascencia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Inspiring Classic Books on your Android device http://t.co/qgLYKVpNiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: Let your heart soar as high as it will. Refuse to be average. -A.W. Tozer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: You can't control how they treat you, but you can sure as hell control if you accept it. - Charles Orlando]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourning your first love is as important as meeting your first love. It's the whole cycle. - Jane Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two ways to be happy: improve your reality, or lower your expectations. - Jodi Picoult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Inspirational Quotes http://t.co/sT5DVgBb3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can see it, you can achieve it.  God helps those who helps themselves. Power is in the act of humility. - Patricia Amis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: People change, memories don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the few things in life that cannot possibly do harm in the end is the honest pursuit of the truth. - Peter Kreeft]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>