<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The weird thing is that this guy teaches in the "Negotiation, Organizations &amp; Markets unit" at HBS. And this is how he negotiates?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will there be a run on MetLife's short-term debt, requiring it to sell off assets and bringing down the financial system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently Blythe Masters wanted to go with JPMorgan's physical commodities business as chief executive officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The IRS doesn't actually give companies extra money if they report negative net income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we can leave the tax code the way it is and simplify it, or you could go to a form of a flat tax. You could go to a fair tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Carl Icahn, among others, gets a pass here, since he's basically playing with his own money.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have, as you may have noticed, become something of a connoisseur of bond market liquidity worries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careful though: The happy-to-grumpy ratio seems to have peaked in mid-2008, some time before the Lehman bankruptcy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one, on the other hand, is on the way out. Congrats everyone on beating the scourge of illiquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-- but the shareholder thing is reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you put bonds into the trust, your liquidity comes from selling trust certificates, not taking the bonds out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if it is a subsidy, what do you do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without a professional adviser, the research contends, these savers would simply leave their money in the bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is purportedly in some momentarily exciting line of business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, a law telling people what is and isn't criminal might be nice. And: "Insider trading law is a mens rea morass."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certainly the restrictions seem bad for liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WCW, which is owned by ECW Wireless, has the same address and senior managers as high-frequency trader Jump Trading LLC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, volatility is back, and that's not entirely a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, the post office went to the SEC and said "hey we have guys who keep demanding that we delay their mail to avoid your regulations?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone seems to have calmed down a bit since yesterday morning. So get comfortable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, here are Nicolas Veron and Gavyn Davies on the European stress tests. And even in the Treasury market, liquidity is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't you expect that it was mostly a one-campaign stunt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're looking for derivatives everywhere, you'll find them everywhere, which is possibly ESMA's problem here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulators think bankers are 
bad people
. Your mileage may vary with this one: Is that the deal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, it's discouraged. But the SEC review process is rather less stringent than it is for an initial public offering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's not expecting a numbered list of 22 reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stealing $41 million from your company? Not securities fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, yes, PwC represented that it was "maintaining integrity and objectivity."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor do you hear a lot of people going around saying "hey a guy who has had a lot of success at negotiating things is Eric Cantor."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you run into jerks all day, you're the jerk." Also he is on "Real Housewives of New Jersey."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That "within the Southern District of New York" doesn't mean they were in New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see why the court was unimpressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure. This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of Bloomberg View's editorial board or Bloomberg LP, its owners and investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And because a bank's income is largely about changes in those valuation, measurements of income are also "grossly undermined."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That said, you probably don't care about microsecond-level efficiency, so it's not clear, like, how much HFT efficiency you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some relevant points: 
  One question is, will Goldman match? Will there be an arms race among banks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it was an obvious pyramid scheme, it would have been obvious by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valeant. I wrote about Valeant on Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it's not particularly easy or pleasant for humans to be human either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should companies be able to use poison pills 
keep out activists
? I'm kind of a no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ecuadorean gold swaps. Ecuador, like many other countries, keeps some of its reserves in the form of a pile of gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks are more profitable when rates are higher and steeper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is the easiest, most predictable and safest way to invest," Tormos says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Felix Salmon's alphabetical list of reasons for Alphabet is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[), and the SEC won't answer questions or publish guidelines to help people understand it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bond dealers 
price discriminate
. The SEC is investigating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Or equivalent badness, e.g. criminal penalties.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine There's this, and this, and just imagine being the last well-known bear to capitulate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckcrberg said "yes" and that he could not pay $4,300,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is also adding features to broaden its appeal, and berating itself for being terrible at handling abuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is, don't buy a basketball team, but you knew that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those investors could have trouble cashing in if the IPO market isn’t able to support even higher valuations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can read a lot of obituaries for Bill Gross's bond-picking skills; here are Megan McArdle and Gillian Tett, for instance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil. Things are bad, if you're in the oil business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh fine and this:  After a free historical tour of the Israeli port city Jaffa, Weis had offered to tip his tour guide in bitcoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One simple view might be that public ownership is not optimal for some (all?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For months everyone in financial markets has been talking about liquidity," says Antonio Weiss of Treasury, and don't I know it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valeant will hold a conference call on Monday to say more, but Monday is kind of a long time from now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_C_Klein In the future, the only jobs that the robots won't take will be the jobs that require specifically human attributes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of paperwork, Bill Ackman messed up a presentation about Valeant's cash flow, which, I mean, it happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine (Incidentally there is some empirical evidence against this proposition.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Ackman some friends of his for their time, for obvious enough reasons, but still what is the incentive to do this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M&amp;A types are not happy about this; one says "The measures were clearly thought up by people living in the last century." At least!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically the way to commit accounting fraud is to overstate your income, and the way to commit tax fraud is to understate your income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not for any particular regulatory reason, just so we can all kibbitz about short campaigns the way we do on long activist campaigns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investment banks will pitch a deal to anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" But that premise is unexamined and also sort of demonstrably wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like Credit Suisse is going to invest the 6 billion francs in something revolutionary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if they claw back your prior pay -- and they won't! -- you still end up with zero, which is still an asymmetric incentive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're looking for derivatives everywhere, you'll find them everywhere, which is possibly ESMA's problem here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Are you ready to read an interesting letter? Because Carl Icahn has promised to send one to Apple today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Twitter gets more terrible in an effort to become Facebook, Facebook is outflanking it by becoming even more terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But its laser focus on pleasing the people who don't like or understand Twitter is not a great sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" If Uber went public and raised just under a billion dollars, that would be the fourth-largest U.S. initial public offering this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The current strategy of bonuses going up while profits go down doesn't seem to be working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, also: There are actually laws against theft!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh by the way it's worth noticing (?) that this argument doesn't run in reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, it paid $150 million for the shares, so I guess $20 million of the gain is DB's problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asness and his crew at AQR Capital Management have a very interesting and thorough defense of high frequency trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" Is that just whining about regulation, or does he mean it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the thinking here seems to be: I see the logic, but I don't buy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand the impetus for Twitter to attract new users who don't already like Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational risk is just made up to reflect a best guess as to how much a bank is likely to, oh, you know, pay in fines, mostly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are complications involving tender offers; consider the Valeant/Pershing Square bid for Allergan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Twitter Followers. Carl Icahn's letters about Apple are a great study in financial rhetoric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere, here is William Cohan asking, "Can Bankers Behave?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Fidelity Labs unveiled StockCity, a Sims-like virtual reality game that turns your stock portfolio into a city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story continues as you might expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The statute of limitations for bringing securities fraud cases is five years. Do you see the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as a big shareholder, you have some ability to influence the activists who are, after all, campaigning for your vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you choose to learn about a baseball game this way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is much harder to follow than actual Twitter. Even worse is this Moment about the Nobel Prize in Physics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of Bloomberg View's editorial board or Bloomberg LP, its owners and investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, though, people are worried about bond market income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess the analysts always want to believe that they're special.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "misappropriation theory" of insider trading does not seem to me to be obvious on this point, but I guess I wouldn't do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a twenty-hour-a-week job, and still probably worth it for all of them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*** I topped out at VP too, since you ask, but I usually supervised someone. I mean I supervised them pretty loosely, but still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or maybe "people are coining weird new unicorn words."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which sound ... celebratory rather than manipulative? I don't know.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>