<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Move IT Engineer: Requisition ID: 17032718 Primary Location:United States-North Carolina-Raleigh Category:Product &amp; Systems Design Engineering Description Conduent is the world’s largest provider of diversified business process services with leading… https://t.co/QzEXLEQTAh https://t.co/nlzpxtWRKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Program Protection and Anti-Tamper Engineer: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical reconnaissance radars, as well as… https://t.co/jKCp7dpigY https://t.co/Hg1gJpOXMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Blue Tactics and CONOPS Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team… https://t.co/DryY3z4mby https://t.co/rOU1enIkeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Helpdesk Support Specialist: ARC Document Solutions, Inc. provides technology and services to businesses of all types, with a focus on the architectural, engineering and construction industry. ARC provides its solutions at thousands of customer… https://t.co/qMVnMi5Bmw https://t.co/LszwggvyJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Full Time: Job Description Are you a natural programmer who loves to build real-time applications and systems that make an immediate impact? Are you passionate about building software that challenges and inspires you every day? At… https://t.co/c2GPjIsmPI https://t.co/XvCDU6lQV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Network Analyst (CAN) – Level 1 (TS/SCI FSP required): Candidates must already possess an Active TS/SCI Full Scope Polygraph RESPONSIBILITIES * Perform research utilizing Agency resource tools and databases; * Provide analytic support at… https://t.co/cKrM0z2Y58 https://t.co/eLdlOR4IaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With ‘Sniffs’ and ‘Licks,’ Petzbe Makes Social Media Nice Again: When people are impersonating their pets online, they tend to be really, really nice. https://t.co/6zN7bPmATG https://t.co/nts0j2rEmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager CRM: The Dynamics NAV Project Manager will ensure that project teams have a full understanding of the customers requirements and the direction for a Dynamics NAV solution. In addition, they will oversee and manage the planning, design and… https://t.co/XLErRYfV4Q https://t.co/VgXWHdGte7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Analyst: What you’ll be doing: As a Security Analyst you will be trained from the ground up in security risk, remediation, vendor risk assessments, and healthcare security frameworks. This is a great opportunity to learn from an expert in the… https://t.co/HNJfJDJyUS https://t.co/bkk1plPJ4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/QA Tester: Description: Conduent is the world’s largest provider of diversified business process services with leading capabilities in transaction processing, automation, analytics and constituent experience. We work with both government and… https://t.co/yWGqa1LRje https://t.co/wLVaH2xhTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer, Originations: UI Developer, Originations Why Work For Credit Acceptance? Credit Acceptance is rapidly-expanding our IT department with a variety of dynamic opportunities. Our culture has landed us on Computerworld’s list of the Best Places… https://t.co/XqwjeoEVAW https://t.co/mjfbuROLxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Device Driver Developer: Embedded Software Engineer Santa Clara, CA Fulltime Position Job Description – Bachelors, Masters or PhD. Degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science or Engineering, Software Engineering, Mobile Communications or… https://t.co/R1zLBubNnU https://t.co/ybNW7PeiRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. ETL Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Los Angeles, California, United States Position ID: J0318-0397 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: POSITION DESCRIPTION CGI has an immediate need for an Informatica ETL Developer to… https://t.co/SveCRkNFRr https://t.co/j43FiKtSf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Applications Manager: Business Operations Applications Manager Posted Date 1 week ago(3/8/2018 4:13 PM) ID 2018-30359 Job Location USA-MN-Bloomington | USA-MA-Taunton Category Information Technology Employment Type Full Time Hiring… https://t.co/qA9LiIDAEs https://t.co/lgxb2MUnwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer | Informatica/Oracle (Dimensional Data Modeling and Data Profiling): ETL Developer | Informatica/Oracle (Dimensional Data Modeling and Data Profiling) | CareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service… https://t.co/dfJ7yT4kOV https://t.co/8PAyt42XK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. C++ Developer Client Development / Client Delivery | Loraine, OH | Contract Job Description WE ARE A TRANSFORMATIONAL PARTNER We marry design and… https://t.co/Gbyl02OGgw https://t.co/bTSVvvVzWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: We are seeking a Senior .NET developer responsible for the design, build and maintenance of .NET applications/services, both within our self-hosted and cloud (Azure) environments. The primary responsibilities will be to design,… https://t.co/HyoUcPULOf https://t.co/UCGiFKnJ95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partner Engineer: As a Partner Engineer, you will develop and drive Procores App Marketplace technical relationship with key software partners and their customers, establishing deep technical integrations and setting clear expectations for business… https://t.co/uYsv8aAW2i https://t.co/hzJIYDucjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Easter Tech Sales (2018): Nintendo, Apple, Dyson, Lenovo: When you're done painting eggs and munching on candy, check out these Easter tech deals. https://t.co/odngD3Rsm8 https://t.co/FvGUuOJtEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Overview Ralis Services Corp. is currently seeking bright, motivated and result-oriented candidates to fill a full-time position as a Salesforce Developer within our expanding, dynamic IT team. The ideal candidate will have a strong… https://t.co/1FS3BqZdcD https://t.co/8FOW4dGx3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer: Job Description: The Petaluma Health Center’s mission is to provide high quality health care, with access for all, in Southern Sonoma County. The Center accomplishes this mission through collaborative, innovative programs, services… https://t.co/hzXtaNdqZs https://t.co/b9g9qcNd9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sales: Zycus is hiring Regional Software Sales Manager for North East Region. Zycus headquarters was incorporated in Princeton, U.S. in 1988. Since then, we have grown everyday, and established as an organization which now is a leading global… https://t.co/dgCBbo3QT3 https://t.co/Pl09wBfGXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Overview New position alert! KUBRA Arizona is looking for a skilled Developer. As a Developer, you will work on a team to implement enterprise customer experience management software for our clients. What you get to do every day Write code and… https://t.co/3jn6L4mjGy https://t.co/83cu9t2vBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Web Applications: CORPORATE VISION STATEMENT: To be and become known as the best service provider in our industry. SUMMARY OF RESPONSIBILITIES: Every team member of the C Spire Crew is charged with bringing our strategic vision of… https://t.co/lsGGbMndZ0 https://t.co/vzfYHO9F7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager: Duties: Software deployment and systems architect Requirements: Experience 5 years career experience 2-3 years of experience managing development – team preferred Education Bachelor’s of Computer Science Skills Must be… https://t.co/yoRbQmOufa https://t.co/czJJDBSsnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 1: ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH A POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE Description: Design, development, and testing of Web-based GUIs backed by RESTFUL web services. Design and development of RESTful web services created with… https://t.co/8HSMruhoZj https://t.co/u4tCmazzOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Architect: The American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) is a professional membership organization of songwriters, composers and music publishers of every kind of music. ASCAP’s mission is to license and promote the music… https://t.co/2evq5GybwP https://t.co/1jz1vOn73P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Engineer 1 (Linux Administrator): ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH A POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Job Description: Provide intermediate/advance Linux user and server support. Responsibilities of this position include, but not limited to:… https://t.co/idvhGs24sU https://t.co/1Ib3AdNIGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counter-Air Threat Modeling Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Counter-Air Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions… https://t.co/0UJyfU7j4e https://t.co/s9hjZCT7dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Desktop Support: POSITION SUMMARY: Pace, North America’s leading and largest independent brand storytelling agency, is looking for an IT Desktop Support Specialist to join our team in Greensboro, NC. The IT Desktop Support Specialist is responsible… https://t.co/RMzNG5GpL7 https://t.co/CIsLIF6lcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Software Engineering: SUMMARY This role will be responsible for Leading and developing a global software engineering product team responsible for the development of Jamfs flagship Apple device management solution, Jamf Pro, and the Jamf… https://t.co/4T9LipJ2xV https://t.co/usd1I7AuEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Fold 5 High-Flying Stunt Paper Airplanes: "The Paper Airplane Guy" John Collins shows us how to fold planes that do loops, flap their wings, and fly world-record distances. https://t.co/zenG4nIXv3 https://t.co/RhgZSdr4Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magento Developer: The Evolutions Footwear, Inc. Family of Brands is currently seeking a full-time, on-site Magento developer to join our team in Camarillo, CA. Duties would primarily consist of developing new projects built using the Magento platform,… https://t.co/FjwsninqTw https://t.co/UcbTuMTIv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer: ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Description: Seeking an experienced Senior Systems Engineer to provide technical support and system engineering for a rules engine processing system. The… https://t.co/cX6PLScCTc https://t.co/sHPqBWNB8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/LiAiFK910k https://t.co/7kg9cmea4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Ruby: Panoply is a podcast network [************************************************** providing listeners with high-quality, smart audio shows. Panoply creates, distributes, and monetizes audio content from dozens of publishers,… https://t.co/fxArcnVH6W https://t.co/lmyQu99Xn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Boston): QuantumBlack helps companies use data to drive decisions. We combine business experience, expertise in large-scale data analysis and visualization, and advanced software engineering know-how to deliver results. From… https://t.co/41rHARZSJZ https://t.co/vVdCzFZPnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: QA AUTOMATION ENGINEER ABOUT US The Farmers Dog is a VC backed (Series A, raised $10.1M) direct-to-consumer pet health brand on a mission to disrupt the $60 Billion pet food industry. Our products are human-quality, personalized and… https://t.co/upGfTrJdw3 https://t.co/qWtkFcrSBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staffing Executive RHMR Salaried Professional Services: JOB REQUISITION Staffing Executive RHMR Salaried Professional Services LOCATION CA SAN JOSE JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within RHI, combining the best of… https://t.co/dbZbhK53SJ https://t.co/wp4JCyOeMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II – UI Angular and Java Developer: Job Summary: The Treasury Services department of the Federal Reserve Bank of Kansas City is seeking a Software Engineer II. The Federal Reserve plays a major role in operating the nation’s payment… https://t.co/Rcp2FegA4S https://t.co/Keuj9Jkuwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29772BR Domain Utilities Skillset SharePoint Portal Server (SPS) , Country USA State / Region / Province Delaware Work Location Wilmington, DE Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys – MSWTPU –… https://t.co/DbHHQLYQe6 https://t.co/gwDP5wBjs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mainframe Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Baltimore, Maryland, United States Position ID: J0118-1738 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI Federal is… https://t.co/yC6MinjBbO https://t.co/8dyYlE5FgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Developer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA… https://t.co/P0Blml69iK https://t.co/ynL4ACYfGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Managers: Microsoft Corporation currently has the following openings in Irvine, CA (job opportunities available at all levels, e.g., Principal, Senior and Lead levels). Program Managers: Coordinate program development of computer software… https://t.co/BU4Uy0XKbl https://t.co/bscJ0IHOm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoPro Hero: Specs, Price, Release Date: The new camera, called simply GoPro Hero, can't do 4K, but it's a great value at $1`99. https://t.co/OwvOo79Lua https://t.co/8w00dbVUM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPER: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, Cary, NC: Limited domestic travel and/or relocate occasionally to client locations nationwide to design, develop, maintain various applications using .NET, C# technologies; work with MVC design pattern, LINQ, MS… https://t.co/r5JQcKZJgA https://t.co/8WIyms2mpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer:   TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center… https://t.co/ykWu0S6vju https://t.co/F6WP93Hjcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Project Supervisor: Gratiot County is seeking an Information Technology Project Supervisor for oversight and operation of our IT systems. This position will oversee, coordinate and assist the county’s full service IT contractor… https://t.co/jD3TOZkB8O https://t.co/2svLdE0jaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: JOB RESPONSIBILITIES: Contingent on Award Would you like to perform rewarding work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company?Pragmatics, Inc. is seeking aSoftware Developer to support our government customer.… https://t.co/b6M6ktGL7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: The Business Operations Analyst will help support internal business intelligence, metrics, reporting, and modeling of data. Reporting to the Business Operations Program Manager, they will work directly with leadership and… https://t.co/UHhH1EgXDh https://t.co/uAxMUsAoyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary Operations Analyst: Temporary Operations Analyst This is a temporary full time position, expected to last between 6 to 9 months. Individual will reside within the Operations group, reporting directly to the Director of Operations in our… https://t.co/2b9t15miQS https://t.co/vDwD07guc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analysts #CG, 555: TransUnion, LLC seeks Senior Analysts for Chicago, IL location to assist in the design, implementation &amp; administration of strategic compensation programs. Master’s in Economics/Applied Economics, Compensation, or Statistics + 2… https://t.co/rBGL2rsDtY https://t.co/xNvac0TENb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst III: Iowa State University is seeking applicants for a Network Architect. This position works within a team of network architects and engineers responsible for architecting, implementing, securing, and administering the university’s data… https://t.co/r1lCAgx3h7 https://t.co/ogfaSUYXfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Information Analyst – Seton Northwest: Shift : Tuesday – Saturday 7a -3:30p Set your sights on a role making a real difference in the healthcare system. We’re looking for a self-motivated Health Information Analyst to join our team. We have a… https://t.co/PjaQ5XZG54 https://t.co/WlEqymLleV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/XTFZweqyXP https://t.co/nA3aQB5aCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Systems AnalystBriXcel IncRichardson, TX BriXcel Inc, a Texas based Software &amp; Technology Consulting Company, has multiple openings for Systems Analyst.Oversee engagements with focus on ERP applications, Cloud solutions, System… https://t.co/YwR4L9Adqi https://t.co/zhS3B0i0KY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Hot Tech Deals: Dell, Amazon Echo, HTC Vive, August Smart Lock: Get ready for warmer weather with some tech deals. https://t.co/heaU4qT2aL https://t.co/y2lJZTvRkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineering – Job #: 180028050: Job #: 180028050 Associate, Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Provide high quality tech. solutions that address business needs by developing applications within mature technology environments. Duties:… https://t.co/7zcttJk5NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst: Sr Analyst, Asset Mgmt – Perform complex financial investment analyses for Asset Mgmt Business, incl analysis of equities, fixed income securities, private investments &amp; other instruments using advanced mathematical, statistical &amp; financial… https://t.co/SWQpARwWI4 https://t.co/pFkIOS7AGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Processor: Description: MSW-ARS performs global market research, primarily through online surveys. By collecting information on consumers’ needs and preferences, market research enables informed decision making. Data Processors transform raw data… https://t.co/Vpm2rL4UXQ https://t.co/Wgwi1aHWRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/LRLpo7gabR https://t.co/IJaprxqnfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ (High Frequency Trading) Software Developers: A financial firm with offices in downtown Boston is seeking qualified C++ Developers to join their growing software engineering department. This person will be responsible for helping to develop and… https://t.co/qveCW6UmLD https://t.co/7gBJQWAYOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accounting Systems Project Manager: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around… https://t.co/UqKUu6zEGb https://t.co/MyspfmbtxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intermediate Software Engineer: Careers Center | Intermediate Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/f9XvfR7YWG https://t.co/QJLiiDRtnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Sales: Director of Sales Applause is seeking a Director of Sales. The Director will have a role in hiring and major responsibilities in training, onboarding, coaching and driving the success of a team of 5+ Commercial Account Managers who are… https://t.co/A9pd1rjXvj https://t.co/y2e7dlNYB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Business Analyst: Job Description: The Information Systems Business Analyst plays a critical role in providing administration, operational, and project management support for the Business Systems at company. Computer Systems used in… https://t.co/NMe8ylxLuU https://t.co/XVWUnrz1hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer – Angular and React: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us Front End Developer – Angular and React Job Attributes Job Id: 17578Job Category: Software Applications… https://t.co/S80nAxqe9T https://t.co/hRdnlSraUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information and Technology Specialist: The School District of Glenwood City is looking for an Information and Technology Specialist to support the learning environment for students and staff through leadership in technology. The successful applicant will… https://t.co/GgFygD28Fo https://t.co/2T8LvQ6uCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Administrator: ORACLE DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR ADT LLC has an opening in Irving, TX for an Oracle DB Administrator. Help manage &amp; maintain Oracle EBS R12.x.x apps. &amp; DB, &amp; other non-ERP Oracle DBs. Provide tech. &amp; oper’l DBA support for… https://t.co/p9mu0ljWlT https://t.co/WJPvfy8Dez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xbox One Spring Sale Roundup (2018): Life is Strange, Overwatch, and More: We picked the best Xbox One games and deals in Microsoft's massive 2018 Xbox Spring Sale! https://t.co/LdMeP2grUF https://t.co/Wz2bQoIIzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Programmer Analyst #17SCS01: Synergy Computer Solutions, Inc. has job openings for Lead Programmer Analyst. Job is located in Bingham Farms, MI and various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S. Convert project specifications and statements of… https://t.co/vsoSpZE1tL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scientist: PROJECT SCIENTIST sought by University of California, Irvine in Irvine, CA. Conduct research on human-computer interaction applied to the “Internet of Things” including electronic devices and software applications for advancements in… https://t.co/96d4b3F2w8 https://t.co/4Y9Dfv0ZB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineers #IRVEYO: Software Developers Western Digital Technologies, Inc. has opportunity in Irvine, CA for Principal Engineers. Experience in C, C++, Java &amp; programming languages required. Equal opportunity employer. recblid… https://t.co/SXqlLmd0kD https://t.co/IWvQGopGq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Technical Program Specialist (Mountain View, CA) Define feature sets to ensure that the technical aspects of Google programs satisfy the business needs of Google’s clients and users. #1615.19122 Exp Incl: data… https://t.co/Z8BAJwxD8u https://t.co/qOJfhcLYTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager of Network Services: Manager of Network Services Central Bucks School District is accepting applications for a Manager of Network Services.  This full-time administrative position offers excellent benefits and competitive salary in accordance… https://t.co/7yti6WwgVe https://t.co/TiMlvNTWOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Job #:180028444: Job #:180028444 Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Duties: Provide quality technology solutions that address line of business needs by contributing to writing Pega applications, developing stored procedures and general… https://t.co/5UKUA0ymNu https://t.co/62M2kVDQFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: Software QA Engineer, AT SLEEP NUMBER CORPORATION, 111 W Saint John St Suite 1200 San Jose, California 95113, 8+ yrs exp software tester;Tech fld BS rqd;Exp design verification, reviewing specs/ test planning;Exp creating software… https://t.co/wz5ju29yzZ https://t.co/TKgetlI1L9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL backend coding, knowledge of UWP, WinForms,… https://t.co/l1DTtwXtRq https://t.co/LXOAc9KhnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sap Otc Manager #0617RC: Sap Otc, Manager Sought by Ingram Micro, Inc., Irvine, CA: Lead &amp; provide strategic systems direction to the Business for all key design decisions &amp; principles related to the overall SCE business process design &amp; integration with… https://t.co/agkW8C3PyC https://t.co/44I4aLnxUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Manager – Marketing: Timbers Resorts, Internations Developer and Operator of luxury resorts and residence clubs is looking for a: Database Manager – Marketing to join our growing team in Carbondale, CO. Candidate will be responsible for overall… https://t.co/dOnSyGHzkG https://t.co/LAz38A8Gsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA location for… https://t.co/pWJMdzbyyx https://t.co/Ss0Wpk79YT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple iPad (2018): Price, Specs, Release Date: Apple's lowest cost iPad ($329) now includes support for Apple Pencil ($99). https://t.co/GOObCuM59D https://t.co/hjWKeR6WXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager II: A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082: Provide sophisticated technical program management for the build-out of massively scalable, robust,… https://t.co/qS5kbzs9lK https://t.co/9ycS6VQu5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst: TransUnion, LLC seeks Senior Analysts for Chicago, IL location to assist in the design, implementation &amp; administration of strategic compensation programs. Master’s in Economics/Applied Economics, Compensation, or Statistics + 2 years… https://t.co/4IQ8na1aNu https://t.co/E5VaZm9ZKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job Description: Parsley Energy Operations, LLC seeks Software Developer to work at its office in Austin, TX. Develop new software solutions, including responsibility for components of medium size and complexity and… https://t.co/M1CdBBI69z https://t.co/Rt79A5vrft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Who Are We? ForeFront (Fair Haven, NJ) is a global technology consulting firm. Our expertise enables enterprise-wide digital transformation through cloud strategy, systems integration, agile delivery and change management of custom… https://t.co/23vzg3kP5i https://t.co/B8Bdu1UjHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director – IT Project Management: DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT FULL TIME PERMANENT POSITION – No H1B LOCATION: ATLANTA, GA SALARY: up to $110k/yr DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT SUMMARY This position is responsible for leading cross functional teams… https://t.co/gV8f13jOW7 https://t.co/vDAOaWMFTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server / Oracle Database Administrator: Req ID 94687BR Business Title SQL Server / Oracle Database Administrator Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Bethesda Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Systems Development Job Duties and Responsibilities… https://t.co/XP4AevGG81 https://t.co/0wWiAVmD0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Programmer/Analyst: EXTREMELY STABLE COMPANY LOCATED NEAR LITTLE ROCK, ARKANSAS HAS AN IMMEDIATE NEED FOR AN ORACLE PROGRAMMER ANALYST FOR A PERMANENT POSITION. REQUIREMENTS INCLUDE: * BACHELOR DEGREE * 3-4 YEARS DEVELOPING APPLICATIONS AND… https://t.co/Xc2tfyOY0u https://t.co/gqSETLWlc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Project Manager – Mission Critical: Electrical Project Manager – Mission Critical (Reston, Virginia) – Goliath Construction Consulting Please click here if you are not redirected within a few seconds. – Home – About – About Goliath –… https://t.co/asw2VRiWZn https://t.co/BxR3LKAqMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABIS Systems Analyst / Network Admin: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. ABIS Systems Analyst / Network Admin Mission Services | Fairmont, WV | Full Time Job Description Systems Analyst / Network… https://t.co/foK0cmOYtP https://t.co/5JB12lngen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Engineer: Systems Engineer sought by S&amp;S Enterprises LLC in Brea, CA. Design sub-system components. Analyze &amp; verify design meets requirements. Apply systems analysis techniques &amp; procedures. Requirement: BS + 1. recblid… https://t.co/X7V1QyA4eG https://t.co/5FUnlFtLl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer I: https://t.co/3oDnQZgHNq Services, Inc. and A2Z Development Center, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Quality Assurance Engineer I, Job Code AZ0078: Adopt best practices in software engineering to test code at… https://t.co/6UivBhxmNX https://t.co/xFsc8rxgeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager ITS Applications #7661: Manager – ITS Applications Job #7661 $100,000 – $135,000 depends on qualifications. Basic Responsibilities:  Manages the utility’s Enterprise Asset Management (EAM) systems program and team performing software… https://t.co/4DajjKmAHP https://t.co/ODTMwS3p2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Apple Lost Its Place in the Classroom: Apple's new, cheaper iPad still can't compete with Chromebooks in the classroom. https://t.co/PjrUFqlk4g https://t.co/DOpcq5qC9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Morrisville, NC): Perform system analysis &amp; design &amp; develop IT applications for internal (management information) &amp; external (regulatory) Liquidity Risk reporting in accordance with IT standards… https://t.co/TRiIJbPCyW https://t.co/oaFIakG78T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Information Technology: Organizational Description: Advocates for Youth is dedicated to creating programs and advocating for policies that help young people make informed and responsible decisions about their reproductive and sexual health.… https://t.co/QWKHS2L6WH https://t.co/pui3kaTr3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Materials Program Manager: Management Position Sunnyvale,CA, Cupertino,CA, San Jose,CA &amp; Palo Alto, CA A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/3oDnQZgHNq Services, Inc. candidates for the following positions (multiple positions available for… https://t.co/ASekE7vhY5 https://t.co/cgNW5GujUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Developer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA… https://t.co/lvEI5YvRqr https://t.co/dkIqbTzg8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data #SSE228SU: PeopleConnect, Inc. has an opening for a Sr. Software Engineer – Core Data (Ref# SSE228SU). Work Location:  1501 4th Ave. Suite 400, Seattle, WA  98101. Job Duties:  Build large-scale backend systems, develop… https://t.co/kdDP5t00mB https://t.co/WQaPIQyLra]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>