<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scotlandteam: Scotland team here goes! R Lamont Jones De Luca S Lamont Evans Parks Cusiter Jacobsen Ford Murray Gray Hamilton Stroko ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicrawley I saw a crawley on the teamsheet and wondered!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depressed, hungover and stuck on a broken train is not how I planned spending my full Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #starshiptroopers. #wouldyouliketoknowmore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @aspy87 @rory_g_macrae I have no need for your condescension Laughland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LadyxFarrah: I'm dying here. Just saw this on FB &gt;&gt;&gt;  http://t.co/uTn0pHR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChemmySki: I know I may have disappointed myself and some of you but I promise you all I can do soo much better! Give me a chance ca ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilesBarrie: RT @PickardJE: RT @oliver_wright: Alex Salmond is to publish independence plans on Burns night. No cliche too low. #mur ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that's saying something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damien Comolli performing even worse at @LFC than he did at #spurs. He's got one job to do! Henderson and Downing are far worse than Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @rmcnairn 1.30 city spurs game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having an awesome time in the library this staurday afternoon #grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brober87 @rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 @rmcnairn  As im penniless. We could have a sesh at my mum and dads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @aspy87 I'm game for super sunday, have spoken to @rmcnairn he's keen as well. Would be keen to avoid pub...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BelieveInSarah: Smile on. http://t.co/Zgkf4MPJ #WeLoveSarah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheChainSpokers: Doing #LEJOG or #JOGLE this year? Cycling for @mariecurieuk? Check out our 2 wheeled blog at http://t.co/DggYhePH @ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very bored and I really want to go skiing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Magdalen Oxford gets rejection letter from student http://t.co/TQgEnbdX ---- Great! one from the school of @rossmcnairn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Freeskier: Friends, word just in from @sarah_j_burke's family that they'd like to see the hashtag read #BelieveInSarah. Let's push it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get well soon @sarah_j_burke #BelieveInSarah #believeinburke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Carroll cannot possibly be this shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GusTheFox: The circle of life. Just ate a worm out of my own bum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpools final ball has been shocking. Downing and Henderson not good enough. Adam been terrible as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really starting to dislike #yaya #toure. Always bloody moaning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the spl could a player not be sent off for headbutting another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixu doing analysis for derby. Sacking of him was beginning of hfc's problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the hibees get paid! #hfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GaryJanetti: Why aren't we giving plastic surgery to kids yet?  Some of them look like shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carroll going to grab a goal tonight! #lfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexa_chung: Incapable of keeping a pair of gloves together. Need mittens on a string. Glove will tear us apart again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah did you go last night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rustyboy2310 @rossmcnairn @rory_g_macrae would rather hit a flat to be honest! #skint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn I think the boy is one for the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#messi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @HeatherLaLand ...The Ugandan govt executes homosexuals simply for being so- perhaps the overall governance needs improving?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @HeatherLaLand Read that article this morning, thought a bit of it missed the mark but overall agreed with it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamHarrisOrg: Join the remarkable grassroots effort to bring Joseph Kony to justice: http://t.co/Ph9TTvrW #makekonyfamous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 certainly is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rosicky on the other hand completely driving arsenal. Where has he been last couple of years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Walcott is so frustrating to watch. Raw pace but no idea what to do with ball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Walcott is so frustrating to watch. Raw pace but no clue about what to do with the ball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: Uni of Salzburg is testing the new 35m skis, day 1: thrown out back. day 2: blown knee. Safer huh? No joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChemmySki Just absolutely killed it. Awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rmcnairn im not altogether sure lunch is something we will be allowed to avoid! standard across the road though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rmcnairn How can you dislike Tim Riggins? Mon Dieu! yeah meeting you guys at Leo's. What time is KO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmcnairn @rory_g_macrae sorry forgot the link http://t.co/HuKzY6LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very keen to see this, think it might be right up your back alley? @rmcnairn @rory_g_macrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bleakoldshopofstuff is bloody hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae delighted to hear that they were worthy of a best of album after two shite records.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoying Castrogiovanni's mane #sixnations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae ha-HA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae thoroughly erotic fae Berba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae agreed. Collymore is a piece. Quite like pat nevin though. Looking forward to seeing Lodeiro and Ericsson for Ajax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Downing and Frazier Campbell in #Eng squad. #lollapalooza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the Scotland squad. Levein is a complete fud @OfficialMannah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBig_Sam: What does Big Sam put on his pancake? Maple syrup? Sugar? Lemon juice? No. Another fucking pancake. Boom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: I want to use this friendly to see if Kenny Miller can play upfront on his own #oneforthefuture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon Chemmy! #dancingonice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChemmySki: I love all ur support on twitter and thanks for the nice words but need u to pick up the phone please 09016161002]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#skisunday has been great this year, they've done away with top gear-esque antics, and are giving decent racing coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stack is having an absolute mare for #hibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah excellent joke mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMarkBeaumont Get in line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@u01naf6 are you playing at heriot watt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pkelso: Second-placed #Rangers docked 10 points and plummet to, er, second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCSport: Carlos Tevez says he was 'treated like a dog' by boss Roberto Mancini during touchline row but prepared to play for Manche ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: I have ruled myself out of the Wolves job as they simply don't have enough quality upfront to stay up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: David Silva has just left Alan Hutton in another postcode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rugby is now causing me physical pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same old story #grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ff @u01naf6 : Nicky Forrest picking up his twitter game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomEnglishSport: After the loss to Redknapp and Mandaric, HMRC need a result against Rangers. They won't just be sweating at Ibrox...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think that the 'continental' model using various team directors will ever work in en-ger-land #comolli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted that comoli has left #lfc. Terrible at a job he supposedly specialises in. Carroll, Henderson, downing- £75million of garbage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DTguardian: Damien Comolli was the guy who decided Andy Carroll was worth £35m, then rang Man City in January to offer swap for Tevez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: RIP Moneyball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HomerJSimpson: I don’t know what state we live in, but our house is worth a lot less than in 2007.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[loving having my proper headphones back. #bass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a mammoth study week #beersrequired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBC6MusicNews: Sad news that Guitar amp innovator Jim Marshall has passed away, aged 88.
He founded Marshall Amplification 50 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PANDA WATCH!! “@edinburghpaper: Panda Watch - Yang Guang and Tian Tian have 'met'.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: I will continue to pick Goodwillie despite him pleading guilty for assault, because I love acting inconsistently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charliesimo: As if Anchor Man 2 wasn't enough... Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels have both just signed on for Dumb and Dumber 2!! Pure a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae aye it looks incredible. Plus Mila kunis. Did you see the trailer for total recall. Also looks immense. Different from arnie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NimbusIndpndnt: Bacon in drinks?  Good for you Canada. http://t.co/6jdwZR08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@MikeDski: Damn kids! RT @johnwbradley: First ever skateboarding 1080 landed—by a 12-year-old. http://t.co/h7jdqSqh”&gt;&gt;&gt; holy shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RacerReady: One weeks Prem Footballers wages could support GB Alpine skiing for a season. GB Coaches not retained after funding issu ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah way to upgrade. bet you feel a big difference!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteepSkiing: This poster has lived on my boys wall for 4 years @shanemcconkey @ClifBar @redbull  http://t.co/IBe6txxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrageously good lunch. Kilo of mussels, fries and a beer. #yaldi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inverleith park a pretty awesome place to be working today! #sunny http://t.co/dtBfNdPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sickipediabot: I'm sure the bloke who invented the drawing board didn't get it right the first time.

I wonder what he went back to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMannah: It's so sad to hear about the passing of Liam Kelly's dad. He must have been so proud. A bad weekend for football #R ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HansOlssons: Longest day of my life.: I guess most of you guys have already read or heard about me getting injured at the eur... htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: Won the second run on the 35m skis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah according to linkedin you've got a job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah saw that, but it's also a massive improvement on last year.  comes from the £600m debt they were sitting on- been refinanced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae to be fair, prob would have hated them if they had been that popular #toocoolforskool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those calling for robinsons head need a complete reality check #Sru #Scotland  #sixnations]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>