<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/pD7sIThqYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/0EUYWit73D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/WIqumYDa1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/oroHuBHMMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/ENGxgQe2zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/6zzbRVSEFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/UFziJ8jbLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/rgyKcaMnzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/yYJggcNb5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/TAYFIsxVOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/c68fZVFk1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/LOpU3CVFwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/e5sKnxxmtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/ySOQtlxzlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/cnjt6guq63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/AVyiKUA5ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/XGS3POqfgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/dKkeTs1S8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/tdlsXO9K3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/NJT7OGZe2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/Wl2jtPS9TD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/3ODKXwxDpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/rdIg2yQWmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/EZuqCjDBNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/tgosU5IDTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/j1tsvOPLRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/QVXxKTarCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/9AaRruJXSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/gcQKcHuPui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/M8Xe2m3eee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love sports?  Read about the great sports teams of the Northern California Bay Area!  http://t.co/QsWbK4CyF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/oXl97WC5Q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/dXL3ub7nZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theory is a hunch with a college education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/wUWcPbsQ3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/Ue90PAZMXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/BhDZGK31RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/hbYz4zpFk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/p0SidJ5rdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/UFziJ8jbLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/6F0dTllTnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/OVc1Lf8qCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/ekoCz6kJCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/0iHZrFQymn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>