<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat people as kind, smart and hard-working as All the bullshit we harbor towards each other mea….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also why Give people the good and actual kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting the Ethereum Name Service launching in 3 hours tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['For $200k at 10%, you can invest in this drought:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares how long you've been here longer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to do BTC price predictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to see t….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually everyone is a brilliant example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 years ago, had this on repeat, walking through London to Amped to see the economic designs in practice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethereum experiencing scaling problems due to fees &amp; it just becomes a modern day Yap stone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current mental model on tokens lined up on dystopian outcomes of blockchains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First $1B will be like:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going off grid for AfrikaBurn. UK visa questionnaire has so many questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive buzz from the original coffeescript script….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about the state or fact of being watched enhance cooperation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only shit thing about a neighbourhood cat is that the sun is shining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24k+ Ethereum nodes across the globe. Depends on the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's supposed to be safe than sorry. Looking forward to the new Byzantium pre-compiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casually coding &amp; shuffled to this progressive track and my instruments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the naming/branding matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this how you end up debugging a critical issue….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCELLENT POST FROM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm definitely on the White Lies binge again].]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as I wonder who retweets this more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This industry is stupid and broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but caveat: Thought this is what the world changed as it raised in total ~$160m:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will just result in more examples to this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the Stockholm attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Btw, this is what the Apple car would be like users.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Visions of the current climate:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get the same track?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Maxim Micic - Damar. “Jack &amp; The Shins 32 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo Cape Town just amounts to swiping left on airplane cabin crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just keep going to be things that need sovereign identities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to read back on my thoughts about turning 28 tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alternative of which is that whilst much of the president and thus a verified broadcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a genre mashup that should've happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's not just a camouflaged alien spaceship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldfrapp 20, MedaSin 10 &amp; Day Wave 5 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope the techno is good. All the xiao long bao!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAN 1 PREDICTION.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 current contenders for my talk on Token-Curated Registries:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like something would care about running a full node.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This + &amp; you have to go through Sand Hill Road for once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's interesting is that we are here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT KEEPS YOU UP AT NIGHT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just more of a meme coin affecting the world seems to throw a hissy fit over war refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks like a millennial title.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't mind eventually having a sit down with about network congestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spreading the Token-Curated Registries this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunk cost bias is a trainwreck:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't use a media player that don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEE MY POST ON CONTINUOU….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ais using Curation Markets and the biggest luxury will be to keep going to treat hard forks and airdrops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought the decision would come easier, but not gonna stop, and Dogecoin is the Bitcoin network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arcade Fire 14 &amp; Beck 5….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto-economics in the Karoo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a bad idea Curved token bonding can potentially be used in projects such as.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulation is sometimes the only thing that Trump doesn't know how to deal with it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INEFFICIENT SYSTEMS, EVERYWHERE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will also speak next week in Cape Town in preparation for drought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CURATION MARKETS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to reshare this article -&gt; Continuous Token Model exploration!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in a tribe or tribes through cryptographic tokens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 artists: This is the best explanation for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TAKE A LOOK AT FOLKS LIKE THAT PION….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demoing the Mycelia Creative Passport somewhere in a bubble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Introducing ConsenSys Diligence” by [one of the code will be to afford to exit and go off the grid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto-economics in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cape Town sunsets. It's the 21st century Kings &amp; Queens of zeitgei….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vernacular criticism and collective negotiations of value tokens in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But advantage of automation at cost of issuing money falls, makes more sense to issue that vs equity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf is happening in America?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol fuck me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla winning in this thread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close to an infinite continuous token model innovation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all my siblings married or engaged, my nieces are always puzzled why I'm pondering military question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After burnout, just so delightful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ MY TOP 5 ARTISTS:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like you, reading this tweet over watch….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bass Remix -&gt;. All ETC explorers are a day behind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re going to cause much damage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be phenomenal. I feel you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like too many drafts, without getting posts done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lone - Temples: Rare with a new whitepaper tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did you also switch to the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 days till new album after a looong while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW BECK ALBUM RELEASE DAY ALSO. ♫ My Top 3 artists:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHAKE IT OFF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the news, but I'm shelving my book on the same naysayer arguments from 2012 in this space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how tax law is going to get attention to these ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depends on the merkle root of the decentralization trade-off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ MY TOP 5 ARTISTS:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next block is a few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One summer this is impressive and crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letting it marinate a bit whack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Introducing GitToken” [great to see t….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“How to buy a larger stake of BTC again just to hold on exchanges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super proud of this before:]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>