<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[junior java developer: Junior Java Developer Springfield, OH FULLTIME Roles and Responsibilities: Design, develop, enhance, maintain and support business applications A minimum of 3 years of professional Java software development experience. Strong… https://t.co/dlkuUPwQAV https://t.co/u0CeWlPItV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyahu: Israel thanks Trump for his courage: Israel's Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu says Israel fully supports President Trump's decision to withdraw from the Iran nuclear deal. https://t.co/CCC8qaYkVC https://t.co/Jo5lwYdwJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Full Stack Developer: Careers Center | Senior Java Full Stack Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/KXeBCsglEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could this island be the next Iceland? https://t.co/U8CPpZrweh https://t.co/PY90qDTGX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java: Java/J2EE Ref No.: 18-18154 Location: blue ash, Ohio Job Title: – Java Developer Job Location: – Irving, TX/ Blue Ash, OH Job Type: – Fulltime (Permanent) Job Description: Must having experience in Java/J2EE development Good knowledge of SOA… https://t.co/tzHOClF0nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack/Java: Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack/Java at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Waltham, MA Senior Software Engineer, Front End Constant Contact, Inc. helps small businesses and nonprofits connect… https://t.co/nKBcVuCjc8 https://t.co/d1Q8d1u7qR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer w/ VAADIN experience: Carrollton, TX Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer w/ VAADIN with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us -Fast growing company. A ton of growth opportunities. -Great… https://t.co/nbZWFf2dJ0 https://t.co/NZeMNUmbLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber crash reportedly caused by software that ignored objects in road: Uber has reportedly discovered that the fatal crash involving one of its prototype self-driving cars was probably caused by software faultily set up to ignore objects in the road,… https://t.co/IrGOxQgxnx https://t.co/sFc5Gorah4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He rents Lamborghinis, Bentleys &amp; Ferraris in exchange for illegal guns: Sick and tired of senseless violence, one Miami businessman is attempting to rid the streets of guns -- one Rolls-Royce at a time. https://t.co/FaNowsflTh https://t.co/1oRg4aLtiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Software Engineer: Chicago, IL Prestigious Financial Organization is seeking a candidate to develop and support User Interfaces for Floor Trading, Order Management and Systems Management/Control. DUTIES INCLUDE: * Participate in full project life… https://t.co/On4EWhvhFw https://t.co/iNOjc4ikxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr.-Mid Level Java Developer: Seeking a talented Jr. to Mid Level Java Software Developer with Backend skills with Spring Boot, Micro services and Elastic Search. This is a full-time opportunity with a growing group! https://t.co/z62i8LsiJW https://t.co/2hjC4XcoUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft repurposes Kinect to boost AI and Azure development: Kinect didn't die, it just changed forms. Today at its annual Build developers conference, Microsoft announced Project Kinect for Azure saying that the sensor array will have all the… https://t.co/1uJxfzSW97 https://t.co/xLeZ0d1dT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Falls Church, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/16/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/FsvDaCzsxC https://t.co/4DPVXKGYly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Development Internship (Paid): $13/hr Diverse Computing is looking for a Java Development Intern to join our team. Internships with Diverse Computing are different from most; theyre more like part-time jobs, in fact. We believe in helping our young… https://t.co/oTh7X8vGFA https://t.co/B3k2URLeXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Giuliani has jumped the shark: In his now famous, wide-ranging interview with Fox News' Sean Hannity on Wednesday night, former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani did the unthinkable. https://t.co/SBV9u9Rn15 https://t.co/i74JNRIvEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Enterprise Developer: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Java Enterprise Developer Key Role: Implement and test features using Java and technologies, including J2EE, Spring, JMS, AOP, JPA, JUnit 4, and Mockito, and EasyMock. Work… https://t.co/wfnfJQGpnc https://t.co/RA8ciD7DFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as volcano insurance in Hawaii?: With homes destroyed and lava spraying into a Hawaiian neighborhood, the concern for many homeowners is: Will the damage be covered? https://t.co/DlIlnsswr6 https://t.co/m1PmHdSFD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: WHO WE ARE: Freedom Financial Network is a family of companies that takes a people-first approach to financial services, using technology to empower consumers to overcome debt and create a brighter financial future. The company was… https://t.co/LLZnPI5duE https://t.co/fBw2cYTNk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Giuliani has said so far: Rudy Giuliani joined President Donald Trump's legal team last month, and in a whirlwind few days, he has made a series of eye-opening statements about a hush money payment to Stormy Daniels. https://t.co/dO2ezKzLF4 https://t.co/Q56OwIsdXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (C#, .NET, JavaScript): At TherapyNotes, our software developers work in a collaborative, team environment to develop the best behavioral health EMR software in the industry. We’re expanding our team and looking for developers who love… https://t.co/eOWx0qEgDv https://t.co/18HO18XO3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheriff: Highway sniper idolized Parkland shooting suspect: A sniper who targeted cars on a Georgia highway left behind a "hate-filled" document describing the Parkland, Florida high school gunman Nikolas Cruz as a hero, a sheriff said. https://t.co/X8z2Etrk64 https://t.co/8jtTJBvDBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. level Java developer: Sr. level Java developer Birmingham, Alabama – United States Job Start Date – 03/12/18, Posted Date – 03/12/18 Primary SkillsJava,JavaScript,DevOps,Python,DOM,etcTax TermsC2COverview Hello Everyone, I am looking for a mid to Sr.… https://t.co/8hA7Fp5Oc8 https://t.co/IXEDL9hslm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (Big Data): Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’ lives.… https://t.co/Lg7OiQ1Bwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Storm's a comin', baby,' porn star tells Baldwin's Trump: Adult film star Stormy Daniels appeared in "Saturday Night Live's" cold open alongside many other big names that surround President Donald Trump. https://t.co/smtypI0ZCf https://t.co/p1iSgIBmf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Mid Level: Java Developer – Mid Level Job in San Antonio, TX at USAA – – Career Center – About USAA – Career Areas – Locations – Military – University – Life @ USAA – Returning Applicants IT JOBS AT USAA – Careers – / – Search Jobs – –… https://t.co/F6dlFLS8pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Level Software Engineer (Java): TE2, The Experience Engine, a division of accesso, provides consumer-facing enterprises an engine to drive personalization, recommendations and commerce for the physical world, in real-time. We believe every consumer… https://t.co/4yPt1ZhhCy https://t.co/WTPBEYJvvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developers: Description: If you are a qualified Software Engineer or Cybersecurity professional in Morgantown or surrounding areas and are interested in working in a rewarding environment, we would like to meet with you.   Leidos is seeking… https://t.co/zBbgOLetgD https://t.co/UzFsFcCiuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to expect at Microsoft's Build 2018 conference: Fresh off of Windows 10's major April update, Microsoft is gearing up for its Build conference in Seattle on Monday. The annual event, like Google I/O (which starts just one day later), is a… https://t.co/z4db44UnwQ https://t.co/HQF3lZMEKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineering – C/C++, Python, Java: Req ID : 430675BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : We are seeking a Software Engineer to join the dynamic and growing Space Protection Programs Software Development Team.… https://t.co/NroNgnHsQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Professional: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/8QmQneq8ff https://t.co/A0Q31oktz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developers: Passionate about technology? Do you like shipping software and seeing real results? If that describes you, you’ll feel right at home at Chariot. We are a tight knit group of software professionals, putting our expertise to work… https://t.co/27941JAybV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk IT – Java Quantitative Analytics Developer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/ihSqE4ZnCc https://t.co/yD3JkMUq77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotic woks are the chefs in this Boston restaurant: Four MIT students who once built a soccer ball-kicking robot got together with a Michelin-starred chef to build a restaurant that's not quite what you're used to. How? Well, it's staffed by robots,… https://t.co/toVh32T2w3 https://t.co/Al55oZjCNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – JavaScript: Software Developer – JavaScript =============================== Req #: ******Location: Annapolis Junction, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be… https://t.co/7SU7e60Eqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting the 'scariest place on earth': All eyes are on the Korean Demilitarized Zone (DMZ) right now, where South Korea's President Moon Jae-in and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un met in April and vowed to bring peace to the peninsula. https://t.co/XCUPrWGkfa https://t.co/sUUMXuiUVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Tech, Marketing &amp; Sales Jobs in Lake Mary Florida | Technology and Digital Marketing Recruiters Skip to content MENU ************** ******************* – Home – About Us – Meet the Team – 7 Step Recruiting Process – Testimonials –… https://t.co/OU1NXP0N82 https://t.co/GJlkZkvs6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/UKuofj8chs https://t.co/sJ2bhAyyLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders: I learned about Stormy Daniels payment from Giuliani's interview https://t.co/Z84tzUO6sg https://t.co/ojBScvgJ8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a CNN investigation, Daimler announces new child labor safeguards https://t.co/0p5b6k7aYd https://t.co/yIIhHJ7jBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 04/04/18, Posted Date – 04/04/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12 months contract. F2F Required. Any visa okay from trusted party. Must have genuine exp. Must… https://t.co/7w3oxCFW4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/JEE Developer (Entry Level): Careers Center | Java/JEE Developer (Entry Level) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/4ZUW6VbA7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: HomeAdvisor wants a Java Developer with demonstrably strong internet-focused Java development experience to join our team of dedicated, passionate software engineers. Every application you work on will directly impact how our… https://t.co/Hquitftye8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Java: Job Description Job ID: R43242 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/Lcxf8Z582l https://t.co/LhvqQQnZ5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new requirement for all cars sold in the US https://t.co/100NKIHxhW https://t.co/rZPdgMZDc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Engineer – Top legal tech company: As part of the Engineering Team, you will be given the opportunity to display your creativity and deliver continuous end-user value in an Agile environment. We are self-motivated engineers who like to research,… https://t.co/113pIWCO9D https://t.co/SreXyCyEZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The $200 Uno synth crams a ton of features into a small package: IK Multimedia is known for its wide variety of music gear, including MIDI controllers, mixers and instrument interfaces. Now the company has just launched its first analog synth, a compact… https://t.co/z31xwTilSn https://t.co/oNwqruXIpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has a new, aggressive approach to Mueller's probe, and it doesn't include Ty Cobb: On Wednesday at 12:16 p.m. ET, ABC News tweeted out this quote from Ty Cobb, one of the lead lawyers on President Donald Trump's legal team, about the possibility of… https://t.co/JujLsBLWew https://t.co/OCOP7qPWwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developers: Description: We have immediate opportunities for Senior Software Developers to join a world class, center of excellence.  Leidos was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes’ "America’s Top 500" list. At… https://t.co/oP0GhKRFG9 https://t.co/41ztlEGv6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Bornstein in 2016 double down on Trump's health: Dr. Harold Bornstein tells CNN's Drew Griffin that he meant everything he wrote in the much-scrutinized note that touted Donald Trump's fitness. https://t.co/18Ahsw83pE https://t.co/Dzhe0yQ2Bg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: We are looking for a Java Developer for a direct-hire permanent opportunity in Austin, Texas. You will join an Agile team, developing enterprise level web applications. You: Have 5+ years experience developing Java web applications using… https://t.co/hieC2owwVb https://t.co/DeSeQ0GNSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Augmented reality and yard sale junk collide to make art: Who doesn't enjoy digging through piles of old junk at yard sales? They're a window into the past, capturing lives and forgotten memories. At the Tribeca Film Festival, the installation Objects in… https://t.co/yA1V00j586 https://t.co/2wk3QDwiRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Java: Job Description Job ID: R43242 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/sNOc2O8zkM https://t.co/7otBZ4uNV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon pushes Signal creators to change their anti-censorship tool: For years, Open Whisper Systems has used clever tricks to circumvent censorship of its Signal messaging app on the part of countries trying to silence political dissent. Those methods… https://t.co/F8o0tgLF76 https://t.co/IBEX7J6wJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Market Risk Qauntitative Analytics – Application Systems Engineer 5: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/NhO85GXSFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller's real questions for Trump will be a lot tougher https://t.co/9PieLBCS7G https://t.co/4j0EDPHEJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – DHS Public Trust Clearance: Herndon, VA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today We are a government IT consulting firm based in Herndon, VA. THsi is a full time permanent opportunity requiring a DHS Public Trust Clearance. What You Need for… https://t.co/ZiVR53IyTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook users will be able to make normal photos look 3D: Facebook has been working to implement 3D objects into user interactions, but at the company's F8 conference today, announcers introduced a few new features to add dimensionality and VR to… https://t.co/4Fj3sYpdUC https://t.co/N89EXHjHAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says 'there's no reason to apologize' for his Muslim ban call: President Donald Trump, speaking Monday alongside the President of Nigeria, derided US immigration laws as "weak," "pathetic" and "obsolete." https://t.co/5buyrbgsfr https://t.co/q1amqDOsn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer Job: Senior Java Developer (Job Number:434557) Description: Job Description: The developer will possess a strong problem solving skill set and the ability to learn new technologies quickly to meet dynamic, fast- paced development… https://t.co/c5uGUTdLlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18005012) Sr Backend Java Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18005012 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/SqEd0BLrDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US economy just hit a milestone https://t.co/PZ6wlubv0a https://t.co/3vflmYFZnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: Our client, a global fintech leader, is looking for SR JAVA DEVELOPERS to help them with an upcoming project. The details of what we’re looking for are below: * Multi-year contract, min 2-4 months commitment from you * Starting May 1,… https://t.co/4xMlITFImT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18006074) Sr Full Stack Java Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18006074 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/irJhMGWlv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence's physician alerted White House about Ronny Jackson last fall: Vice President Mike Pence's physician privately raised alarms within the White House last fall that President Donald Trump's doctor may have violated federal privacy protections for a… https://t.co/rZevOylXEc https://t.co/tVsgwZkDFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juror: Cosby's words sealed fate: Harrison Snyder served on the jury in the Bill Cosby trial and is speaking out about why he found the comedian guilty. https://t.co/4iDkXh4piL https://t.co/w12r13cuBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: UNABLE TO WORK WITH 3RD PARTY AGENCIES LOCAL CANDIDATES ONLY UNABLE TO SPONSOR H1BS AT THIS TIME We are looking for a full stack engineer who feels strongly about delivering good software but also about running software in the real… https://t.co/vpnOq5vUIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Enterprise Java Engineer 100% TELECOMMUTE: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $300k Posted Today We currently have offices in San Fran, Santa Monica and Miami but are open to hiring telecommute people if you are a strong match. We need 2 – 3… https://t.co/Q5ZHR86IGR https://t.co/AWwBvKl2pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment… https://t.co/nibx4R6KL4 https://t.co/ljovhaXlrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer (REST API, Spring MVC): San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today Based in San Francisco, CA we are a innovative FinTech company purely focused on streamlining the home buying experience for consumers. We've developed a… https://t.co/7J5tEJIOz4 https://t.co/VcmEakN4MK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla owner faces 18-month ban for leaving the driver's seat: Tesla will be one of the first to tell you not to put too much faith in Autopilot. It's currently more of an advanced driver assist than a full self-driving system. However, one driver… https://t.co/yskb7y93gO https://t.co/awlRxWNgnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions): IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions) Job Number: 1600620 Description This position is responsible for providing leadership and technical deliverables in the design, development, testing, documentation, and… https://t.co/wT8MUpXeWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java, Angular, or Full Stack Software Developers (Clearance Sponsorships Available): Java, Angular, or Full Stack Software Developers (Clearance Sponsorships Available) =========================================================== Req #: ******Location:… https://t.co/sBZgUnEtfW https://t.co/104tSfTMr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: ALIS Software is currently seeking an experienced JAVA DEVELOPER for a contract position located in Austin, Texas. WHAT YOU WILL NEED TO QUALIFY: * Extensive experience writing Java programs on Linux J2EE platforms * Extensive experience… https://t.co/osoGoPLGdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- Innovative Company!: Irvine, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Java Developer with experience, please read on! Are you a Senior Java developer that is looking for something new and exciting? Do you want… https://t.co/P5O84S9zkN https://t.co/ecNdDeYGqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businesses are dying in this Arizona border town: W. Kamau Bell visits a border town in Arizona where small businesses are struggling due to increased border security after 9/11. Watch "United Shades of America with W. Kamau Bell" on Sundays at 10 p.m.… https://t.co/Ilvu7gbnwn https://t.co/CKpyJ1QVko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Siri JavaScript Engineer: Apple is looking for a highly motivated engineer with strong software development skills to join their Siri team. You’ll ship code that runs on the devices and powers the products used by you and millions of others every day.… https://t.co/5VT4ac1l4U https://t.co/lV8NUEQdaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatens shutdown over border security: President Donald Trump told supporters at a speech on Saturday that if Congress did not meet his funding demands for border security, he may support a government shutdown this fall. https://t.co/CSyxFnSoAA https://t.co/jW6gMuhIMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer- Full Stack: Required Technical Skills: * 3-7 years of enterprise software development experience * Excellent understanding of object-oriented design patterns * Excellent core Java skills Preferred Technical Skills: * Enterprise RDBMS… https://t.co/jve0TsNGb2 https://t.co/APcmtlZsox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Java/Mobile: Senior Software Engineer – Java/Mobile Posted January 12, 2018 Company Overview FreedomPay is a dynamic technology company that provides a state of the art payment processing platform and stored value systems. We… https://t.co/1X4aJ8R0Ny https://t.co/NUkfpIJIL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Roles &amp; Responsibilities: Effectively communicate technical information to numerous audiences (including senior management), develop relationships inside and outside of IT, deliver technical recommendations and influence others to… https://t.co/UcTcMee4m7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Engineer – AI Java Platform: Our close client, a FinTech startup, is on a mission to enable companies to attract, engage, support, and transact with their customers via human-like, intelligent conversations, anytime, anywhere. Their… https://t.co/CuMbNa28Ai https://t.co/aJKqB2rINt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Javascript Web Front End Application Developer: As a Front End Web Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers products (Consumer, B2B, plus our Browser Extensions). Youll own our customer-facing web sites, lead enhancements, and optimize… https://t.co/DPBi8Qmwx7 https://t.co/SZ42A91gkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In court, Trump's fortunes are plummeting https://t.co/qY4Stn2Chk https://t.co/lyNOJVCMd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Responsible for designing, coding, testing, implementing, maintaining and supporting applications software that is delivered on time and within budget. Work closely with customers, business analysts, technology and project team to… https://t.co/ArRER7RTev https://t.co/bY63jIZRtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: **************’s mission is to provide easy, accessible and affordable online health care services for everyone. Everything we do focuses on helping our patients become healthier and happier. We have easy-to-use online platforms… https://t.co/cFAjjk88HB https://t.co/tajtNVhg4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer, Front-End Focused: Description * Intertech is looking for exceptional candidates with solid Java full-stack development experience * Need to have strong front-end skills with Angular and JavaScript experience for an exceptional… https://t.co/QD7YYSORSd https://t.co/nkUkQxV5Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Java Developer: Skylight is at the forefront of a civic movement to reinvent how the government serves the public in a digital world. Were looking for experienced developers to join our talented team of technologists in driving this movement… https://t.co/zoZc541QyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Junior Web Developer/Java Developer: – Junior Web Developer/Java Developer Job Locations US-CT-Greenwich ID 1658 Department Software Development Company Overview Interactive Brokers LLC, a subsidiary of Interactive Brokers Group, Inc. (NASDAQ:… https://t.co/Fn5FqzT78Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Golden State Killer case means for your genetic privacy: Fears about the privacy of our data have become commonplace amid credit monitoring hacks and a political firm accessing Facebook users' information. A recent arrest takes it one step… https://t.co/Po48Nici1h https://t.co/z2AE3DR3mb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Manager Software Development – Hands-On/Sm Co./.NET,C#,Javascript: HOT!!! AMAZING SMALL COMPANY SEEKING A SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT MANAGER The company has been around for over 15 years and is looking bring on a manager that can help further develop… https://t.co/wbf07bALtV https://t.co/J5GaUkniXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Engineer: TAISTech is looking for a Sr. Java Engineer to join their GSF Project within their E-Commerce group. Duration:- 6+ Months however, its likely it will extend into a couple of years. Requirements GSF Project opening: Candidates with… https://t.co/jW0ZXHZlSh https://t.co/Fe55Ruzufn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human cost of America's immigration policy: W. Kamau Bell sees where Mexican deportees are first sent when they're forced out of the United States. Watch "United Shades of America with W. Kamau Bell" on Sundays at 10 p.m. ET/PT. https://t.co/eeMxDPSym4 https://t.co/XaIbHA7hKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering or of study. 5 years work experience as a Java developer, implementing test data solutions. Minimum 3 years work experience developing solutions in a environment, e.g. AWS. Full… https://t.co/MzwcYLcMls https://t.co/rtqNRpeaVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigators used online DNA databases to hunt Golden State Killer: Yesterday several police departments in California announced the arrest of the "Golden State Killer," who killed a dozen people between 1978 and 1986 and has been accused of over 50… https://t.co/1P34auBbkP https://t.co/lKwlxpkPWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer evanston, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/29/18, Posted Date – 03/29/18 Primary SkillsJava,Spring,SecurityTax TermsC2COverview Company: Accuity Role: Java Developer Location: Evanston, IL 60201 (client prefers… https://t.co/sEPPuPFhSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/JAVA Developer: Software Engineer/JAVA Developer ================================ Req #: ******Location: Fort Detrick, MD USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is… https://t.co/pbldr8a4VY https://t.co/RMI9AwPyIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curbing salt intake could add years to your life: Potato chips. Pretzels. Pizza. French fries. https://t.co/YC0imwasqR https://t.co/TJ9nLNvGjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Java Developer (SWE 1): Careers Center | Front End Java Developer (SWE 1) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/mMp1Fq20ND https://t.co/LMVuHuiBRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 53 most stunning lines from Trump's 'Fox &amp; Friends' interview: Minutes after his nominee to head the Veterans Affairs department withdrew from consideration amid a maelstrom of negative headlines, President Donald Trump called into his favorite show… https://t.co/9su7pxyI7x https://t.co/Cjfr6IoOls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Javascript Developer: BENEFITSABOUT O3 WORLDABOUT O3 WORLDO3 World is seeking a JavaScript developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site… https://t.co/bbuIZomPdU https://t.co/CfR4BiGkVS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>