<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development,distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products toprofessional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/Jof1QOkxOe https://t.co/z9GCvs6Ydt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola Philippaerts wraps up double success in Chantilly: It was a golden weekend for Nicola Philippaerts in Chantilly, who picked up his second win of the Longines Global Champions Tour season. https://t.co/ltiGtwhtTT https://t.co/mCLq9GEK3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Support – IT Technician: Field Support – IT Technician Ref No.: 18-01658 Location: Columbus, Ohio Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 07/16/2018 to 01/31/2019 Qualifications: Associate’s degree (AA) or equivalent from two-year college or… https://t.co/eKK5WLNRLT https://t.co/FrzVrrNaJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job in US – OH – Wickliffe for Precision Castparts Corp. | Information Technology Software Developer US – OH – Wickliffe Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 17109 Req. Id 317 Req. Code ******.2… https://t.co/xkLPnM5ckp https://t.co/0AieU8jYRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British PM: Trump 'told me to sue the EU': US President Donald Trump told UK Prime Minister Theresa May she should sue the European Union, rather than go into negotiations with them. https://t.co/dIXCUzhOCK https://t.co/x55y44dJli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant Managed Services – Fusion Middleware: – Senior Consultant Managed Services – Fusion Middleware Posted Date 1 month ago(5/16/2018 1:56 AM) ID 2018-2944 # of Openings 3Category Consulting Work Site – City Columbus Department Consulting… https://t.co/YtjyeW6DC8 https://t.co/sDj1ftcNYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Technician- Entry Level: IT Support Technician- Entry Level / Cincinnati , OH Overview: Seeking an IT Support Technician who is passionate about technology and customer service. Our technicians work directly with end users to diagnose and… https://t.co/dieOuMvLWa https://t.co/9S2h5kArT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL/SSIS Data Integration Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 2 months ago(5/1/2018 1:12 PM) Job ID 22084 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/thVcwiNiCv https://t.co/mC3pFJo2Uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump is the distraction Putin needs: When Russian President Vladimir Putin meets President Donald Trump in Helsinki, Finland, on Monday, he will be riding a symbolic high: The Helsinki summit comes a day after the World Cup final in Moscow, a… https://t.co/eKI7ULZmBp https://t.co/Xac3HaeEHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analyst, Financial Systems: What Financial Systems contributes to Cardinal Health Financial Systems is responsible for overseeing the design, modification, installation and maintenance of accounting and financial systems to ensure the accuracy of… https://t.co/4N355z06GF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative – Tier I: Windstream is seeking entry level Specialist’s for Tier I Repair. Our Specialist will assist Windstream Broadband Internet customers with troubleshooting and incident creation to resolve customer trouble. In… https://t.co/iRNMQcG5Ev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge blasts HHS official's warning of endangering children as 'cover' to Trump admin in key immigration case: A federal judge has blasted a declaration from a senior official at the Department of Health and Human Services who claimed that using a… https://t.co/wZb4WDaPEc https://t.co/bAxCdHxqo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Systems Administrator: Strategy &amp; Planning – Create and modify Operation &amp; Support documentation. – Coordinate production maintenance activities. – Perform quarterly assertions to ensure adequate amount of resources are available to systems… https://t.co/hNRkFKAhVK https://t.co/hjDk9w3f7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP HCM: SAP HCM Ref No.: 18-28742 Location: Johnston City, Illinois Job title: SAP HCM Location: Johnston City, IA Duration: 12 months Must have 5-7 years of in-depth SAP Payroll/Time experience Should have configuration knowledge of Personnel… https://t.co/PK4m6jdPCw https://t.co/MyFCxmE7yJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formula E: Frenchman Jean-Eric Vergne clinches title on Bastille Day: Jean-Eric Vergne clinched the Formula E title for France on Bastille Day as the penultimate round in New York was won by departing champion Lucas di Grassi. https://t.co/4YT5bYke9B https://t.co/2OVpa2p2jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead API Developer Job: Req #: 79388 Location Name: Home Office, Columbus Department: Information Technology At DSW, we believe in the power of shoes. We understand shoes bring out something great from within, and since 1991 we’ve been helping everyone… https://t.co/f4gKwUIBhq https://t.co/oQGDivGaTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Fortnite' fever to generate a new type of World Cup next year?: As soccer's World Cup wraps up, the globe might not have to wait four more years to witness another international competition -- in fact, we might only have to wait 12 months. The… https://t.co/dVDTekliQD https://t.co/apa953R4IL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 12 minutes ago(6/18/2018 9:45 AM) Job ID 23422 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/LeZLC7xbf2 https://t.co/6LVw24LDyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Text Exstream Developer: Open Text Exstream Developer Ref No.: 18-27660 Location: Columbus, Ohio Good Knowledge/Hands-on on working in OT Design Manager and Designer Creating, Mapping – Data files, Pages, Documents, templates, output queues, Rules,… https://t.co/k7RTrrT2MV https://t.co/ePZQWWML1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web/Core System Sr. Programmer: Web/Core System Sr. Programmer – GBS Corp – Home – Company Information – Document Library – MyGBS – GBS Assist – Careers – Contact Us – SOLUTIONS – – Content Management – – Document Imaging – – Disaster Recovery – E-Forms… https://t.co/wdzJYBGt2b https://t.co/dEsuMp1NGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transmission Project Analyst – Cincinnati, OH: More than a career – a chance to make a difference in people’s lives. Build an exciting, rewarding career with us help us make a difference for millions of people every day. Consider joining the Duke Energy… https://t.co/223sZ03h6k https://t.co/HjpUgWzExz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protester paraglides over Trump, gets away: A paragliding protester hovered within surprising proximity of President Donald Trump on Friday night as the president admired the view from Trump Turnberry, his golf resort in Scotland. https://t.co/ApUMraDlZG https://t.co/T8upIz5dBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wire EDM Operator/Programmer: Search Display *************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=56 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=****** Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job… https://t.co/FU1wo92mk9 https://t.co/0rMlLDMLC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: What Software Engineering contributes to Cardinal Health Software Engineering is responsible for designing, developing, implementing and supporting applications, systems and IT products required to achieve the company’s business… https://t.co/2JFoWygUhR https://t.co/j2agnQ0PMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impact of Sessions' asylum move already felt at border: Immigrants are already being turned away at the border under Attorney General Jeff Sessions' recent reinterpretation of asylum law. And advocates for them fear there may be no end to it anytime soon. https://t.co/rAcCZJVzNd https://t.co/nLW2NOv4KL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/ADmbtWEI92 https://t.co/ASIhnhKQVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trumps are spending the weekend at the President's Scottish golf resort as UK protests continue: US President Donald Trump is spending Saturday at his Turnberry golf resort in southwestern Scotland, as protests against his visit to the United Kingdom… https://t.co/fHFNcVISjQ https://t.co/FoYHymoiUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator Sr: POSITION OVERVIEW At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR SR within… https://t.co/2nBBQmqvlu https://t.co/JnJsMXFBJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead: The BioPharma Reporting &amp; Analytics – Tech Lead is a software engineering craftsman that is a full-stack engineering lead and coach that is an expert at working in all layers of an application and guiding and building a team of engineers. They… https://t.co/7174N2T2aN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Toledo, OH: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by Postal… https://t.co/p1E0QqMPnz https://t.co/zvJnUsag7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Sinatra, former wife of Frank Sinatra, dead at 101: Nancy Sinatra, the first wife of singer Frank Sinatra, died Friday at the age of 101, her daughter said. https://t.co/u4wi4sf3K1 https://t.co/We3gZe6qti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Description at SUSE Skip Navigation ******** Home Page Grab hold of a dynamic, colorful career. Search Our Jobs Search Our Jobs Keyword Search City, State or ZIP Search RadiusRadius5 miles15 miles25… https://t.co/rhxJaIGxw4 https://t.co/y2ZwZqHhfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-10623 Location: Houston, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Role: .Net Developer Location: Houston, OH Job Type: Contract Roles and responsibilities: – Resource should be strong on C# Design and… https://t.co/fnZ41RThV3 https://t.co/EluDulMZAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-CIA director: Mueller investigation will have 'a widening circle' of indictments: Former CIA Director Michael Hayden anticipates many more indictments -- including those of Americans -- to come in special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into… https://t.co/bHMH5u93sD https://t.co/G45NeGBgKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Global Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/D7oB44ee5C https://t.co/c9drWgS4Ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/13/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/Rn4aZWCWLK https://t.co/O5KZH7HSvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he's more popular than Abraham Lincoln. That's a hard claim to back up: President Trump said in an interview on Thursday that he is the most popular person in the history of the Republican Party and told The Sun he was, "[b]eating Lincoln. I… https://t.co/IjBPGepCh9 https://t.co/rZEctlLCOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 12 minutes ago(6/18/2018 9:45 AM) Job ID 23422 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/dx7SUfeBJB https://t.co/7O8as3hNZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight endangered black rhinos die in Kenya national park: Kenya is probing the death of eight rhinos at one of the country's national parks just weeks after the animals were moved. https://t.co/EfKBdXIHAP https://t.co/EX7QrR2BBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Manager (Provider Network Manager): *Ideal candidate will be located in or near Cincinnati or Toledo, OH metro area* Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging… https://t.co/IBQR7rgWr6 https://t.co/Cwh5hoBsCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Immigration is 'changing the culture' of Europe: President Donald Trump said Friday that European leaders "better watch themselves" because immigration is "changing the culture" of their societies. https://t.co/4vLvjnylQo https://t.co/aRgHxkDBCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Food Technology Specialist, Quality Systems: now Corporate Food Technology Specialist, Quality Systems ===================================================== Company Name: Kroger Manufacturing Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Position… https://t.co/K505AcjM4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Capability Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/FlRxjeAzlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ikea is postponing its first store opening in India over quality concerns: The Swedish furniture giant is delaying the opening of its store in Hyderabad, India, because it needs more time 'to live up to its expected quality commitments.' https://t.co/aZl2p3CIc1 https://t.co/oatg8VEKqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers.… https://t.co/rynYFMkSMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On sale in Australia: Avocados as big as your face: The world's largest avocado has just premiered Down Under. Dubbed "Avozillas" -- these souped-up avocados are about five times bigger than a regular one. https://t.co/DwwIHZYKje https://t.co/CohjBjkrta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist: We are seeking an IT Support Specialist to join our information technology team in our Independence, Ohio support center. This individual will be responsible for performing on-site desktop repair, and installations. Provide technical… https://t.co/UkZDhHAC0i https://t.co/lnLRARU3qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple is spending millions to clean up China's environment: Apple is setting up a clean energy fund with some of its suppliers that plans to invest $300 million in projects in China. https://t.co/2iIXEvd6q3 https://t.co/nMlILT9VNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Scientist/Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides integrated services to… https://t.co/7n1UhCz0zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[58 immigrant children reunited as government slowly reconnects families: Fifty-eight immigrant children under the age of 5 have been reunited with their parents after being separated at the border, the Trump administration said in a Thursday evening… https://t.co/lrQ2fDWqI1 https://t.co/1jwSwfCfjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Developer: Senior Big Data Developer : Job Description Roles and Responsibilities: 1. Gathers requirements from stakeholders, designs the solution aligned to requirements, platform(s) architecture and infrastructure. 2. Engages with… https://t.co/PKcVg6GYD5 https://t.co/wELuGvPlER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (JAVA Developer): Cardinal Health at Home is a best-in-class provider of medical supplies to patients in the home. It is comprised of two separate operating segments: Edgepark, a leading direct-to-consumer (DTC) medical… https://t.co/7CwMM5skRo https://t.co/rs5IDNQJQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump criticizes British PM Theresa May over Brexit deal: US President Donald Trump touched down in the United Kingdom Thursday and spoke with a major British tabloid where he differed with British Prime Minister Theresa May on her approach to Brexit. https://t.co/wi4bNAuhXc https://t.co/yazpxCNTzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: What the Enterprise Digital Marketing UX Design team contributes to Cardinal Health The UX team is responsible for supporting website design needs, user experience development and front-end code creation for the business units… https://t.co/VHfH3b8SRX https://t.co/tkXTtrvVyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quickly catch up on the day's news: Here's what you might have missed today on CNN. https://t.co/xu1UadEh7F https://t.co/gPe1ewycS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Senior Application Developer Job Description Make Your Mark on one of America’s most crucial industries! POSITION SUMMARY Join us to develop the future of real-world, user-centered construction technology with a creative and… https://t.co/RtYCRpjdzm https://t.co/2aceUhnelM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware/Web Engineering Manager: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/KkGMA3fIuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Roseanne' scores two Emmy nominations, despite controversy: "Roseanne" may get the last laugh. https://t.co/TWdzNut8kq https://t.co/tIP109ggxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Developer: Roles and Responsibilities: 1. Gathers requirements from stakeholders, designs the solution aligned to requirements, platform(s) architecture and infrastructure. 2. Develops, tests, maintains, and enhances data stores (tables, views,… https://t.co/n4JnibaMAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Quality Assurance Analyst: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 26 minutes ago(6/19/2018 10:01 AM) Job ID 23728 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance Group. As… https://t.co/IyXp2A7qgC https://t.co/OI4S1nt1gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: JOB SUMMARY: Designs, develops, documents and tests software systems, especially embedded systems, for use within equipment or machinery. ESSENTIAL/PRIMARY DUTIES: – Design, develop and maintain embedded firmware for process… https://t.co/9hML4gPTVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next Air Force One could be red, white and blue: The next Air Force One will likely be red, white and blue — but don't expect any eagles painted on the side of the presidential aircraft. https://t.co/eFBjQ0dLEd https://t.co/Clm8MdF0lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tavolara: Sailing to the 'smallest kingdom' in the world: If you travel to the eastern coast of Sardinia to the island of Tavolara, you will almost certainly be graced with the presence of a royal: Antonio Bartoleoni. https://t.co/tgLaM1Ctet https://t.co/C98RD8Oy0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[91-year-old man beaten with a brick asks God's forgiveness for his attacker: The 91-year-old man who says he was beaten with a brick in Willowbrook, California, doesn't resent the woman who assaulted him, he told CNN affiliate KABC. https://t.co/9OqIkAb1jM https://t.co/nAizqsYMGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Support Analyst: Multi-Color Corporation is seeking a Senior IT Support Analyst to join our Corporate Information Technology team, located in Batavia, Ohio! As a member of the Helpdesk Team, the support analyst will be responsible for… https://t.co/lzIZDzqP6D https://t.co/5LQY8fyzqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump's disdain for NATO could help Putin: The big takeaway of the so far bad-tempered NATO summit is that President Donald Trump has little time for the alliance and a thin appreciation of the track record and historic purpose of an organization… https://t.co/unNSoTQmom https://t.co/qaCFBGfIdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer | experience testing data treatment processes from data ingestion to output to reporting: SQL BI Developer | experience testing data treatment processes from data ingestion to output to reporting Columbus, OH, Dublin, OH 06-13-2018… https://t.co/A6SpCzlRae https://t.co/VkTdYNi4Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst – SAP ABAP: Careers Center | Senior Programmer Analyst – SAP ABAP Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/lDW013wUV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration to turn away far more asylum seekers at the border under new guidance: The Trump administration is implementing a new asylum policy at the border that will result in potentially thousands of asylum seekers being turned away before… https://t.co/51ZVikdhUJ https://t.co/N3XBF9Rzj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Implementation Specialist: Summary:Heartland Payroll, a division of Global Payments, delivers the industry’s most comprehensive packages of reliable and value-added payroll and human resource solutions to thousands of small to mid-sized… https://t.co/1fmkY61HKn https://t.co/sRZJDWHuQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Ref No.: 18-26117 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Role: Solution Architect Location: Cincinnati OH Duration:9-12 months JD – Strong Architect experience with skillsets reflecting that of Java, Spring MVC, CRM, IVR,… https://t.co/X41XoSSve1 https://t.co/I8OIAP8mmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, SAP FICO: At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers and… https://t.co/1gGZNygtz7 https://t.co/x6krJiHKqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her father left to provide for them. Her mother was detained trying to join him. Now they're a family again: Yoselyn spent a month apart from her family in a children's shelter. The last three hours she spent waiting to be reunited with her mother felt… https://t.co/yJJGOcNVxH https://t.co/5Ayb9pFti5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Scheduler/Project Manager: Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Planner Position Description The Master Scheduler is an energized and independently driven change management leader on the StandardAero team.… https://t.co/UGcpmOhIEs https://t.co/DZXyWueisx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consulting Engineer Cisco Network/Data Center: Senior Consulting Engineer – Cisco Network/Data Center in Columbus, OH – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join the CDW COMMUNITY true Home… https://t.co/Y4GyvmDL6O https://t.co/mDUOQdkago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Capability Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/19/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/aQa22XFq5R https://t.co/3eUV7RSV4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blood pressure linked to lesions, signs of Alzheimer's in autopsied brains: Older people with higher-than-average blood pressure have more markers of disease in their autopsied brains, a new study found. https://t.co/94LcExOIpa https://t.co/umKy8ptaaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer Email Marketing Consultant: Web Developer – Email Marketing Consultant – Columbus, OH We are currently seeking a Web Developer to work as an email marketing consultant for a National Fortune 100 company in downtown Columbus, OH. An ideal… https://t.co/8bB5FwUezU https://t.co/JikC0Z4Bnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Lead: Job Title: .NET Lead Location: Findlay, OH Job Number: JO-1806-27512 Description ProKarma is currently seeking a .NET Lead to join our team in Findlay, OH! Qualified candidates must possess a minimum of 8 years’ experience with at least… https://t.co/agiXUVMxp4 https://t.co/jmgozX7hPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial Turkish televangelist arrested: Police arrested controversial Islamic televangelist Adnan Oktar in an early-morning raid on his upscale home in the Turkish capital, according to state news agency Anadolu. https://t.co/AkZufoTfSd https://t.co/5ndLkVRDWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 4 days ago(6/14/2018 9:27 AM) Job ID 23219 # Positions 3 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity for… https://t.co/CaaIS62LUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Manhattan: Job Title: Systems Analyst – Manhattan Requisition Number: 23510 Position Type: Full Time City: Columbus Campus: Columbus State/Province: Ohio Job Description: The Systems Analyst I – Manhattan is responsible for analysis,… https://t.co/nxHLkVISJU https://t.co/nGbD6vRvxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court watch: What Brett Kavanaugh's paper trail means for the confirmation timeline: President Donald Trump's Supreme Court nominee is kicking his closed-door meetings with senators into high gear Wednesday, all as the parameters of the fight… https://t.co/gJ3s0TGuih https://t.co/Hlsfdt7Ngz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Appraisal Tax: Project Manager, Appraisal &amp; Tax ================================ The Project Manager successfully manages the implementation of Tyler software for new and existing accounts, from the contract signing through formal… https://t.co/oCPjXDU3rr https://t.co/5YCZ1cx8sS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer $140k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Android Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily in our… https://t.co/89Gn1tuqFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elayne Boosler: Saying 'joke' is no excuse for offensive behavior: Elayne Boosler: Stop calling "vile" statements "jokes." "No. You are not going to cloud up our art form." https://t.co/5Ltg1Btu7N https://t.co/FyGKwd84It]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive:   Job Description – Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive (019775) Job Description  Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive-019775 Description   As the Diebold Nixdorf Americas Managed Service Delivery Executive… https://t.co/tvlj0Ykhqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Lead System Administrator: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 days ago(6/29/2018 11:44 AM) Job ID 23766 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/Gm4uupa6Wt https://t.co/6hgKvdpDJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump accuses Germany of being a 'captive of Russia' ahead of NATO summit: President Donald Trump on Wednesday accused fellow NATO ally Germany of being beholden to Russia because it buys energy from Moscow, in pointed remarks ahead of a summit of the… https://t.co/jibWP6Yqtt https://t.co/ot9lUxxwvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistani Taliban claims responsibility for deadly election suicide attack: The Pakistani Taliban have claimed responsibility for Tuesday's suicide attack which left at least 20 people dead in Peshawar, a city near the Afghan border. https://t.co/X5ZFS3N1gX https://t.co/y3A5iVGzus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA MySQL Developer: JAVA – MySQL Developer Ref No.: 18-28163 Location: Columbus, Ohio Foundation : MySQL, Assurance : Java Unit Testing Frameworks (Junit, *Unit, *Mock, Cactus, etc), Foundation : Java EE – EJB 3.0/JPA, Spring MVC https://t.co/AxLkGfzODD https://t.co/rOAIz7Asr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Department Ops Mgmt Employment Type Full time Minimum Experience Mid-level Environmental Management Specialists, Inc. (EMS) is a professional environmental contractor specializing in environmental cleanup and site remediation, emergency… https://t.co/doBTDHvLCF https://t.co/sFCfStYf1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/HwaHkHs90H https://t.co/HZc60NmCFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort's lawyers have new concerns about where he should be jailed: Paul Manafort's lawyers have new concerns about where the formmer Trump campaign chairman should be held in jail. https://t.co/itQ67bWh15 https://t.co/A5YXYL7pQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Scheduler/Project Manager: Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Planner Position Description The Master Scheduler is an energized and independently driven change management leader on the StandardAero team.… https://t.co/AfoPvYIlYk https://t.co/yjbnBUZv1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: **Software Engineer** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle Management-PLM **Requisition… https://t.co/IchQGJeV6d https://t.co/9A2ULFw5xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump launches new tariffs on China: The Trump administration is readying another round of tariffs on Chinese goods worth $200 billion. https://t.co/z892dglHRG https://t.co/WuxBJrYVTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France beat Belgium's 'golden generation' to reach World Cup final: Twenty years after France first won the World Cup, Les Bleus moved to within one match of repeating the feats of the celebrated team of 1998 by beating Belgium to reach Sunday's final. https://t.co/ehR5Wqlwle https://t.co/8CDHS3j6Fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grandparents went to visit their soldier son-in-law at an Army base on July 4 and were turned over to ICE: Concepción and Margarito Silva planned to enjoy July 4th with their family at an Army base in upstate New York. But their day ended instead in a… https://t.co/7iAb16WpMU https://t.co/z53fvMU5KW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The oil market has very little room for error: The world was awash in excess crude oil just two years ago. Now, there's barely enough crude being pumped to meet unquenchable thirst for energy. https://t.co/dh4VLoEgB7 https://t.co/RNI5BJKDi6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>