<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/4stPaXhv4A https://t.co/ySLIiH3wCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap loses users for the first time, beats on revenue: Snap Inc's Snapchat app unexpectedly lost users in the second quarter, the company said on Tuesday, likely adding fuel to investor fears about slowing growth in the social media sector. https://t.co/G4v11oJtO2 https://t.co/vdrNWrh8wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect III: Cupertino, CA. Amazon Web Services, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Solutions Architect III, Strategic Accounts, Job Code AZJMSolArc: Serve as a primary technical contact for AWS customers to drive technical… https://t.co/edR5gZK7n9 https://t.co/OaXjby2G63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer #KI072018ID: Informatica Developer (Irvine, CA): Design and develop applications; Deliver ETL and related components as specified in the design, functional, and non-functional requirements for data warehousing projects,… https://t.co/UiY6xmUb1H https://t.co/y0X56uENHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Honolulu, HI Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/11/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Data Analyst, Senior The Challenge: Are you interested in using data… https://t.co/4FLfrGDkc0 https://t.co/UHer2mqQh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baidu ready to beat Google if U.S. firm returns to China: CEO: Baidu Inc is prepared to win against Alphabet Inc's Google in China, its chief executive officer said on social media, amid rumblings the U.S. search engine giant was planning to re-enter a… https://t.co/GioSo5ofK0 https://t.co/3GByh9jLJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Java Developer (Junior, Mid Sr. Level): Overview Job Description We are looking for a Back-End Web Developer with 2+ years’ experience responsible for managing the interchange of data between the server and the users. Your primary focus will be… https://t.co/JblfosVTi2 https://t.co/bFklsfm45U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Support Analyst: Job Description Since 1996, Surgical Information Systems (‘SIS’) has been dedicated to providing surgical care providers with the solutions and services they need to deliver improved operational, financial, and clinical outcomes.… https://t.co/ZJ54jJn8zB https://t.co/3O165JsiOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Systems Training Support Engineer: Cyber Systems Training Support Engineer Job Locations US-VA-Springfield Job ID 10525 Minimum Clearance Required Secret Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is seeking a Cyber Systems… https://t.co/06n3L912xi https://t.co/SeegSYDCVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst – Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation: For BNY Mellon Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst – Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation job – Information Technology… https://t.co/QEy0lM8frq https://t.co/QJUC1EFAbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Audit: IT AUDIT MANAGER We are unable to sponsor as this is a permanent full time role. RESPONSIBILITIES * Drive end-to-end audit services * Perform independent audit and advisory services * Audit scoping, walkthroughs, procedure development… https://t.co/ctVWMtUNCk https://t.co/7sImecRsQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Analyst #13122: Sno-Isle Libraries invites applications for the position of: Senior Systems Analyst Location: Service Center (Marysville) Pay Range: $31.94 – $43.92 Hourly Hours per week: 40 Job #req13122 Closing Date: August 8, 2018 Job… https://t.co/BK0OW9Ckes https://t.co/A1E5LLKdxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Location: Langley, WA Summary This business analyst position is a key interface between users, systems, and the project manager as they gather information, document processes, and measure success with the users.  Duties… https://t.co/5mXpk0z71O https://t.co/PFmlBUaoJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk SRM Tech Lead Secret Clearance: Requisition ID *******Posting Date 03/23/2018Category ServicesLocation Norfolk, Virginia | United StatesSchedule Full-timeEmployee Status Day JobEEO Tagline: DXC Technology is EEO F/M/Protected Veteran/… https://t.co/MCyHyjVSbb https://t.co/IhbUOKgJ3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solutions Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: El Segundo, CA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Cloud Solutions Developer, Senior Key Role: Support the full… https://t.co/of0AEWb2iQ https://t.co/zpqDqYXTat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Data Analyst: Sr Data Analyst : 18-02840 Ref No.: 18-02840 Location: Aurora, Colorado Akraya is looking for a Sr Data Analyst for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Vassem Raja at ************ If… https://t.co/hBbeOFrcrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Developer: Peoplesoft Developer Ref No.: 18-33721 Location: Tempe, Arizona Job Role: Peoplesoft Developer Location; Tempe, AZ Contract Role Skills &amp; Responsibilities: – We are looking for a Peoplesoft Sr. Developer/Designer that has experience… https://t.co/Mz5qovvwrH https://t.co/r88xzLnR9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Electronic Content Management (ECM) Developer: Job Description DaVita, a leader in the medical services industry, is currently seeking an experienced Enterprise Content Management (ECM) professional to join our team. This team is organized as a… https://t.co/4j80yD1sOS https://t.co/BJBvfzXcyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Defined Radio (SDR) / Embedded Systems Design Engineer: Job Description Software Defined Radio (SDR) / Embedded Systems Design Engineer (14586) The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific… https://t.co/mb3tSTRqQf https://t.co/SjCAZgKrd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer job in San Antonio, Texas, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE Systems – Our Culture – Diversity &amp; Inclusion – Veterans – Students &amp; Graduates… https://t.co/fuXgL5OuUs https://t.co/TJaC3Fj6Qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Development Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… You will be in a technical leadership role with the Network Automation engineering team. In that capacity, you will participate in all aspects of development and engineering… https://t.co/mBMAPQKo0w https://t.co/3VNIA8w3or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-43345 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description For more than 50 years, General Dynamics Information Technology has served as a… https://t.co/JeeiXnbnu1 https://t.co/A5Qo5fbodD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Application Developer: We have a unique opportunity for a Enterprise Application Developer to join our team supporting our U.S. military customer and their vital mission. We are an award winning company that cares about its customers and its… https://t.co/paOWsfORX9 https://t.co/ZYJdpZObeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAGTF IO Sr. Principal Operations Analyst/Planning Support TS/SCI Quantico, VA: Requisition ID 2018-42012 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides military… https://t.co/KlqOz76LP0 https://t.co/1CLk0qbK7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: APPLICATION SUPPORT ANALYST TYPE: Direct Hire LOCATION: The Woolands, TX SALARY: $85k/yr APPLICATION SUPPORT ANALYST SUMMARY This position is responsible for supporting core business applications, including but not limited to… https://t.co/gFxnhLxNng https://t.co/uUVbOesNCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei in British spotlight over use of U.S. firm's software: Huawei Technologies [HWT.UL] is facing increased scrutiny in Britain because it is using an aging software component sold by a firm based in the United States, one of the countries where… https://t.co/XbRyeMokAT https://t.co/1CWmTHognw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: ProtonMail – Careers – EN – English – ES – Espaol – DE – Deutsch – FR – Franais – HU – Magyar – ID – Inggris – IT – Italiano – JP – – NL – Nederlands – PL – Polski – PT-BR – Ingls – RO – Romn – RU – P – TR – Trke – UA – – Help Translate Toggle… https://t.co/iIJDvpk1Ib https://t.co/EXW8SstbLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project-Manager—Pharmaceutical-Exp-: PROJECT MANAGER – PHARMACEUTICAL EXP. PRINCETON, NJ Project Description: – Looking for a candidate with Agile experience (Scrum Master or Product Owner experience). – Preference will go to candidates with following… https://t.co/XDA9k6QH5k https://t.co/Y42pOTOBNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Job Description The Team: Fueling the technologies that drive our products and support our company’s infrastructure, the Technology team within our Corporate team consists of talented developers, network architects, and IT experts who… https://t.co/rLJC6VycNy https://t.co/olRmDH2D7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Technology Information Technology Alexandria, Virginia, United States 7/11/16 Job ID: 12088900 Qualifications Bachelors degree in computer science, information systems, or other related discipline 8+ years of computer security consulting… https://t.co/6mtMmrpkCQ https://t.co/y3WWxPQeuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Job Title Associate Project Manager Job ID(Requisition ID):3588 Job Summary Benchmark products and designs have been seen at the Olympics, the Super Bowl, and in Hollywood. America’s women and men in uniform count on our… https://t.co/6A4C4w5aUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-32625 Location: Santa Clara, California Software Engineer (******) Print Job Title:Software Engineer Duration: 13-Aug-2018 – 08-Feb-2019 Status:Open Business Unit:****** – Silicon Valley Digital Operations… https://t.co/vZePyXktXS https://t.co/Nobo4uSV6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic candidates told not to use ZTE, Huawei devices: source: The Democratic National Committee warned party candidates running in November elections not to use devices made by Chinese telecommunications companies ZTE Corp and Huawei Technologies… https://t.co/kDgEGVcAhT https://t.co/RnUY98n06y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Web Developer: Connecticut College Associate Web Developer Create proof-of-concepts, build production-quality programming code and web sites; experience in HTML, CSS, Java Script.  AA/EOE. recblid maik999v254v04iuq5g3czom2vx1ur https://t.co/tsfMwjAGNl https://t.co/MfSEkv4zEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS ANALYST II: University of Kansas Hospital has an opening in Mission, KS for an Applications Analyst II, responsible for implementation and support of application. Requires BS in computer science and 2 yrs experience in a healthcare setting… https://t.co/wTGsE7CIy1 https://t.co/UjezmaOmG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Quality Expert for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) location to work on programs or unit levels or across organizational boundaries with special focus to quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process.… https://t.co/Ww6kKHVQ5G https://t.co/P2pVvmTX0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Administrator Governance, Risk and Compliance Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with… https://t.co/k3134FtpBR https://t.co/R0bq0lOb0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYSE-owner ICE to form new company for digital assets: Intercontinental Exchange Inc, the owner of the New York Stock Exchange, said on Friday it plans to form a company and trading platform for digital assets, such as bitcoin, as well as a physically… https://t.co/XWjo1yYepd https://t.co/eI6JPIJGSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Job Description PSI Title: Data Scientist (Analytical Methodologist) Work Location: DC – Washington Description This position located at Bolling AFB supports the development and application of analytic methods within the process of… https://t.co/dFKH5y0uy3 https://t.co/oNRluQOig0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator – TS/SCI with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-41274 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the analysis,… https://t.co/jMakDqf4uc https://t.co/F0YO36SV7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration and Test Engineer: 112572BR Senior Integration and Test Engineer CO – Aurora 112572BR Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving… https://t.co/rwtjsgRmnz https://t.co/23B4UKKAIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Engineer (SDET, JAVA, Automation): Job Details San Diego************ Phoenix************ – About – The Company – Our Team – Why Sayva – Solutions – Sayva Consulting – Sayva Financial – Sayva Technology – Sayva Accounting Services – Careers… https://t.co/r1eVcdsghy https://t.co/zRyUPYmt5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Software Engineer (Mid-Level): Supporting the Most Exciting and Meaningful Missions in the World Mobile Software Engineer (Mid-Level) PAE is seeking a Mobile Software Engineer (Mid-Level) to support the National Media Exploitation Center(NMEC) in… https://t.co/EwSLisJFOM https://t.co/g71Wus8Vys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior/Entry Level Backend Software Engineer: JUNIOR/ENTRY LEVEL BACKEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER CENTREVILLE, VIRGINIA Ready for a challenge that will keep you on the cutting edge of cyber-security? Employer works on top level cyber-security for national… https://t.co/pk9qYv40VH https://t.co/sI8yfk42Qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run your dishwasher when the sun shines: dynamic power pricing grows: One day, the weather could drive your domestic schedule. Your dishwasher springs to life at the windiest time of day. The washing machine starts spinning when the sun beats down. https://t.co/mYt1PEWLE0 https://t.co/VsPKIyNUx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/21/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/icRg0ut2KW https://t.co/WFb32ji3in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Application Specialist Internship: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables,… https://t.co/2UI3kGJqla https://t.co/n1rFGvRieF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab sees strong demand from investors to buy into business: president: Southeast-Asian ride-hailing firm Grab is seeing strong demand from investors keen to buy into it, a top executive said on Thursday, after the company announced new investment of $1… https://t.co/h0PsnOTTN4 https://t.co/6tRPEV7XkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – Associate – CHC: Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Associate – CHC Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: UPMC Health Plan Department: Community HealthChoices Location: 600… https://t.co/DCzjKay3Bu https://t.co/nvO8GHjyh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Application Architect – Seattle: Job Description Cloud Application Architect – Seattle Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Job Description Are you an experienced cloud architect/developer who can assist our… https://t.co/a5YJuGBzEI https://t.co/LFfxhzSKxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla second-quarter report could be an $850 million boon or bane for short-sellers: Tesla Inc - the most heavily shorted U.S. company - is set to report quarterly results on Wednesday, and short-sellers could be dealt a nearly $850 million loss or gain,… https://t.co/5aenC0uDkX https://t.co/CB02xeeiyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineers (Multiple Positions) Netflix, Inc. has career opportunities in Los Gatos for Engineers including: Software, Quality Assurance, Applications, Systems, Data Architect, IT Applications, User Interface, Localization,… https://t.co/Rrm9Mk0eW3 https://t.co/0gJ3jsbR1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Backend Developer Jersey City, New Jersey – United States Job Start Date – 07/03/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsBackend developerTax TermsC2COverview This is NOT Fullstack. We talked to the manager on Friday and he wants a… https://t.co/4lIm4UH5rS https://t.co/hQ96XGn5HM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst – Associate (Application Trainer): Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Associate (Application Trainer) Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: Corporate Information Services… https://t.co/L3LJh7pZvx https://t.co/tysc79MEHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: SR Number ERS-/ERS-/2018/****** Designation Technical Lead Location Utah Job Family Engg (Engg – S/W &amp; S/W Product Engg) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for managing technology in projects and providing technical guidance /… https://t.co/C9HtC4L7OZ https://t.co/gjym2vYd8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator TS/SCI required: Contract: I2TS 3 Position: Administrator, Systems – Systems Administrator (L2) Location: Fort Shafter, Hawaii GENERAL SUMMARY: GDIT is seeking candidates to support the US Army Intelligence and Security Command… https://t.co/T0zWyCYAvQ https://t.co/S8fdO2WDBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response Security Engineer: Position: Incident Response Security Engineer Job Description: Job Summary; Part of Arrow Electronics Global Enterprise Services Team, the Incident Response Data Analyst will generally assist with service delivery by… https://t.co/Sjpuyglhtm https://t.co/Vv78U5tJPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Position Summary Coordinates, processes and resolves incidents and requests related the support of technology products, infrastructure, business processes and enterprise services. Takes full responsibility for handling customer… https://t.co/Rz70LMqA6A https://t.co/prcDMVzoBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager, Global Quality Regulatory: Senior Program Manager, Global Quality &amp; Regulatory in with LinkedIn Job Number SMNA00726 Job Family Global Regulatory Affairs and Quality Assurance Position Type Permanent Country USA City Minneapolis… https://t.co/jgo39xlMSB https://t.co/y9fDbNTo7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase hires chief compliance officer: Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has hired finance executive Jeff Horowitz as chief compliance officer, to help it navigate regulations for virtual currency companies, the company said on… https://t.co/DFfoyXmAPT https://t.co/qizl7Uqt7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr, Database Admin.: IT: Rakuten USA, Inc. seeks Mgr, Database Admin. in San Mateo, CA. Duties incl, but not limited to designing &amp; mng’g database syst’s by using several DBMS techs like Oracle, Oracle RAC &amp; MySQL for mission critical bus. which handle… https://t.co/3ZBAJSMOS7 https://t.co/a5nchHRmtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer II: https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Services, Inc. and A2Z Development Center, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Data Engineer II, Job Code AZ0306: Identify, design, develop, implement, test, document, and operate large-scale,… https://t.co/HyDnqvBBOh https://t.co/iTgAiE1l5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase hires first chief compliance officer: Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has hired finance executive Jeff Horowitz in its new role of chief compliance officer, to help it navigate regulations for virtual currency companies,… https://t.co/i50rjUtMrL https://t.co/gdyewcGH6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Manager – IT Service Management/ITIL: Requisition ID 2018-40867 # of Openings 2 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics Information Technology – Federal Civilian… https://t.co/jsRc8XQNVX https://t.co/W5MmpRs6C8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Technical Support Specialist-Concrete Equipment: SunIRef:Sales:title Sales &amp; Technical Support Specialist-Concrete Equipment Liebherr USA Co. – Newport News, VA Job Summary: The Sales &amp; Technical Support Specialist assists the sales and marketing… https://t.co/pKi3SM8aJB https://t.co/TpPX3ilVSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OPIR Next Gen Acquisition and Data Exploitation Job: Date: Jun 14, 2018 Location:El Segundo, CA, US Company: SAIC OPIR Next Gen Acquisition and Data Exploitation (Job Number:435123) Description: Job Description: SAIC is currently looking for a senior… https://t.co/vcickYqasp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dot net developer: Job Titledot net developer – ID:32167 Duration4 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsC#, .net, Mvc, SQL LocationHilliard, OH Date Posted07/19/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for dot net developer… https://t.co/zWlnviD671 https://t.co/xBD6E8v2Lq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Sunnyvale, CA. https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Services, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Software Development Engineer in Test II, Job Code AZJM-SDET2: Create and execute test plans and cases for large-scale… https://t.co/ltycjBb936 https://t.co/NPbnPPUzif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks and China's Alibaba to partner on delivery: media reports: Starbucks Corp and e-commerce company Alibaba Group Holding Ltd are set to join forces on coffee delivery, according to media reports, as the coffee retailer seeks to rebound from a… https://t.co/KcRp33OB7p https://t.co/wvpsOX3cRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: TECHNOLOGY Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) has multiple openings at our Santa Clara, CA facility for the following positions: Software Engineer 2 (req. 000028), Software Senior Engineer (req. 000187), Software Principal… https://t.co/YgjYKXW2hx https://t.co/FjpHRgX7NH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Hardware Engineer: ENGINEERING: ARRIS Global Services, Inc. sks Staff HW Engr in Santa Clara, CA Coord, plan &amp; dev derivative des &amp; intro new component tech into existing products, improving quality &amp; reducing cost. Job ID MS+4 (18001991). Degree… https://t.co/ryxNwMre36 https://t.co/Jha3fwhgrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: The Edmonds School District is hiring a Systems Administrator! Edmonds School District is committed to workplace diversity and aims to attract and retain employees with the right skills, knowledge, and life experiences to meet the… https://t.co/ywQp1W9F1P https://t.co/cs48ZHLWke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical Systems Analyst I: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Stanford Health Care seeks Clinical Systems Analyst I to support integration of SHC’s health system IT apps. Reqs Bach. (or foreign equiv.) in Comp Sci, IT, MIS, Eng., Healthcare Admin, Bus, or clinical… https://t.co/0Yf3OjKyCX https://t.co/0k0DCDfAM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Cyber security software dvlpmt, database admin &amp; diagnostic positions available at SonicWall, Inc. (Milpitas, CA): Sr Oracle Dvlpr (REQ #227); Test Sr Engr (REQ #228); Test Staff Engr (REQ #229); Software Dvlpmt Staff Engr (REQ… https://t.co/cw2B5ZrkYz https://t.co/ny6hXsBLX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phone monopoly is big prize in Ethiopia sell-off: In the weeks since Ethiopia announced sweeping privatization plans after decades of state control, foreign businessmen have been beating a path to Belachew Mekuria's office. https://t.co/EOO9UZlOVC https://t.co/J8vRdkQ3jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Tools and DevOps: Software Engineer – Tools and DevOps Jobs in St Louis at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space –… https://t.co/EeK7v6OIWO https://t.co/7P5tJVlNZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Regular QA Automation Engineer: Project Description You will be working in a team which develops an operational risk assessment and reporting solution. You will be working with people located around the world. Our teams are self organized and take… https://t.co/apt6epVcdA https://t.co/Z1Uf129NIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Materials Manager (m/f) – Inspection Technologies: 3076493 Materials Manager (m/f) – Inspection Technologies Oil &amp; Gas Digital Solutions GE Oil &amp; Gas Germany, Ireland, Slovakia, United States Lead weekly PSI/S&amp;OP process to evaluate revenue plan versus… https://t.co/OGJstMNZMy https://t.co/4LPvpreO1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science Test Developer, Alternate Assessment: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10811 Job Location United States Alternate locations Washington, D.C. Category Test Development/Content Overview AIR Assessment is one of America’s leading K -12 educational… https://t.co/eBGnApDlah https://t.co/HLvbCLkqkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Protection Engineer – Cisco Tetration: Information Security Protection Engineer – Cisco Tetration We are building a team of Information Security professionals who will work with other security, network and application experts to… https://t.co/tANtz6ucJg https://t.co/7t4tSbRMsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some banks in Finland face card payment problems: Clients at some banks in Finland have faced problems with the use of their payment cards on Sunday, payment firm Nets said. https://t.co/iKahaDs4xG https://t.co/ZXp2G5grPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[201- Mid-Level Software Engineer: GENERAL DUTIES * Demonstrated experience developing with Ruby on Rails * Demonstrated experience with MongoDB Demonstrated experience with ElasticSearch/ELK Stack * Experience with Application Programming Interface (API)… https://t.co/A2pyWk6Rlz https://t.co/Kx2PwTXYjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Iron Mountain – Careers -Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/o0M1KaM6pv https://t.co/73oSiVyNoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Senior Software Developers interested in joining our team in Alexandria, VA and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this Role the… https://t.co/vyPhgo2gng https://t.co/fwheoutNrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Oracle Database Analyst: Sr. Specialist Oracle Database Analyst ‘ Designs, implements, and supports database management structures, as well as database back-up, recovery, security, archiving and conversion strategies. Collaborates with… https://t.co/xAhlDIF4iF https://t.co/jdoT7TlUlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: OVERVIEW The candidate will be responsible for owning and delivering complex cloud based solutions using technologies such Salesforce, Heroku and J2EE. The candidate will be responsible for owning the architecture and… https://t.co/lnkrg9sX8g https://t.co/m5QX26H5G3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET Tester: SDET Tester Ref No.: 18-28757 Location: Kirkland, Washington Associate should be SDET Minimum 8+ Yrs experience Need strong knowledge in Java , .Net , Linux Testing experience in backend Service Integration , Cloud related testing Test… https://t.co/4ssBwJxCAQ https://t.co/4R0eOKefzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Administrator: Job Description Responsibilities include: – Identifying and correcting hardware and software issues on servers, clients, and networks – Helping to maintain a complex server-based enclave, to include developing and managing… https://t.co/L9EhH2RFIa https://t.co/QMAuNkz8PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech firms should be made liable for 'fake news' on sites: UK lawmakers: Tech firms like Facebook should be made liable for "harmful and misleading" material on their websites and pay a levy so they can be regulated, British lawmakers said, warning of a… https://t.co/eiAfb0NeQt https://t.co/KWtutEMkth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence Analyst 3 – TS/SCI required:   Job Description – Intelligence Analyst 3 – TS/SCI required (18008656) Intelligence Analyst 3 – TS/SCI required Requisition ID : 18008656 Location : United States-Virginia-Quantico US Citizenship Required for… https://t.co/9NIpznZa1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead User Experience Designer: Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceGeneral ManagementHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLearning &amp;… https://t.co/VohQX6nOBX https://t.co/uoGUsYQv7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – North America, Global Support Center: Job Description LocationChandler – AZ, US LevelBachelor Experience0-2 Starter Available since6/29/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq3565 Introduction ASML brings together the most… https://t.co/hLdnREURMO https://t.co/j7OrjcJWWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube plans original programing in India, Japan and other markets: Alphabet Inc's YouTube is creating scripted series and other original programing for international markets including France, Germany, Japan, Mexico and India to try to draw new… https://t.co/8vxdSBHRDb https://t.co/5xKGV9HT3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM wins $83 million from Groupon in internet patent fight: A U.S. jury on Friday awarded International Business Machines Corp $83 million in a patent dispute with e-commerce company Groupon Inc . https://t.co/FA28LeYnOx https://t.co/ctXj5AezCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Embedded Software Engineer: Sr. Embedded Software Engineer Tracking Code ******** Job Description What you’ll be doing: We’ve have been named one of the fastest growing insulin pump companies in the U.S! Why? Tandem has created the simple-to-use… https://t.co/CZ29ubcsAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location US-Hayward-CA, United States Posted By Aegion Corporation Date Posted 6 hours ago Expires 12 Jul 2018 Qualifications None Project Manager II in US-Hayward-CA, United States US-Hayward-CA, United… https://t.co/tVoM4wpfqd https://t.co/md9MNf2Ugd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/21/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/6nHFXlOZ8Y https://t.co/9srAxZpSJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Project Manager: Agile Project Manager : 18-02695 Ref No.: 18-02695 Location: San Bruno, California Akraya is looking for an Agile Project Manager for one of our ecommerce clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or… https://t.co/L85aafkpl3 https://t.co/80qX1bJKG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank to launch mobile payments service in Japan with India's Paytm: SoftBank Group Corp said on Friday it will team up with India's Paytm to launch a digital payments service in Japan. https://t.co/hZBUxBpi2s https://t.co/dlcmGYgq5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform Developer – App Engine: Technology Services Group’s Application Engine is a strategic platform and container as a service that schedules and runs containerized and non-containerized applications on Linux and Windows across our data centers.’ Our… https://t.co/VClmnUx4rH https://t.co/baFhvQg0kx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>