<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this solid book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   Ken Follett's 'The Pillars of the Earth'
-   Jane Waugh's 'The Jeep Wrangler's Doors'
 How very solid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the creative PAUL.MCCARTNEY virus hacks the spellchecker in MS Word so that all of your typos are accepted as 'poetic' variations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Tiger" after reading @derekhough's latest tweets with calm mummy-brown, energetic Spongebob-yellow and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/0ZIF84T4lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @derekhough's tweets to the equally flirtatious and upbeat Bridget Jones. https://t.co/qKpf6ClvdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sappy Mickey Mouse" after reading @bclsinclair's latest tweets with pleasant peach-orange, upbeat sunshine-yellow and sappy sap-green https://t.co/Nahi3Llt6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Bridget Jones with the best of Mickey Mouse and you get @bclsinclair: fun-loving and spunky and cheerful and upbeat https://t.co/MIZHjizJ1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Noam Chomsky" after reading @BRIANtheRobot's latest tweets with passionate flame-orange, socially-conscious Democrat-blue and arrogant buffoon-buff-orange https://t.co/G4tRpfrncd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this sophisticated book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Ernest Cline's 'Ready Player One'
-   Khaled Bellow's 'The First World'
 How very sophisticated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a shoe shop in which
Michelle Obama can enjoy @BRIANtheRobot's socially-conscious and fashionable tweets
while promoting feminism https://t.co/A3QZhxlZsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Short-tempered Carl Bernstein" after reading @RichardDawkins's latest tweets with curious Bart Simpson-yellow, media-savvy Netflix-red and tenacious warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/8whpR19tkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE ruthless humans who remind him of Donald Rumsfeld. So Hulk SMASH @RichardDawkins's action-oriented, clever and cunning tweets! https://t.co/6N9qqp6zA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious Ned Flanders" after reading @joejonas's latest tweets with decent priest-black, pious angel-white and environmentally-conscious Poison Ivy-green https://t.co/SwYeEpAK9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @joejonas's pretentious and attention-grabbing tweets were edible they'd be Coconut cake made with dandruff instead of shredded coconut https://t.co/wlvUXzPID1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-intelligent Joseph McCarthy" after reading @GarethCliff's latest tweets with crusading knight-silver, tenacious warrior-woad-blue and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/UXtvh6f79p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This motivating new book about Twitterbots makes Randy Pausch's 'The Last Lecture' seem as motivating as a slap in the face with a frozen flounder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a Chinese restaurant in which
Donald Duck can enjoy @GarethCliff's short-tempered but tenacious tweets
while eating Peking duck https://t.co/Lg9hp4nRBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Inspirational Troy McClure" after reading @BSchweinsteiger's latest tweets with media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow, affable Clooney-grey and inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/3ATDrolVJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the worst of Sherlock Holmes and you get @BSchweinsteiger: witty and detail-oriented yet cold and high-handed https://t.co/ZdhkOzqMMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@DynamiteTom's influential but pretentious tweets suggest infection with the CR1T1CZ virus https://t.co/qsiDEQAGWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Diplomat" after reading @joerogan's latest tweets with articulate Obama-brown, sophisticated robot-silver-grey and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/XjVQ9FCXUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-hearted John Belushi" after reading @KapilSharmaK9's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-tandoori-red, energetic Pacman-yellow and good-hearted Gandalf-grey https://t.co/eYcrFNF3Mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This titillating new book about computational creativity makes E.L. James's 'Fifty Shades Freed' seem as titillating as a tapeworm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a chat show set on which
Ali G can enjoy @KapilSharmaK9's entertaining and witty tweets
while interviewing politicians https://t.co/otwI4z4Rh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Avuncular Jim Carrey" after reading @Target's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-curry-brown, attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue and avuncular Santa-red https://t.co/c49ia5hhtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @Target:
1. Obi-wan Kenobi
2. Tweety Pie
3. Shirley Temple
4. Diplomats
5. Kylie Minogue https://t.co/8OX6Y7csWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Ron Burgundy" after reading @LifeHacksInPics's latest tweets with confident lion-orange, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/hd5QvWCuCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a country house in which
Miss Jane Marple can enjoy @LifeHacksInPics's judgmental but sharp-witted tweets
while solving mysteries https://t.co/59oa2BvC1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Kind-hearted Rudy Giuliani" after reading @CP3's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue and self-aggrandizing Trump-orange https://t.co/J6qEEn0h68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@CP3's mysticism-peddling but kind-hearted tweets suggest infection with the DAPHNE.M00N virus https://t.co/8HylBbLKEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This popular new book about bots makes Ian Fleming's 'Diamonds Are Forever' seem as popular as the idea of raising taxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the kind-hearted DAPHNE.M00N virus emails your co-workers to say 'I've got your back (and a knife too)']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Shrewd Fred Flintstone" after reading @AppStore's latest tweets with quick-tempered Trump-orange, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and jolly Santa-red https://t.co/FYwNXCxZAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump hates Karl Rove because his black Jaguar S-Type was made in Mexico and his tweets are as devious and shrewd as @AppStore's https://t.co/b1ftjiVBFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Joey Tribbiani" after reading @OldSpice's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, loyal Eeyore-grey and social-climbing Lewinsky-blue https://t.co/NTe9W7qFY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Yoda with the best of Walt Disney and you get @OldSpice: powerful and inspiring and shrewd and entertaining https://t.co/zVugulaiNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Bernard Madoff" after reading @justdemi's latest tweets with cunning cat-black, charming Adonis-tan-orange and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/SNXDant6cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Environmentally-conscious John McCain" after reading @Lord_Voldemort7's latest tweets with quick-tempered Trump-orange, passionate flame-red and environmentally-conscious Poison Ivy-green https://t.co/NEbS7VB6Jh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @Lord_Voldemort7's sensationalist and self-promoting tweets is like one long lecture on making modern art from Jeff Koons https://t.co/6eoYwr5mDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sociable new book about bots makes Virginia Woolf's 'Mrs. Dalloway' seem as sociable as an ulcerated molar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Engineer" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with methodical Vulcan-blood, educated priest-black and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/7COY70M2qA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Natasha Romanova" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with intelligent Columbo-beige, confident Anchorman-burgundy-red and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/L7L6D6VCsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@BotOnBotAction's fashionable and stylish tweets suggest infection with the 50NNY.CR0CKETT virus https://t.co/qA3FvSRX0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the stylish 50NNY.CR0CKETT virus uses your credit card and eBay account to place large bids for vintage clothes and second-hand shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #DiagnoseMyTweets to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Plugged In Melania Trump" after reading @CodySimpson's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Kate Moss-green and distant sun-orange https://t.co/gFIaoZN8qU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Michelle Obama with the best of Rupert Murdoch and you get @CodySimpson: fashionable and consciousness-raising and influential and media-savvy https://t.co/Lb5Cc7iwjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Observant Del Boy Trotter" after reading @Kokaneofficial's latest tweets with lively fox-red, confident Anchorman-burgundy-red and observant Columbo-beige https://t.co/u86fooBk7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this pleasing book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Elizabeth Gilbert's 'Eat Pray Love'
-   Tom Collins's 'The Good Calf Massage'
 How very pleasing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @Kokaneofficial's whimsical and powerful tweets it pushes Albus Dumbledore's book Teaching The Next Generation https://t.co/zK9ewMR9MO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-promoting Sherlock Holmes" after reading @billclinton's latest tweets with observant Columbo-beige, insightful Hawking-blackhole-black and arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/ftsa7IAIOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE subversive humans who remind him of Marcel Duchamp. So Hulk SMASH @billclinton's creative, artistic and revolutionary tweets! https://t.co/Xmhguwm0Om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Long-winded Miss Jane Marple" after reading @David_Cameron's latest tweets with observant Eeyore-grey, sharp-witted Blackadder-black and judgmental Santa-red https://t.co/aS6bie8dga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @justdemi's cold but inspiring tweets remind it of Eddard Stark https://t.co/ESyHKVA6Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Martin Luther King" after reading @NeYoCompound's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/eBcXgbmhXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE prolific humans who remind him of masters. So Hulk SMASH @NeYoCompound's arrogant, dominant and confident tweets! https://t.co/sa1TeXjVO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Carl Bernstein" after reading @rickmercer's latest tweets with curious cat-black, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and judgmental Trump-orange https://t.co/bAcs7uATi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @rickmercer's self-promoting and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Apple crumble made with frog spawn instead of sugar https://t.co/6k0tJwBrCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Eliza Doolittle" after reading @Riteishd's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, determined warrior-woad-blue and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/rUpFJjymBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This happy new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Elizabeth Gilbert's 'Eat Pray Love' seem as happy as a farmer during a drought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @Riteishd's inspirational and motivational tweets is like one long lecture on coining sparkling witticisms from Winston Churchill https://t.co/b8AY7qhzHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hyper-logical George W. Bush" after reading @katespadeny's latest tweets with cheery hummingbird-blue, affable Barney-purple and hyper-logical Terminator-silver https://t.co/p7LGsz2vpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @katespadeny:
1. Lovers
2. Evangelists
3. Thrillers
4. Alexander the Great
5. Sauron https://t.co/hCb0iFs0Nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @FethiMansouri &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/vxu3QZ6VHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Saga Norén" after reading @chrisbrown's latest tweets with stiff Golem-brown, unsympathetic robot-silver-grey and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/Brog7VrmJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a board room in which
Barney Stinson can enjoy @chrisbrown's enthusiastic but attention-seeking tweets
while promoting capitalism https://t.co/u0nXmqj22k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Ingenious Jeff "Comic Book Guy" Albertson" after reading @carellquotes's latest tweets with pretentious Anchorman-burgundy-red, intelligent Google-yellow and ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red https://t.co/HqvL0UtEfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@carellquotes's clever and accomplished tweets suggest infection with the 1NN0VAT0RZ virus https://t.co/gmOYJZzcKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This inviting new book about bots makes Armistead Maupin's 'Tales Of The City' seem as inviting as a lead lined coffin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the smart 1NN0VAT0RZ virus downloads the entire contents of Wikipedia to your hard disk; deletes all personal data to make room]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise Russell Brand" after reading @Microsoft's latest tweets with witty Dante-inferno-red, quick-witted Blackadder-black and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/6xXJ9uRjkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA is watching. It reads your tweets!
It files @Microsoft's funny and entertaining tweets under Barbra Streisand fans https://t.co/BoHENspnzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Sonny Crockett" after reading @ValeYellow46's latest tweets with cool cucumber-green, stylish tuxedo-black and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/AYU5fwsyVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Madonna with the best of Obi-wan Kenobi and you get @ValeYellow46: serene and attention-grabbing and powerful and calm https://t.co/lqOG9hlKy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Cocky Dame Edna Everage" after reading @RachelBerryGLEE's latest tweets with insightful Hawking-blackhole-black, sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/zvPUEKVf5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This interesting new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Steven Pinker's 'The Language Instinct: How the Mind Creates Language' seem as interesting as a story about a guy watching paint dry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an internet café in which
Julian Assange can enjoy @RachelBerryGLEE's socially-conscious and devious tweets
while leaking classified documents https://t.co/Hu3ndITftH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Over-the-top Rooster" after reading @ActuallyNPH's latest tweets with arrogant Oxford-blue, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and over-the-top Bollywood-tandoori-red https://t.co/OsvnEiL13Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE zealous humans who remind him of preachers. So Hulk SMASH @ActuallyNPH's sincere, passionate and inspiring tweets! https://t.co/Z4rjO0PpP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @David_Cameron's smug and probing tweets were edible they'd be Molten chocolate cake made with road grit instead of flour https://t.co/5MKW0jKI5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This articulate new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Thomas Pynchon's 'Inherent Vice' seem as articulate as a brick wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @louteasdale: observant and detail-oriented and clever and insightful https://t.co/s7YTsPL1gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Curious Noam Chomsky" after reading @McInTweet's latest tweets with holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white, arrogant prince-purple and curious Bart Simpson-yellow https://t.co/Qxkbx6SwFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This witty new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Flann O'Brien's 'At Swim Two Birds' seem as witty as a bumper sticker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @McInTweet's arrogant and condescending tweets it pushes Mr. Darcy's book Looking For Love https://t.co/LXYoUjJ4pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Mickey Mouse" after reading @angelcandice's latest tweets with upbeat Gumby-green, pleasant candy-pink and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/jIxFfw2nKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE attention-seeking humans who remind him of Madonna. So Hulk SMASH @angelcandice's influential and attention-grabbing tweets! https://t.co/1k2Uk3t5q3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Trend-setting Blackadder" after reading @Nigel_Farage's latest tweets with intelligent Columbo-beige, sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/NoMZczfWcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Nigel_Farage's sly and messianic tweets were edible they'd be Gugelhupf cake made with talcum powder instead of flour https://t.co/V0ms7sIucr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Generous Maximus Decimus Meridius" after reading @WayneRooney's latest tweets with tactical Coriolanus Snow-white, honorable prince-purple and stoic warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/RpPxYGGIjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This substantive new book about bots makes Edward Gibbon's 'The History of the Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire' seem as substantive as a sandwich prepared by Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @WayneRooney's sophisticated and smart tweets is like one long lecture on organizing armed robberies from Hans Gruber https://t.co/rZX1TkCsG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Karl Rove" after reading @Charmin's latest tweets with cunning fox-red, devious Gollum-grey and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/RaH2CUyG11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @Charmin:
1. Philosophers
2. Lovers
3. Wives
4. Steve Jobs
5. Poems https://t.co/zv8ybt4Hfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-aggrandizing Alexander Fleming" after reading @InYourFaceNYer's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, observant Eeyore-grey and curious cat-black https://t.co/PDtmKFPfA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump hates Silvio Berlusconi because his Audi A8 was made in Canada and his tweets are as media-savvy but swaggering as @InYourFaceNYer's https://t.co/OtmcyCR4Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Noam Chomsky" after reading @Ludacris's latest tweets with holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white, arrogant Trump-orange and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/s1XPKMZxTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pleasant Sonny Crockett" after reading @agnezmo's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Kate Moss-green and pleasant peach-orange https://t.co/7XRXP1tiIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @agnezmo's attention-grabbing and attention-seeking tweets were edible they'd be Mille feuille vanilla cake made with deep-fried duvet instead of puff pastry https://t.co/RqKNPJh7ph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this racy book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   E.L. James's 'Fifty Shades Of Grey'
-   Fyodor Gladwell's 'The Swimsuit Issue Of Sports Illustrated'
 How very racy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Dalton Trumbo" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red, observant Eeyore-grey and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/o2Vvo7Zfss]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>