<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/B6Jl1yh3kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/0jHAzkXmPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/8gnRdIl6Sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/D2M5ARhqvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/1JKdPqL1jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/QX7n4m6CEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/uThgHQdmeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/0jTr7qubcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/AuYWibcneT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/LpEesLn4am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/mruF88Wz9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/sn4wOXjL0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/ZVNEY9hh9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/pnxnYxyim7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/pVQQ5gWECd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/kOrpotZTid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/q1dwisOOeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/qOvV2tOm3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/RhDWKH7FGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Brahma Beer  http://t.co/crLy6Soeoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/PB8T7cZVdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/PPKaEqiGfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/L4hAOelmJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/OvCSJ4s4CC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/5b07tpvDG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/TdqBHXegTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/A3SD4ArskU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/ifVWb8aToC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/255skaNTTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All My Friends Are Dead - Kids Book - Darkly Hilarious!  http://t.co/WOtSPMcAZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/mLMC7lfX5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/CUKHqVyQJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/q1Jq4dWD9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/OkxEDZoyfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/rjtDb29emL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/sqxn6memBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/U4STvcvSuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/LAorJ9WrgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/f9jy0ZddT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/WU5IHpfFKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/lSwp4Abo3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/jvPQDsDUMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/MP8xN3sIvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/f9ioelbPwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/gV9k1QzaWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/NnaUxy8S6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has been good to me since I quit trying to play it. - Whitey Herzog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/nQqq0WmRPI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>