<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/F1NAqX9tpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/lLrxeK8rqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All My Friends Are Dead - Kids Book - Darkly Hilarious!  http://t.co/smFb1JiJzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/oCILm0ka7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Minecraft Lord of the Rings Mod - http://t.co/rK78igNj38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/Ex8TYnMg89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/TRqp4TsgYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/63SbTZQZXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/sm69AXFhZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/kB0QvtemWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/9nipHIdif8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/wJhoJ44sb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/MD5VKxqCrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/3Yr92opB9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/MgYHNMMrfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell that you're in trouble when you feel the air on the back of your neck instead of in your face. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/kROx5yOFux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/ElpLU1eom1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/wmm8m0Pm2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/aSegZFQ1T8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/VmonH1fYYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/ohklEmFYTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/z45NoXUY8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/vxBcMtHsHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/OReD0x2sm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/hcRSqEKOFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/9qn0UR26ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/BzKGNH8V0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/7MUMlTbUOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/HFuNbH2zdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/LDmoiZVhqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/ONH2854doK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/llsmNw0C48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/Fz6ArVR6Jz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/5xFhYONDtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/degYNuB4zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/pWj5kzgQ1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/aDU0VAuOvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/cnh4Wrkmpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/ovfAztOUoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to being a good manager is keeping the people who hate me away from those who are still undecided. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/ZJy7SirQFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/dGQJ5hW8LF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/QhzLwRXeqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/3Yr92opB9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Soccer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/twTQ7imMwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/gQZhsZze0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chordettes  http://t.co/ftsBs3CGZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/pJ1xowR6jH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/wF4kgvAsC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape! - George Taylor - Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/QyzoFLdKMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/EWLqlAo5mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/mkvbtX5CfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is Known as The Kings Sport  - find out why... http://t.co/HpBZF6KawM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/ELZtPyx61Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine is God's way of saying you're making too much money. - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/81eRldYImC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>