<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Company Summary =============== First American Financial Corporation (NYSE: FAF) operates through its family of companies to help people achieve and protect their dream of homeownership. First American was named one of FORTUNE’s… https://t.co/zJs7UkTdVj https://t.co/GyCr9sRCEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing / Quality Assurance Analyst – II: Job TitleTesting / Quality Assurance Analyst – II – ID:31734 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsRF TEST, BOT test LocationSouthlake, TX Date Posted05/15/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global… https://t.co/4PunyzPWR9 https://t.co/eqRXXiWgql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology. Cadence Design Systems is looking for a highly motivated software engineer to work as a member of the R &amp; D staff on… https://t.co/Lg8IqkktjO https://t.co/svE753PAYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-27449 Location: Irving, Texas Position Title : Scrum Master Location : Irving, TX Duration : Full Time Permanent Roles &amp; Responsibilities Knowledge of agile methodology and frameworks Managing the scrum process with… https://t.co/7fMMuYAf1j https://t.co/q1AQ3uAlOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Telecom Engineer: Career Opportunities |Sr. Telecom Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/J1SDt193cO https://t.co/CmtNBxwsii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Engineering) – I: Job Description Project Manager (Engineering) – IAmarillo, TX Posted: 4/18/2018 Category: T &amp; D Job Type: – Minimum Experience: 5 years + Required Education: Bachelor (BA, BS…) Branch: Staffing Solutions Group Job… https://t.co/sO6xDKJkzp https://t.co/wBQDnc0bvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GLOBAL MARKETING PROJECT MANAGER: Job Description Responsible for building efficiencies and processes for the global marketing team. Supports production for both national projects as well as regional collaboration groups. Responsible for proactive… https://t.co/2hxLTeZgWe https://t.co/jTKq0dESBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Unix Systems and Cloud Engineer: Lead Unix Systems and Cloud Engineer The Systems Administrator Lead will be responsible for documentation, deployment and troubleshooting of the complete IT Unix environment including, but not limited to: Red Hat… https://t.co/yPQB2fKjny https://t.co/CNxJtV3oeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented JavaScript Developer Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. JavaScript Developers are engaged in all phases of the software development lifecycle which include; gathering and analyzing… https://t.co/BRsErW97iM https://t.co/q9yngusfdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prolog c developer: Prolog c developer dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 06/21/18, Posted Date – 06/21/18 Primary SkillsUNIX,C,prologTax TermsC2COverview Role: PROLOG, C, UNIX with Fares Experience Location Dallas, TX Position Type:-… https://t.co/Zl0vE6viJr https://t.co/gzCyzHqx4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Network Engineer: Information Technology Job: Lead Network Engineer at Altice in Plano, TX | Altice Careers SHARE THIS Welcome to Altice USA Careers Search Opportunities SEARCH 5 Miles10 Miles25 Miles50 Miles100 Miles GO JOB DIVISION Search Jobs by… https://t.co/oMI8dEIDJ7 https://t.co/W5BZ2JsSaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: AS400 Developer Ref No.: 18-27658 Location: Dallas, Texas Role AS400 Sr Developer Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills – Candidate should have good hands on in AS400 System. – Should have good knowledge of RPGLE/CL 400/SYNON. – PBM or… https://t.co/JxtDh8YxMq https://t.co/9bHJBr7hjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Delivery/EnerGov: Software Engineer, Delivery/EnerGov =================================== Engineers build, design and write scalable code to enhance the product or resolve issues within the product. Expectations for this professional… https://t.co/hSlW0RvPRX https://t.co/tfnalocRjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer in Coppell, TX at Brink’s – Careers Home – About Brink’s – Veterans – – Featured Careers – Driver-Messenger – Cash Logistics Processors – Corporate – All Jobs – Join Our Talent Network SEARCH OUR JOBS Keyword:… https://t.co/UtrrSoxhog https://t.co/4XmrhNzjbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of Verizon’s bleeding-edge Networks and Platforms. With your… https://t.co/IxnTxb0xra https://t.co/lRmGhUzfIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer/Developer, IT Applications: Associate Developer/Developer, IT Applications View Profile – Join Our Talent Community – Featured Jobs – Jobs at the Airport – Professional – Technical Operations &amp; Maintenance – Customer Service – Pilots… https://t.co/Wr77uuLqYx https://t.co/LcQoRPPhBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Technical Project Manager: Contract Technical Project Manager – Job ID #: 13923 – Job Category: Project Management – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Technology Services Group – Department: Technology Services – Operations… https://t.co/25Fa3P6Veu https://t.co/cwjqcvBjG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Basis Lead: SAP Basis Lead Ref No.: 18-30572 Location: Plano, Texas – Responsible for Connectivity, Administration and availability of global SAP system landscape. – Expert in solution manager to work on different SAP modules. – SAP BASIS… https://t.co/9fvHn9Made https://t.co/w1ChWzRO9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager/Business Analyst: Our well-known client in Austin, TX, is in need of a motivated Project Manager/Business Analyst to join their team. This is a diverse and collaborative work environment; they are looking for a creative individual with… https://t.co/BTlYx30z6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Software Developer Mid level for our San Antonio, TX (Vista Corporate Center) or Plano, TX facility Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software… https://t.co/QILIXjx0Oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIM Data Integrity Specialist I 1pm-9:30pm: HIM Data Integrity Specialist I 1pm-9:30pm Location: Texas Health Resources System Services Job ID: ****** Department: HIS Data Integrity Area of Interest: Health Information Management Job Type: Full Time… https://t.co/nkUb23lGYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment Process –… https://t.co/vAGwi7xhaL https://t.co/c4SXNxNNya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer: 18-02164 Ref No.: 18-02164 Location: Richardson, Texas Akraya is looking for a Network Engineer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Viplove Singh at… https://t.co/DKceofcNgg https://t.co/mdEI2fSCoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Job Description PSI Title: System Administrator Work Location: TX – San Antonio Description Essential Functions and Job Responsibilities: System Administration responsibilities involve account monitoring; installing security patches… https://t.co/J4kuVxY0ai https://t.co/OrNV08Kb38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Technical Support Engineer (Cloud Identity): Job ID #: 13543 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Administration – Department: Information Technology – Primary Country: USA – Primary… https://t.co/3pR1Crwndt https://t.co/G1MuvcoB7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Analyst – Downtown Dallas: IN AN EFFORT TO PROVIDE A MORE HEALTHY, SAFE AND SATISFYING ENVIRONMENT TO OUR EMPLOYEES, INDIVIDUALS TO WHOM JOB OFFERS ARE EXTENDED MAY UNDERGO NICOTINE TESTING AS A PART OF THE PRE-EMPLOYMENT PROCESS. Senior… https://t.co/FXFB7CVPBA https://t.co/HVTJgqnctX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DATA ANALYST: Data Analyst at Under Armour, Inc. Skip Navigation Under Armour Careers Menu – Life At UALife At UA – Overview – Mission &amp; Values – Benefits – Culture – Talent AreasTalent Areas – Overview – Corporate – Retail – Distribution – Technology –… https://t.co/37d3ASSDtV https://t.co/ZQt0jH9FYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Retail Systems Business Analyst: Job Description The Senior Retail Systems Business Analyst will work within a growing and highly visible retail systems portfolio, which is undergoing transformational change. The position will be responsible for… https://t.co/EQhjuKfuiw https://t.co/ykIJ928Hjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist, Hosting Operations: IT Specialist, Hosting Operations ================================= Tyler Technologies has an IT Specialist opening on our hosting operations team in Plano, TX. The IT Specialist position provides Tier I system… https://t.co/t5rVml6A25 https://t.co/nrZvWJmRFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack .NET Developer: SENIOR FULL STACK .NET DEVELOPER HIGHLIGHTS LOCATION: Plano, TX POSITION TYPE: 6 month Contract to Hire HOURLY/SALARY: BOE! JOB SUMMARY GTN Technical Staffing is currently seeking Senior Software Engineer for a 6 month… https://t.co/h3qxrdinNn https://t.co/3flQO0fNXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer IV: Application Developer IV Frisco, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 07/16/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Greetings from Saxon Global Inc. We have an Immediate need for a talented **********… https://t.co/3H0ncjZoD5 https://t.co/Yf9TyUWMZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail Systems Business Analyst: Job Description The Retail Systems Business Analyst will work within a growing and highly visible retail systems portfolio, which is undergoing transformational change. The position will be responsible for driving and… https://t.co/TwvVGtP0Vm https://t.co/3y1b9oMcpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court: Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court =================================================== This role provides basic-level software support for Tyler clients in the use, functionality, and… https://t.co/lOufEj7Vhw https://t.co/LLTNKgG3N6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Design Intermediate Engineer: UX/UI Design Intermediate Engineer Job at Citi Skip Navigation – ************* – Alumni – Language – English – Espaol – Francais du Canada – Portugus – Polski – – – – Magyar – open main navigation menu – Search &amp; –… https://t.co/QjQOZVK7hQ https://t.co/Oiz23B4mAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Engineer: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Entry Level Software Engineer java, IT | Dallas, TX | Full Time Job Description We are seeking qualified applicants for the position… https://t.co/cjTiKfc7Qa https://t.co/xa5uFYozuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Tester: Job TitleQA Tester – ID:31999 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSCRUM LocationPlano, TX Date Posted06/22/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of us direct, referencing the job# below: Kindest Regards: SUMIT… https://t.co/vDz6ENBA9i https://t.co/p504JwzgRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer III: ETL Developer III Description at Tenet Healthcare Skip to content Navigation – About Us – Our Story – Our Business – Our Leadership – Our Heroes – Our Commitment to Compliance – Partnering with Us – Giving Back – For Patients – Our… https://t.co/xeKRDThgFJ https://t.co/2OTD0WrHhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court – Lubbock, Texas: Job Description Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court This role provides basic-level software support for Tyler clients in the use, functionality, and understanding of… https://t.co/KV7UpiGV8O https://t.co/uzJqGf1BFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finesim Developer: 16410BR Job Description and Requirements Responsible for the developement, implementation, and maintenance of Finesim SPICE and FastSPICE Circuit Simulator, as an R &amp; D. – Excellent coder in C/C++ – Strong background in algorithms and… https://t.co/dzrl24fMRf https://t.co/JeBOdMNr4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Software Engineer (Swift): Senior iOS Software Engineer (Swift) with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications –… https://t.co/PuuwStDL4g https://t.co/ueqr9Myqj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Solution Architect: Big Data Solution Architect Primary Skills Architect,Big data Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Big Data Solution Architect for location Fort Worth, TX for one of our Top clients.… https://t.co/0KTBxazdAs https://t.co/1XUraNpMdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Electrical Engr: 106989BR Sr Principal Electrical Engr TX – McKinney 106989BR The Receiver Exciter and Signal Processing (RESP) Department in the Electrical Design Directorate (EDD) at Integrated Defense Systems (IDS) is seeking an… https://t.co/So8mpeU8LL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoLang Software Engineer: Summary: Established leadership experience in large organizations comparable to CBRE Proven ability to effect organizational change. Possesses expertise across multiple architecture domains, forward- thinking, and well-versed in… https://t.co/Dz7EHplaKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer, Flight Service Web Based Training: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Flight Crew Category: Instructors &amp; Trainers Jobs Location: Integrated Operations Ctr (DFW-IOC0) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20049 Overview… https://t.co/uTsf61ys8l https://t.co/2CnJFTm1lH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Technical Lead: Job Description BAE Systems is seeking experienced and driven engineering professionals to join our rapidly expanding engineering team developing active EO/IR systems. We are looking for a Product Technical Lead (PTL) who can… https://t.co/EymIxVi8ZG https://t.co/j9Eb21NdUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer: Sr. Developer now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now Email Please wait. Date: Jun 26, 2018 Location: Company: Tesoro Companies Inc. Requisition ID: 74282 Summary: This position is responsible for enhancing and… https://t.co/uafDSFSGSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAFF RELIABILITY ENGINEER (CLOUD/DEVOPS): POSITION PURPOSE If you are passionate about large scale, mission critical software systems, and you have a maniacal focus on system availability and performance, Reliability Engineering is for you. As a member… https://t.co/TUOIX3hTOp https://t.co/sEciKaBJSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Business Systems: Analyst, Business Systems Ref No.: 18-01745 Location: Dallas, Texas Start Date: 07/09/2018 Qualifications: Bachelor’s degree in business or related field and/or 5-8+ years of Peoplesoft experience. Excellent written and verbal… https://t.co/uEknjgbAc1 https://t.co/StlBMBlDQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Integrator I: Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Software Development &amp; Integrator I for our Plano, TX facility. Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software development lifecycle which… https://t.co/ITNAaEoQeR https://t.co/HeMxXqVfxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Recruiter Cogent Data Solutions Llc Location Austin Austin United States Salary Competitive Posted 25 May 2018 Closes 22 Jun 2018 Job role Accountant Sector Management consultancy Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign… https://t.co/0LDCQH9s5H https://t.co/Dtb6sKYElr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Software Engineer: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing, graphics, and… https://t.co/Ub7RFXwMFM https://t.co/5wCdlWmCN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: What does it take to protect and maintain the most sensitive data for over 220 million people and 25 million businesses? What does it take to meet daunting challenges and shape solutions that pioneer industries and improve lives? At… https://t.co/oMo7TttIOS https://t.co/JBZykEjP2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Engineering: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a composite of diverse… https://t.co/gSYEDoDQRl https://t.co/zInVtYsHI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaming Software Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Antonio, TX Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/YmA8llGluR https://t.co/FbksyhmEW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering, construction,… https://t.co/iwZpa6AMk9 https://t.co/jv1y3EuqG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Spring Developer: Req ID: 18685 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our… https://t.co/hMzTQL6TDx https://t.co/UX4D6tWK41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist IV: Job ID 12628 Date posted 06/13/2018 Location Irving TX – US Job Description Aviall, a Boeing Company is the world’s largest provider of new aviation parts and related aftermarket services. Aviall markets and distributes products for… https://t.co/dEYH2Zpjmo https://t.co/wHYISCwNVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High Tech –… https://t.co/JhtxkJOXUx https://t.co/gJz9dVM8xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager Power Plant Decommissioning: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a national engineering, consulting and construction management firm providing integrated services to the power,… https://t.co/Tarm3Gzj6x https://t.co/5Mydsks4O9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecommunications Systems Integrator/Designer San Antonio, TX: About this Job Excellent Opportunity for a non-degreed motivated and highly skilled technical individual to work under senior leadership to develop and implement technical telecommunication… https://t.co/xvUzf4Qf1e https://t.co/U15rkwSJz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Application Security Engineer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate… https://t.co/Sjx40Dwq4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Technical Support Analyst: This is an excellent opportunity with a rapidly growing organization listed on the NYSE with offices in 22 states. You will provide Technical Support in resolving company computing device needs, issues and requests in a… https://t.co/JaWPUv9JIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Analyst: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business unit is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering, construction,… https://t.co/NVfgPQZLjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Integrator Senior: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking a talented Software Developer &amp; Integrator Senior for our Plano, TX facility. Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the software development… https://t.co/rEHnHwwCNJ https://t.co/ShozSR212o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Enterprise Data Warehouse and BI Solution Architect: Job Description Whole Foods Market is looking for passionate and experienced technologists who fully appreciate the meaning behind, with great power comes great responsibility. Someone with a… https://t.co/QtwHxb11wK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Compliance Manager: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing, graphics, and… https://t.co/9uu7TdPZ2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Online Services: Software Developer, Online Services =================================== Have you ever thought about working with an amazing organization, surrounded by amazing, scary smart, people and making the world a better place?… https://t.co/TZ4MdtKUJn https://t.co/bWJkHwqtSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer III (Service Parts Management): Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Senior Manager Jobs Aviall, A Boeing Company is the world’s largest provider of new aviation parts and related aftermarket… https://t.co/LF2DjFrcZm https://t.co/bqF2yjTVb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/IT Technical Project Manager — Senior Level: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking a talented IT Scrum Master/Technical Project Manager Senior Level for our San Antonio, TX facility. Participates in the planning, execution and delivery of… https://t.co/8Df65XgXLX https://t.co/opH2Aq7S8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst/Senior Analyst, Decision Support Systems: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Analyst Jobs Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 19941 Overview Join us for a career with… https://t.co/P9lzotoxl1 https://t.co/EWIqzbMzdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Ruby on Rails Developer: Senior Ruby on Rails Developer, Full Stack Developer for a Dallas, Texas based technology company that seeks a very talented Ruby on Rails Developer to help lead, build, and enhance a rapidly growing company. Qualified… https://t.co/HHzsjNI8wY https://t.co/mnsTlg6n0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Developer: Solution Developer Date: Jun 10, 2018 Location: Dallas, TX, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Now EmailStart Please wait. New York Life Insurance Company (New York Life or… https://t.co/NePVsbeEaB https://t.co/sZSnvNM9HW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection, visualization and… https://t.co/bGVVwOHsEy https://t.co/xfHxTulvd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Applications Testing Manager: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Customer Experience Testing and Certification (CETC) team is looking for a highly energetic, motivated and talented people manager having experience on web, mobile… https://t.co/3KXWFlpdKF https://t.co/1qW92J5Roz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Engineer: Job Information: IT Infrastructure Engineer Job Email Opening Title IT Infrastructure Engineer EOE StatementWe are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment… https://t.co/ebw2NAPR2j https://t.co/nQPmJyMVtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Systems Administrator III: Job ID 12784 Date posted 06/12/2018 Location Irving TX – US Job Description Aviall is a world leading solutions provider in new aviation parts and aftermarket supply-chain management services for the aerospace and defense… https://t.co/QGiNaCKGHl https://t.co/nmpaI64WwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: * [IMAGE] * * Applicant Login * About TI * Company * Careers * Investor relations * Citizenship * University * Public policy * Careers * Our company * Why TI * Career paths * Search jobs ? Completed page Completed page Completed page… https://t.co/aAbkYoJWls https://t.co/UwgejhdBKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer / Architect: UX Designer / Architect Ref No.:18-14041 Location: Dallas, Texas Title :: UX Designer / Architect Location :: Dallas, TX Client :: Banking Industry Primarily Responsibilities : – Work on projects that solve a variety of problems… https://t.co/YgRbNx4YHg https://t.co/rt16753BJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX UI Designer and Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The Financial Systems Group (FSG) has an opening for a Business Analyst responsible for strategy and implementation of systems solutions that support Verizon’s revenue recognition… https://t.co/5sCpCJIOql https://t.co/lwShzZVgmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinical SAS Programmer US: We envision a Luminex solution in every lab around the world seeking to obtain timely and confident answers. We aim to lead with transformative solutions that uniquely accelerate reliable answers while reducing the overall… https://t.co/MaUm3aDLo1 https://t.co/PUB0TzaLhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Multifamily/Wood Frame: Houston, TX Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing – Answering to a Senior Project Manager – 5-10 years’ experience (APM or new PM)… https://t.co/E6P3JHFpOE https://t.co/RgnvQ6WNfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst- IT: Job Summary: Strike, LLC is seeking a Business Analyst to join the Business Applications Team. This position is responsible for providing companywide strategic, analytical, and technical support for business applications including… https://t.co/S7IUSKpp9r https://t.co/mcPsfp83lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Intern: Location: Texas, United States Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Software Engineer Looking for a job where a passion for innovation, a culture of teamwork, and opportunities for growth are valued and rewarded?… https://t.co/vdLLgaWKcJ https://t.co/hbw3BJ9FN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux-System-Administrator-w–Hadoop: Carries out moderately complex information systems and/or information technology tasks within more than one discipline, such as application support, database administration, software quality assurance/quality control,… https://t.co/TB0SA6EaJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Linux/Virtualization: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing,… https://t.co/xVa3CVBT6C https://t.co/YmvsAg9A02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers] Careers Main… https://t.co/YnqmkWJlxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Support Analyst: The company where you can make an impact and bring value. Job Summary: TOPAZ Technologies, a Cultura Technologies company, is an established leader in the development and support of software solutions for the biomedical research… https://t.co/YA6n3yz7Qo https://t.co/x0Kn7fTGuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Business/Support Analyst – Sales/Order Management/Pricing: ERP BUSINESS/SUPPORT ANALYST – SALES/ORDER MANAGEMENT/PRICING LOCATION: Irving, TX INDUSTRY: Steel Manufacturing TRAVEL: Up to 50% – This travel is not a consistent, routine 25% travel. The… https://t.co/FRmwjaQWWe https://t.co/F9ihhVyu8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: IT Trading Business Analyst =========================== Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start apply with Seek… https://t.co/ixUc8LiThb https://t.co/g6Rkxiu9DF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst Manager: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Your role is to deliver value to Verizon and its customers through business intelligence reporting and analytics. You will be part of the Workforce Planning and Analysis team to drive strategic… https://t.co/mr8pfOneVO https://t.co/9wFzh8AMec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: SR Number HCL/HCL/2018/****** Designation Data Analyst Location Texas Job Family Delivery Domain Job Description (Posting). Responsible for indirect purchasing activities, Open POs expediting and Material Return to vendor etc (1.) The… https://t.co/mT62Vq1clC https://t.co/2ihBnESyCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Microservices Engineer: CBRE is the global leader in commercial real estate services, has been ranked the industry’s top brand by the Lipsey Company for 15 consecutive years, and has been named one of Fortune’s Most Admired Companies in… https://t.co/d5PRsuYLug https://t.co/zdu8IWHHgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Service Analyst: Field Service Analyst (Senior/Lead) – DCGS-A Mobile Ref No.:18-00106 Category: ************* Location: Fort Hood, Texas Position Type:Full-time Experience Level: 3 Years Start Date: 04/23/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift… https://t.co/wB9aEwBQzK https://t.co/U1sah89J7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Oil Field Technical Lead: Digital Oil Field Technical Lead ================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start… https://t.co/dTByEBnMkW https://t.co/pRJ5BiUxWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect GES: Application Architect – GES in Dallas, Texas, United States | Information Technology at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students –… https://t.co/XNOyNq54h5 https://t.co/4xr0xOo2V6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member of Technical Staff Product Development Engineering: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in… https://t.co/MWNN5CcMDI https://t.co/05zvdd1uhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise and Fall of Uber HR Chief Liane Hornsey: Her departure is a sign the company’s system is beginning to work. It’s also a crisis. https://t.co/Ey2MIjMPR7 https://t.co/DOimX9JBMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tools Programmer: ZeniMax Careers – Tools Programmer – id Software ZeniMax Jobs – ZENIMAX MEDIA – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS ROCKVILLE, MARYLAND – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS MONTREAL, CANADA – BETHESDA GAME STUDIOS AUSTIN, TEXAS – ID SOFTWARE DALLAS, TEXAS – ID… https://t.co/1EOVmaSqCg https://t.co/GMS0SdcAvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA DEVELOPER: JAVA DEVELOPER at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare – High Tech – Industrials and Energy –… https://t.co/wPGCjAzVl2 https://t.co/FoyEI1FVRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integrator/ System Administrator- TS/SCI Required: System Integrator/ System Administrator- TS/SCI Required in Austin, TX | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | –… https://t.co/33EZ4gvTPl https://t.co/iTqwqchveP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>