<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleMsCant @good Good to know!  'Cause I'm completely untrustworthy clean-shaven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshepstein1 @jessierelephant @stratfest Yay!  Excited!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver Okay.  What about this Monday or Tuesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver What's your schedule like on Tuesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take that, fungal dermatitis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Harry Potter!  Oh . . . and my sister too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blizzard Friday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver @peteratpsp Thanks again for coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadiansee Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific Northwest Raptors:  awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thought that Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows:  Part 2 was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CelinaDean I miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty Thanks again for coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is excited to see Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows:  Part 2!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElliottLoran Thanks for the show.  I enjoyed myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @littlemscant It's not awful.  No worse than ketchup chips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vanderfluit Ah, I see.  Have a great time in Alberta!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RideTheCyclone Yup!  I saw it on Wednesday evening.  I enjoyed myself. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HP-3days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @littlemscant Yes, apparently ketchup popcorn salt is Kernels' most popular flavour.  Who knew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vanderfluit Bummer!  I won't judge you too harshly.  How was the Stampede though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is excited to see Ride the Cyclone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Stampede, all y'all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thought that Midnight in Paris was excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadiansee It's in the mail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thought that It's All Gone Pete Tong was very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meatbulbs and pasghetti.  Yummy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that was disappointing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[has boarded the Coastal Renaissance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thought that Bridesmaids was very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for a great mini-vacation, Alberta!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaclynnishi Well, you do to be in the cast, but not to musical direct.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is closing The Lawyer Show production of A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum this evening at 8:00 pm. One chance left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting to board the train to New York!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vanderfluit @JessieRelephant Next time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful Stratford morning.  About to head to hear friends sing at the Dragon Boat Festival, then Titus Andronicus, then back to Toronto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, forgot to mention that White Biting Dog at Soulpepper was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stratford report so far:  Camelot was excellent; Jesus Christ Superstar was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to take the train to Stratford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to the Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, Old Montreal and the Bell Centre. Now off to Diese Onze for some jazz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just landed in Toronto!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N.B.:  Today's performances are at 1:00 pm and 7:00 pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver Me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djkeng: @RyanInVancouver Enjoy! Saw #Elegies last night with Jeff. Intense show. @MikeVancouver & @greenfieldsteve & cast should be  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Just a Pipedream Equity Co-op's production of Elegies closes this evening at CBC Studio 700. Only two chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djkeng You're welcome.  Glad that you enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver No worries.  There will always be other shows.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djkeng Thanks for coming to see the show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Just a Pipedream Equity Co-op's production of Elegies plays at CBC Studio 700 until September 11. Only four chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver Thanks for the RT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Homorazzi: Musical Review: Elegies – A Song Cycle http://t.co/0EIOyNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Just a Pipedream Equity Co-op's production of Elegies plays at CBC Studio 700 until September 11. Only five chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playbill: Avenue Q, Shrek, Elegies, Hairspray, Mamma Mia!, Cabaret, Frankenstein and More Will Play Paris This Season  http://t.co/k ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AprilTheMusical: Vancouver musical theatre audiences are pretty lucky Next to Normal starts wed The Light in the Piazza, next week a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Just a Pipedream Equity Co-op's production of Elegies opens this evening at CBC Studio 700. Only six chances left to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krisjoseph Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Just a Pipedream Equity Co-op's production of Elegies previews this evening at CBC Studio 700.  Only seven chances to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feuzbowl Gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pita Pit's new logo/mascot looks like a pretty douchy pita, if you ask me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to dock in Vancouver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alannag123 I will be home on Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuietHumTheatre I know, right?  Yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3.  Sold out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only seven chances left to see it! Few tickets left!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleiades42 Yup!  By the end of Elegies, I will have spent a third of the year working with Colleen.  Who could ask for anything more?  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleiades42 Congratulations on the holdover!  Break legs!  Next up for me is a production in September of Elegies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only eight chances left to see it! Tickets are going fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleiades42 Yup!  This is the third production that Colleen and I have worked on together.  What are you up to these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourOnlyJoy Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleiades42 I sure is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only 10 chances left to see it! Tickets are going fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only 11 chances left to see it! Tickets are going fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only 13 chances left to see it! Tickets are going fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof at the Chemainus Theatre Festival until September 3. Only 15 performances left! Tickets are going fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gave correct directions to a different tourist (I must look like I know my way around).  Karma restored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate when I realise that I've accidentally given tourists incorrect directions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Well, without the glasses, I look like 'Dewey' from the Scream trilogy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Yup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant 'George Harvey' is Stanley Tucci's character in The Lovely Bones, who I look like in West Side Story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Stanley Tucci as 'George Harvey' was in West Side Story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see Amadeus this afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw 50/50.  It was excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I now blend in on Main Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see Audra McDonald in concert this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love our new grill.  It almost makes up for not being able to have a barbecue.  Almost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next to Normal was amazing.  So much fantastic theatre playing in Vancouver right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @joshepstein1 @GreenfieldSteve On Newsies?  Newsies was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see Next to Normal this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Light in the Piazza was very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteratPSP Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see The Light in the Piazza this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vanderfluit @jessierelephant Wow!  Really?  That's fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielLegend @jessierelephant Yup!  It's the perfect après-theatre listening.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord Oh, and, yes, Sleep No More was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the dentist!   :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Crucible was very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanInVancouver Thanks, buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord Will do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackgord No, I'm not doing a show with Rumble, I start rehearsals for West Side Story with the Opera today in which there is a rumble.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to join the rumble today.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>