<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running and #life are much the same. A fantastic support system of friends or family can make a big difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different people in your life for different reasons. Goodness can come from multiple sources. Take time on your runs to be #thankful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get busy living, or get busy dying" Shawshank Redemption #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It only seems impossible until it's done." ~ Nelson Mandela #run #train #dream #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does not matter how slowly you go so long as you do not stop.~Confucius #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The block of granite which was an obstacle in the pathway of the weak, became a stepping-stone in the pathway of the strong ~ Carlyle #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We acquire the #strength we have overcome. ~Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And you can #dream, so dream out loud."
U2 via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running makes me feel alive, appreciate my legs, and the friends that run with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest healing therapy is friendship and love - H. Humphrey AND #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The #heart has its reasons, which reason does not know." -Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running is a balance of physical exertion, enhanced mental awareness and spiritual peace. (via @JeffGalloway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saucony slogan: "Maybe #strong is just what you have left when you've used up all your weak."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You will never succeed beyond your wildest #dreams unless you are willing to have some wild dreams.” via @Kattemie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If everything seems under control, you're just not going #fast enough." ~ Mario Andretti via @CharityIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If U want 2 become the best #runner U can be, start now. Dont spend the rest of your life wondering if Ucan do it" Welch via @Run2SaveLives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of #life. ~Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hope is a #good thing, maybe the best thing, and no good thing ever dies” Shawshank Redemption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the midst of regular #life, running is the touchstone that breathes adventure into my soul -Kristin Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is meant to be lived. Take risks. Feel passion. Discover love. Run free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you do something positive, even if no one else knows it or sees it, you are making a difference.” via @MiraclesGoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who #dream by day are cognizant of many things which escape those who dream only by night - Edgar Allen Poe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some have natural talent, others make up for it with tremendous heart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who believe in you, encourage you & help you exceed your #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often hear someone say I’m not a real runner.We are all #runners, some just run faster than others.I never met a fake runner via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that you can't go a day without thinking about.~Unknown #life #goals #dreams #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One is hardly sensible of fatigue while he marches to music." -Thomas Carlyle, Scottish writer and historian via @zumadog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laziness is an option #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ever have that problem where the treadmill doesn't go #fast enough for ya?....... No me neither.” via @Mirindacarfrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes a run is needed with no rules, no distance planned...just your heart and the road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have to go for what we think we're fully capable of, not limit ourselves by what we've been in the past." Vivek Paul #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the #courage to follow your heart, pursue your #passions, and chase your dreams. Life is too short to do otherwise via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy to say I will start training tomorrow, next month, next year. But why wait, when you can start today #noexcuses #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what you are that holds you back, it's what you think you are not." - Denis Waitley #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find the fire in you, find what excites you, find your inner #passion AND go for it!" #run #give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run happy, Run strong, Run free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in #can. I believe in #do. I believe in #dreams. I believe in the #impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He #can who thinks he can, and he can't who thinks he can't. This is an inexorable, indisputable law. ~Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you have the enthusiasm and the #passion, you end up figuring how to excel." Deena Kastor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you want to do, do it now. There are only so many tomorrows. ~Michael Landon #life #live #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because running helps me give back to others #whywerun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run for the love of running #whywerun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing matters except life and the love you make" — Coldplay #run #love #life #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People moving all the time inside a perfectly straight line. Don't you wanna just curve away? When it's such a perfect day." Coldplay #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if you never #try, you never know, just what you're worth" — Coldplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I have learned to use the word #impossible with the greatest caution.” - Wernher von Braun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I know no matter how fast we are #running..Somehow we keep..Somehow we keep up with each other." — Dave Matthews Band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if you give, you begin to live." — Dave Matthews Band #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're going to make it, your desire for your #dreams has to be greater than your fear of failure." via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A runner must #run with dreams in his heart." - Emil Zatopek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is short, surround yourself with kind people. via @CharityIdeas #run #friends #charity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Goals are not only absolutely necessary to motivate us. They are essential to really keep us alive." -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never underestimate the miles you run, and the people you run them with. -- via @runtowin #friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take what you can from your #dreams Make them real as anything, It takes the work out of the courage" Dave Matthews Band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fast girls have better times" -- #running shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No matter how slow you are...you're still lapping everyone on the couch.” via @411Fit #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you come in first, in the middle of the pack, or last. You can say, 'I have #finished' There is a lot of satisfaction in that~Lebow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the most important single thing, beyond discipline & creativity is daring to #dare. -Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Train where your fitness is NOW, not where you want to be.”~ Scott Jurek #ultra #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When purpose steps up, doubt stands down.” via @affirmationspot #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest achievement is to outperform yourself." -Denis Waitley #running #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, what's your excuse? #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all have different paths to the start, but what is important is to start" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners, imagine their #dreams 1st. They want it with all their heart & expect it to come true. There's no other way to live ~Joe Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to run, run a mile. If you want to experience a different life, #run a #marathon. Emil Zatopek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is meant to be lived, live it! Body is meant to be used, use it! #run #truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is short, live it. Love is rare,grab it. Anger is bad, dump it. Fear is awful, face it. Memories are sweet, cherish it via @freakyfact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't wait for inspiration. You have to go after it with a club." ~Jack London #charity #run #giveback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gun goes off and everything changes... the world changes... and nothing else really matters. ~ Patti Sue Plummer #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most people would rather be certain they're miserable, than risk being happy." - Robert Anthony #change #run #happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite sign at #RnRLV  "Nut up, Princess." Really helped last miles via @CGIprguy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does 24 hours in a day control you or do you control the 24 hours in a day #getyourrunin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble is, if you don't #risk anything, you risk even more. -Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Each one of us has a fire in our #heart for something. It's our goal in #life to find it & to keep it." Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there's no way you're not crossing the finish line. It's a misery that non-runners don't understand~ Costello #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop dreaming, ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If the hill has its own name, then it’s probably a pretty tough hill.”  - Marty Stern via @TNTOntario @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything seems  #impossible, until it's done." Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running shirt on the back said... If you see me collapse, please hit 'Pause' on my garmin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The person who says it cannot be done, should not  #interrupt the person doing it." ~ Chinese proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He conquers who endures."~Persius, #endurance #coaching #training via @RickRunNRide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find the people in #life that will go the extra mile for you & run with them. This is one race you don't need 2 win" unk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference in winning & losing is most often, not quitting. -Walt Disney via @hmgiraffy @Inspire_Us #run #endurance #persevere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you aim for nothing, you'll hit it every time" -unknown via @ironmikestone #dream #do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There is an eloquence in true #enthusiasm” Edgar Allan Poe via @ironmikestone @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could not be content to take my place by the fireside and simply look on. #Life was meant to be lived -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't get fit in one workout, just as you can't live your life in one day." -Johnny G #running #quotes via @running_junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're an #ultrarunner when you don't finish on the same day as the winner.” via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To uncover your true potential you must first find your own limits and then you have to have the #courage to blow past them ~ Picabo Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you are not willing to risk the unusual, you will have to settle for the ordinary." -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There's no magic to running far or climbing Everest. Endurance is mental strength. It's all about heart.” Bear Grylls via @Running_Junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["dont quiet them. embrace them. its natural, normal &shows how much you care. when the gun goes off they will be gone!” via @chrissiesmiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people think about making it happen and others make it happen!" #DO #IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To dare is to lose one's footing momentarily. To not #dare is to lose oneself ~ Kierkegaard via @CharityIdeas @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most mistakes in a #race are made in the first two minutes, perhaps in the very first minute." - Jack Daniels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep some room in your #heart for the unimaginable." -Mary Oliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We were meant to live an extraordinary #life. Don't believe anything less. Never settle for ordinary.” via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What excites you? What makes you dream? #run #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't underestimate anyone around you. Everyone has the #power to surprise anyone at any point of time.” via @Kcancer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>