<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[One of crypto’s longest-running exchanges has been sold: One of the longest-standing crypto exchanges has new owners after Europe-based Bitstamp was sold to South Korea’s Nexon, marking the gaming firm’s second such acquisition. The acquirer is NXMH, a… https://t.co/SDrMWGTe2R https://t.co/dIQqDDs0wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: It's not a blue wave. It's a realignment of American politics: In next week's midterm elections, President Donald Trump is poised to put his stamp on each party's demographic and geographic base of support as surely as he formerly fastened it… https://t.co/oHLNsoaTKd https://t.co/hBt55vXP46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Configuration Specialist / Localize in French / Excel: French Classification Specialist / Localize in French / Metadata / EXCEL / 3 months + contract / West London The Classification specialist is in charge of running different types of research… https://t.co/TbPLMoBBUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer, Product Platform: Sr Software Engineer, Product Platform Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox… https://t.co/1zEAc63m0j https://t.co/CCufxX4S3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior IT Support Analyst: Technical Support Engineer urgently required to join an award-winning local authority based in Essex. The ideal candidate will have knowledge of Microsoft Server and/or Cisco networking skills. Recent ICT graduate or completed… https://t.co/0FawikkkyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's currency just hit its lowest level in a decade. What's next?: China's battered currency is trading at its lowest point since the global financial crisis, leaving investors asking how much farther it might fall. https://t.co/FYsyDq9rMl https://t.co/RrvLMPbtaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer 2:   Job Description – Systems Engineer 2 (18016822) Systems Engineer 2 Requisition ID : 18016822 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/chgFvNerfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior MicroStrategy (MSTR) Engineer: Senior MicroStrategy Developer – 40k – 50k AED p/m (£8,500 – £10,500 per / month) Long Term contract Dubai Skills: MicroStrategy 10x, Semantic Layer Modelling, Oracle 12c, Exadata, Google Analytics, R Analytics,… https://t.co/r4ZbLSNzxP https://t.co/QCPavvnhO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3GPP Wireless Consultant: We are working with a Global pioneer within Telecoms &amp; IT services who are looking to develop technologies at the forefront of the connected world. The role of 3GPP Wireless Consultant will seek to develop plans and strategies… https://t.co/wtd1V7O1fK https://t.co/mb2JMOG9Wt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acquisition Analyst: Req #: 213179 Location: Arlington, VA US Job Category: Consulting Security Clearance: Secret Clearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI is seeking an Acquisition Analyst to provide acquisition and contracts support to PEO… https://t.co/tKIeKakwEt https://t.co/uehgwooWaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – London: CV-Library is one of the UK's largest online job sites, with over 10 million candidates and 3.8 million unique visitors every month. With a client list crammed full of the biggest brand names in recruitment and also a healthy… https://t.co/5FBRDCSEPJ https://t.co/EY7IeGNHSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer (Server side): Senior Java Developer (Server side) at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact… https://t.co/4u1Y9yrDse https://t.co/pX4FPXIBDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBAer shows why he is one of the greatest shooters of all time https://t.co/cBSmxbL49L https://t.co/SfxvWsuwFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Developer: Careers at NforcePro – About Us – Overview – Customers – Contact Us – Products – Products Overview – Process Management – Document Management – Issue Management – Audit Management – Risk Management – Policy Management – Role Management –… https://t.co/a91SzFMDqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Performance Engineer: Requisition Number: SS-13919 Area of Interest: Information Technology Organization: Corporate Brand/Division: Shared Services Position Type: Full-time JOB DESCRIPTION About the Role Williams-Sonoma Inc. (WSI) is seeking an… https://t.co/BRAlveFz6a https://t.co/mj2lPXJNxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China allows use of tiger and rhino products, infuriating wildlife activists: The Chinese government has legalized the use of endangered tiger and rhino products for medical purposes, a move wildlife activists say will be a setback to efforts to protect… https://t.co/JsaaY5dYur https://t.co/MnooHyEDoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager – Retail &amp; Consumer:   Job Description – Business Development Manager – Retail &amp; Consumer (40275) Job Description  Business Development Manager – Retail &amp; Consumer-40275 Description   Business Development Manager – Retail &amp;… https://t.co/1bC5t7RCL6 https://t.co/XcgmVUDYjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer (1&amp;2nd line) + customer visits: Our client are a growing IT Support and Managed Services Provider, based in Bolton. We have an up-coming vacancy for a talented servicedesk professional looking to work in the SME sector. Our small… https://t.co/0JeTFW2xj3 https://t.co/J5syVrAOlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI/UX Designer: Product Designer Are you an innovative Product Designer full of fantastic ideas? Join a company that is at the forefront of its industry! Product Designer needed to join a commerce company who are revolutionising and disrupting the… https://t.co/w4PBqvmEOx https://t.co/Msmi3DHoYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Executive: SEO Executive is sought by a top ranked, highly regarded Search marketing agency based in Leeds city centre. Reporting directly to the Head of SEO this Executive will join a well-established SEO team that has recently won a string of high… https://t.co/eu3wn9xsJM https://t.co/MlKesch9ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Privacy group calls on US government to adopt universal AI guidelines to protect safety, security and civil liberties: After months of work, a set of guidelines designed to protect humanity from a range of threats posed by artificial intelligence have… https://t.co/2zSCVUGGGW https://t.co/uizsoOqnYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's history of promoting false theories: CNN's Jake Tapper explores President Donald Trump's history of promoting conspiracy theories and how social media helps to spread them. https://t.co/XRNLnoUXaB https://t.co/0rHs9Xmiom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Architect – Serverless, AWS LAMDA: AWS Architect – Serverless, AWS LAMDA London Up to £625 p/d Some travel across EMEA, therefore, candidates with travel restrictions cannot be considered. AWS, Lambda, Kubernetes, ECS, Terraform, Packer, Helm,… https://t.co/vSuyxj8jbQ https://t.co/v6kifu9M5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Scientist/Theorist: Req ID 97574BR Business Title Artificial Intelligence Scientist/Theorist Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Quantico Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Scientific / Analytical Job Duties and Responsibilities… https://t.co/OkkevCoq37 https://t.co/q8ne2znkSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FrontEnd Developer: Frontend Developer A Frontend Developer with strong technical skills in JavaScript and AngularJS is required for an exciting role with our client based near Telford, Shropshire. A salary up to £35,000 basic is available. The… https://t.co/07v8xn75nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR: Job #: SC13400 SENIOR SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR Location: Houston, TX 77077 (Energy corridor/Westchase area) QUALIFICATIONS: Education, Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities: 8+ years of experience as a Systems Administrator… https://t.co/71du6tjWhU https://t.co/BZiOkbXruq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java software developer/engineer – Glasgow: Java software developer/engineer – Glasgow   Java developer with massive transatlantic bank Work with global teams  Developing and enhancing existing platforms   Provide expertise to business teams Candidates… https://t.co/GL6ucX4Yyj https://t.co/XrVtLqDq0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acosta asks Sanders about Trump's media tweets: White House press secretary Sarah Sanders defends President Trump's use of the phrase "fake news" following suspicious packages being sent to his critics and organizations like CNN. https://t.co/bXfSqYbr2m https://t.co/xtChLdBb7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Captain – Architecture &amp; Design: San Jose, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based in San Jose, CA, we are a growing design oriented interior and architectural design firm that has recently been ranked as one of the Top 10… https://t.co/pzbL7WZ1q9 https://t.co/nvZGnrN4LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: Exciting opportunity for a high achieving Independent School in the Surrey area in search for a talented Service Desk Analyst / Senior ICT Support Technician. Great benefits including Free daily lunch onsite, free use of the onsite… https://t.co/pHBt3eAT6a https://t.co/Y5VENvvKzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMO Lead – Change – Perm/FTC – Edinburgh – to 50k plus excellent benef: PMO Lead – Change – Perm/FTC – Edinburgh – to 50k plus excellent benefits This is an exciting time for Abrecco`s Edinburgh based client, and so they`re looking for an experienced… https://t.co/nSIkHPtBs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevSecOps Engineer: DevSecOps Engineer Are you a DevSecOps Engineer who is keen to own the Security function for a FTSE 250 company? Want to help drive best practice through the development team? All of this whilst working with AWS, Lambda and… https://t.co/68g5wEtSQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tweet captures what many American Jews are feeling: Dismay, horror and disbelief were feelings shared by many in the aftermath of the mass shooting at a synagogue in Pittsburgh Saturday that left 11 people dead and six wounded. https://t.co/M6wWU0fINN https://t.co/SVizo8naMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer: Talent Forte are working with a global leading management consultancy that have urgent requirements for Performance Engineers/Test consultants at different levels of seniority. We require a large selection of the following skills: *… https://t.co/F6oRuJ0dFT https://t.co/s9F4U1kcTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Web Developer: PHP Web Developer – About the company A well renowned Glasgow based trading platform is seeking an experienced PHP Web Developer with good PHP Development experience to join their growing team. PHP Web Developer – About you and the… https://t.co/8l4ixrXZ41 https://t.co/sRaCR8gGET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: IT Helpdesk Technician opportunity Based in Fujitsu Bracknell Pay rate:  £18,200 to £21,195 per annum  Shifts:               40 hours per week, Monday to Friday with one weekend in approx 10 weeks, rotating shifts Hours:            … https://t.co/smuXlK4zSs https://t.co/TFet2Nc3Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Section Manager: 111568BR Section Manager CA – El Segundo 111568BR This position requires a U.S. person or the ability to obtain an Export Authorization from the appropriate government agency for non-U.S. persons Job Description: The Systems Development… https://t.co/GSJ0pUDvkU https://t.co/GNcdAxC1bY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st / 2nd Line CRM Application Analyst; Salesforce; London £42k: 1st/2nd Line Salesforce Support professional required by a finance services company based in Holborn. This is a newly created position due to continued success and future expansion plans.… https://t.co/MFRkrN4CiL https://t.co/cbzC0f1S3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copywriter &amp; Content Editor (Gambling Sector): Copywriter &amp; Content Editor (Gambling Sector)  This innovative, successful London based Online Gambling Company are looking for a Copywriter &amp; Content Editor to support the Head of Content marketing in the… https://t.co/y1d5RO0Wfg https://t.co/aOmHOXMIKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Sox cap stellar season: Total domination is complete. The Boston Red Sox, Major League Baseball's best team from start to finish in 2018, are World Series champions. https://t.co/eVbsJxDQCu https://t.co/aH0r3WZfSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Software Engineer: Graduate Software Engineer – Basingstoke – £25,000 – £35,000 Java, Python, C++. .Net Graduate Software Engineer require for an excellent client based in Basingstoke. Our client are a rapidly growing technology company and a… https://t.co/FXxAZ3DUuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Lead,Ruby,Python,C#,Java,Selenium,Cucumber: Automation Test Lead,Ruby,Python,C#,Java,Selenium,Cucumber You will join a highly successful e-commerce company looking to hire their first automation tester within the technology team which is… https://t.co/Mjewex7KVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Technical Consultant – 3 mth contract – Edinburgh – circa 4: Office 365 Technical Consultant – 3 mth contract – Edinburgh – circa 480 (GBP) / day I`m kicking off this Monday morning with an URGENT contract requirement for one of our Edinburgh… https://t.co/hbELtXe65H https://t.co/GqfRzOqTUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (Sales Data required): Sunnyvale, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted 09/10/2018 If you are a Data Analyst (Sales Data required) with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Analyze massive amounts of Sales data to identify unusual… https://t.co/rq11exytXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Support: Technical Project Support I am currently working with a leading software consultancy based in the Didsbury area who are heavily involved in eLearning Development. This organisation is an excellent one with a new opportunity.… https://t.co/dJ0GjhAUOx https://t.co/L6GazPZHlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Semitism is often an early indicator that extremism is gaining momentum in a society: The mass killing at a Pittsburgh synagogue, likely the worst anti-Semitic incident in US history, has Jewish Americans questioning whether they are now fated to… https://t.co/4w5ypS3eL9 https://t.co/WMFMrUN1Fr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Web Developer – Current SC Clearance Required: A growing developer of bespoke Digital Solutions are providing onsite resource to a prestigious central London client and require a number of skilled Front End Developers to join the business on a… https://t.co/gRiOiQahfi https://t.co/VCt7SZS0OH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Hybris Solution Architect: I am recruiting for a senior SAP Hybris Soluiton Architect opportunity for a $8b global IT outsourcing/offshoring consultancy company specialising in engineering, application &amp; infrastructure services, systems integration,… https://t.co/KMi2OOG0sD https://t.co/CsHsB4Bk2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia Lion Air flight crashes en route from Jakarta to Pangkal Pinang: A Lion Air flight capable of carrying up to 189 passengers has crashed during a short flight from the Indonesian capital Jakarta to Pangkal Pinang, according to Indonesia's… https://t.co/DsgsqNB5gI https://t.co/tJ0JU6VhME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-04738 Location: Arlington, Virginia Position Type: Contract to Hire Project Manager Arlington VA MUST: 10+ years of relevant experience with at least 3 years leading DoD or Federal projects and programs 5+… https://t.co/gdIIbdSiqF https://t.co/7NarvRpopX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Dir Product Manager: Associate Dir Product Manager Job Title: Associate Dir Product Manager About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries and markets that drive… https://t.co/r656Oybnt0 https://t.co/eqTQxMRCvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singer opens up about son's cancer: In an emotional appearance on "Carpool Karaoke" with James Corden, singer Michael Bublé said his "whole life ended" after he received the news about his son's cancer diagnosis. https://t.co/u5rgerOSPW https://t.co/FAY5htP2bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Financial Software): Project Manager (Financial Software) A market leading Coventry based financial software organisation are looking for new Project Manager / IT Project Manager. Joining an already well established software team you… https://t.co/X9lwShAxoM https://t.co/zySyaH0Q7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM to acquire cloud computing firm Red Hat for $34 billion: In a massive deal that could reshape cloud computing, IBM is acquiring open software company Red Hat for $34 billion. https://t.co/WDzny9gMSS https://t.co/g7DAFy45N9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager – Enterprise Applications: IT Manager – Enterprise Applications – Social Enterprise Founded 1963 London, Kings Cross £65,000 Per Annum + Extensive Company Benefits Are you an experienced IT Manager with experience of managing Enterprise… https://t.co/kysEOca9ff https://t.co/xvxjzn4QB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Loughborough – C / C++ – £30,000 – £37,000: This employer is looking for a motivated C / C++ Software Engineer with a passion for delivering high-quality technological solutions. This fresh, exciting company are passionate about… https://t.co/AmHkWQHri8 https://t.co/qb0mOOOC0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 years after abuse, survivor finds hope in former priest's guilty plea: With just four words, Chris Templeton's tears started flowing. For the first time in his life, he was hearing the priest who abused him more than three decades ago say, "Guilty,… https://t.co/JitgkDr7cL https://t.co/owmhfWnI3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: We specialise in the recruitment of high quality candidates in the IT, Digital &amp; Telecoms sector. We have an excellent opportunity for a Digital Product Manager to coordinate the delivery of Agile projects and ensure these are… https://t.co/AJHq3pa876 https://t.co/4selJ0qgIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fareed: One of the saddest weeks I've witnessed: CNN's Fareed Zakaria says there is an unmistakeable rise of anti-Semitism in America and decades worth of increasingly nasty political rhetoric on both sides of the aisle. https://t.co/AFHSotmT3W https://t.co/3Ay9009a4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Designer: Product Designer Are you an innovative Product Designer full of fantastic ideas? Join a company that is at the forefront of its industry! Product Designer needed to join a commerce company who are revolutionising and disrupting the… https://t.co/7BfLTAY2uP https://t.co/T5fPkCI56i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Analyst and Developer: Great American Insurance Group Job Opportunities Property Casualty Specialty | Annuity Application Analyst and Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the… https://t.co/YPtp4bSO52 https://t.co/2KEP1KGomj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insight Analyst: Insight Analyst Location – Nottingham Salary – up to £30,000 to £40,000 A well-known, fast paced company based in Nottingham are looking for an Insight Analyst to join the growing team. You will be working to provide insight to various… https://t.co/EA0kBdkb54 https://t.co/EQT14eLt7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – Manual: ECS Resource Group are currently looking for a Manual Test Analyst to join a Software House based in Birmingham. As a Test Analyst you will be responsible for providing testing activities and producing accompanying documentation in… https://t.co/CkUSziLpkK https://t.co/tnRBBwoht0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data &amp; BI Consultant – Edinburgh – £competitive + benefits: Data &amp; BI Consultant – Edinburgh – SQL Server | Qlikview | SAS – £competitive + benefits A market leading Data Management and Analytics consultancy across the UK are recruiting for Data &amp; BI… https://t.co/mFLgyYZsuM https://t.co/FNZkLHIidi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[• Opinion: A scary time in America: Less than 24 hours after authorities arrested a man accused of terrorizing the nation with mail bombs, another man, shouting anti-Semitic slurs and armed with an AR-15 assault rifle and three handguns, opened fire in… https://t.co/Dw6llDxhuN https://t.co/C3m6631qk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-Sales MPS Analyst: Role: Post-Sales MPS Analyst Location: London City (Field Based) Technical Skills: Papercut, Equitrac, eCopy, Uniflow, Autostore Salary: £25,000 – £35,000 + Benefits One of the industries’ leading office technology solutions… https://t.co/KESoXK5K5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Marine Industry – £40K: Software Developer – Marine Industry – £40K A great opportunity for a skilled Software Developer with .Net and front end web technology experience to join a market leading company operating in a global,… https://t.co/qlVfAnqV6G https://t.co/QLr4kpROkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A look inside the journey of the US-bound caravan migrants: Carlos Gomez took a break on a potholed road in southern Mexico littered with abandoned shoes and empty water bottles. The journey's toll is etched across his face. https://t.co/mjojQ9JpFh https://t.co/S1N5fNabcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Researcher, London: UX Researcher, London This innovative and award winning Market Leader is looking for a UX Researcher with a strong track record of UX Research to join their small but expanding team based in Central London.   We are looking for an… https://t.co/RrCD2Lff2C https://t.co/TrpGHOCgSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Web Developer: Would you like a job in Web Developer? Are you an ambitious and enthusiastic techie, looking to change their life by becoming the next Bill Gates or Mark Zuckerberg? Well now is your chance to become a Web Developer! The Training… https://t.co/b7H1yYpXt9 https://t.co/lvvYcKCrVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Network Engineer: Careers – Sr Network Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/aiLHVf20f8 https://t.co/R6YzM6thJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Production Support Analyst – Investment Banking: We are looking for Graduates to join our July Alumni Graduate intake in London. The Opportunity: If successful, you will gain a place on our Graduate Programme and start your journey by training… https://t.co/kzyD8FOMXp https://t.co/2HEgSD7QrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abortion pills now available by mail in US: Signaling a new chapter in the battle over abortion access in the United States, a European organization has stepped into the fray, providing Americans a way to get doctor-prescribed pills by mail to medically… https://t.co/HmNTDPv8si https://t.co/gQySMF2CX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Cambridge MA – Relocation Expenses: OUR TEAM IS WHAT MAKES OCTO GREAT. AT OCTO YOU’LL WORK WITH SOME OF THE SMARTEST AND MOST ACCOMPLISHED PEOPLE YOU’LL FIND IN YOUR CAREER. OCTO OFFERS FANTASTIC BENEFITS, AND ITS AN AMAZING… https://t.co/vHeoyXcsyV https://t.co/F7BT0MfoBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Scientist: Job Portal – All-In Analytics – 855-SAS-1101 – ************************** – – Home – Account Login – Candidate – Client – About Us – Hiring? – Contingency – Privatized Database – Job Portal – Sign-up/ – Consulting – Consulting… https://t.co/ZencmNKjCJ https://t.co/0xA2GPefIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['French Spiderman' climbs 46-floor building: A daredevil climber known as the "French Spiderman" has scaled a London skyscraper with his bare hands. https://t.co/U2Bxtn2XOw https://t.co/jm16N9AkjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animator: Animator London Production – Production Permanent/Full-time Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the creation of new realities. In gaming and… https://t.co/ErcOR5YRgl https://t.co/r1GaGw1FMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Oracle E Business Suite: Business Analyst with strong Oracle ERP experience required to join our client in West Lothian. This is an opportunity to work for a leading global organisation whose client list boasts some very notable… https://t.co/rImDGgYqGp https://t.co/2zfP0NX4tS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighborhood was once home to Mr. Rogers: Ask the residents who live there and they'll tell you that Squirrel Hill -- the site of the Pittsburgh synagogue attack -- is generally a happy, safe community. https://t.co/Kc8CK5kkbu https://t.co/RKhLGKv7zF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester: Our Client, based in Worcester, are looking to add a Software Tester to their existing team. Reporting to the Testing Team Lead, the purpose of the role is to work within an Agile team, delivering Quality, increasing the velocity of the… https://t.co/5R2k8nbG9e https://t.co/mXCJ8PSQgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics Finance – Product Manager – London, Greater Londo: Role You be a senior member of a large team, with responsibility for developing the Dynamics Product, at a leading Partner firm. As well as developing the Product Solution you will… https://t.co/5x53xyTseV https://t.co/0osrY37pcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Lead: Our client is an award-winning Software Financial Services business based in the south of Birmingham who, due to continued expansion and growth, are looking for a Software Development Lead to join their existing team. ROLE:… https://t.co/tW8ZM7naES https://t.co/g6sw8DeRe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Bruce Springsteen thinks Trump is going to win in 2020: Bruce Springsteen isn't a big fan of President Donald Trump. https://t.co/xd5fW39hgk https://t.co/gdIgZK3OXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Forensic Specialist: Benefits will include: * 25 Days Holiday * Company Pension * Private Medical Insurance * Subsidised Gym Membership * Childcare Vouchers * Company Benefits Portal * Share Save Scheme MASS, a technology company requires a… https://t.co/FptXl1RGnm https://t.co/HkXuAizZ8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC): Software Developer (https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs) £45,000 Sheffield Interaction Recruitment are currently recruiting for a Software Engineer for a leading house in Sheffield. You will be part of a small… https://t.co/qaY0tKGabU https://t.co/UjlMT93wV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPPLY SYSTEMS ANALYST: – Videos – Duties HelpDuties Summary You will serve as a SUPPLY SYSTEMS ANALYST in the Aviation Analysis Division, Aviation Operations Department of the Fleet Outfitting, Planning and Support Directorate of NAVSUP WEAPON SYSTEMS… https://t.co/F2GEZtP05k https://t.co/5OF5FF56OJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplier Quality Project Manager: Vacancy details General information Entity Safran is an international high-technology group, operating in the aircraft propulsion and equipment, space and defense markets. Safran has a global presence, with more than… https://t.co/94bCL8rY3b https://t.co/S842e70EXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Architect: 05-Jun-2018 Computer Systems Architect Space Colorado 434787BR – Demonstrated experienced with complex computer systems – Demonstrated design experience – Must be able to work in a production/operational environment – Must be… https://t.co/ZSfBDO114N https://t.co/Fo2ylTutIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is talking up his trade truce with China. The reality is far more unsettling: At the post G20 Summit in Buenos Aires, US President Donald Trump held what the White House called a "very successful meeting" with Chinese leader Xi Jinping and agreed… https://t.co/4gZ769y08q https://t.co/sMamq7qwQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kareem Hunt apologizes in ESPN interview: Former NFL player Kareem Hunt apologized in an interview with ESPN after a video was released which appears to show him push and kick a woman. Hunt was cut from the Kansas City Chiefs following the video and lost… https://t.co/6LmZJt0QYj https://t.co/KBRJhoN5Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer: Business Intelligence Developer Gloucester Salary £45,000 – £55,000 plus company bonus, pension, health cash plan and much more Trading for over 100 years this Financial Services client has revitalized its products and… https://t.co/wdHWj86tbS https://t.co/PYgA6TDcrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Donaldson on George H. W. Bush's relationship with the press: Former ABC correspondent and host Sam Donaldson, who covered the White House going back to the 1960s, remembered George H.W. Bush as a president who was "accessible" and "understood" the… https://t.co/vYQcjbjQOf https://t.co/6LqG5S1tH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solution Architect – £65-70,000 – Flexible Working: SharePoint Online Solution Architect – £65-70,000 – Flexible Working Are you a SharePoint Solution Architect who prides themselves on their technical knowledge as well as their ability to… https://t.co/lP8Qf9M7rO https://t.co/3Wki4CWdLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niantic confirms that Pokémon GO is getting PvP battles ‘soon’: Two and a half years after the launch of Pokémon GO, it’s still missing one major staple of the main series games: player versus player battling. That’s about to change. In a series of… https://t.co/O2FvQ9EfQy https://t.co/jxdQst4t9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Integration Analyst/Engineer:   Job Description – Product Integration Analyst/Engineer (18023373) Product Integration Analyst/Engineer Requisition ID : 18023373 Location : United States-Virginia-McLean US Citizenship Required for this Position:… https://t.co/odrLD0NRDN https://t.co/IER0tJYMmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, if you're attacking the FBI, you're losing: "When you're attacking FBI agents because you're under criminal investigation, you're losing," Sarah Sanders, then a Donald Trump campaign aide, famously said of Hillary Clinton supporters before the… https://t.co/cWEb5zerVs https://t.co/ewL1T77HkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Solutions Architect: Our customers are at the heart of everything we do, and our business plan is designed with the clear goal of improving the service we provide to the Bristol community. As part of this, we are going through an ambitious… https://t.co/SolweF7hfS https://t.co/Vg948Gxlyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Data Migration Consultant (S/4 HANA, MDG, Ariba): SAP Data Migration Consultant (S/4 HANA, MDG, Ariba) – Contract – Bracknell, Berkshire (2 days home-based) A leading IT services company is searching for a SAP Data Migration Consultant to join their… https://t.co/6jscDuFQpJ https://t.co/cZXWOc4m9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Architect TEQ Strategy Architecture: Job Description Job Description Sr. Technical Architect Strategy &amp; Architecture The TEQ Strategy &amp; Architecture team defines the TEQ Strategy, Architecture, and Technology Roadmap to increase quality… https://t.co/9Pch8pYF99 https://t.co/lCSYXg3GNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sense of foreboding descended over the journalist. 'God help us,' he wrote. Two months later, he was dead.: In his public writings, Jamal Khashoggi's criticism of Saudi Arabia and its Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was measured. In private, the… https://t.co/DBZsW64ht8 https://t.co/3sMRd6tnRt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>