<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Top U.N. Rights Official Seeks Inquiry on Kashmir Abuses https://t.co/6jJvnsDY8d https://t.co/gWWJrPER1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee Woman Placed Children in Kennels in Back of Her Car, Police Say https://t.co/xGFnugIXrK https://t.co/vEikZPTZzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Kim See New Chapter for Nations After Summit https://t.co/yow8CJQX5P https://t.co/lBZT6CetPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple to Close iPhone Security Hole That Law Enforcement Uses to Crack Devices https://t.co/KaMakOf5Tr https://t.co/7ndizHxN7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Women Are Running for Governor. Men and Money Stand in Their Way. https://t.co/LPN71rBngp https://t.co/ocfTN9Cc8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast and 21st Century Fox in Focus After AT&amp;T-Time Warner Approval https://t.co/1JzVhO7C1Q https://t.co/JWYEbUOjb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comey Cited as ‘Insubordinate,’ but Report Finds No Bias in F.B.I. Decision to Clear Clinton https://t.co/xKq99rzgAw https://t.co/wYvZCXKLFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Made Millions in Malaysia. Malaysia Hopes to Claw Some Back. https://t.co/3yFmUCfKqo https://t.co/cz74qFsw6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringleaders Get 25-Year Sentences in Deaths of 71 Migrants in Truck https://t.co/vz5WM2Ckg7 https://t.co/ufXe0QWuOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Drama, Action, Emotional Power’: As Exhausted Aides Eye the Exits, Trump Is Re-energized https://t.co/z4uMSXhTxJ https://t.co/YHEMwTBNYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to ‘The Daily’: The Narrowing Path to Asylum https://t.co/ml6WvSxZsI https://t.co/mRmSuPHJDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Refuses to Sign G-7 Statement and Calls Trudeau ‘Weak’ https://t.co/xiZZenDqEw https://t.co/CValjeoEUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple to Close iPhone Security Hole That Police Use to Crack Devices https://t.co/KaMakOf5Tr https://t.co/g8JT3vGgaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The First 2020 Race Is Underway: Scrambling for New York Donors https://t.co/blffczatGm https://t.co/fiYZGEcVqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt Smells Like the Ritz https://t.co/N7htA3yYkP https://t.co/2Pm6CKQM1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Trump Administration, Science Is Unwelcome. So Is Advice. https://t.co/Z8Fnj6aXcV https://t.co/B9d6KoYIEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump-Kim Summit Creates New Anxieties for Asian Allies https://t.co/FoHUjDugFb https://t.co/QAIEJ8oHgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Some in Tunisia, Ramadan Is a Test of Personal Freedom https://t.co/9zl0sX38Pa https://t.co/ofNA7Qq4qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting With Kim Tests Trump’s Dealmaking Swagger https://t.co/hWK5aGrXJ2 https://t.co/gHNcv7gEuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen, Trump’s Fixer, Parting With Lawyers as Federal Investigation Continues https://t.co/UIc8ZmTKAw https://t.co/wkkAnON4Cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Arrested in ‘Punish a Muslim Day’ Case in Britain https://t.co/ONADnZ9NaW https://t.co/Q5NdrEyTNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban Announce Brief Cease-Fire, Offering Afghans Hope for Lull in War https://t.co/JSFYRGkLyV https://t.co/62e9bi9aYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Behind Trump’s Links to Arab Princes? A Billionaire Friend https://t.co/sEgGU40xA5 https://t.co/3PiyKzqnRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times Examines Work History of Reporter in Leak Case https://t.co/h5rlrLyL07 https://t.co/bq43b4ZsWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Sets Votes on Immigration as Moderates’ Revolt Falls Short https://t.co/0rX42iAhKB https://t.co/sYh2n8Cwm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fyre Festival Organizer Sold Fake Tickets While Out on Bail, U.S. Says https://t.co/V8BSWpeeyJ https://t.co/Iw8f7OomQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After AT&amp;T-Time Warner Approval, Focus Shifts to Comcast and Disney https://t.co/1JzVhO7C1Q https://t.co/miB6TxBs22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Gaza Protests: Kites, Drones, Gas, Guns and the Occasional Bomb https://t.co/81cjKh0GMQ https://t.co/QpKhpEIjRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-C.I.A. Officer Is Convicted of Spying for China https://t.co/Bwh0qqUBZZ https://t.co/1Y4oAknlL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pixar Co-Founder to Leave Disney After ‘Missteps’ https://t.co/Bu8jGPSCYL https://t.co/izcoqa3ciK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Women, Decision by Sessions Puts Asylum Dreams Out of Reach https://t.co/3QW75LrBJZ https://t.co/vsz0ZixRxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Praises Arrest of Former Senate Committee Aide in Leaks Inquiry https://t.co/sJm2vnP9Dl https://t.co/QEUfKNGS48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bird, the Electric Scooter Start-Up, Is Said to Draw an Investment Frenzy https://t.co/6EMxeTZQs8 https://t.co/VYdpmHecUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says a ‘Big Operation’ Kept Wife, Melania, From G-7 https://t.co/xBtXaoWmn4 https://t.co/nH8UGy5iYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast’s Pursuit of Fox Would Face Hurdles, Regardless of AT&amp;T Ruling https://t.co/kMI7CqeB4P https://t.co/qoHzkBuDVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Trade War Faces Its First Big Test: DealBook Briefing https://t.co/r2fLsM5z9I https://t.co/yE0nGzJSAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Chinese Manuscript Written 2,300 Years Ago Ended Up in Washington https://t.co/CYSJ7NhjxK https://t.co/BGktkLJSDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Letters Might Be Key to North American Bid to Host 2026 World Cup https://t.co/prPkX20J97 https://t.co/OGv4awkiRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Border, a Discouraging New Message for Asylum Seekers: Wait https://t.co/vR4wS4lWeG https://t.co/luZxD3ll4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Man Kills 4 Children and Himself, Ending 21-Hour Hostage Standoff https://t.co/nQVLxk0DTC https://t.co/YVTR0UynDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, Opening Talks With Kim, Welcomes ‘Terrific Relationship’ https://t.co/yow8CJQX5P https://t.co/9yiRL3kV7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prolific TV Producer Greg Berlanti Extends Deal With Warner Bros. https://t.co/V6pmcnLI9o https://t.co/5EdJt85TbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennessee Woman Placed Children in Kennels in Trunk of Her Car, Police Say https://t.co/xGFnugIXrK https://t.co/UNnQhi1SOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House Made a Deal to Save ZTE. Is It Any Good?: DealBook Briefing https://t.co/Tg4V08o7mK https://t.co/xB4jT5EE7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Russia Steal the World Cup? https://t.co/sCY2NR38fi https://t.co/g1HQ9qVuLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘It’s Horrendous’: The Heartache of a Migrant Boy Taken From His Father https://t.co/v569A8ysKU https://t.co/YIx9rKImrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uzbek Asylum Seeker Gets Life in Prison for Deadly Truck Attack in Sweden https://t.co/T3yML70O8q https://t.co/22LOkJDj1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.N. Pulls Out of City in Yemen, Fearing Bloody Assault by Arab Coalition https://t.co/3PtnPl887e https://t.co/YEcLwNahSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions in Bribes Go Unpunished in Mexico as Election Nears https://t.co/P6qtOtbKUX https://t.co/UMWsJERcyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For All His Deals, Trump Has Never Faced an Adversary Like Kim Jong-un https://t.co/LsMswhFFgM https://t.co/pTOvHU9HXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I Am Qualified!’ Why Democratic Women Running for Governor Are Saying This https://t.co/LPN71rBngp https://t.co/vz9FqRkwBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K.K.R. Said to Be Near Deal to Acquire Envision Healthcare https://t.co/B2nXDr3KQH https://t.co/3nXDp3cxen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Pruitt Aides Resign as E.P.A. Ethics Questions Continue https://t.co/aQXE3ydKK9 https://t.co/AA5C89L2xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I Want to Hate …’ https://t.co/Wht5R0RU44 https://t.co/jDhHbFQT9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina-Israel Soccer Game Canceled Over Playing in Jerusalem https://t.co/gCXPqs2Veg https://t.co/G8UROa7PLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imam’s Killer Is Sentenced, but Motive Remains a Mystery https://t.co/mR3cwYef6D https://t.co/sdBTKyzKlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Drama, Action, Emotional Power’: As Exhausted Aides Eye the Exits, Trump Is Re-Energized https://t.co/z4uMSXhTxJ https://t.co/GCvxsrg2Zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Newark, Police Cameras, and the Internet, Watch You https://t.co/Jiq0XpOzGP https://t.co/O5imZ26NBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vladimir Putin, Greece, Facebook: Your Wednesday Briefing https://t.co/q0t4uDq4A7 https://t.co/pg8vRlAcxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Blasts Upend G-7, Alienating Oldest Allies https://t.co/KI6qJUOFaR https://t.co/5oEVnGf0ow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Sadler, Aide Who Mocked McCain, Leaves White House https://t.co/NDck1wfN59 https://t.co/Y4Op5z4cvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico, Hitting Back, Imposes Tariffs on $3 Billion Worth of U.S. Goods https://t.co/TtFwcFW426 https://t.co/ocAvXTbhhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says U.S. Will No Longer Be ‘Piggy Bank That Everybody’s Robbing’ https://t.co/xiZZenDqEw https://t.co/BtFz1kfi08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Agent Who Questioned Reporter Is Investigated for Computer Misuse https://t.co/mInUuk5lb1 https://t.co/7HDvO6N5vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s NATO Visit Marked by Stiff Handshakes and Uncomfortable ‘Family Photos’ https://t.co/ghQzDJavpb https://t.co/L2dSBWKPwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Volunteer Firefighters in North Carolina Charged With Setting Fires https://t.co/v142Euu29P https://t.co/ODyw4Bixoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing F.B.I. Agent Facing Assault Charge Can Carry Gun Again, Judge Rules https://t.co/mqU7iGNyfP https://t.co/irf56hm9Rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He Preyed on Men Who Wanted to Be Priests. Then He Became a Cardinal. https://t.co/mXXu57vYC6 https://t.co/AuDzDBAJhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Expected to Formally Name Successor to C.E.O. Lloyd Blankfein https://t.co/2VEWrYKoBP https://t.co/GvxTh9rDwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Presses NATO on Military Spending, but Signs Its Criticism of Russia https://t.co/fdn9Pr6484 https://t.co/bTYeRaJUEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Poisoning Inquiry Turns to Russian Agency in Mueller Indictments https://t.co/YkXcGZeGUJ https://t.co/0OXEKorT0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ‘King’ of Shambhala Buddhism Is Undone by Abuse Report https://t.co/bPImNXOFk5 https://t.co/R4c9mqam2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gap Between Trump and Justice Dept. Officials Grows Starker https://t.co/SNxC8PRg73 https://t.co/XJIuo2G1ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Koreans Are No-Shows at Meeting to Discuss U.S. Soldiers’ Remains https://t.co/CnoPM5KwW3 https://t.co/gisCPB7NVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Roll Out Trump’s Political Idol: Winston Churchill https://t.co/nzMGU7SwPX https://t.co/4eaunPe7w5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Orders Direct Taliban Talks to Jump-Start Afghan Negotiations https://t.co/9j3HnPnjn9 https://t.co/uHeJxWZJvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom Reaches Nearly $19 Billion Deal to Buy CA Technologies https://t.co/WORS8TRdzn https://t.co/w5Wv0VlmI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Arrested After Paraglider Unfurls Anti-Trump Banner at Scotland Resort https://t.co/lCJvaBP01T https://t.co/BbCNmfKdy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Migrant Families Are Reunited, Some Children Don’t Recognize Their Mothers https://t.co/GTOePJwahA https://t.co/m3yl9jDUDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘They Were Abusing Us the Whole Way’: A Tough Path for Gay and Trans Migrants https://t.co/SE7CQfpDvm https://t.co/d4ss4vq763]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NATO, Trade War, World Cup: Your Wednesday Briefing https://t.co/44pnzocUOA https://t.co/IuwnaKks3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Who Harassed Woman Over Puerto Rican Flag Shirt Is Charged With Hate Crimes https://t.co/7IKofVjxDL https://t.co/g87p4FgyJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Officials Slash Grants That Help Consumers Get Obamacare https://t.co/5odgLSOPVw https://t.co/1EqJvSzGCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Is Killed by Stolen Minivan After Gunfire Near Courthouse https://t.co/y0rhuBXjse https://t.co/WqYUU88Xxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taliban Opponent in Pakistan Killed by Bomb as He Campaigns https://t.co/CrCQbnIUUD https://t.co/kj7RVkNlvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell Simmons Faces New Rape Accusation in a First-Person Account https://t.co/Q0NZP7oC0S https://t.co/9d8EAhIuNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Sorrell Beats WPP in Bidding War for Dutch Marketing Firm https://t.co/yPIp6bX3fz https://t.co/jEItDu3Cko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Opens His Arms to Russia. His Administration Closes Its Fist. https://t.co/4ofaOOGIni https://t.co/QHLa5wpPbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Wave of Migrant Children Reunited With Parents https://t.co/qnhMD0U9Eo https://t.co/lt0Tv0sxA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home of Gerry Adams, Ex-Sinn Fein Leader, Hit With Explosives https://t.co/5OJfibZCBs https://t.co/GzfjDs9r3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fast and Furious Michael Avenatti https://t.co/HuGZYBxlQl https://t.co/91cdVcBWAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her Husband Was a Princeton Graduate Student. Then He Was Taken Prisoner in Iran. https://t.co/51IY51khAt https://t.co/LdkAJ3snrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Crisis Management Guru Bungles a Crisis https://t.co/ImKjhLw4Sz https://t.co/sMa0uHFcHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brett Kavanaugh Is Trump’s Pick for Supreme Court https://t.co/xN8H7YVEz7 https://t.co/HpPgeuLrTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Uber, New Questions Arise About Executive Behavior https://t.co/jPhUSxp8gQ https://t.co/gD7nrlBqv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas in Tow, Man, 72, Tried to Burn Down Condo to ‘Kill All Jews,’ Police Say https://t.co/YXDBbHmarH https://t.co/CDxIyVbp5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Poised to Enter NATO Meeting as Wild Card Among Allies https://t.co/Ljaahd2Kwq https://t.co/oVa8F3JCCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Rejects Long Detentions of Migrant Families, Dealing Trump Another Setback https://t.co/EyEKVNlFng https://t.co/dRiZCQhmKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Plead Guilty to Manslaughter in Gas Explosion That Killed a Fire Chief https://t.co/A1NUjV4Yxs https://t.co/50bCNWFOx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Health Secretary Tom Price Wasted $341,000 on Improper Travel, Inquiry Finds https://t.co/2zrcpYOcNT https://t.co/P7IowM9jwL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>