<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Rarely tweet about football, but making exception for @21LVA's birthday. Here's to the unalloyed genius of El Mago https://t.co/6jKYJrg8Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interested to see @rglucks1's new venture https://t.co/4NKB6G03go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this immensely: Patrick Melrose (2018) | Official Trailer | Benedict Cumberbatch SHOWTIME Series  https://t.co/Un9HWlVIFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent column by @johnthornhillft on the Enigma code, AI and the irreducibility of consciousness https://t.co/wxjNQyy5z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbrtrmstrng Bien sûr. You're familiar, I take it, with that unreleased Philly outtake "Behind the Veil of Ignorance"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rawls + Saint-Simon x Sen = Macron https://t.co/a6urZAKWTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gideonrachman on why Trump and Brexit are no longer identical twins https://t.co/EVEgD4txZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Euclid Tsakalotos, Greek finance minister, on why banking union isn't enough https://t.co/MYYlzd18qO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nicolas_Colin @DaraFrancisElie @FinancialTimes I will get that fixed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The late Peter Sutherland wrote this for the @FinancialTimes on Brexit and trade before the referendum in 2016 https://t.co/q6bXunMRQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @laRadioNova: Vous aussi, vous entendez "Assassin de la Police" dans la scène culte de "La Haine" avec Cut Killer ? Ouais, alors qu'en f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrkocnnll Performative contradiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GavinJKelly1: A well judged, and quietly devastating, @ft leader on the state of NHS funding. 'Sorry isn't enough'. https://t.co/DJ6gbD…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guardiola's mastery of the EPL is a chastening moment in national life, says @JananGanesh  https://t.co/H3WzParpsM https://t.co/ihwTB3dT5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaerB: Alright hen / pet / love / flower / me duck. Given the sticky situation following the Virgin Trains 'honey' dispute, is it time…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rbrtrmstrng: Julian Bonusworthy, sacked by a regulator and a robot https://t.co/na5Q6qZw4G via @financialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are 22-year-old Emmanuel Macron's comments on a manuscript by 86-year-old Paul Ricoeur (from F Dosse's book) https://t.co/zAgFFwoSMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good by @philipstephens: Britain has made itself a Brexit straitjacket  https://t.co/cunojAk1XO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmcternan @Samfr The Library of America editions I've bought in there ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strandbookstore: It is with a heavy heart we share that Strand’s owner, Fred Bass, passed away early this morning at home surrounded by…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your periodic reminder, per @alanbeattie, that distance still matters in trade https://t.co/GCR8oyF0IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frederick65: Smart and elegant Idler appreciation of Ben Austin’s delightful @ftcomment piece on the relevance of Latin in our digital…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Wolf on the "new world disorder" in 2018 https://t.co/WzNf6Zc7Oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK growth to slow to 1.5% in 2018, leading economists predict  https://t.co/piieFBGyVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dawson's Heights SE22, looking towards  fireworks on the Thames #NYE2017 https://t.co/x3Kj5y8nML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KuperSimon: 1. @Andrew_Adonis was my first boss @FT in 1995 and became mentor. He knows more about how UK state works than almost anybo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SimonFraser00: Here is my article today @ft surveying the #Brexit agenda for the year ahead and why #2018 is the time to look before we…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of year again - Alan Bennett's @LRB diary https://t.co/EfY9UnS1G4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gideonrachman wraps up our Year in a Word series with "alignment" https://t.co/pzHatpyckH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great news https://t.co/aJjnQfmsu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Oh yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Will do , but am absorbed in this right now https://t.co/VHCcMJAfLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH I need to watch properly. East Dulwich quality. FH, too, I trust?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FT: Forecasting the world in 2018 https://t.co/sa4YuU2XFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH Kes, your tweets about BBC music documentaries have sustained me over the holiday period. What's the beef here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Butchers' assistants and bell hops, you've had them all in your lair ..." https://t.co/fDzNCP5av5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That said, T Roland's habit of referring to GW as "George", where others are "Llacer", "Le Guen" and "Colleter" makes one somewhat uneasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quel festival George Weah!" Watched PSG a lot 1994-95.This goal remains with me, inscrit par M le Président https://t.co/1XEOxkOCei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMarkHerman Those of us actually who follow the French debate know that Macron has said more of substance about laïcité than any president in years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPittBrooke @Sammy_Goal For me, the defining moment of the season so far is Otamendi's pass into De Bruyne's feet at Chelsea, which led to the goal. Verticality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading this by the great François Dosse https://t.co/DONRv5A6tz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally caught up with Ferdy Mount on Princess Margaret - so good and perfect amuse-bouche to season 2 of The Crown https://t.co/EuJ07SBYV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quite a tale: @MADarbyshire's obituary of Charles Jenkins, American defector and reluctant recruit to the North Korean cause https://t.co/ioIw2AvTYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johnmcternan on the legacy of Powell and Benn https://t.co/TfF5N0ITpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff in today's paper from @TimHarford and the @FinancialTimes's data visualisation team https://t.co/EzUic0IAdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FinancialTimes: Here's some of the best of our comment and analysis this year as Xi Jinping’s China has become increasingly assertive w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are some of the highlights of the @FinancialTimes's Brexit commentary this year https://t.co/gu5IT0u74f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchester is lucky to have someone like @JenWilliamsMEN to tell its stories https://t.co/xS6SguLqsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @FT's @davidpilling with George Weah, PSG, Milan &amp; @ManCity legend and now, it seems, next president of Liberia https://t.co/QasGcwRInB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This by Alison Wolf on technical education and our obsession with university degrees is excellent https://t.co/8OXw1IVYOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever happened to the centre-left? https://t.co/ZS5kJbRsT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChassNews on what Emmanuel Macron owes to Paul Ricoeur https://t.co/cRQ2qBsxBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best present this Christmas https://t.co/DQZnjzt8Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Mitcham for the big one: @OfficialTmufc v @DulwichHamletFC https://t.co/btCOiR2QwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas https://t.co/cgEVTzr8IM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning to do this walk in the new year - Ivry to Saint-Denis https://t.co/zKsltMhMuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheHerne in East Dulwich full of festive cheer today https://t.co/Ujy2jQcS74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rare to see "hegemony" used in a football match report, but Sunday Times says #mcfc won "territorial hegemony" early in yesterday's match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindasgrant @BBCRadio3 Just pronounced Foy on Today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@andrewtghill on the story of the week - Long Island Ice Tea's blockchain "pivot" https://t.co/dPbOi0aRRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalcolmMoore: Watch the UK's rail network go dark over the next few days with this great graphic from @theboysmithy https://t.co/XNgGwp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bronwenmaddox on our ageing population and the end of inheritance  https://t.co/G4pQz6sg5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Baddiel: .@FT are doing a big series of pieces on dementia. I wrote one. Please read it, and/or any of the others, if you have the time…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dark_shark: Patti Smith and Tom Verlaine, 1975 by Anton Perich #Television #music #NewYork https://t.co/uG2UiJSP3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @polyalbion: Today’s Vitamin C shot… https://t.co/IUPXBAa1J0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for @jonathancoe and @StuartMaconie: reading Galen Strawson's essay collection and I learn that he had a 2-week tryout with Henry Cow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djtaylorwriter @FaberBooks @leebrackstone Very much looking forward to this. Heard Rob Young talk about Can before Irmin Schmidt's show at the Barbican last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late to it, but this is a magisterial survey of some of the long-term challenges (esp in labour market) facing Britain by @GavinJKelly1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheosElizabeth Do you know Michael Harrington's The Other America? He was a Catholic Worker alumn https://t.co/TIq9PJCMt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to have received this in the post this morning https://t.co/QEtWztNu8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahoconnor_ Remember the 'sharing economy'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VincentKompany,@FT Business Education cover star https://t.co/ErEQ6MJrSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnharris1969: One of best pieces in weeks is by @RanaForoohar in the FT. Data harvesting allows precisely-targeted insurance based on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the fragmentation, stupid - excellent @Grepsul and @gillplimmer1 Big Read on Britain's railways   https://t.co/mNsrggdXmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wonderful:@kokorokomusic interpreting Fela's "Colonial Mentality" https://t.co/Fiw967oLgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamSJFoulds: https://t.co/Fhnn0lLM5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This excellent review by @Jonhinius really makes me want to read the new Julian Barnes https://t.co/7tpqDmglCP https://t.co/fO853DCyUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new film by Claude Lanzmann plundered from the "treasure" he amassed for Shoah https://t.co/pP1idAFaU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harikunzru Splendid news and well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transpontine https://t.co/l2HzG7tXPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for the Woolwich Ferry https://t.co/GahGg0z8xJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Save our sugar" https://t.co/7k5VOM3iYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtopia, E16 https://t.co/hJ051Ng4tK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durham Arms, Canning Town https://t.co/RvfXGd8cDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[East End dérive: River Lea below Three Mills https://t.co/9PQ8VLvicG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidpilling: RIP Hugh #Masekela: The joyful moment he received Louis Armstrong's trumpet
@FT obit here: https://t.co/tyK0Tk8yqv https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A baobab tree has fallen" https://t.co/DoHre9ENPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimHarford: The economics of happiness - https://t.co/e9wX3pCpPo My column aka whether policymakers should be guided by happiness surve…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahchurchwell: I did a piece on importance of liberal education for @ftcomment. A long list of other world leaders who studied #human…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that you can sign up to receive the @FinancialTimes Opinion email in your inbox six days a week. https://t.co/FPPjXns0vX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good book post today https://t.co/WtfcwGG8j4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What strikes me about this is the importance of MSE's insistence that The Fall were a "group" not a "band" https://t.co/XSxgICaopG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to run the world? Study a 'useless' subject, argues @sarahchurchwell https://t.co/FyrzsSzt02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinwolf_ on good and bad arguments for PFI https://t.co/xdFriW48bM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjwrenlewis Very good piece. I played Ordoliberalism off against the Chicago School in this symposium on @davies_will's excellent book on neoliberalism https://t.co/WT9hyzOqdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent blog by @sjwrenlewis explaining why being pro-market is not the same as being reflexively pro-business  https://t.co/Hpuq8elm87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They have to face the consequences of their own decision" - excellent @Ockrent interview with Michel Barnier  https://t.co/TDRzRWS1RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lilydunnwriter Avital?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Leave the capitol. Exit this Roman shell." https://t.co/YutUTWCKjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djtaylorwriter: I've drunk a jar of coffee, I've had some of these, and I'm Totally Wired! https://t.co/V4ijvtxk3a]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>