<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Consider a Career at MTM From entry level customer service positions, to challenging technology and leadership roles, MTM offers a wealth of employment opportunities. Our corporate culture promotes healthy living,… https://t.co/gqBMXwwaPP https://t.co/96921qTuTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer (Contract to Hire): UX Designer (Contract to Hire) A design studio here in San Francisco that helps leading technology companies build products that make their consumers lives better and easier. Their creative and deep analytical approach… https://t.co/3tkQTijIpq https://t.co/1Fva6FgBhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer # 180031119: Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer Columbus, OH. Design, Develop &amp; maintain various MFTS platforms (Secure Transport, AXWAY API gateway, File Mover, IBM Sterling secure proxy etc.).… https://t.co/M6e9jxyfps https://t.co/ODJnRvpniZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Architect: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/hj73OZiFus https://t.co/ETMRsGjKgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Manager: Overview: The Technical Support Manager is the leader of the technical support group of the Information Technology Department and is responsible for the management of the United Nations Foundation’s desktop support staff; the… https://t.co/cNHxrcU9wy https://t.co/RdkhoJpVQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Expert: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, cdng, tst, QA of cmplx prdct feat in a dvlpmt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt a Master’s &amp; 5 yrs exp. Exp… https://t.co/o5v7Mb7MgV https://t.co/D0ukrm2iQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Marketing Networks Are Changing Because of #MeToo: Content Marketing Networks, like Revcontent, draw eyeballs for ads with outrageous words and images. But post #MeToo, that strategy might be bad for business. https://t.co/RIkFrgjoij https://t.co/KxPp6WtG6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/6VLHzpo8zW https://t.co/F5L1O5PxZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Tech Specialist 5 (Lead Data Warehouse ETL Dev/Tester): Info Tech Specialist 5 (Lead Data Warehouse ETL Dev/Tester) at DSHS-Children’s Administration (CA) Finance &amp; Performance Evaluation Division (FPED) (unabbreviated full text job desc. @… https://t.co/Q6RMkosTR5 https://t.co/0weruSpVEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence / ETL Developer: Benton PUD is looking for a Business Intelligence / ETL Developer with strong competency in Data analytics and ETL development and a passion for creating a data infrastructure and building data visualizations to… https://t.co/Ii6XwRhhD7 https://t.co/WH2puzkjyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers: Oracle America, Inc. has openings for the following positions (all levels/ types) in San Mateo County, including Redwood Shores, CA and San Bruno, CA; Alameda County, including Pleasanton, CA; San Francisco, CA; Santa Clara County,… https://t.co/4KjNKjuJ4s https://t.co/zqOxyk8tm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer:   TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center… https://t.co/4uQBZGrMm5 https://t.co/NwB55Fjnfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG DEVELOPER: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/GIpCmlpcsu https://t.co/8ra9050aDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R43424: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall tech design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer apps using existing &amp; emerging tech… https://t.co/PWBYASrf8B https://t.co/lbA2DDQ6cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG Developer: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/mmN8T102Dz https://t.co/t27bCWBb7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #180032367: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Interface w/ business &amp; IT resources to understand &amp; analyze business, functional, &amp; technical requirements. EOE, AAE, M/F/D/V. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. All rights reserved.… https://t.co/a7fdCkMP35 https://t.co/JIFdmclrYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member Technical Staff #DC1-N: Looking for Senior Member Technical Staff at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Design, architect and create solutions using Java, Micro services and Cassandra NoSQL database.  recblid g3ukvkv7nkb0u6wdafg35aqw5eeugv https://t.co/BHZKwXgIqw https://t.co/Daip5DMvbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It: IT Position Multiple positions available at the following California locations: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II,… https://t.co/d2ORlakxAI https://t.co/IKVaRe3Grj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cryptocurrency Industry Might Actually Benefit From an Ad Ban: Google, Facebook, Twitter, Reddit, Snap, and MailChimp have all decided to shut out cryptocurrency advertising, but some blockchain enthusiasts say that might not be such a bad thing. https://t.co/TTfPydLgaZ https://t.co/ftEad6dDBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI Specialty Nurse- Part Time- 20 hours a week 9am-5:30pm: As one of the nations leading pediatric health care systems, Nemours is committed to providing all children with their best chance to grow up healthy. We offer integrated, family-centered care to… https://t.co/R1Xe1SxqY4 https://t.co/bEla5NiTGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Content Manager / Developer: POSITION: WEB CONTENT DEVELOPER / COPYWRITER TYPE: 6+ MONTH CONTRACT REPORTING TO: DIRECTOR LOCATION: LOS ANGELES, CA THE ROLE: Our client is in need of a Web Content Developer that will be in charge of meeting with… https://t.co/Qh8O40PVdb https://t.co/D8D79cCMjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer- Embedded C/C++: 16178BR Sr. Software Developer- Embedded C/C++ General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in… https://t.co/v4kAVl5haT https://t.co/WaVcgoW0AK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental/Safety Coordinator 16461: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/AhDnxy9hCH https://t.co/IuWe6jce0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Program Sr Mgr: Req ID : 420820BR_2 Job Code/Title : L3286:IT Program Sr Mgr Job Description : This position is in the Space CIO Program Management Office. Senior IT Program Manager responsible for the Space IT Infrastructure Data, Voice, and Video… https://t.co/4ZqXgbDYMy https://t.co/S0MhwggykF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Node/React Developer: Responsibilities * Work in an Agile environment * Deliver timely project execution and project work products that exceed customer expectations * Contribute to functional specifications and detailed design documents for… https://t.co/rKWWWWYORI https://t.co/BOdlTN3fvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Category: Business Analysis (functional and technical) City: Topeka, Kansas, United States Position ID: J0318-1904 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: Working as a Business… https://t.co/4eTt04RV57 https://t.co/kHxxRfNwmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby Developer: The Backend Developer’s mission is to build the APIs and user interfaces that thousands of developers use when they deploy their sites on Netlify. Our main office is located in the Dogpatch district in San Francisco, CA. Currently, were… https://t.co/iDOaMBEjkO https://t.co/OXAS3iK8Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/Zsn0k4ZAcW https://t.co/LjniPthF7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer Analyst – BS CS, Engineering or related + 5 years experience or MS + 2 years experience or any suitable combo. FACETS, Oracle, PL/SQL, C#, Informatica. Travel required.  recblid jlrrs4k2368snahqqwcq903s13boho https://t.co/yFHGZ8USN3 https://t.co/gdfIrC408P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Title:                      DevOps Engineer Category:             Exempt Department:       User &amp; Systems Support Benefits:               22 Days Annual Leave, 15 Days of Sick Leave, 3 Days Personal Leave, 15 Paid Holidays Tuition… https://t.co/3iTYu5dunM https://t.co/Go7l3kjAcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator I: Systems Administrator I Assists in working with stake holders, other IT staff, and vendor(s) to plan and execute applications, systems, and infrastructure installations and updates. Recommends enhancements for the proactive… https://t.co/shNKK3gyYM https://t.co/m5hQpHAlD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Shunned an IPO. Now It's Just Another Public Company: The music-streaming service listed its shares Tuesday without the traditional bankers or ceremony. https://t.co/qxUoIhg9yH https://t.co/Ead5TOKgnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance and IT Manager: Finance and IT Manager The Brattleboro Food Co-op has an immediate need for a Finance and Information Technology Manager. Reporting to our General Manager, this position oversees all of our financial and IT management operations.… https://t.co/YHXMt1z1Ga https://t.co/FetjflLIlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG Developer: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/pDfHea6EY8 https://t.co/hzSvY2L285]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer #7788: Data Engineer Job #7788 $64,000 – $80,000 Annual (Salary DOQ) Basic Responsibilities: Provide analytic support and services across the organization. Support the development of new analytical models and business intelligence solutions… https://t.co/78yc8p3Xm9 https://t.co/QPckgG8leD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA APPLICATION DEVELOPER: KRONSYS is hiring for 2 positions (travel req): Java Application Developer – MS CS, EE or closely rel. XML, Oracle, Java; Business Data Analyst – MS Comp App, Info Sys, MBA or closely rel. + 2 yrs exp. or BS + 5 yrs exp. or… https://t.co/AyUf0nbhrZ https://t.co/gSrX1T0GL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager With Masters Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science, or Computer Engineering, and 1 year experience in job offered. (or) Bachelor’s Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science,… https://t.co/KOQpJpmWC3 https://t.co/iaMiROVML8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/M7SSx3lARp https://t.co/WFcApanrYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Requirements: Bachelor’s degree in computer science, Management information systems, Information technology.  Experience/familiarity with Windows Server, MS Exchange, Cisco routers, WAN networking, SAN, VMware. $28.92 – $33.25 Hourly… https://t.co/3qiUgyMbKB https://t.co/uLfrtI3QVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Success Manager: Overview: Are you passionate about Digital Marketing and Data? Can you translate business needs into strategic marketing plans and tell success stories through data? If this sounds like you, we are looking for a Success Manager… https://t.co/MODddKLh49 https://t.co/J8C6QTw9Dw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager II: Information Technology positions available at the following California locations: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc seeks candidates for the following positions:… https://t.co/DAVJUrUViB https://t.co/9yAho9sADM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Populus Group seeks a Developer in Irvine, CA. Must have a Master’s degree or equiv plus post-baccalaureate exp. recblid jmn15kr5udqc8psl56y5r2phlgpvye https://t.co/BIUdk95XVc https://t.co/BqWID9XGwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS System Developer: Oracle EBS System DeveloperRIC037557678*Richmond, VA*This position will provide key, hands-on technical work to perform programming, analysis, development, implementation, enhancement, revision and maintenance of automated… https://t.co/BsINOdGRVv https://t.co/l4DHVYRlrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Grubhub Analyzed 4,000 Dishes to Predict Your Next Order: Online food-delivery service spent eight years resolving a classic problem of unstructured data. https://t.co/NRn2fQssMb https://t.co/KnR6vID4mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk Support Analyst II: Zelis is a healthcare information technology company and market-leading provider of end-to-end healthcare claims cost management and payment solutions. Inc.5000 award winner: One of the fastest growing privately held… https://t.co/jo2olEHmXC https://t.co/mz47Vmxkko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Estimator: Philadelphia, PA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are an experienced Project Estimator, please read on! Based in Huntingdon Valley, PA, we have been providing construction management, general construction,… https://t.co/J008gU5OOQ https://t.co/xqfy68h228]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics NAV Developer – Los Angeles, CA – $80k – $120k: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:2nd February 2018Location:Los Angeles, CaliforniaContact Name:Sheridan ExTelephone:+ 44 191 230 1883Reference:NAV020218 Salary:$80000 – $120000 per annum Dynamics NAV… https://t.co/ikAasG4niC https://t.co/7DHqUWz8Fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Developer: True Source IT is searching for an up and coming/mid-level database developer well versed in PL/SQL Development to join a trusted client in the northwest suburbs of Minneapolis. This is a fantastic, mid sized company with a… https://t.co/V8EZ150mPZ https://t.co/kKmoY84mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Network Engineer Job: Date: Mar 24, 2018 Location: Fort Belvoir, VA, US Company: SAIC Cloud Network Engineer (Job Number:435220) Description: Job Responsibilities: – Experience in all phases of LAN/WAN/wireless LAN Life Cycle network requirements,… https://t.co/E4LsgEVANI https://t.co/nCfeaKdnE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: Become part of an amazing company that values user experience! Our client is looking for a highly motivated User Experience (UX) Designer to join their talented, award-winning UX team in AUSTIN, TX. As a UX Designer, youll demonstrate your… https://t.co/IqiR75qTmB https://t.co/Sem3zr187z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist (Chicago): QuantumBlack helps companies use data to drive decisions. We combine business experience, expertise in large-scale data analysis and visualization, and advanced software engineering know-how to deliver results. From… https://t.co/s6d6PfI1qs https://t.co/WzKKYYQAto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Analyst: Role Name: SAP Business Analyst (logistic, CSM) (W2 only) Duration: 12+ Months This is for a medical products supply chain client of ours. Requirements: * 5+ years Business Analysis experience * 3+ years SAP (order management, SCM,… https://t.co/3Hu5l0S7aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer: Description:The Civil Health Operation is currently seeking a Lead Windows Endpoint Engineer to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful candidate will work within an ITIL… https://t.co/7WETyPgcEg https://t.co/NzKuqCG4aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description:The Defense &amp; Intelligence Group of Leidos has a career opening for a Network Engineer at Scott AFB, IL JOB SUMMARY: Our customer is the Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA) located at  Scott AFB, IL and acts as the… https://t.co/uutBJthile https://t.co/7JYuD5peVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: Description:  Position Summary: The Systems Engineer serves as the Subject Matter Expert for FuelsManager Defense Enterprise (FMD) Base Level Support Application (BLSA), FASTracker, and all other Enterprise applications supported on… https://t.co/pHAAB2XMLY https://t.co/PToyGliskg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudflare's New Encryption Service Adds Privacy Protection: Internet infrastructure company Cloudflare appears to be preparing to launch a service to encrypt traffic to the computers that look up web addresses. https://t.co/RZd1paJe96 https://t.co/w5kzMqH6Gv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Solutions Architect: Description:Leidos is looking for a Solutions Architect to oversee the transformation of its applications and moving applications. This position is in the Northern Virginia area and requires an active TS/SCI with Polygraph… https://t.co/SEJvdbRjSG https://t.co/qJLDqkeLep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Engineer: A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/0mmkQbDNlH Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following position (multiple positions available for each title): Business Intelligence Engineer, Job Code AZ0136: support… https://t.co/1PO2HhZDQx https://t.co/sNM4eQM35F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Senior Network Engineer at Scott AFB, IL or Ft Meade, MD JOB SUMMARY: The Senior… https://t.co/6oZedJnjgw https://t.co/9vOTZ1NPbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/oR9dtoNv53 https://t.co/gnN3KvJ8A5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/UTkVHTNfA7 https://t.co/UosW1TAfPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead MAC Endpoint Engineer: Description:The Civil Health Operation is currently seeking a Lead MAC Endpoint Engineer to support a large   JOB DESCRIPTION: The successful candidate will work within an ITIL environment. The position is a highly customer… https://t.co/1FAf67oshc https://t.co/RJW9LXziM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst IV: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/Ybq2RR1Yfb https://t.co/tImlseV3dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work challenges. Lead design research education to… https://t.co/tadVLcUY47 https://t.co/Rvigh3tlVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archer Administrator / Developer: Archer Admin/Dev VITA014531449*Chester, VA*  A contractor to provide technical support and expertise to provide the necessary improvements and enhancements to the information database (VMEDS) and/or other IT functions.… https://t.co/ww5a1pOHCY https://t.co/XAteNuCmLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Specialist – PeopleSoft: HCR ManorCare provides a range of services, including skilled nursing care, assisted living, post-acute medical and rehabilitation care, hospice care, home health care and rehabilitation therapy. This Business… https://t.co/l1bjgve0cZ https://t.co/v5bcjeuYKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Program Manager: Description:Leidos is seeking an experienced Deputy Program Manager  for a highly visible cyber security single-award IDIQ vehicle that provides security operations center (SOC) support, cyber analysis, application development,… https://t.co/jlR0bWKTr4 https://t.co/QXp2svJkEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering – Multiple Positions: ENGINEERING: Quantum Secure Inc (San Jose, CA) F/T positions: Solution Engineer III: Resp for analyze &amp; cust security suite; req Master’s or equiv + 2 yr exp + skills (telcom. ok). Big Data Engineer: Resp for large data… https://t.co/loIv4ZRaRv https://t.co/uljZptNFYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmanuel Macron Q&amp;A: France's President Discusses Artificial Intelligence Strategy: In an interview with WIRED, French President Emmanuel Macron describes his plans to enhance the country's AI efforts—and differentiate them from those in the US. https://t.co/j7kRQPuHdi https://t.co/zCspkBzAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Technical Operations Analyst: CO-OP Financial Servicesprovides technically superior products and services to financial institutions across the nation. We are seeking a talentedSr. Technical Operations Analyst to be responsible for performing analysis… https://t.co/VEXXCPXbXO https://t.co/i3X0nMcKWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Engineer / SQA Engineer: The SQA Engineer will be responsible for the quality assurance testing of Scribes products which are built on Microsofts .Net platform and utilizing agile development processes &amp; methodologies. This… https://t.co/0FCnKdQy1x https://t.co/7Ly7zsZLtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Programmer: SUMMARY: The Programmer will assist the Database Administrator with the expansion of firm automation capabilities via web services and assist in the development of in-house case management system. Experience in T-SQL is a must, as… https://t.co/HEpXLLyYe8 https://t.co/CZKSsJtyUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer for Content Management Systems: Software Engineer For Content Management Systems | Snowbound Software Skip to main content Search form Search this site – Products – HTML5 Document Viewer – Demos – Video – Features – Connectors /… https://t.co/qP5GnzYGo2 https://t.co/xrdPBqcEtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Metal Processing Engineer: Stockton, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Sr. Metal Processing Engineer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Located in Stockton, CA we are seeking an experienced Metal Processing… https://t.co/y7avkEFzYV https://t.co/flgZOCIZ4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: MediaSilo and Wiredrive have combined forces and we’re expanding! We are looking for a Technical Support Specialist to join a growing team that manages a family of creative collaboration and media management software tools,… https://t.co/ZyU2IkpX6r https://t.co/MYvkbXQRnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Sales Data Analyst: About Continental With sales of 40.5 billion in 2016, Continental is among the leading automotive suppliers worldwide and currently employs more than 230,000 employees in 56 countries. Information management in and beyond the… https://t.co/MLhHakVuN4 https://t.co/Ke8u6Fprjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Group Product Marketing Manager, Developer Ecosystem: This Position is available either in our San Francisco or San Jose Office Product Description: From hailing a cab to collaborating with coworkers, modern web and mobile applications have… https://t.co/xQNBNUXQeJ https://t.co/td3Txel63F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Interface w/ bus. &amp; IT resources to understand &amp; analyze bus., functional, &amp; tech. reqs. EOE, AAE, M/F/D/V. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. All rights reserved. recblid s4tdmbmqz4jwxnb20qg1j65iqca8bj https://t.co/BOtsfSzpV1 https://t.co/dqhAH3yDIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software II: Engineer Software II for Tridium Inc. (Honeywell co) (Richmond, VA) responsible for development &amp; testing software as part of Agile team for Tridium’s Niagara Framework. Requires Master’s in Electrical Engineering, Computer… https://t.co/fXhcOrHgZC https://t.co/XKX1red21N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Information Technology: DIRECTOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Tribal Office Building Closing date: 4/10/18 or until filled.   Qualifications: An undergraduate degree in Computer Science or equivalent field.  (Master’s degree preferred, or… https://t.co/FUbD71k4Zx https://t.co/kNQqyb8G2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Next Cold War Is Here, and It's All About Data: The General Data Protection Regulation coming to Europe this spring emphasizes how different societies value personal data and privacy. https://t.co/FGZqZPoGJN https://t.co/nOf4UrlzSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Specialist: Network Security Specialist Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of Network Security Specialist located at our Milton R. Young Station located near Center, ND. Responsible for the… https://t.co/gAsD5sHzpX https://t.co/E18ev3xqvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/bcS3uNxPlE https://t.co/WV46SexDrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/9n510MMSar https://t.co/rnFyLy5MOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/nuKTM0iLlw https://t.co/WxDtfB2Gk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development, optimization, and… https://t.co/lgu235D4qQ https://t.co/eBV5EF1B5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R44563: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer apps using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/IRKAYhNuiY https://t.co/SAArQQGxLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Computing Software Engineers: Description:Leidos is seeking Software Engineers with extensive experience in DevOps implementation within Commercial Cloud Computing environments.  This position requires extensive hands on experience migrating… https://t.co/JzQB6ZV382 https://t.co/CQwVnJWk2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA location for… https://t.co/p6cLqgIr2z https://t.co/JjHcrdh8na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Expert: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5… https://t.co/4fTDGd40hy https://t.co/89jvTFvWyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member Technical Staff: Senior Member Technical Staff Verizon Irving, TX Design, architect and create solutions using Java, Microservices and Cassandra NoSQL database. To apply, mail resume to Ramesh Babu Ramakrishnan, Sr. Manager, Verizon, 700… https://t.co/apSvTAAJFw https://t.co/3zbYB8bQSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member Technical Staff Consultant: Member Technical Staff Consultant Verizon Irving, TX Responsible for the deployment, operations and administration of the Hortonworks Hadoop Data Platform and Tableau infrastructure. To apply, mail resume to Mufazzal… https://t.co/NulCXnkHyP https://t.co/5Dnx0OO4R4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description:This is Software Engineer position for the Live Team Programs AFCTC Upgrade Program.  The candidate shall be involved in the development of applications and services that are used to monitor and stimulate MILES equipment as… https://t.co/agKG81yrHV https://t.co/l201n5QkbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Brooklyn Architect Wants to Rewire Puerto Rico with Solar: Architect Jonathan Marvel is building solar arrays to serve community centers, and soon, he hopes, communities. https://t.co/mwpTNbm3rk https://t.co/Fy5SfZC0X6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Software Engineering: SUMMARY This role will be responsible for Leading and developing a global software engineering product team responsible for the development of Jamfs flagship Apple device management solution, Jamf Pro, and the Jamf… https://t.co/fSvn3QZlpw https://t.co/K3FlXKmaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: Aristotle is looking for a UI/UX Designer (with some JS development experience) that believe those companies that champion a design-centric approach to their product interfaces are the ones that rise above the rest. You live and breathe… https://t.co/JPziiEND4v https://t.co/SYCthLAfW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: In search of a Desktop Support Technician for a direct hire role in Houston, TX. The Desktop/Network Technician role supports the overall Help Desk function and ensures that end users are receiving the appropriate level of… https://t.co/DAj1KC0KY3 https://t.co/wk5iKUnK3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. UI Developer – Lead :: Denver CO: Sr. UI Developer – Lead :: Denver CO – PurpleDrive – Denver, CO – 03-05-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/RhjlBOxE3u https://t.co/Tds1Mp69l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Developer: Job Information: Senior Oracle Developer Job Email Opening Title Senior Oracle Developer EOE StatementWe are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without… https://t.co/pRRGeDJy7M https://t.co/qKCffYB0mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Designer: UX/UI Designer – Try K2 – Contact Us – – Platform The K2 Platform – Platform Overview – Packages &amp; Pricing Demos &amp; Trials – One-Minute Demos – Request a Demo Marketplace – Community Market Department Solutions – Human Resources – Finance… https://t.co/yHFom5l0qf https://t.co/rW2moGfgt8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>