<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bluthquotes: #HappyThankgiving https://t.co/jiFI6viPO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10:45pm snack. https://t.co/SBxhvq46er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finish. Leftovers time! https://t.co/eLyZjYnSDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needed mini marshmallows for sweet potato casserole. They only had one size... https://t.co/YM0b0tPI6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A&amp;H The ESB. Start of the holiday events for the brewery... @ The Merchant, Canary Wharf https://t.co/qX1RiQF7Kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My office today. Possibly, a metaphor for my mind right now... @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/UEKCwQR1Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StuartElden: A number of hard-to-find Foucault texts – notes, lectures and interviews
https://t.co/gClrCjGwdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left Boston with these two, now about to teach with these two... long Tuesday... https://t.co/Hjii41kyIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading my 3part NOISE def through Lefebvre’s 3part spatial schema to highlight 3 phil points of sound studies. Trilectics all the way down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 Done London-Cape Town-Sydney &amp; LA-Sydney. Have some perspective...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 I’d let either of them teach my class on Trajan/Hadrian today after a flight...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @raylaurence1: The haves and have-nots: four cities in crisis

https://t.co/lLgQomdofi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ll be behind the bar for this great event! Get a ticket before it sells out! https://t.co/N1vhyV5w84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: This Friday we'll be pouring our L'Ermitage collad Rye Stout at the Tap Room from 5pm ... C'est Bon!

#collab #belgian #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 Seriously, just landed. 5:40 hour flight. Although, I’m teaching in 5 hours... w/ hours of sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, AAR/SBL 2017 is done for me. Thanks everyone for a great time in Boston. Nice to meet so twitter folks in the flesh! Now flight/sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haggia Sophia: Sound, Space and Spirit in Byzantium #soundstudies #aarsbl17 https://t.co/4OJPRGZxIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got stopped by someone, who enjoyed my paper, to make sure I knew! So, important to go out of your way to complement speakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @profdavidharvey: Audio: Marx For The 21st Century, Lecture at RSA, 10 November 2017 https://t.co/DtlTJYeBRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This AMs panel ‘New and Emerging Spatial Theories’ or (my title) ‘how can you talk about space w/out mentioning Lefebvre?’ https://t.co/jcsOJPLiVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeraECBaker Yeah, &amp; w/ a conf discount $31.50 street corners...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pub partner. Walked out to Leyton today. @ King William The Fourth https://t.co/AVSbu6BzfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man, the myth, the legend. A&amp;H Taproom weekend hours. Closed tomorrow &amp; back to normal hours next week… https://t.co/TzyaslsJDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned something new today (actually 2 things): I am ill prepared to ride in snow &amp; 4 Seasons… https://t.co/pTBmdRR45c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsargins Which of the 12 systems got him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alwaysriding: It’s sale time again! Pick up some great kit at great prices in the Always Riding Boxing Day and January Sale! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProgHist: By which we mean @electricarchaeo - apologies for the vowel trouble! https://t.co/4vZ5aOp3dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made it back before the rain, clouds &amp; cold set in! 45km to bring #festive500 total to 160km;… https://t.co/CBEaU1DVDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status: https://t.co/RzLw74Ws2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First post-ride recovery... https://t.co/7C07KpUpbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made it! 50.6km added to the #festive500 Little cyclocross at the end, but fun ride. Time for… https://t.co/iJQaYAxaeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit wet this AM so, not to many pics... but made it St Albans! First 100km ticked off the… https://t.co/vBAdvsOmj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! Stage one, 4th Tour de Veitch Christmas ride. https://t.co/PoU0KYc8o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up, coffee, read, cycle, eat, coffee, read, repeat. #festive500 is under way. https://t.co/tyGJ7Y58Ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is definitely not how I’m recovering from my bike ride. No way, wouldn’t even try it... https://t.co/QyvKnJ4sLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @legogradstudent: When I see people post about their major academic accomplishments on social media, I remind myself that it's a biased…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taprooms closed for Christmas. @brewbynumbers 21/05 Pale Ale Citra to mark my holiday. @ The… https://t.co/THMWxPtBgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddClibbs I will always give England that one. Maybe it should be your passport colour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: For you reading pleasure...a round up of our fav. beers of 2017. https://t.co/WgfkUcsz2P #beeroftheyear #lovelystuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas in The Taproom! The Pfeffernüsse Saison. @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/7ndYU3C3Lu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin Google Fusion tables make simple visualisations (various options). Gephi is what I use for more complex network vis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo Tell me about it! I should post the tally of rejections because of it. Send it as a retirement present...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo Yeah, feedback was great &amp; frustration was with the PhD fiasco as that was the reason I was rejected. Great feedback on the postdoc app too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SAGEGeography: Inserting rights and justice into urban resilience: A focus on everyday risk https://t.co/VfniDAhxK2 https://t.co/704f4s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good/bad news day: didn’t get a post, but wonderfully hopeful feedback (‘cutting edge’ research) + 1st reveiwer comments of postdoc app. https://t.co/a4vNSqKpwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: Our taproom hours over the Christmas period. #hohoho https://t.co/FFYHaeTH6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @profdavidharvey: A Marxist critique of higher education (interview with David Harvey) • FreshEd Podcast with Will Brehm https://t.co/gQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covent Garden, Seven Dials, Leicester Square... Now onto the real Christmas shopping. Burnt… https://t.co/s0yJCPuVIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelESmith: Many archaeologists think Childe's "Urban revolution" is about identifying the earliest cities. Not so! The term refers…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariakneafsey https://t.co/b2JlCE5NlG{u0113}m{u0113}tr{u0113}s./axygalatas+demetres/-3,-1,0,B/browse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariakneafsey Roger Ulrich. Roman architecture stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariakneafsey Lorenzo Quilici on streets &amp; topography of Rome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long day cap. https://t.co/0YFW52e3OY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmabridges: This week's @IcsDirector blog post features Visiting Fellow Susan Dunning (Toronto) talking about her research on the Roma…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JWexlerBM Yes, your situation has concerns for me (&amp; El). No good for any of us. Hoping for the best, &amp; actively working for it, for you &amp; Sam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve got to know @JWexlerBM over the last yr &amp; this is a horrid story. Scary for anyone, but archaeology is dependent on movement. https://t.co/FZBRy9CxS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having sorted (for now) Lefebvre’s conception of ‘total body’ as a precursor to embodied… https://t.co/oXyRPBdLY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s challenge. Making sense of my notes... https://t.co/61cqNPqsg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: Holiday hours for The Taproom! Closed on Sunday, but open Fri &amp; Sat both weekends. Details here: https://t.co/HEm9OgvJHM…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CambUP_Classics: "This work goes beyond filling a major gap in scholarship on Roman processions: Latham’s decision to approach the pomp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 Used some conference discounts, review compensation &amp; beer money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ginlindzey Yes, that’s why I left it for later. It will motivate me to keep reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ginlindzey It looks fantastic, but I didn’t start with that one. I’ll definitely let you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having finished my Lefebvre primary readings, it’s time to start Roman streets in physical &amp; mental infrastructures... https://t.co/gqEfWfyDN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Historians Uncover Evidence Stonehenge Once Prominent Druid Make-Out Spot https://t.co/GGcKWz4qlv https://t.co/cBYiogCsyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbell798 She says thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E’s b-day. Long walk, pub lunch, Star Wars &amp; beer at every occasion... https://t.co/HEr8YOi7o8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for @electricarchaeo on replay the past...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob. https://t.co/D2yBVxBAGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funding app motivation. Or aargh! Huurrugh! Huurugh! https://t.co/UFHjc8DLG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmabridges: New @IcsDirector blog post in which @Woolf_Greg reflects on sensory studies, Roman religion, and humanities collaboration:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-game. Another December, another Star Wars 12:01 AM showing. https://t.co/Ym6VR1DL8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 Here’s the front of the can... https://t.co/GIADchOkXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 Modernist poison?...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis Mumford is on my beer... @raylaurence1 https://t.co/XUc2olEOYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pompeiana79 @electricarchaeo Well, that’s were it gets interesting! It should give you a range (at least a max) of pop. before a ‘system crash’ were bifurcation happens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pompeiana79 @electricarchaeo I guess I would start w/ everyone following the rules, then scale up 10% until the system breaks down. I’m interested in the capacity...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let the ‘traffic’ congestion begin... Use the traffic map as an agent based model platform &amp; run it until the traffic system breaks down. https://t.co/jm3KajT4iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Man Can’t Wait To Find Out If Millennium Falcon Gets Out Of That Tunnel https://t.co/OdAGrS0grv https://t.co/gD8McWiovG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness to de Certaeu, Arch of Enjoyment was not available in the 1980s. And de Certaeu admits to taking strategy/tactic from Lefebvre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[de Certaeu’s strategy/tactics = Lefebvre’s dominated/appropriated space w/out dètournement (&amp; use value) 1/2 https://t.co/MT3w3fp2T7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRomanSoc: 16 Dec is our 'Trajan' conference!  Have you got your ticket? It's with @RomanArchaeoUK at @britishmuseum. #Trajan100  htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard Latham present at SBL on the pompa circensis. Was bummed the book wasn’t on display for a flip-through. Looks &amp; sounds interesting! https://t.co/rs2LxfsiQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisbrooke: On the 11th day of Christmas my V-C gave to me,
Eleven piles of marking,
10 brand new targets
9 glossy brochures
8 new bit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s score: fresh corn tortillas &amp; Valentina from a New Mexican market. https://t.co/L46JYzctJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the porticoes I have been writing about today, but emblematic of the conception of portico space. https://t.co/BQSOwMXluJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@critt1967 Already to late. Saw it three time opening week...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This afternoons Rio Cinema matinée. Fun dark humour in the basement (Screen 2). @ Rio Cinema https://t.co/yyGKPQcnli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s stack: Roman street porticoes &amp; noise through Lefebvre’s Arch of Enjoyment &amp; embodied history of space (my article submitted Mon)... https://t.co/Fjui4pL0fg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicked this virus, survived the brewery &amp; now The Triple to celebrate! https://t.co/nsIecXX4VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnspachHobday: VERY PLEASED to announce our first 2 guest beers for our 4th Birthday tasting...Rosé de Gambrinus &amp; Fou' Foune from one…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheSocReview: Embodying culture: Body pedagogics, situated encounters and empirical research https://t.co/3YxXKTXFf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s that time again... time to binge watch Rome. https://t.co/WgUCAG2Qjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTEarle: You are aware that you ran the state with the highest number of KKK members in the US? Right? https://t.co/AaCQaIOjAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romeremembered We got someone’s shit wine when I got back after Xmas. Wanted to poster the neighbourhood with my superior wine taste...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or is the ‘exasperation’ an indication of noise &amp; other nuisances to every Roman ritual?... https://t.co/wIBwLdmaQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My copies of Arch of Enjoyment &amp; TPS have become archive artefacts. Will have to order new… https://t.co/sb9ookYBTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upping my banana game... apps, articles &amp; sickness are today’s cocktail. https://t.co/ZcwXLExaeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to kick a virus by shuffling between article edits, BSR app &amp; Leverhulme app. My general take on today... https://t.co/LyXlqwX8RJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering signing up for a charity long distance ride. It’s 5x my longest ride &amp; 8 months way...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>