<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VrhLFQwMWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/ixXPaetlzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/PusJXNGIXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/uMtzadLRZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/lSiPAfgiMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/nyaTSCJtcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/2sNB3tI527]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/BqvmTHQ9rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/X9l06dFRvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/6gGm3GlRvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/EHhcALmJJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/YaeUR2MUtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kEpLl45wgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/hhiTeKLUd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the the History of Burger King  http://t.co/dQKs0SWyUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else. - James M. Barrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/F8Abx2E36h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/PrJpU8lj9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/PusJXNGIXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/Py2tqN4SP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/VwyhOdH1Jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/YzByaiia3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/uMtzadLRZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/3mXtOGZoEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/6p1RxJomYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Gadgets -- Digital Jump Ropes  http://t.co/P2h7hcptxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/0M2DkAUVqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/emc3kPAtEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/2EOKXZSq0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/9Wl45pCfY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/MTiVrTW3ND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/ex8SZK3dfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/rlYr6igVqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/uqO2OxRfhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/yhiKVcyUEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/dVqGcnMlrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/65ij7T074E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/lrFGQhQ29w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/FZ969GCMmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/k34eNxD45I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/jrWsNvVeKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/lXg2GtQAAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/NK4iEV4DH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/2pWy8nyq5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/g7zk7OX8m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/tLoaLqntab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>